<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:00:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[BARC.L] FactSet Research Systems (FDS) Valuation After New Multiyear Barclays Agreement</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-research-systems-fds-valuation-001813159.html</link><description>Barclays has entered a multiyear arrangement with FactSet Research Systems (FDS), using the company’s analytics, data and technology to support its long term market data strategy and services for global clients. See our latest analysis for FactSet Research Systems. The Barclays agreement comes after a tough stretch for shareholders, with a 1 year total shareholder return decline of 37.91% and a relatively flat pattern in recent share price returns. This suggests momentum has been subdued even...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-research-systems-fds-valuation-001813159.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] My Top 3 Chip Stocks for 2025 Crushed the Market. Here's Why They Can Repeat Again in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/my-top-3-chip-stocks-for-2025-crushed-the-market/</link><description>AI spending is expected to stay elevated in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/my-top-3-chip-stocks-for-2025-crushed-the-market/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 Reasons to Buy TSMC Stock Like There's No Tomorrow</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/reasons-to-buy-tsmc-stock-like-no-tomorrow/</link><description>The semiconductor manufacturer just reported stellar fourth-quarter results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/reasons-to-buy-tsmc-stock-like-no-tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] GM To End Production Of Its Most Affordable EV, Move Buick From China To US: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gm-end-production-most-affordable-203104675.html</link><description>General Motors Co. (NYSE:GM) will reportedly end production of its most affordable EV, the Chevrolet Bolt, as well as move Buick production out of China into Kansas. GM's Production Reshuffle The Detroit-based automaker will shift production of the Gas-powered Chevrolet Equinox and the upcoming Buick Envision away from Mexico and China, respectively, to its facility in Fairfax, Kansas, TechCrunch reported on Thursday. Don't Miss: Missed Nvidia and Tesla? RAD Intel Could Be the Next AI Powerhouse</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gm-end-production-most-affordable-203104675.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Drops After Q4 Earnings: Is INTC a Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214534/intel-stock-drops-after-q4-earnings-is-intc-a-buy-now</link><description>Intel enters 2026 facing near-term pressure, with the first quarter expected to remain challenging.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214534/intel-stock-drops-after-q4-earnings-is-intc-a-buy-now</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Could a Wearable AI Pin Be the Next Big Thing for Apple Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214375/could-a-wearable-ai-pin-be-the-next-big-thing-for-apple-stock</link><description>A wearable AI pin may be niche, but it hints at Apple's plans to weave AI deeper into its ecosystem.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214375/could-a-wearable-ai-pin-be-the-next-big-thing-for-apple-stock</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 19:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Ultra Clean Holdings (UCTT) Valuation Check After AI Fueled Rally On TSMC Capex Plans</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-valuation-180834088.html</link><description>AI driven chip spending puts Ultra Clean Holdings (UCTT) in focus Ultra Clean Holdings (UCTT) jumped into the spotlight after its share price surged recently, as investors reacted to TSMC’s plan to lift AI and high performance chip spending. This move drew attention to key semiconductor suppliers. See our latest analysis for Ultra Clean Holdings. UCTT’s recent AI driven spike sits on top of a 66.12% 1 month share price return and a 59.19% year to date share price return, while its 1 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-valuation-180834088.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Dow Jones Futures: Trump Threatens 100% Canada Tariff; Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, Apple Lead Earnings Wave</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-100-canada-tariff-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>President Donald Trump threatened a 100% tariff on Canada if it makes a trade deal with China, a week after endorsing the idea. Tesla, Microsoft, Meta and Apple lead an earnings wave.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-100-canada-tariff-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] The Bull Case For FactSet Research Systems (FDS) Could Change Following Barclays Multiyear Platform Win Learn Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-factset-research-systems-170958297.html</link><description>On 22 January 2026, Barclays announced a multiyear arrangement with FactSet Research Systems to access a broad suite of FactSet’s data, analytics, and technology solutions for its global client base. This win highlights FactSet’s role as a core market data and analytics provider to a major global bank, reinforcing the relevance of its integrated platform for large institutional clients. Next, we will examine how FactSet’s expanded role in Barclays’ long-term market data strategy shapes the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-factset-research-systems-170958297.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Samsung drops Galaxy S26 Ultra bombshell</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/samsung-drops-galaxy-s26-ultra-bombshell</link><description>Samsung Electronics is getting ready for the launch of a lifetime, the Galaxy S26 Ultra, on March 11, Forbes reported. Now, with its most important product for 2026 set to debut, the marketing blitz and margin test are front and center. Investors, retailers, and customers are eagerly anticipating ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/samsung-drops-galaxy-s26-ultra-bombshell</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Binance and OKX To Enter TradFi With Tokenized Stocks</title><link>https://beincrypto.com/binance-okx-tokenized-stocks-crypto-liquidity-drought/</link><description>Binance and OKX may revive tokenized US stocks as crypto liquidity weakens and exchanges chase TradFi-style yield.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://beincrypto.com/binance-okx-tokenized-stocks-crypto-liquidity-drought/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Reveals Why Apple (AAPL) Stock is Struggling</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-reveals-why-apple-155944112.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Even though Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)’s shares have remained muted, Cramer has continued to defend the stock. The shares are down by 8.3% year-to-date. UBS recently discussed the stock as it kept a Neutral rating and […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-reveals-why-apple-155944112.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] I Predicted TSMC Would Be a Must-Own Stock in 2025. I Still Think It's a Fantastic Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/predict-tsmc-would-be-must-own-stock-buy-2026/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing will benefit from the same tailwinds in 2026 as it did in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/predict-tsmc-would-be-must-own-stock-buy-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Won't Rush Costly Chip Capacity Buildout Despite AI Boom, Even As Rivals TSMC And Samsung Spend Big Bucks: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-wont-rush-costly-chip-153108516.html</link><description>On Thursday, Intel Corp. (NASDAQ:INTC) said it will not accelerate major chip capacity investments without clearer customer commitments, even as rivals Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (NYSE:TSMC) and Samsung Electronics Co. (OTC:SSNLF) ramp up spending. Intel Prioritizes Discipline Over Speed In AI Expansion During the company's fourth-quarter earnings call, Intel struck a cautious tone on capacity expansion, pushing back against concerns that it could fall behind in the intensifying AI-d</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-wont-rush-costly-chip-153108516.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] This Tech Stock Could Turn $1,000 Into $16,000</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/this-tech-stock-could-turn-1000-into-16000/</link><description>A little patience could go a long way for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/this-tech-stock-could-turn-1000-into-16000/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] UBS Reaffirms Its ‘Neutral’ Rating with a $280 Price Target on Apple (AAPL)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ubs-reaffirms-neutral-rating-280-142920042.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the best stocks to buy and hold for 20 years. On January 21, 2026, UBS maintained its ‘Neutral’ rating with a $280 price target on Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) ahead of earnings. While reflecting on the strong early demand for the iPhone 17 series, the investment firm reported that its […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ubs-reaffirms-neutral-rating-280-142920042.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Notable open interest changes for January 23rd</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/notable-open-interest-changes-january-140135546.html</link><description>Thursday’s total option volume of 66.7 million contracts resulted in net open interest growth of 9.22 million calls and 6.95 million puts. NVIDIA (NVDA), Intel (INTC), Tesla (TSLA) and Netflix (NFLX) saw the greatest growth. Top five new positions opened include 145k Netflix (NFLX) Sep-26 100 calls, 127k NVIDIA (NVDA) 1/30 weekly 165 puts, 122k Netflix (NFLX) Sep-26 120 calls, 60k Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) 1/30 weekly 220 puts and 48k Broadcom (AVGO) 1/30 weekly 297.5 puts.Claim 50% Off TipRa</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/notable-open-interest-changes-january-140135546.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Morning Movers: Nvidia up after report of potential China move on H200 chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-movers-nvidia-report-potential-135536896.html</link><description>Stock futures are modestly lower, pressured in part by Intel’s sharp pre-market slide following a weak outlook from the chipmaker and ongoing geopolitical uncertainty. Markets are trading mixed and cautiously softer on Friday after a volatile week that has reflected shifting investor sentiment around geopolitics, earnings, and economic data. Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper decisions Stay ahead of the market with the lat</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-movers-nvidia-report-potential-135536896.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel price target raised to $54 from $46 at Northland</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-price-target-raised-54-134531764.html</link><description>Northland raised the firm’s price target on Intel (INTC) to $54 from $46 and keeps an Outperform rating on the shares after the company reported non-GAAP EPS upside in Q4, but gave downbeat Q1 guidance due to internal capacity constraints. While the process remains disappointing, Intel is a U.S. strategic asset and “too critical to fail,” says the analyst, who adds that guidance is “very likely to be conservative.”Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-price-target-raised-54-134531764.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trump-weary Danes turn to technology in boycott of US brands</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-weary-danes-turn-technology-133000567.html</link><description>To that, a popular new mobile app in Denmark assigns a failing red X — a message to shoppers to put that American stuff back on the shelf.  Denmark, a country one-sixteenth the size of Texas, is tired of feeling pushed around.  Since Trump began threatening to grab Greenland, which is part of the Kingdom of Denmark, downloads of such apps have exploded.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-weary-danes-turn-technology-133000567.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Market Week Ahead: Fed Meeting, Shutdown Risks, And Heavy Earnings</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/investing-action-plan/market-week-ahead-fed-meeting-shutdown-risks-and-heavy-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market faces a Fed meeting, a federal funding deadline, a heavy earnings slate and harsh winter weather in the coming week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/investing-action-plan/market-week-ahead-fed-meeting-shutdown-risks-and-heavy-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Calculating The Fair Value Of Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/calculating-fair-value-apple-inc-130010864.html</link><description>Key Insights The projected fair value for Apple is US$226 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity Apple's US$248...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/calculating-fair-value-apple-inc-130010864.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Stays Constructive on Cognex (CGNX) as Industrial Tech Demand Holds Up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-stays-constructive-cognex-cgnx-114958829.html</link><description>Cognex Corporation (NASDAQ:CGNX) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 12, Barclays trimmed its price target on Cognex Corporation (NASDAQ:CGNX) to $54 from $56, while keeping an Overweight rating on the stock. The move came as part of the firm’s broader 2026 outlook for industrial technology and distribution […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-stays-constructive-cognex-cgnx-114958829.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates First American Financial (FAF) in Broader Coverage Reset</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-first-american-financial-114754482.html</link><description>First American Financial Corporation (NYSE:FAF) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 6, Barclays slightly lowered its price target on First American Financial Corporation (NYSE:FAF) to $68 from $71, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The firm’s broader 2026 outlook suggests it still sees opportunity […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-first-american-financial-114754482.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What Are the 3 Top Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks to Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/what-are-the-3-top-artificial-intelligence-stock/</link><description>AI chip stocks still have a lot of upside from here.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/what-are-the-3-top-artificial-intelligence-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Jim Cramer on Intel: “If You Give Up on It, I Think You’re Making a Big Mistake”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-intel-think-making-113733098.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his take on. Cramer believes that the stock “will be a very hot stock,” as he commented: Some think that Intel took itself out of the running today after announcing a quarter that was less than expected. That’s wrong. You have to look out. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-intel-think-making-113733098.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Initiates Badger Meter (BMI) Coverage, Citing Valuation and Growth Concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-initiates-badger-meter-bmi-112352633.html</link><description>Badger Meter, Inc. (NYSE:BMI) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 7, Barclays analyst William Grippin launched coverage of Badger Meter, Inc. (NYSE:BMI) with an Underweight rating and a $157 price target. In his view, Badger is a “solid company with a difficult setup.” He argued that the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-initiates-badger-meter-bmi-112352633.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] TD Cowen Trims Coty Inc. (COTY) Target Ahead of Q4, Keeps Hold Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/td-cowen-trims-coty-inc-104835503.html</link><description>Coty Inc. (NYSE:COTY) is among the overlooked penny stocks to invest in. On January 21, TD Cowen cut the price target on Coty Inc. (NYSE:COTY) to $3.40 from $3.50, and maintained a Hold rating, according to TheFly. This revision, suggesting upside potential of nearly 4%, was part of the firm’s Q4 preview, during which it […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/td-cowen-trims-coty-inc-104835503.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Investing.com’s stocks of the week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-com-stocks-week-093005578.html</link><description>Investing.com – There was no shortage of big-name stock moves this week, with earnings releases ramping up and significant gains in some tech names.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-com-stocks-week-093005578.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple iPhone just had its best year in India as the smartphone market stays broadly flat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-iphone-just-had-best-050000323.html</link><description>Apple shipped a record 14 million iPhones in India in 2025 and gained market share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-iphone-just-had-best-050000323.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Analyst sends blunt 3-word warning on Intel stock after earnings</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/analyst-sends-blunt-3-word-warning-on-intel-stock-after-earnings</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock tumbled 17% on Jan. 23 after the chipmaker issued weaker-than-expected guidance for the current quarter. The company beat expectations in the fourth quarter of 2025. Adjusted earnings came at 15 cents per share, well above Wall Street’s forecast of 8 cents. Revenue reached ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/analyst-sends-blunt-3-word-warning-on-intel-stock-after-earnings</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Tesla and Buys This Consumer Electronics Stock Instead</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-tesla-and-b/</link><description>Peter Thiel significantly reduced exposure to Tesla stock and swapped his gains for Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-tesla-and-b/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] How Intel Came Crashing Back to Earth After Its Trump Bump</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/intel-problems-trump-bump-17d2c941?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>After months of riding positive vibes, the troubled chip maker reminded investors why it needed a rescue in the first place.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/intel-problems-trump-bump-17d2c941?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Stock Crashed Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-intel-stock-is-down-today/</link><description>Investors are taking profits after the popular tech stock's recent run-up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-intel-stock-is-down-today/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] U.S. Millionaires Considering Migration: The Numbers</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/u-s-millionaires-considering-migration-the-numbers-b7ab6089?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A new survey of 1,0000 millionaires suggests that a third are motivated to leave the U.S. a year into President Donald Trump’s second term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/u-s-millionaires-considering-migration-the-numbers-b7ab6089?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>