<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Exclusive: Is Apple Late To Foldable iPhones? Ming-Chi Kuo Says Cupertino Isn't At 'Disadvantage' As Samsung Sees Foldables Go Mainstream</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-apple-foldable-iphones-ming-033130804.html</link><description>Apple Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AAPL) long-anticipated entry into the foldable iPhone market may not be as delayed — or as risky — as it appears, according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, even as Samsung Electronics Co. (OTC:SSNLF) says the category is nearing mainstream adoption. Apple's Timing May Not Be A Problem After All Apple has yet to launch a foldable iPhone, but Kuo, a TF International Securities analyst known for tracking Apple's supply chain, told Benzinga that timing alone does not put Cupertino at a</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-apple-foldable-iphones-ming-033130804.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trump Takes Credit For Intel's Surge But Hesitant To Raise Stake: 'I'll Invest More In Other Things'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-takes-credit-intels-surge-230112226.html</link><description>President Donald Trump stated that his intervention in Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) has resulted in substantial gains for the U.S. chipmaker. However, he is not sure if he would invest more in the company. “I don’t know about Intel but I’ll invest more in other things,” Trump said. Speaking to reporters at Joint Base Andrews in Maryland on Tuesday, Trump said that after he assisted Intel, the company’s valuation soared. He added that Intel’s success had attracted other major players’ investme</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-takes-credit-intels-surge-230112226.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today, Jan. 15: Nvidia Rises on Strong AI Demand and Data Center Growth Optimism</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/15/stock-market-today-jan-15-nvidia-rises-on-strong-ai-demand-and-data-center-growth-optimism/</link><description>Today, Jan. 15, 2026, investors are weighing surging AI data center demand against fresh questions about the durability of that growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/15/stock-market-today-jan-15-nvidia-rises-on-strong-ai-demand-and-data-center-growth-optimism/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Small-cap records, chip stock gains, silver: Market Takeaways</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/small-cap-records-chip-stock-221522267.html</link><description>US stocks (^DJI, ^IXIC, ^GSPC) close Thursday's session higher following AI optimism tied to the US trade deal with Taiwan. Yahoo Finance Markets and Data Editor Jared Blikre breaks down the biggest market themes from today’s trading day, including how small-cap indexes are reaching record highs, stock movements in semiconductor chip manufacturers, and price trends in silver (SI=F). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Asking for a Trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/small-cap-records-chip-stock-221522267.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) Valuation Check After Strong Recent Share Price Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-banking-group-lse-lloy-221036842.html</link><description>Event context and recent share performance Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) has attracted fresh attention after recent share price moves, with the stock showing gains over the past week, month and past 3 months that stand out against its longer term track record. See our latest analysis for Lloyds Banking Group. Set against this, Lloyds Banking Group’s recent 7.56% 1 month share price return and 23.97% 3 month share price return sit alongside a very large 5 year total shareholder return. This...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-banking-group-lse-lloy-221036842.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Is Back From the Brink, But It Only Gets Tougher From Here. How Should You Play INTC in 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37071510/intel-is-back-from-the-brink-but-it-only-gets-tougher-from-here-how-should-you-play-intc-in-2026</link><description>Intel is looking up but faces more headwinds ahead. Here's what's next for Intel as the company prepares to report earnings late next week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37071510/intel-is-back-from-the-brink-but-it-only-gets-tougher-from-here-how-should-you-play-intc-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Dell Stock Has Been a Victim of AI. These Analysts Say It’s a Winner.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-price-buy-analysts-ai-winner-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Barclays and Goldman Sachs both urged investors to buy the shares, citing AI server demand, expense discipline, and accelerating earnings growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-price-buy-analysts-ai-winner-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 5 AI Chip Stocks Most Exposed to Trump’s New 25% Tariff</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/5-ai-chip-stocks-most-exposed-to-trumps-new-25-tariff/</link><description>Trump’s 25% tariff on AI chips landed the same day Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) posted blowout earnings and dismissed AI bubble fears. TSMC’s stock surged 8% Thursday, pulling AMD up 12% and NVIDIA 3% in sympathy. Now investors face a critical question: which chip stocks are most exposed when the tariff hits? The policy ... 5 AI Chip Stocks Most Exposed to Trump’s New 25% Tariff</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/5-ai-chip-stocks-most-exposed-to-trumps-new-25-tariff/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Gene Munster Says Apple's Move From OpenAI's ChatGPT To Google Gemini Significantly Raises Chances Of New Siri Succeeding: 'Nice Job'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gene-munster-says-apples-move-213113224.html</link><description>On Tuesday, Deepwater Asset Management's managing partner Gene Munster said that Apple Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AAPL) switch from OpenAI's ChatGPT to Alphabet Inc.'s (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google Gemini gives Siri a much stronger chance of success. Apple Partners With Google Gemini To Reinvent Siri Munster took to X and said, "Odds of new Siri succeeding just went up," while praising Apple CEO Tim Cook for turning long-standing Siri shortcomings into an opportunity for future device and services gro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gene-munster-says-apples-move-213113224.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Best Dividend ETF to Invest $500 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/best-dividend-etf-to-invest-500-in-right-now/</link><description>Dividend ETFs have been getting another look as the market rotates into non-tech sectors to kick off 2026. This Vanguard ETF, in particular, looks well-positioned to benefit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/best-dividend-etf-to-invest-500-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Datadog (DDOG) Faces Competitive Pressures in 2026, Goldman Says in Sell Call</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/datadog-ddog-faces-competitive-pressures-203038399.html</link><description>Datadog, Inc. (NASDAQ:DDOG) is one of the Must-Watch AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 12, Goldman Sachs analyst Gabriela Borges assumed coverage on the stock with a Sell rating and a price target of $113.00. Firm analysts see 2026 as a pressure year for DDOG as competition intensifies and weighs on fundamentals. “We assume coverage […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/datadog-ddog-faces-competitive-pressures-203038399.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Microchip, Analog Devices target raised ahead of semiconductor earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microchip-analog-devices-target-raised-201302724.html</link><description>Investing.com --Wolfe Research raised estimates on select semiconductor names ahead of the fourth-quarter earnings season, arguing that while demand visibility remains mixed across end markets, downside risks appear limited and company-specific drivers are becoming more important.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microchip-analog-devices-target-raised-201302724.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s (AAPL) AI-Powered Siri and Foldable iPhone Are Key Catalysts, Analyst Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-powered-siri-200804438.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Must-Watch AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 12, BofA Securities analyst Wamsi Mohan reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $325.00 price target. Firm analysts anticipate upside surprises as the tech giant heads into F1Q26 earnings on January 29 after markets close, particularly driven by […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-powered-siri-200804438.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise as TSMC boosts AI hopes, bank stocks rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-tsmc-boosts-ai-hopes-bank-stocks-rally-195049176.html</link><description>Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-tsmc-boosts-ai-hopes-bank-stocks-rally-195049176.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How Apple Stock Could Add $100 Per Share in 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37068991/how-apple-stock-could-add-100-per-share-in-2026-and-beyond</link><description>Here is how Wedbush analyst Dan Ives thinks Apple could add $100 per share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37068991/how-apple-stock-could-add-100-per-share-in-2026-and-beyond</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Michael Burry Bets Against Nvidia, Says'I Do Not See How That Math Works' Amid AI Chip Boom Fears</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-burry-bets-against-nvidia-190119667.html</link><description>Investor Michael Burry, famed for predicting the 2008 housing crash, is now betting against Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA), warning that the AI-driven chip boom is vulnerable to a sharp reversal. Burry Calls Nvidia ‘Purest Play’ On AI In a Substack post over the weekend, Burry said he is shorting Nvidia because the chipmaker is "simply the purest play" on artificial intelligence and is dangerously reliant on hyperscaler spending. "I do not see how that math works," he wrote, adding that Nvidia could</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-burry-bets-against-nvidia-190119667.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Just Got a New Street-High Price Target. Should You Buy INTC Here?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37067938/intel-stock-just-got-a-new-street-high-price-target-should-you-buy-intc-here</link><description>Intel has been on an absolute tear in the past year, surging 50% during this period, as it inked partnerships with Nvidia, SoftBank, and others.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37067938/intel-stock-just-got-a-new-street-high-price-target-should-you-buy-intc-here</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Massive Corporate Layoffs Changed Everything, Says Robert Kiyosaki. Calls Going To School For Job Security An 'Obsolete Idea'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/massive-corporate-layoffs-changed-everything-183114744.html</link><description>Robert Kiyosaki says the recent wave of corporate job cuts shows that the traditional promise of stability through schooling no longer holds up in today's economy. In a recent post on X, the investor and author of “Rich Dad Poor Dad” argued that going to school for job security has become an “obsolete idea,” especially as layoffs hit industries that once symbolized safety, prestige, and high pay. His comments come amid continued workforce reductions across logistics, retail, manufacturing, and t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/massive-corporate-layoffs-changed-everything-183114744.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] India Presses Ahead With Apple Probe</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-presses-ahead-apple-probe-181600941.html</link><description>Regulators warn after year long delays</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-presses-ahead-apple-probe-181600941.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Corning (GLW) Stock Is Up, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corning-glw-stock-know-175137337.html</link><description>Shares of glass and electronic component manufacturer Corning (NYSE:GLW) jumped 3.8% in the afternoon session after BofA raised its price target on the company's shares to $110 from $95 while keeping a Buy rating.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corning-glw-stock-know-175137337.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 4 semiconductor stocks giving the AI boom 'more legs'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-semiconductor-stocks-giving-the-ai-boom-more-legs-175135867.html</link><description>Crossmark Global Investments chief market strategist Victoria Fernandez explains why a new wave of earnings from the semiconductor sector signals the AI race is just warming up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-semiconductor-stocks-giving-the-ai-boom-more-legs-175135867.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Western Digital (WDC) Stock Is Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-western-digital-wdc-stock-175042827.html</link><description>Shares of leading data storage manufacturer Western Digital (NASDAQ: WDC) jumped 6.6% in the afternoon session after positive analyst actions, including an upgrade to "Overweight" and a significant price target increase from Barclays. Barclays raised its price target on the company to $240 from $200, while keeping an "Overweight" rating. Separately, other analysts upgraded the stock to "Overweight," citing optimism about its future performance. This wave of positive sentiment from analysts was e</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-western-digital-wdc-stock-175042827.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Goldman Sachs Profit Climbs 12% as Earnings Top Estimates</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/bank-earnings-wells-fargo-bank-of-america-morgan-stanley-blackrock-goldman-sachs-citigroup/card/goldman-sachs-profit-climbs-12-as-earnings-top-estimates-XrJtIaMtKJRZ6S4uLDPI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Goldman Sachs reported fourth-quarter net earnings of $4.62 billion, up 12% from a year earlier. The firm earned $14.01 a share, topping analysts’ forecasts for $11.70, according to FactSet estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/bank-earnings-wells-fargo-bank-of-america-morgan-stanley-blackrock-goldman-sachs-citigroup/card/goldman-sachs-profit-climbs-12-as-earnings-top-estimates-XrJtIaMtKJRZ6S4uLDPI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Taiwan Semi Stock Just Hit a New All-Time High But AI Fears Remain</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37066859/taiwan-semi-stock-just-hit-a-new-all-time-high-but-ai-fears-remain</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor (TSM) shares are trading at new all-time highs. Shares are up nearly 70% over the past 52 weeks. TSM maintains a 100% technical “Buy” opinion from Barchart. The stock hit new highs Thursday after Taiwan Semi reported record profit in its fourth-quarter earnings. Today’s Featured Stock Valued at...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37066859/taiwan-semi-stock-just-hit-a-new-all-time-high-but-ai-fears-remain</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple makes high-stakes Siri change as Services growth takes center stage</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/apple-makes-high-stakes-siri-change-as-services-growth-takes-center-stage</link><description>Apple is wagering that it can resolve a long-standing problem with one of its products rapidly by using a competitor's artificial intelligence. This might lead customers to buy new iPhones and use more services, which would boost Apple's income. Apple and Google have announced a multi-year ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/apple-makes-high-stakes-siri-change-as-services-growth-takes-center-stage</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Analysts Say Dell Is Becoming an AI Winner. Buy the Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-analysts-ai-upside-buy-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Barclays and Goldman Sachs both urged investors to buy the shares, citing AI server demand, expense discipline, and accelerating earnings growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-analysts-ai-upside-buy-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Faces Final Warning From India in Antitrust Dispute</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-faces-final-warning-india-165816638.html</link><description>Regulator threatens to move ahead after yearlong delay in Apple's response.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-faces-final-warning-india-165816638.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] OpenAI seeks US hardware partners for expansion into devices and data centers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openai-seeks-us-hardware-partners-164641000.html</link><description>Investing.com -- OpenAI is searching for US-based manufacturing partners as it prepares for a major expansion into consumer devices, robotics, and cloud data centers in the coming years, according to a report Thursday from Bloomberg News.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openai-seeks-us-hardware-partners-164641000.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 3 Technology Stocks to Sell in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-technology-stocks-sell-2026-163117495.html</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Information Technology Index is down -1.75% year to date and -2.53% over the past month, signaling a sketchy outlook for tech stocks in 2026, though not for all big sector names. As usual, artificial intelligence, especially in the software realm, is using up most of the tech industry’s oxygen. “There’s a lot of optimism around AI, but also a lot of hype,” said Anthony Saglimbene, chief market strategist at Ameriprise, in a recent research note. “2026 will be more about the proof of</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-technology-stocks-sell-2026-163117495.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Nasdaq Plays Catch-Up: Is the Tech-Heavy Index Ready to Breakout?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-plays-catch-tech-heavy-161600773.html</link><description>The themes we saw last year appear to be carrying over into 2026, a positive sign that this multi-year rally still has legs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-plays-catch-tech-heavy-161600773.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Can Intel's Upgradation in AI PCs Strengthen Its Business Growth?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intels-upgradation-ai-pcs-strengthen-161400884.html</link><description>INTC is pushing deeper into AI with next-gen AI PCs, pairing powerful on-device processing, new Core Ultra chips, and key partnerships to reshape everyday computing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intels-upgradation-ai-pcs-strengthen-161400884.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock at 52-wk. high: Here's what's driving enthusiasm</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-52-wk-high-161055829.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock hit a 52-week high on Thursday as investor enthusiasm continues to grow. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley sits down with Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman to explain how Intel's high-powered laptop chip, which debuted at CES 2026, is part of what's driving investor interest in the company. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-52-wk-high-161055829.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Siri to Get Smarter With Gemini: The ETF Playbook for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/siri-smarter-gemini-etf-playbook-160500261.html</link><description>Apple teams up with Google's Gemini to supercharge Siri, creating a win-win AI deal and pointing investors toward tech ETFs for diversified exposure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/siri-smarter-gemini-etf-playbook-160500261.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights AbbVie, Intel, Boeing and Tandy Leather Factory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-abbvie-154300644.html</link><description>AbbVie leads a Zacks Analyst Blog roundup highlighting strong pharma execution, AI-driven chip gains and an aviation rebound.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-abbvie-154300644.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights Qualcomm Technologies, Advanced Micro Devices, Intel and NVIDIA</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-qualcomm-153800690.html</link><description>Qualcomm takes a slight edge in a Zacks Analyst Blog comparison as chipmakers race to capitalize on AI-driven demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-qualcomm-153800690.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 1 Oversold Software Stock With Too Much AI Fear Priced In</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/1-oversold-software-stock-with-too-much-ai-fear-priced-in/</link><description>AI has really landed a heavy shot on some of the software names, especially the SaaS (Software as a Service) companies that have been quite slow to brace for the rise of the artificial intelligence (AI) age. Undoubtedly, with agents, robotics, and all sorts of transformative and revolutionary disruptive tech up ahead, standing pat and ... 1 Oversold Software Stock With Too Much AI Fear Priced In</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/1-oversold-software-stock-with-too-much-ai-fear-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153025915.html</link><description>HIVE Digital Technologies Ltd. 2,672,229 3.47</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153025915.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Soaring Memory Prices Lift Chipmakers, Pressure Apple and HP</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/soaring-memory-prices-lift-chipmakers-152001445.html</link><description>AI-driven memory shortages are boosting suppliers while rising costs weigh on hardware makers' margins and outlooks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/soaring-memory-prices-lift-chipmakers-152001445.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CRWD to Acquire Seraphic: Is Browser Security the Next Growth Engine?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-acquire-seraphic-browser-security-151400300.html</link><description>CrowdStrike agrees to acquire Seraphic to extend Falcon into browser security, targeting AI-driven risks inside browser sessions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-acquire-seraphic-browser-security-151400300.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why ASML Stock Is Climbing Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-asml-stock-climbing-today-151159957.html</link><description>ASML Shares Jump on TSMC Capex Boost, but 2026 Growth Remains Unclear</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-asml-stock-climbing-today-151159957.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Expected to Beat Earnings Estimates: What to Know Ahead of Q4 Release</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-expected-beat-earnings-150010242.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-expected-beat-earnings-150010242.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Is Getting Better. That Doesn’t Make the Stock a Buy, This Analyst Says.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-chips-18a-nvidia-9bd2f0af?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock has risen 34% over the past month but RBC's Srini Pajjuri is cautious on its prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-chips-18a-nvidia-9bd2f0af?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia initiated, DraftKings upgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-initiated-draftkings-upgraded-wall-145300434.html</link><description>Nvidia initiated, DraftKings upgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-initiated-draftkings-upgraded-wall-145300434.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump places 25% tariff on AI chips with some exemptions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-places-25-tariff-ai-145022185.html</link><description>The Trump administration has placed a 25% tariff on “certain advanced computing chips," according to a White House statement, with exemptions for chips contributing to the buildout of the US AI infrastructure. Crossmark Global Investments chief market strategist Victoria Fernandez comments on this announcement. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-places-25-tariff-ai-145022185.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq jump as TSMC boosts AI hopes, bank stocks rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-jump-as-tsmc-boosts-ai-hopes-bank-stocks-rally-143402983.html</link><description>Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-jump-as-tsmc-boosts-ai-hopes-bank-stocks-rally-143402983.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Nasdaq leads Dow, S&amp;P 500 higher as TSMC's strong outlook buoys AI hopes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-nasdaq-leads-dow-sp-500-higher-as-tsmcs-strong-outlook-buoys-ai-hopes-143402160.html</link><description>Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-nasdaq-leads-dow-sp-500-higher-as-tsmcs-strong-outlook-buoys-ai-hopes-143402160.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bernstein names winners and losers in the AI driven data explosion</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-names-winners-losers-ai-143310844.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Bernstein says the accelerating AI-driven data boom is reshaping the technology landscape, lifting memory and storage providers while pressuring hardware makers struggling with surging component costs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-names-winners-losers-ai-143310844.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Chip stocks jump as Nvidia supplier TSMC dismisses bubble fears: 'AI is real'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-jump-as-nvidia-supplier-tsmc-dismisses-bubble-fears-ai-is-real-142119829.html</link><description>Nvidia's chip manufacturer Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) posted a strong forecast for AI revenue growth and capital expenditures.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-jump-as-nvidia-supplier-tsmc-dismisses-bubble-fears-ai-is-real-142119829.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Unlike Ben Shapiro And Grant Cardone, Most Americans Still See Retirement As One Of Life's Biggest Goals And Not A 'Stupid Idea'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unlike-ben-shapiro-grant-cardone-141611894.html</link><description>While it seems that some of the most vocal figures in media and business don’t believe in retirement, most Americans still view it as a key life milestone worth working toward. Many Still Dream Of Slowing Down, Even If It Feels Out Of Reach Real estate mogul Grant Cardone, who is 67 years old, posted on X last year that he’ll never retire, citing three reasons: love for work, a sense of purpose, and the thrill of deadlines. “Work gives me a sense of purpose and contribution,” he wrote. “I do bet</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unlike-ben-shapiro-grant-cardone-141611894.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How to Boost Your Portfolio with Top Computer and Technology Stocks Set to Beat Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boost-portfolio-top-computer-technology-140005190.html</link><description>Finding stocks expected to beat quarterly earnings estimates becomes an easier task with our Zacks Earnings ESP.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boost-portfolio-top-computer-technology-140005190.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley Report Atop Multi-Month Rallies</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/goldman-sachs-earnings-q4-2025-gs-stock-dow-jones-morgan-stanley-ms-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Dow Jones financial giant Goldman Sachs posted mixed results early Thursday. Morgan Stanley advances on its Q4 beat.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/goldman-sachs-earnings-q4-2025-gs-stock-dow-jones-morgan-stanley-ms-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Got $3,000? 3 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks to Buy and Hold for the Long Term</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/got-3000-3-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-to-bu/</link><description>Each of these companies is a staple in its respective industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/got-3000-3-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-to-bu/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Here Are Thursday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Applied Materials, BankUnited, Broadcom, Dell Technologies, DraftKings, Lam Research, NVIDIA, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/here-are-thursdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-applied-materials-bankunited-broadcom-dell-technologies-draftkings-lam-research-nvidia-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: Futures are trading mostly higher after another risk-off day on Wall Street on Wednesday. Despite more solid news on the inflation front, as the producer price index report came in below estimates, the swirling geopolitical issues around the world and at home are starting to weigh on Wall Street’s bullishness. The potential ... Here Are Thursday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Applied Materials, BankUnited, Broadcom, Dell Technologies, DraftKings, Lam Research</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/here-are-thursdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-applied-materials-bankunited-broadcom-dell-technologies-draftkings-lam-research-nvidia-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Goldman Sachs earnings: Bank tops profit estimates as dealmaking boom bucks Wall Street trend</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-earnings-bank-tops-profit-estimates-as-dealmaking-boom-bucks-wall-street-trend-125649196.html</link><description>Wall Street’s dealmaking boom didn’t slow at Goldman Sachs (GS) in the fourth quarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-earnings-bank-tops-profit-estimates-as-dealmaking-boom-bucks-wall-street-trend-125649196.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Here’s Every Company Worth $4 Trillion — Should You Buy or Sell These Stocks?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/every-company-worth-4-trillion-125512305.html</link><description>These companies are worth $4 trillion—should you buy, sell or hold? Explore what makes them valuable and what investors need to know now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/every-company-worth-4-trillion-125512305.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Goldman Sachs Profit Rises on Jump in Dealmaking</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/banking/goldman-sachs-profit-rises-on-jump-in-dealmaking-eacd5db7</link><description>The bank reported record annual revenue in its core Wall Street engine of investment banking and trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/banking/goldman-sachs-profit-rises-on-jump-in-dealmaking-eacd5db7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Rally Extends on Manufacturing Optimism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rally-extends-manufacturing-optimism-121821915.html</link><description>Analyst upgrade and foundry progress keep momentum alive</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rally-extends-manufacturing-optimism-121821915.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] World’s biggest chipmaker TSMC doubles down on AI, sees profit lift</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/business/2026/01/15/worlds-biggest-chipmaker-tsmc-doubles-down-on-ai-sees-profit-lift?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</link><description>A surge in AI-driven demand has pushed TSMC’s profits and investment plans higher, reinforcing its position as one of the world’s most advanced semiconductor producers.View on euronews</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.euronews.com/business/2026/01/15/worlds-biggest-chipmaker-tsmc-doubles-down-on-ai-sees-profit-lift?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple, Qualcomm Hit AI Supply Snag</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-hit-ai-supply-113456357.html</link><description>Japan glass cloth emerges as bottleneck</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-hit-ai-supply-113456357.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Chip Stocks Rally After TSMC Earnings Boost AI Boom Outlook</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-15-2026/card/chip-stocks-rally-after-tsmc-earnings-boost-ai-boom-outlook-a36pcgoEQupV0J7HHQIq?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Companies that provide picks and shovels for the artificial-intelligence boom jumped after record earnings from Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. suggested that the AI rally still has room to run.  U.S.-listed shares of TSMC jumped 6% in premarket trading.  The world’s largest contract chip maker said it plans to increase capital expenditure this year to up to $56 billion, a sign that demand remains strong from clients such as Apple, Google and Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-15-2026/card/chip-stocks-rally-after-tsmc-earnings-boost-ai-boom-outlook-a36pcgoEQupV0J7HHQIq?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Palantir and CrowdStrike: Daniel Ives Reveals His Top AI Stocks for 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-crowdstrike-daniel-ives-reveals-110620738.html</link><description>AI has been generating hype and headlines over the past three years, since OpenAI launched the generative AI revolution with the release of ChatGPT. Since then, AI stocks have been driving the market’s bull run, and fueling gains in the tech sector – gains that, in some cases, have been measured in the trillions of dollars. Wedbush’s Daniel Ives has been looking into the sector, and putting his finger on the pulse of leading stocks at all scales. The analyst describes AI as a new Industrial Revo</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-crowdstrike-daniel-ives-reveals-110620738.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:06:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] ASML Soars Above $500 Billion Value on TSMC’s Upbeat Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-soars-above-500-billion-093955329.html</link><description>ASML surged above the symbolic level after TSMC on Thursday forecast capital spending to rise to as much as $56 billion in 2026, more than expected, showing how the chipmaker is benefiting from the artificial intelligence boom.  “The milestone means a lot for the market sentimentally,” said Barclays Plc strategist Emmanuel Cau.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-soars-above-500-billion-093955329.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trump’s Rare Earth Push Extends Lifeline to Green Tech</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-rare-earth-push-extends-103032971.html</link><description>In response, investors are pouring a record amount of money into US startups, providing support to an industry that also plays a key role in the energy transition.  China controls roughly 60% of the world’s rare earth mining output and more than 90% of the global refining capacity, according to an October report by the International Energy Agency.  Venture capitalists invested more than $628 million in US startups working on rare earth minerals in 2025, according to PitchBook data, accounting for 90% of all funding globally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-rare-earth-push-extends-103032971.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC smashes forecasts with record profit, flags more U.S. factories</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-smashes-forecasts-record-profit-100501507.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: TSMC smashed profit forecasts in the fourth-quarter as the AI boom continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world's main producer of advanced AI chips said Thursday (January 15) profits jumped 35% to $16 billion during the October-December period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It further predicted strong growth this year and said it was working on building more U.S. manufacturing capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taiwanese firm - which counts Nvidia and Apple as major customers - announced plans last year to invest $100 billion in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was on top of $65 billion pledged for three plants in the state of Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TSMC said more land had been bought in the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York Times has also reported the Trump administration is close to a trade deal with Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It aims to reduce its tariff rate to 15% and Washington wants TSMC to commit to building at least five more facilities in Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, TSMC believes first-quarter revenue could surge as much as 40% from a year earlier to $35.8 billion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AI boom has helped TSMC outshine its rivals and its&amp;amp;nbsp;Taipei-listed shares jumped 44% last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm's stock is up around 9% so far this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-smashes-forecasts-record-profit-100501507.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bitcoin price rallies as BlackRock drives fresh inflows</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-crypto-efs-blackrock-trump-094656477.html</link><description>Bitcoin extended its recent gains on Thursday, rising roughly 1.4% over the past 24 hours.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-crypto-efs-blackrock-trump-094656477.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] FTSE 100 LIVE: London muted as UK economy beats growth forecasts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-london-muted-uk-economy-gdp-092334894.html</link><description>Traders are betting there is a 6% chance of a reduction in borrowing costs in February, down from 7% on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-london-muted-uk-economy-gdp-092334894.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Taiwan computer chip maker TSMC's to expand investment as profit jumps 35%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-computer-chip-maker-tsmcs-080725424.html</link><description>Taiwan-based TSMC, the world’s largest computer chip maker, plans to increase its capital spending by about 40% this year after it reported a 35% jump in its net profit for the latest quarter thanks to the boom in artificial intelligence, the company said Thursday.  Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corp., a major supplier to companies including Nvidia and Apple, reported a net profit of 506 billion new Taiwan dollars ($16 billion) for the October-December quarter, a 35% surge from a year earlier, better than analysts’ estimates.  TSMC said Thursday that its revenue in the last quarter increased 21% from a year earlier to more than 1.046 trillion new Taiwan dollars ($33 billion).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-computer-chip-maker-tsmcs-080725424.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Boosts UNM Price Target, Sees Life Insurers Supported by Consolidation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-boosts-unm-price-target-075048654.html</link><description>Unum Group (NYSE:UNM) is included among the 14 Best Mid Cap Dividend Aristocrat Stocks to Buy Now. On January 8, Barclays raised its price target on Unum Group (NYSE:UNM) to $96 from $94 and maintained an Overweight rating. The firm said it remains “cautiously optimistic” on life insurers as the industry heads into 2026. Barclays […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-boosts-unm-price-target-075048654.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates 2026 View on Life Insurers, Lowers RGA Price Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-2026-view-life-074149491.html</link><description>Reinsurance Group of America, Incorporated (NYSE:RGA) is included among the 14 Best Mid Cap Dividend Aristocrat Stocks to Buy Now. On January 8, Barclays reduced its price target on Reinsurance Group of America, Incorporated (NYSE:RGA) to $237 from $251, while still maintaining an Overweight rating. The firm said it is heading into 2026 feeling “cautiously […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-2026-view-life-074149491.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] RenaissanceRe (RNR) Target Lifted by TD Cowen and Barclays as Market Pricing Softens</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/renaissancere-rnr-target-lifted-td-073724479.html</link><description>RenaissanceRe Holdings Ltd. (NYSE:RNR) is included among the 14 Best Mid Cap Dividend Aristocrat Stocks to Buy Now. On January 8, TD Cowen nudged up its price target on RenaissanceRe Holdings Ltd. (NYSE:RNR) to $280 from $278 and maintained a Hold rating. The firm said the move came after updating its model ahead of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/renaissancere-rnr-target-lifted-td-073724479.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] UK economy grew by more than expected in November despite budget uncertainty</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-economy-gdp-november-budget-073004115.html</link><description>The UK economy returned to growth in November, despite uncertainty in the run up to chancellor Rachel Reeves delivering the autumn budget.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-economy-gdp-november-budget-073004115.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC’s Strong Outlook Shores Up Hopes of Sustained AI Boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-strong-outlook-shores-hopes-072434087.html</link><description>It also foresees revenue growth of close to 30% in 2026, faster than the average analyst estimate.  Shares in key supplier ASML Holding NV rose 5% on Tradegate in Europe.  The outlook from TSMC — a bellwether for the artificial intelligence boom — reflects a development frenzy by the likes of Meta Platforms Inc. and Amazon.com Inc. that’s spurred demand for Nvidia Corp. accelerators.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-strong-outlook-shores-hopes-072434087.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Taiwan's TSMC logs net profit jump on AI boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwans-tsmc-logs-net-profit-061920911.html</link><description>Taiwanese chipmaking titan TSMC announced Thursday a forecast-busting net profit for the fourth quarter in a sign of sustained global demand for AI technology.Net revenue for the fourth quarter rose 20.5 percent from a year ago to NT$1.05 trillion, TSMC said, also beating expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwans-tsmc-logs-net-profit-061920911.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How The Evolving Story On NMI Holdings (NMIH) Is Shaping Fresh Views On Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evolving-story-nmi-holdings-nmih-060918826.html</link><description>NMI Holdings has just seen a small lift in its fair value estimate, rising from US$44.14 to US$45.14, alongside a slightly lower discount rate assumption of 7.64% instead of 7.72%. These tweaks reflect recent Street research that balances confidence in a stable credit backdrop and potential support from a stronger mortgage origination market in 2026 with ongoing caution around sector regulation and volatility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep track of these kinds of narrative shifts as they...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evolving-story-nmi-holdings-nmih-060918826.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC Ends 2025 With a Bang as AI Keeps Boosting Profits</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/tsmc-ends-2025-with-a-bang-as-ai-keeps-boosting-profits-9f775b1e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The world’s largest contract chip maker ended 2025 with another quarter of record earnings amid supply challenges and mounting pressure to bring production to American soil.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/tsmc-ends-2025-with-a-bang-as-ai-keeps-boosting-profits-9f775b1e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] First-time buyers save an average of £22,900 by negotiating prices</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/first-time-buyers-save-negotiating-house-prices-060053281.html</link><description>First-time buyers who negotiated on the asking price saved an average of £22,900, according to a TSB poll.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/first-time-buyers-save-negotiating-house-prices-060053281.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] UK rents expected to rise 2% in 2026 amid 'chronic' housing shortage</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rent-prices-london-shortage-rightmove-060052568.html</link><description>The national average asking rent outside London was £1,370 in the fourth quarter, slightly lower than the previous three months, according to Rightmove.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rent-prices-london-shortage-rightmove-060052568.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] NatWest, Barclays, Nationwide and Halifax cut mortgage costs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-barclays-halifax-bank-of-england-interest-rates-060030835.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-barclays-halifax-bank-of-england-interest-rates-060030835.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC Q4 profit jumps 35% to record, beats expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-profit-jumps-35-053601365.html</link><description>TSMC, the world's largest ​contract chipmaker, posted ‌a 35% jump in fourth-quarter ‌net profit on Thursday, beating market forecasts and hitting a record as ⁠it benefited ‌from surging demand for semiconductors used ‍in artificial intelligence applications. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co, whose customers include ​Nvidia and Apple, ‌saw October-December net profit rise to T$505.7 billion ($16.01 billion). The profit handily beat a T$478.4 billion LSEG ⁠SmartEstimate, which is ​weighted toward ​forecasts from analysts who are more consistently accurate.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-profit-jumps-35-053601365.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple drops a generous offer for creative users</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apple-drops-a-generous-offer-with-creator-studio-for-creative-users</link><description>Another mixed year is behind Apple. The tech giant reported a record-breaking $416 billion in revenue for fiscal 2025, up from $383 billion in 2024. While revenues rose, Apple’s stock performance was less impressive, gaining only around 9% amid scrutiny over delayed AI features. Despite ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apple-drops-a-generous-offer-with-creator-studio-for-creative-users</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>