<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Can Apple Stock Reach $350 in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/can-apple-stock-reach-350-in-2026/</link><description>Apple bulls hope that the consumer tech giant's shares can rise 35% before this year is over.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/can-apple-stock-reach-350-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] IBN's Q3 Earnings Dip on Higher Provision &amp; Expenses, NII Rises Y/Y</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibns-q3-earnings-dip-higher-172900554.html</link><description>ICICI Bank's Q3 FY26 earnings fall 4% due to higher provisions, costs and treasury loss, even as NII, fee income and loans post solid growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibns-q3-earnings-dip-higher-172900554.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC Jumps on Strong Q4 as AI Chip Demand Surges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-jumps-strong-q4-ai-165640626.html</link><description>The chip giant tops expectations and signals another strong year ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-jumps-strong-q4-ai-165640626.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Analysts reset Intel stock price target ahead of earnings</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/analysts-reset-intel-stock-price-target-ahead-of-earnings</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock has gained about 26.27% year to date, at the time of writing, Saturday morning, Jan. 17, according to Yahoo Finance. Meanwhile, SPY is up 1.43% in the same period. What caused Intel stock to outpace the S&amp;amp;P 500 by almost 25%? Two significant analyst notes boosted the stock. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/analysts-reset-intel-stock-price-target-ahead-of-earnings</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Gets New Street-High Target -- Analyst Sees Major Foundry Breakthrough</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-gets-street-high-162323983.html</link><description>Intel Stock Keeps Climbing. A KeyBanc Upgrade and Apple Tie-Up Are Fueling the Rally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-gets-street-high-162323983.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Magnificent 7 is Over: What Stocks Will Replace It?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-over-stocks-replace-161400706.html</link><description>Amazon and Tesla have underperformed for 5 years. Is it time to give them the boot?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-over-stocks-replace-161400706.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Well, there goes the metaverse!</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/well-goes-metaverse-160000767.html</link><description>The metaverse is on its last legs as VR is eclipsed by AI. But that's not the only thing that went wrong for Meta's VR ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/well-goes-metaverse-160000767.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock in Spotlight -- Tops China as Holiday iPhone Sales Soar</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-spotlight-tops-china-153443045.html</link><description>Apple Surpasses Rivals in China Despite Overall Market Decline</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-spotlight-tops-china-153443045.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Taiwan Semi Crushed Q4 Earnings. That Makes This 1 AI Chip Stock a Top Buy.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37111188/taiwan-semi-crushed-q4-earnings-that-makes-this-1-ai-chip-stock-a-top-buy</link><description>As Taiwan Semi reported solid Q4 results, Citi analysts upgraded Intel stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37111188/taiwan-semi-crushed-q4-earnings-that-makes-this-1-ai-chip-stock-a-top-buy</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Berkshire Hathaway Has 56% of Its Portfolio in These 4 Stocks. Are They Buys to Begin 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/berkshire-hathaway-has-56-of-portfolio-in-these-4/</link><description>You can't go wrong with adding blue chip stocks to your portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/berkshire-hathaway-has-56-of-portfolio-in-these-4/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL) Achieved an Adjusted EPS Growth of +13%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-achieved-adjusted-eps-143228140.html</link><description>Wedgewood Partners, an investment management company, released its fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. The firm anticipates stronger market volatility in the coming years and has moderated its enthusiasm. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The Wedgewood Composite returned -1.8% (net) in the fourth quarter compared to the S&amp;amp;P 500’s 2.7%, the Russell 1000 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-achieved-adjusted-eps-143228140.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Congresswoman Violates STOCK Act With Over 200 Late Trade Disclosures: Purchases Include Mag7, Healthcare Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/congresswoman-violates-stock-act-over-143116760.html</link><description>Rep. Julia Letlow (R-La.) reportedly violated a federal transparency law by failing to disclose her personal stock trades within the required time frame. Lawmaker Missed STOCK Act Trade Filings Letlow, a third-term Louisiana congresswoman, failed to disclose 224 stock and bond trades within the 45-day reporting window required under the Stop Trading on Congressional Knowledge (STOCK) Act, reported NOTUS on Thursday. Letlow also amended all five of her annual financial disclosures dating back to</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/congresswoman-violates-stock-act-over-143116760.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] ASML Stock Drops Due to Trade War Worries. These Chip Companies Are Suffering Too.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-stock-price-stmicroelectronics-trump-tariffs-chips-cf81cc8a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>ASML Holding  and shares of other companies in the semiconductor sector were dropping Monday.  The prospect of a trade war between the European Union and the U.S. is hurting chip stocks.  Dutch company ASML was down 3.3% in trading in the Netherlands.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-stock-price-stmicroelectronics-trump-tariffs-chips-cf81cc8a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Zacks Investment Ideas feature highlights: Netflix, Intel and Johnson &amp; Johnson</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-134700989.html</link><description>Netflix, Intel and Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson headline Zacks Investment Ideas as key earnings reports approach amid steady estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-134700989.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer on Apple: “It Worries Me That the Buyers Haven’t Figured Out to Buy It Yet”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-apple-worries-buyers-132945742.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer put under a microscope. Cramer mentioned the stock during the episode and said: “One listen to the words of Taiwan Semi, one gander at the transcript tells you that it’s worth buying Meta… as well as Apple, which was down today because expensive phones were […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-apple-worries-buyers-132945742.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Robinhood Stock a Millionaire Maker?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/is-robinhood-stock-a-millionaire-maker/</link><description>It's certainly performed as if it wants to be one.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/is-robinhood-stock-a-millionaire-maker/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] More AI means a higher need for cybersecurity: CrowdStrike CEO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/more-ai-means-higher-cybersecurity-110043500.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Co-Founder and CEO George Kurtz sits down with Yahoo Finance Executive Editor Brian Sozzi on Opening Bid for a conversation about the concerns around AI chatbot deployment and the role cybersecurity will have as more tech companies invest in building out AI data center infrastructure. Also watch George Kurtz discuss CrowdStrike's latest streak of acquisitions. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/more-ai-means-higher-cybersecurity-110043500.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Goldman Sachs Downgrades HP Inc (HPQ) to Sell</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-downgrades-hp-inc-124929663.html</link><description>​HP Inc. (NYSE:HPQ) is one of the Most Undervalued Tech Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 13, Mike Ng from Goldman Sachs downgraded HP Inc. (NYSE:HPQ) from Hold to Sell and lowered the price target from $24 to $21. ​The firm downgraded the stock, noting concerns regarding pressures affecting the company’s PC margins and […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-downgrades-hp-inc-124929663.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Are you concerned about Trump's tariff threat over Greenland? Have your say</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tariffs-greenland-investing-poll-124142379.html</link><description>President Donald Trump's threat of new tariffs over opposition to his proposed takeover of Greenland has spooked investors, sending global stock markets lower.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tariffs-greenland-investing-poll-124142379.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Inc. (AAPL) Faces Added Uncertainty from Regulatory Scrutiny in India</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-inc-aapl-faces-added-115314843.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is among the best debt-free stocks to buy now. On January 15, Reuters reported a significant development in India’s antitrust case against Apple over its anti-competitive policies on the App Store. As per the report, India’s penalty rules use the company’s global revenue to calculate penalties, a practice Apple contends is unfair. If […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-inc-aapl-faces-added-115314843.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Cathie Wood Bets Big on TSMC -- Loads Up Millions After Strong Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-bets-big-tsmc-114246476.html</link><description>Ark Invest Boosts TSMC Stake as AI Chip Demand Surges</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-bets-big-tsmc-114246476.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] SEC Approves Expanded Option Expirations for Magnificent Seven Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sec-approves-expanded-option-expirations-113650138.html</link><description>Decision allows Nasdaq to list Monday and Wednesday expiries, moving single-stock options closer to a daily trading structure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sec-approves-expanded-option-expirations-113650138.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike (CRWD) Valuation Check As Short Term Returns Cool And Long Term Gains Remain Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-valuation-check-short-111231831.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) is back in focus after recent trading, with the stock last closing at US$453.88. Investors are weighing this price against recent returns and the company’s current fundamentals. See our latest analysis for CrowdStrike Holdings. The recent 7 day share price return of 2.81% decline and 30 day share price return of 5.69% decline contrast with a 1 year total shareholder return of 27.14% and very large 3 year total shareholder return, which indicates that long term...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-valuation-check-short-111231831.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Which Vanguard ETF Is Most Likely to Soar in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/which-vanguard-etf-is-most-likely-to-soar-in-2026/</link><description>One Vanguard ETF stands out above the rest.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/which-vanguard-etf-is-most-likely-to-soar-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Eurozone inflation dips to 1.9%</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/eurozone-eu-inflation-economy-ecb-103353555.html</link><description>It marked the first time since May that inflation has come in below the European Central Bank’s (ECB) 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/eurozone-eu-inflation-economy-ecb-103353555.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 'I sold my house and risked everything on Smoke Free - we've now helped 1m people quit'</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/stop-smoking-app-smoke-free-subscription-101610356.html</link><description>David Crane is founder and CEO of Smoke Free, the UK’s leading quit-smoking app which has hit its one-millionth quitter milestone.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/stop-smoking-app-smoke-free-subscription-101610356.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays and Wells Fargo Lift Price Targets on Micron Technology (MU)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-wells-fargo-lift-price-091921903.html</link><description>Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) is one of the best strong buy growth stocks to buy according to hedge funds. On January 15, Barclays lifted the price target on Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) to $450 from $275 and maintained an Overweight rating on the shares, telling investors that it adjusted price targets and ratings on the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-wells-fargo-lift-price-091921903.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: These 5 Unstoppable Stocks Could Join the $5 Trillion Club in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-these-5-unstoppable-stocks-could-join-t/</link><description>These household names have been long-term winners, and that trend appears poised to continue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-these-5-unstoppable-stocks-could-join-t/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] US futures sink after Trump warns of higher tariffs for 8 countries over Greenland issue</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-sink-trump-warns-064219161.html</link><description>U.S. stock futures skidded Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened to slap a 10% extra tariff on imports from eight European countries due to their opposition to his desire to take control of Greenland.  The European countries targeted by Trump blasted the move, saying his threats “undermine transatlantic relations and risk a dangerous downward spiral.”  The unusually strong joint statement from Denmark, Norway, Sweden, France, Germany, the United Kingdom, the Netherlands and Finland was the most forceful rebuke from the European allies since he returned to the White House almost a year ago.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-sink-trump-warns-064219161.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Hamptons reports fall in rents in 2025 for first time on record</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/rents-fall-2025-property-housing-hamptons-letting-060053110.html</link><description>Newly agreed rents across Britain fell by 0.7% in 2025 to an average £1,371 per month, according to Hamptons' latest letting index.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/rents-fall-2025-property-housing-hamptons-letting-060053110.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How to get your tax return done in time</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tax-return-deadline-hmrc-personal-finances-060039370.html</link><description>As the self-assessment tax return deadline looms, here are seven things that can help you get it done in time.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tax-return-deadline-hmrc-personal-finances-060039370.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 3 Stocks to Buy for 2026 That Are Practically Money Machines</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/3-stocks-to-buy-for-2026-that-are-practically-mone/</link><description>These stocks don't literally print money. But they come close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/3-stocks-to-buy-for-2026-that-are-practically-mone/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] 1 Momentum  Stock to Target This Week and 2 We Find Risky</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-momentum-stock-target-week-043923009.html</link><description>The stocks featured in this article have all approached their 52-week highs. When these price levels hit, it typically signals strong business execution, positive market sentiment, or significant industry tailwinds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-momentum-stock-target-week-043923009.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Magnificent Seven Drove Markets. Now They’re Pulling in Different Directions.</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/mag-7-stocks-ai-trade-766bf561?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Magnificent Seven is now the Mag Five.  Investors are no longer grouping the market’s big tech stocks together in quite the same way.  The fortunes of what was once Wall Street’s favorite band of megacap names have diverged in the past year, as professional and ordinary investors alike take a more cautious view of the artificial-intelligence spending boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/mag-7-stocks-ai-trade-766bf561?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] By 2027, This Could Be One of the Most Important Stocks in Its Industry</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/2027-most-important-stock-industry-intel/</link><description>Semiconductor manufacturing tech is powering the AI revolution and other big trends. The industry could be poised for a shake-up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/2027-most-important-stock-industry-intel/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] BTIG Sees Strategic Value in CrowdStrike’s (CRWD) SGNL, Seraphic Acquisitions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/btig-sees-strategic-value-crowdstrike-215505035.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the Trending AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 13, BTIG analyst Gray Powell reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $640.00 price target. Firm analysts believe Crowdstrike’s recently announced acquisitions, SGNL &amp;amp; Seraphic, make strategic sense. BTIG highlighted how Crowdstrike’s acquisitions directly target the identity […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/btig-sees-strategic-value-crowdstrike-215505035.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Apple (AAPL) Still Priced Attractively After Recent Share Price Weakness?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-still-priced-attractively-210852314.html</link><description>You might be wondering if Apple’s current share price still makes sense, or if the stock is starting to look expensive or interesting again based on the numbers. Apple recently closed at US$255.53, with a 7 day return of a 1.5% decline, a 30 day return of a 6.6% decline, a year to date return of a 5.7% decline, an 11.6% return over 1 year, and returns of 88.1% and 88.8% over 3 and 5 years respectively. These moves sit against a backdrop of ongoing product updates, services expansion, and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-still-priced-attractively-210852314.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>