<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 07:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Apple iPhone just had its best year in India as the smartphone market stays broadly flat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-iphone-just-had-best-050000323.html</link><description>Apple shipped a record 14 million iPhones in India in 2025 and gained market share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-iphone-just-had-best-050000323.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Analyst sends blunt 3-word warning on Intel stock after earnings</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/analyst-sends-blunt-3-word-warning-on-intel-stock-after-earnings</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock tumbled 17% on Jan. 23 after the chipmaker issued weaker-than-expected guidance for the current quarter. The company beat expectations in the fourth quarter of 2025. Adjusted earnings came at 15 cents per share, well above Wall Street’s forecast of 8 cents. Revenue reached ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/analyst-sends-blunt-3-word-warning-on-intel-stock-after-earnings</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Tesla and Buys This Consumer Electronics Stock Instead</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-tesla-and-b/</link><description>Peter Thiel significantly reduced exposure to Tesla stock and swapped his gains for Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-tesla-and-b/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] How Intel Came Crashing Back to Earth After Its Trump Bump</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/intel-problems-trump-bump-17d2c941?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>After months of riding positive vibes, the troubled chip maker reminded investors why it needed a rescue in the first place.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/intel-problems-trump-bump-17d2c941?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Stock Crashed Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-intel-stock-is-down-today/</link><description>Investors are taking profits after the popular tech stock's recent run-up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-intel-stock-is-down-today/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] U.S. Millionaires Considering Migration: The Numbers</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/u-s-millionaires-considering-migration-the-numbers-b7ab6089?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A new survey of 1,0000 millionaires suggests that a third are motivated to leave the U.S. a year into President Donald Trump’s second term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/u-s-millionaires-considering-migration-the-numbers-b7ab6089?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Review &amp; Preview: Shiny Days</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-today-gold-silver-rally-59e013a4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 finished the week down 0.4% while the Nasdaq Composite was off 0.1%.  While stocks ended where they began, the real action came in precious metals, with investors rushing to gold and silver amid an increasingly uncertain geopolitical environment.  Ed Yardeni, president and chief investment strategist at Yardeni Research, thinks the precious metals rally can continue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-today-gold-silver-rally-59e013a4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What Ultra Clean Holdings (UCTT)'s Rising AI Chip Supply-Chain Profile Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-rising-001840733.html</link><description>In the past week, Ultra Clean Holdings drew attention as enthusiasm around the AI chip supply chain lifted suppliers tied to advanced semiconductor manufacturing, following TSMC’s plans to ramp up spending on AI and high-performance chips. Because Ultra Clean provides specialized subsystems and ultra-high purity manufacturing services essential for leading-edge fabs, many investors now view it as a critical enabler of AI-related semiconductor production rather than just a traditional...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-rising-001840733.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Mag 7 earnings, Fed's rate decision: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mag-7-earnings-feds-rate-000012663.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come throughout next week, including a wide array of earnings results due out from major companies like Microsoft (MSFT), Meta Platforms (META), Apple (AAPL), Tesla (TSLA), and many more; and the Federal Reserve's latest interest rate decision followed by a press conference with chairman Jerome Powell. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mag-7-earnings-feds-rate-000012663.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Heard on the Street Recap: Go for Gold</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-go-for-gold-g4mAqNHKflLQbU4xt8W4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>What Happened in Markets Today Stocks ended a wild week on a mixed note. The S&amp;amp;P 500 was slightly higher on Friday, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average shed 285 points, or 0.6%. The Nasdaq Composite gained 0.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-go-for-gold-g4mAqNHKflLQbU4xt8W4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] US stocks end mixed as Intel's outlook weighs on risk appetite</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/us-stocks-end-mixed-intels-231146805.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Wall Street's main indexes ended mixed on Friday, with the Dow dropping nearly six-tenths of a percent, the S&amp;amp;P 500 ending basically flat and the Nasdaq gaining almost three-tenths of a percent.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Friday's mixed close capped a turbulent week for stocks, with the indexes whiplashing in reaction to President Trump's see-sawing tariff threats on European allies who opposed his ambition to acquire Greenland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stocks on Friday, however, took on a more familiar look, said Brad Conger, chief investment officer at Hirtle Callaghan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we are seeing today is a very classic setup from last year, all the way from May, all the way through October - which was Mag 7 working, everything else not working. So banks, nuclear energy, meme stocks, smallcaps, they're all dramatically underperforming. And so this is in a way a flashback to sort of a pattern that we know very well, but we haven't seen it in a few months. I think this tells us something about the rotation that happened, starting around early November, that maybe it's gone far enough.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next week may test whether many of those Magnificent Seven stocks can continue their momentum, with Apple, Tesla and Microsoft among those set to report earnings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia - which doesn't report until late February - rose on Friday after Bloomberg News reported Chinese officials have told Alibaba, Tencent and ByteDance they can prepare orders for Nvidia's H200 AI chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One tech stock that didn't perform well Friday was Intel, which nosedived 17% after the company forecast quarterly revenue and profit below market estimates, saying it struggled to satisfy demand for its server chips used in AI data centers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors now turn their focus to the Federal Reserve's two-day policy meeting beginning Tuesday, during which the central bank is expected to leave interest rates unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/us-stocks-end-mixed-intels-231146805.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Did GlobalFoundries' (GFS) New Board Appointment Signal a Deeper Shift in Its Manufacturing Strategy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-globalfoundries-gfs-board-appointment-230814506.html</link><description>GlobalFoundries has appointed Ganesh Moorthy, former president and CEO of Microchip Technology and longtime Intel executive, to its board of directors, effective January 15, 2026. His concurrent roles across semiconductor, materials and precision technology companies position him to bring a cross-industry perspective to GlobalFoundries’ manufacturing and power-efficient technology ambitions. We’ll now examine how Moorthy’s four decades of semiconductor leadership may influence...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-globalfoundries-gfs-board-appointment-230814506.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Markets Passed a TACO Test. Another Kind of Stress Test Is Coming.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/markets-passed-taco-test-stress-test-tech-edc2b260?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>One clear beneficiary of the turmoil: precious metals. Silver has been unstoppable, hitting $100 for the first time in history with a 43% year-to-date gain.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/markets-passed-taco-test-stress-test-tech-edc2b260?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Magnificent 7 Earnings Loom: What to Expect?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-earnings-loom-expect-225400270.html</link><description>Four of the Mag 7 members are on the reporting docket next week, including Apple, Microsoft, Meta Platforms, and Tesla. Can the results keep broader sentiment in check?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-earnings-loom-expect-225400270.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Is Still Making Too Many Unforced Errors. Can the Chip Giant Get Out of Its Own Way?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-is-still-making-too-many-unforced-errors-can/</link><description>Investors are betting big on a turnaround, but the company keeps making execution mistakes.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-is-still-making-too-many-unforced-errors-can/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today, Jan. 23: Intel's Weak Outlook Weighs on Dow While Nasdaq Edges Higher</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-s-weak-outlook-weighs-on-dow-while-nasdaq-edges-higher/</link><description>Intel's downbeat outlook knocked the Dow while strength in mega-cap and AI names kept the Nasdaq in the green, today, Jan. 23, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-s-weak-outlook-weighs-on-dow-while-nasdaq-edges-higher/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today, Jan. 23: Intel Plunges After Weak Outlook Highlights Supply Constraints and Foundry Losses</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-plunges-after-weak-outlook-highlights-supply-constraints-and-foundry-losses/</link><description>Today, Jan. 23, 2026, investors are weighing whether Intel’s supply snags and foundry losses threaten its AI data-center ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-plunges-after-weak-outlook-highlights-supply-constraints-and-foundry-losses/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia Dethrones Apple As Taiwan Semiconductor's Largest Customer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dethrones-apple-taiwan-semiconductors-223132958.html</link><description>Nvidia Corp's (NASDAQ:NVDA) surge in artificial intelligence demand is reshaping the global semiconductor supply chain. Nvidia has overtaken Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd's (NYSE:TSM) largest customer. Nvidia chief Jensen Huang confirmed the change publicly for the first time during a recent podcast. Nvidia now ranks as Taiwan Semiconductor's biggest client—an outcome he suggested would please Taiwan Semiconductor founder Morris Chang. Don't Miss: Missed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dethrones-apple-taiwan-semiconductors-223132958.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Broadcom Stock Fell Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-broadcom-stock-fell-today/</link><description>Broadcom stock fell after another major chip player reported earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-broadcom-stock-fell-today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Dow Jones Futures: Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, Apple Lead Earnings Wave After Whipsaw Trump Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings-wave-trump-week/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tesla, Microsoft, Meta and Apple lead an earnings wave after the stock market weathered whipsaw action from President Trump's moves</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings-wave-trump-week/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Earnings live: Intel stock plunges, with more Big Tech earnings from Apple, Microsoft, and Tesla ahead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-intel-stock-plunges-with-more-big-tech-earnings-from-apple-microsoft-and-tesla-ahead-213536730.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear in the week ahead, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-intel-stock-plunges-with-more-big-tech-earnings-from-apple-microsoft-and-tesla-ahead-213536730.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] How major US stock indexes fared Friday, 1/23/2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/major-us-stock-indexes-fared-212106052.html</link><description>The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 0.6%, and the Nasdaq composite rose 0.3%. The majority of U.S. stocks fell, including Intel, which gave a weaker financial forecast for upcoming results than analysts expected. The U.S. dollar's value slid against the Japanese yen, euro and other currencies, while gold rose to another record in a signal that nervousness remains in the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/major-us-stock-indexes-fared-212106052.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel’s High-Flying Stock Wasn’t Priced for Reality</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-s-high-flying-stock-wasn-t-priced-for-reality-3Yfq0Pade7OOtd1bIAN2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel just experienced its worst selloff in nearly 18 months.  Intel closed down 17% Friday.  The selloff came after the company’s fourth-quarter report made clear that Intel’s turnaround is still a work in progress.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-s-high-flying-stock-wasn-t-priced-for-reality-3Yfq0Pade7OOtd1bIAN2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel's Lip-Bu Tan is making the 'right' moves, analyst says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intels-lip-bu-tan-making-205400064.html</link><description>Intel stock (INTC) continues sinking ahead of Friday's session close after the chipmaker reported disappointing guidance for its first quarter of 2026, admitting that the company is struggling to meet AI data center demands. Bernstein managing director and senior analyst Stacy Rasgon comments on Intel CEO Lip-Bu Tan's — who took charge of the company almost a year ago after Pat Gelsinger's sudden departure in December 2024 — leadership and what he brings to the table while helping reorganize the chipmaker. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intels-lip-bu-tan-making-205400064.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel stock plunges as hopes for a 'clean' turnaround story meet reality</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-plunges-as-hopes-for-a-clean-turnaround-story-meet-reality-202949131.html</link><description>Intel stock plunged on Friday following the chipmaker's disappointing first quarter outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-plunges-as-hopes-for-a-clean-turnaround-story-meet-reality-202949131.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Buy the Dip in Apple Stock Before January 29, According to Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37202450/buy-the-dip-in-apple-stock-before-january-29-according-to-goldman-sachs</link><description>Goldman Sachs analysts expect robust iPhone sales growth ahead of Apple’s Q1 earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37202450/buy-the-dip-in-apple-stock-before-january-29-according-to-goldman-sachs</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Fed Meeting, Apple, Microsoft Earnings: What to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/fed-meeting-apple-microsoft-earnings-what-to-watch-next-week-VNAIhG6O6w0ELdN06BAb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>It's shaping up to be a busy week ahead. Earnings season is in full throttle, with results expected from the likes of UnitedHealth, Chevron and Boeing. A trio of tech giants—Apple, Meta Platforms and Microsoft—will also report earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/fed-meeting-apple-microsoft-earnings-what-to-watch-next-week-VNAIhG6O6w0ELdN06BAb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Marvell Technology, Western Digital, Photronics, FormFactor, and Amkor Shares Plummet, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/marvell-technology-western-digital-photronics-195606673.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after Intel reported disappointing earnings report and weak forecast for the current quarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/marvell-technology-western-digital-photronics-195606673.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel vs. TSMC: Can Intel Close the Gap?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-tsmc-intel-close-195400413.html</link><description>Intel stock is selling off following its earnings report, but is there more to this story?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-tsmc-intel-close-195400413.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Plunges: Time To Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-stock-plunges-time-to-buy-the-dip/</link><description>Intel's guidance disappointed the market. Is the turnaround story still alive?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-stock-plunges-time-to-buy-the-dip/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 6 of My Top 10 Stocks for 2025 Increased by More Than 25%. Are They Still Buys Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/6-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-increased-by-more-t/</link><description>The market delivered a strong gain in 2025, but it was no match for these stock picks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/6-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-increased-by-more-t/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Dow Jones Stocks: Nvidia, Amgen Are Near Buy Points But This Longtime Loser Is Winning The Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stocks-nvidia-amgen-buy-points-procter-gamble/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan upgraded long-ailing consumer goods giant Procter &amp;amp; Gamble. Nvidia and Amgen are among several Dow Jones stocks near buy points.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stocks-nvidia-amgen-buy-points-procter-gamble/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Binance plans to bring back tokenized stock trading after 2021 retreat</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2026/01/23/binance-plans-return-to-stock-tokens-after-2021-retreat-the-information</link><description>The exchange shut down its earlier effort under regulatory pressure, but it's now back to exploring offering tokenized equities on its platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2026/01/23/binance-plans-return-to-stock-tokens-after-2021-retreat-the-information</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel realized overwhelming AI date center demands 'too late'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-realized-overwhelming-ai-date-183000576.html</link><description>Intel stock (INTC) continues to plunge in Friday's trading session after the chipmaker reported disappointing first quarter guidance, revealing a struggle to meet AI data center demands. While the semiconductor manufacturer topped fourth quarter earnings and revenue estimates, was there anything new unveiled in this report? Benchmark Company managing director and senior semiconductor research analyst Cody Acree and Wedbush Securities managing director of equity research Matt Bryson comment on Intel's latest earnings and guidance figures and what they mean for the AI chip stock going forward in 2026. Also catch Cody Acree and Matt Bryson discuss the ripple effects that Intel's guidance may have on memory chipmakers and prices. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-realized-overwhelming-ai-date-183000576.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Applied Materials Stock Rises On Deutsche Bank Upgrade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-stock-rises-deutsche-181343411.html</link><description>Applied Materials Gains Analyst Support Amid Rising Memory Capex</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-stock-rises-deutsche-181343411.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock plunges, consumer sentiment high, gold &amp; silver rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-plunges-consumer-sentiment-181224097.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance's John Hyland tracks Friday's top moving stocks and biggest market stories in this Market Minute, including US consumer sentiment hitting a five-month high, Intel (INTC) stock's nosedive, and gold (GC=F) and silver's (SI=F) record-setting weekly performance. Stay up to date on the latest market action, minute-by-minute, with&amp;amp;nbsp;Yahoo Finance's Market Minute.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-plunges-consumer-sentiment-181224097.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Morgan Stanley Names ASML and ASMI as Top Pick Ahead of Q4 Results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-names-asml-asmi-181200829.html</link><description>ASML and ASMI Set to Surge as Morgan Stanley Calls Breakthrough Quarter Ahead</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-names-asml-asmi-181200829.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Does New Safety-Certifiable Multicore Platform Deepen Curtiss-Wright’s Mission-Critical Edge (CW)?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-safety-certifiable-multicore-platform-180915670.html</link><description>In January 2026, Green Hills Software and Curtiss-Wright announced a new commercial off-the-shelf platform that pairs Curtiss-Wright’s SOSA-aligned V3-1222 3U VPX processing module, featuring 13th Gen Intel Core i7 and Iris Xe graphics, with Green Hills’ FACE-certified INTEGRITY-178 tuMP real-time operating system for safety-certifiable aerospace computing. This collaboration expands Curtiss-Wright’s reach into mission- and safety-critical markets by offering a pre-integrated,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-safety-certifiable-multicore-platform-180915670.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Investors Are Acting As if QQQ Is the Perfect Investment Right Now (And Maybe It Actually Is)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investors-are-acting-as-if-qqq-is-the-perfect-investment-right-now-and-maybe-it-actually-is/</link><description>Shares of the Invesco QQQ Trust (NASDAQ:QQQ) are having a good week, coinciding with a surge in retail investor sentiment on Reddit and X. The fund now carries a social sentiment score of 90, one of the highest readings tracked across all ETFs and stocks. This optimism centers on aggressive options positioning, particularly in the ... Investors Are Acting As if QQQ Is the Perfect Investment Right Now (And Maybe It Actually Is)</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investors-are-acting-as-if-qqq-is-the-perfect-investment-right-now-and-maybe-it-actually-is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Advanced Micro Devices Could Be This Year's Best Value Play</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-advanced-micro-devices-best-value-play/</link><description>Is AMD still in the early stages of benefiting from artificial intelligence (AI) tailwinds?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-advanced-micro-devices-best-value-play/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump Ushers in the Era of ‘Big America’—Around the World and Here at Home, Too</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-big-america-davos-66b56574?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>New measures from the White House touch on countless facets of our economy and society. And then there’s the president’s many forays overseas.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-big-america-davos-66b56574?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel (INTC) Stock Is Falling Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-falling-171036238.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) fell 15.6% in the morning session after the company reported underwhelming fourth quarter results with sales guidance for the next quarter falling short of Wall Street's expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-falling-171036238.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Vishay Precision (VPG) Shares Are Sliding Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-vishay-precision-vpg-shares-170550204.html</link><description>Shares of precision measurement and sensing technologies provider Vishay Precision (NYSE:VPG) fell 6.1% in the morning session after negative sentiment spread across the semiconductor sector following a disappointing forecast from industry giant Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-vishay-precision-vpg-shares-170550204.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] This Semiconductor Stock Could Be at the Center of the Artificial Intelligence Spending Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/semiconductor-stock-center-ai-spending-micron/</link><description>Micron is in a prime position to benefit from the increasing demand for high-bandwidth memory.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/semiconductor-stock-center-ai-spending-micron/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Are You Looking for a Top Momentum Pick? Why Lloyds (LYG) is a Great Choice</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-top-momentum-pick-why-170002198.html</link><description>Does Lloyds (LYG) have what it takes to be a top stock pick for momentum investors? Let's find out.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-top-momentum-pick-why-170002198.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Falls After Investor Expectations Get Ahead Of Reality</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/intel-stock-falls-on-disappointing-q1-2026-outlook/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Intel turnaround story is going to take longer than expected to play out, analysts say. Intel stock dropped Friday after its Q4 report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/intel-stock-falls-on-disappointing-q1-2026-outlook/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Where Will Apple Stock Be in 1 Year?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/where-will-apple-stock-be-in-1-year/</link><description>Key catalysts lie ahead for this market giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/where-will-apple-stock-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Falls, Recovers On Trump's Greenland Shifts; Intel, Netflix, Tesla Key Movers: Weekly Review</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/stock-market-falls-recovers-on-trumps-greenland-shifts-intel-netflix-tesla-key-movers-weekly-review/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market plunged initially on President Trump's Greenland tariffs, but recovered as he backed off. Intel, Netflix, Tesla were key movers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/stock-market-falls-recovers-on-trumps-greenland-shifts-intel-netflix-tesla-key-movers-weekly-review/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:10:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The US Has Lost $2.4 Billion on Its Intel Stake Today</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-us-stake-loss-8b399820?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>One of Intel’s largest shareholders is the U.S. government, stemming from an August deal that converted some of Intel’s CHIPS Act subsidies into newly issued shares overseen by the Commerce Department.  With the stock down 15.2% in midday Friday trading, the government has taken a $2.4 billion loss on the day—but has still notched a 121% return overall since August.  Over two tranches, the Commerce Department bought 278 million shares of  Intel  through the end of last year, at a weighted average price of $20.73.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-us-stake-loss-8b399820?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Are you concerned about the Greenland dispute? How readers voted</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/greenland-trump-stocks-poll-results-160631727.html</link><description>Markets have whipsawed this week, driven by US president Donald Trump's rapid shift in tone over his ambitions for Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/greenland-trump-stocks-poll-results-160631727.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Advanced Micro Devices Stock Popped Friday</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-advanced-micro-devices-stock-popped-friday/</link><description>Intel's troubles may be AMD's opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-advanced-micro-devices-stock-popped-friday/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Airbnb CEO Brian Chesky says Steve Jobs proved being a micromanager is good for workers—in reality, it could actually be holding Gen Z’s careers back</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-ceo-brian-chesky-warns-154507291.html</link><description>Airbnb CEO says Steve Jobs taught him that obsessing over details isn’t about control—it’s about helping people think bigger. Gen Z might disagree.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-ceo-brian-chesky-warns-154507291.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks to watch next week: Tesla, Meta, Microsoft, Apple and Lloyds</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-meta-microsoft-apple-lloyds-stocks-to-watch-153735797.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-meta-microsoft-apple-lloyds-stocks-to-watch-153735797.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017784.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017784.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] As Apple Builds Its New Campos Chatbot, Should You Buy, Sell, or Hold AAPL Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37197885/as-apple-builds-its-new-campos-chatbot-should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-aapl-stock</link><description>Apple is building a new chatbot that it plans to integrate into its operating system by the end of the year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37197885/as-apple-builds-its-new-campos-chatbot-should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-aapl-stock</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Boeing Stock Rips Higher Ahead Of Q4 Results; 3 Data Storage Stocks In Earnings Spotlight</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/boeing-stock-rips-higher-q4-earnings-data-storage-western-digital-seagate-sandisk-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Boeing stock has been on a tear ahead of its Q4 report as Wall Street bets on clearer skies ahead for the aerospace giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/boeing-stock-rips-higher-q4-earnings-data-storage-western-digital-seagate-sandisk-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Q4 2025 Earnings Call Transcript</title><link>https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/23/intel-intc-q4-2025-earnings-call-transcript/</link><description>Over the last 10 months, we established the foundation for new Intel, a more focus and execution-driven company.  Along with our next-generation Nova Lake coming at the end of 2026, we now have a client road map that combines best-in-class performance with cost-optimized solutions giving me confidence that we are on the path to fortify market share and profitability in both notebooks and desktops over the next several years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/23/intel-intc-q4-2025-earnings-call-transcript/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel's honesty about AI demand struggles is 'encouraging'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intels-honesty-ai-demand-struggles-144650397.html</link><description>Intel's (INTC) disappointing first quarter guidance has sent the stock tumbling while also topping fourth quarter earnings and revenue estimates, stating that the chip foundry company is struggling to meet AI data center demands. Hennion &amp;amp; Walsh CIO Kevin Mahn expands upon why he thinks Intel's honesty over demand struggles is "encouraging." To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intels-honesty-ai-demand-struggles-144650397.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds set to see annual profits rise despite motor finance hit</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-set-see-annual-profits-144621947.html</link><description>Most analysts expect the lender to deliver a 7% rise in pre-tax profits for the year, with the City pencilling in £6.38 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-set-see-annual-profits-144621947.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel stock sinks as company's Q1 outlook falls short of Wall Street expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-sinks-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143343615.html</link><description>Intel reported fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-sinks-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143343615.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Andrew Ng Thinks AI Apps are “Underinvested”—Here are the Stocks I’d Buy in Response</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/andrew-ng-thinks-ai-apps-are-underinvested-here-are-the-stocks-id-buy-in-response/</link><description>While others see an inflating AI bubble that could burst and lose investors a boatload of money, others see underinvestment in some specific parts of the theme. Undoubtedly, it’s hard to know with any degree of certainty where the AI trade goes next, especially as other volatility drivers (think Trump tariffs) are thrown into the ... Andrew Ng Thinks AI Apps are “Underinvested”—Here are the Stocks I’d Buy in Response</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/andrew-ng-thinks-ai-apps-are-underinvested-here-are-the-stocks-id-buy-in-response/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Can Intel Live up to the Hype This Year and Shoot Through $100?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/can-intel-live-up-to-the-hype-this-year-and-shoot-through-100/</link><description>Investors rewarded Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) prematurely heading into earnings on January 22, but it ended up being a disappointment. Revenue and EPS both beat consensus, but it wasn’t enough to lift the mood. Revenue came in at $13.67 billion vs. the $13.39 consensus. Non-GAAP EPS came in at $0.15 vs. the $0.08 consensus. What disappointed the ... Can Intel Live up to the Hype This Year and Shoot Through $100?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/can-intel-live-up-to-the-hype-this-year-and-shoot-through-100/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Intel, AMD, Tesla, Capital One, Booz Allen, BitGo, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-c4ed1582?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel shares plummet following disappointing guidance, while rival AMD is poised to add to an eight-day winning streak.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-c4ed1582?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock sinks on weak guidance: Q4 earnings takeaways</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-sinks-weak-guidance-141418133.html</link><description>Intel stock (INTC) continues to fall lower in Friday's pre-market trading after the hardware and chip manufacturer released disappointing first quarter guidance. Yahoo Finance Tech and Markets Reporter Laura Bratton comes on Morning Brief to break down the biggest takeaways from Intel's earnings release, examining the company's foundry business in terms of AI data center demands and its outlook on its Panther Lake processors. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-sinks-weak-guidance-141418133.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel's stock falls 13% in premarket trading, after missing Wall Street estimates</title><link>https://qz.com/intel-stock-ai-chipmaker-shares-semiconductor</link><description>The chipmaker issued a softer-than-expected outlook for the first quarter, reigniting concerns about its turnaround</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://qz.com/intel-stock-ai-chipmaker-shares-semiconductor</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike (CRWD) Is a Trending Stock: Facts to Know Before Betting on It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-trending-stock-facts-140005624.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Therefore, it is wise to be aware of the facts that can impact the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-trending-stock-facts-140005624.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Most-Watched Stock Apple Inc. (AAPL) Worth Betting on Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-apple-inc-140002795.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately. So, it is worth exploring what lies ahead for the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-apple-inc-140002795.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel shares tumble as supply chain snarls hamper turnaround</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-shares-tumble-supply-chain-135036641.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Intel shares plunged 12% on Friday (January 23).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors sold off after the company struggled to meet strong AI demand for data center chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It blamed that on supply constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm had also forecast quarterly revenue and profit below market estimates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market watchers were disappointed as many had bet on Intel's turnaround.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm is a latecomer to the AI boom and has finally enjoyed a demand surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers want its traditional server chips which are used alongside AI processors in data centers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investor interest also grew due to investments in the firm from the U.S. government, Softbank and Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intel's stock outpaced most semiconductor firms last year with an 84% gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It extended its rally into this year - and was up close to half this month so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the company couldn't keep up with the demand surge even as it runs factories at capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also warned a spike in memory chip prices could hurt sales in the PC market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its new "Panther Lake" PC chips were expected to spark a comeback after years of market share losses to AMD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The memory chip surge is driven by growing AI demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Intel said it expects available memory supply to improve in the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That after hitting its lowest levels in the first quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-shares-tumble-supply-chain-135036641.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple, Microsoft, and Tesla Earnings Loom as Stocks Stall and Risks Mount. Something’s Got to Give.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-microsoft-tesla-earnings-stock-market-risk-eed32393?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>With U.S. stocks stuck in their worst rut since the summer, Treasury bonds in a slump, gold testing $5,000 for the first time on record, and geopolitical risks dominating, the stakes couldn’t be higher for the first round of mega tech earnings coming up next week.  Four of the so-called Magnificent Seven tech giants—  Microsoft Meta Platforms Tesla  and  Apple  —are slated to post quarterly earnings next week.  Outside of the Mag 7 updates, just over 100 companies are expected to post fourth-quarter updates over the coming week, as well as near-term outlooks that will either test or consolidate that current investor rotation away from tech and growth stocks into so-called value names.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-microsoft-tesla-earnings-stock-market-risk-eed32393?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls In Wake Of Greenland Deal Rally; Intel Plunges After Earnings (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Friday following two days of gains from the Greenland deal rally. Intel plunged on earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Shares Drop 12% on AI Supply Constraints</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-drop-12-ai-125949151.html</link><description>Shortfall in data-center chip supply weighs on turnaround hopes.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-drop-12-ai-125949151.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dow Jones Futures Fall As Intel Dives, Nvidia Gets H200 China Boost; Tesla Self-Driving In Focus</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-intel-dives-nvidia-h200-chips-china-tesla-self-driving/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Futures fell after as Intel dived, but Nvidia H200 chip sales may be close in China. Tesla has big self-driving robotaxi news..</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-intel-dives-nvidia-h200-chips-china-tesla-self-driving/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Faces Memory-Price Crunch. Why Apple Will Be the Next Victim.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-memory-8b5df4e5?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock was falling as it faces headwinds from soaring memory-chip prices, which could hit other companies such as Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-memory-8b5df4e5?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] BTIG Remains a Buy on CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (CRWD)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/btig-remains-buy-crowdstrike-holdings-123952313.html</link><description>​CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the Best Cybersecurity Stocks to Buy in 2026. Wall Street is bullish on the stock, with analysts’ 12-month price targets suggesting more than 26% upside from current levels. Recently, on January 20, Gray Powell from BTIG reiterated a Buy rating on CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) with a $640 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/btig-remains-buy-crowdstrike-holdings-123952313.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Slid After Supply Shortages Hit Its Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-slid-supply-shortages-123453421.html</link><description>Supply shortages weigh on guidance, manufacturing execution in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-slid-supply-shortages-123453421.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is It Too Late to Sell Lucid Motors Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37193765/is-it-too-late-to-sell-lucid-motors-stock</link><description>Lucid Motors stock fell to a record low and briefly plunged below $10. Is it too late to sell the struggling startup EV stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37193765/is-it-too-late-to-sell-lucid-motors-stock</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Gold Has Shone. How Trump, Fed Can Keep It Surging in a Turbulent Market.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/gold-prices-trump-fed-things-to-know-today-e48324fb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel is still facing supply constraints, Trump vows retaliation as ‘Sell America’ list grows, airlines brace for chaos ahead of winter storm, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/gold-prices-trump-fed-things-to-know-today-e48324fb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Shares Slide After Weak Forecast, Manufacturing Issues Resurface</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slide-weak-forecast-113556797.html</link><description>First-quarter revenue outlook misses estimates as CEO warns low yields and supply constraints will take time to fix.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slide-weak-forecast-113556797.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Shares Nosedive On Disappointing Outlook Despite Q4 Beat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-nosedive-disappointing-outlook-113235121.html</link><description>Intel Stock Slides After Outlook Disappoints. Why Investors Looked Past the Q4 Beat</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-nosedive-disappointing-outlook-113235121.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Greg Abel's First Significant Move Since Warren Buffett's Retirement Was Likely Just Revealed by One of Berkshire Hathaway's Largest Holdings</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/greg-abel-first-move-since-warren-buffett-retired/</link><description>Although everyone is waiting for Abel's first stock purchase as CEO, it's his selling activity that could leave an indelible mark.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/greg-abel-first-move-since-warren-buffett-retired/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Lenovo looking to partner with multiple AI models, CFO says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lenovo-looking-partner-multiple-ai-110900834.html</link><description>Lenovo is seeking partnerships with multiple large language models around the world to power its ​devices as it aims to establish itself as a global AI ‌player, the company's chief financial officer said.  Lenovo, the world's largest personal computer maker, plans to equip its ‌broad range of products - from PCs to smartphones and wearables - with AI technology.  "We are the only company besides Apple with significant market share across both ⁠PCs and mobiles, and in ‌the open Android and Windows ecosystems," Lenovo CFO Winston Cheng told Reuters on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum in ‍Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lenovo-looking-partner-multiple-ai-110900834.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[PHNX.L] Aegon attracts bidders for $2.7bn UK insurance business</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/aegon-uk-insurance-business-bidders/</link><description>Since late last year, the Netherlands-based insurer has been reviewing options for its UK insurance and workplace business.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/aegon-uk-insurance-business-bidders/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple and Dell supplier Pegatron expects US plant to be completed by end of March</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230142.html</link><description>TAIPEI, Jan 23 () - Taiwanese ​contract electronics ‌manufacturer Pegatron's first ‌U. factory is expected to be ⁠completed ‌by the end of ‍March, with trial production to ​begin around ‌then or April, President and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng said ⁠on Friday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230142.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Friday: Intel, Capital One, CSX</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-intel-capital-one-csx-9Goek52ChmE0WrX9mR8l?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ Intel (INTC): The chip maker swung to a bigger-than-expected loss and forecast more losses this quarter. It said it hadn’t adequately anticipated demand from AI data centers. Shares slid more than 12% in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-intel-capital-one-csx-9Goek52ChmE0WrX9mR8l?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple supplier Pegatron expects US plant to be completed by end-March</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230268.html</link><description>Taiwanese contract electronics manufacturer Pegatron's first U.S. factory, in Texas, is expected ​to be completed by the end of March, with ‌trial production to begin around then or April, President and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng ‌said on Friday.  The company, a supplier to Apple, Microsoft and Tesla, said in October it had acquired an industrial building and land in Texas, joining other Taiwanese tech manufacturers investing in the state ⁠including Foxconn, Inventec and ‌Wistron.  "It is currently scheduled to be completed by the end of ​March, and we should be able to begin trial ‌production in late March or April."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230268.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Falls After Loss Exceeds Forecasts</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-stock-falls-after-loss-exceeds-forecasts-FbF4fVVxIbHSiWm2Uo72?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock dropped offhours, after the chip maker swung to a larger-than-expected quarterly loss.  Shares slid 13% in recent premarket trading.   Intel forecast further losses to start 2026, as it spends heavily to ramp up production of its latest chips and contends with an inventory shortage.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-stock-falls-after-loss-exceeds-forecasts-FbF4fVVxIbHSiWm2Uo72?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trending tickers: Tesla, Intel, Ericsson, Ubisoft and Oracle</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-intel-ericsson-ubisoft-oracle-trending-tickers-092310095.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Friday</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-intel-ericsson-ubisoft-oracle-trending-tickers-092310095.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>