<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 02:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AV.L] How The Latest Price Target Shift Is Rewriting The Story For Aviva (LSE:AV.)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-price-target-shift-rewriting-010715321.html</link><description>Why Aviva’s latest price target shift matters now The latest change in the price target for Aviva puts fresh focus on how analysts are reassessing the story behind the stock, even without a clear, published rationale attached to the move. With no detailed commentary provided on what is driving this revision, you are left reading between the lines and weighing what it might signal about expectations for the business. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of future price target updates and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-price-target-shift-rewriting-010715321.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:07:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Podcast: Stocks Rise as Tariff Tensions Cool</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/podcast-stocks-rise-as-tariff-tensions-cool-tDi4j8GoDf8BPnjJawUX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The gains occur as investors look for more details about President Trump's desire to annex Greenland. Plus, Intel predicts further losses next quarter in an after-hours earnings report. And shares in Abbott Laboratories fall after the company misses sales expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/podcast-stocks-rise-as-tariff-tensions-cool-tDi4j8GoDf8BPnjJawUX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Returns to Losses as Supply Shortages and Spending Weigh on Q4 Results and Forecast</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/intel-intl-q4-earnings-report-2025-9271b096?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The troubled chip maker has seen its shares rise with AI demand and new investors, but revenue sagged 3.9% year-over-year to $13.7 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/intel-intl-q4-earnings-report-2025-9271b096?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/intel-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) executives used the company’s fourth-quarter 2025 earnings call to highlight progress on an internal reset, improving execution on new process technologies, and accelerating efforts to meet what management described as intense AI-driven demand that remains constrained by supply.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/intel-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures inch up as Trump Greenland drama marks latest volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-inch-up-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147076.html</link><description>Wall Street is taking a breather following a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off behaviour regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-inch-up-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147076.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures slip as Trump Greenland drama marks latest volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147947.html</link><description>Wall Street is taking a breather following a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off behaviour regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147947.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Markets Up on Decent PCE &amp; Earnings. Q4 After the Close: INTC, COF, CSX</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-decent-pce-earnings-q4-230100566.html</link><description>Year over year PCE moved back up to +2.8% after dipping 10 bps the prior month, and Intel sells off even after beating estimates in Q4.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-decent-pce-earnings-q4-230100566.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Reports Q4 Earnings: What Key Metrics Have to Say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-reports-q4-earnings-230001051.html</link><description>The headline numbers for Intel (INTC) give insight into how the company performed in the quarter ended December 2025, but it may be worthwhile to compare some of its key metrics to Wall Street estimates and the year-ago actuals.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-reports-q4-earnings-230001051.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Sinks on Weak Outlook. CFO Says Chip Supply Will Improve Later This Year.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-1c25d034?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock fell sharply on Thursday after the chip maker offered disappointing guidance for its first-quarter revenue.  The company reported adjusted earnings per share of 15 cents in the quarter versus Wall Street’s consensus estimate for 8 cents, according to FactSet.  Intel shares fell as much as 10.9% following the company’s earnings release Thursday evening.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-1c25d034?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dow Jones Futures Fall After Stocks Extend Rebound, Tesla Rallies On Self-Driving News; Intel Dives Late</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-greenland-tesla-rallies-self-driving-news-intel-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market extended its Greenland bounce, with Tesla rallying on big self-driving robotaxi news. Intel tumbled late.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-greenland-tesla-rallies-self-driving-news-intel-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel shares plunge on earnings expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-plunge-earnings-expectations-223932017.html</link><description>Intel shares dove more than 10 percent Thursday despite the struggling US chip maker doing better than expected in the recently ended quarter, as its revenue forecast disappointed investors.While the depth of losses beat market expectations, Intel's revenue forecast for the current quarter fell far short of what Wall Street analysts were predicting amid recently raised expectations for the company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-plunge-earnings-expectations-223932017.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Beats Q4 Earnings and Revenue Estimates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-beats-q4-earnings-222003648.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) delivered earnings and revenue surprises of +86.10% and +2.29%, respectively, for the quarter ended December 2025. Do the numbers hold clues to what lies ahead for the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-beats-q4-earnings-222003648.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Stock Is Crashing in After-Hours Trading</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/why-intel-stock-is-crashing-in-after-hours-trading/</link><description>Intel exceeded analysts' Q4 2025 expectations, so what's driving the after-hours sell-off?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/why-intel-stock-is-crashing-in-after-hours-trading/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Struggles to Meet Demand, CEO Says After Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-struggles-meet-demand-ceo-215440905.html</link><description>Intel Corp.&amp;amp;nbsp;gave a lackluster forecast for the current quarter because supply shortages are making it harder to meet customer demand. Chief Executive Officer Lip-Bu Tan told Bloomberg's Ed Ludlow that demand is "quite strong." Ludlow reports on "Bloomberg The Close."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-struggles-meet-demand-ceo-215440905.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple's reported moves could mean John Ternus will be next CEO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-reported-moves-could-mean-214431755.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) reportedly quietly expanded the role of the company's hardware chief John Ternus, who is seen as a top contender to succeed Apple CEO Tim Cook, according to reporting from Bloomberg. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley sits down with Market Domination host Josh Lipton to take a closer look at what the report means for the iPhone maker and investors. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-reported-moves-could-mean-214431755.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel shares slip 4% as weak guidance overshadows Q4 earnings beat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slip-4-weak-213829898.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) shares fell 4% Thursday after the chipmaker issued disappointing first-quarter guidance that overshadowed better-than-expected fourth-quarter results, as the company continues to navigate supply constraints while transitioning to new technologies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slip-4-weak-213829898.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks Settle Higher as Global Tensions Cool and the Economy Expands</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37183261/stocks-settle-higher-as-global-tensions-cool-and-the-economy-expands</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Index ($SPX ) (SPY ) on Thursday closed up +0.55%, the Dow Jones Industrials Index ($DOWI ) (DIA ) closed up +0.63%, and the Nasdaq 100 Index ($IUXX ) (QQQ ) closed up +0.76%. March E-mini S&amp;amp;P futures (ESH26 ) rose +0.52%, and March E-mini Nasdaq futures...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37183261/stocks-settle-higher-as-global-tensions-cool-and-the-economy-expands</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock drops on weak outlook: Analyst reacts to Q4 earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-drops-weak-outlook-213310075.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock is under pressure after the company's weak outlook overshadowed its fourth quarter results that beat on the top and bottom lines. TECHnalysis Research president Bob O'Donnell joins Market Domination Overtime to share his instant reaction to the legacy chipmaker's earnings print. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-drops-weak-outlook-213310075.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] US stocks rally again after Trump backs off Greenland tariff threat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</link><description>Global stocks rallied Thursday, lifting US indices for a second straight day after President Donald Trump dialed back tariff threats on Europe over their opposition to a US takeover of Greenland.But relief came Wednesday when Trump backed down on threats to seize the Arctic island by force from ally Denmark and retracted his tariff threat.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Drops On Weak First-Quarter Guidance After Q4 Beat</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/intel-stock-intc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Chipmaker Intel beat estimates for the fourth quarter but badly missed with its guidance for the current quarter. Intel stock fell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/intel-stock-intc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel: Q4 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-q4-earnings-snapshot-212044392.html</link><description>The average estimate of 16 analysts surveyed by Zacks Investment Research was for earnings of 8 cents per share. The world's largest chipmaker posted revenue of $13.67 billion in the period, which also beat Street forecasts. Fourteen analysts surveyed by Zacks expected $13.37 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-q4-earnings-snapshot-212044392.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock falls after Q1 outlook disappoints</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-falls-q1-outlook-211218296.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) reported fourth quarter adjusted earnings of $0.15 per share versus an estimate of $0.09. However, it's first quarter earnings and revenue outlook were shy of Wall Street estimates. Market Domination Overtime Anchor Josh Lipton reports the breaking details. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-falls-q1-outlook-211218296.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple further expands role of rumored CEO candidate John Ternus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-further-expands-role-rumored-200012255.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Apple Inc. has expanded hardware chief John Ternus’s responsibilities to include design work, according to a Bloomberg report Thursday, further positioning him as a potential successor to Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-further-expands-role-rumored-200012255.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Elon Musk Drops Major Cybercab, Optimus Production Update: 'Insanely Fast'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-drops-major-cybercab-190110898.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared an update regarding the upcoming Cybercab, as well as the Optimus Humanoid Robot's production timelines. Elon Musk Says Tesla Has Revamped Cybercab Production In a response to influencer Sawyer Merritt's post on the social media platform X, Musk, on Tuesday, shared that the initial production for any product "is always very slow and follows an S-curve." Merritt's post shared a video that showcased the Tesla Cybercab being produced with the "unbox</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-drops-major-cybercab-190110898.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Expands Hardware Chief’s Role in Latest Sign of CEO Candidacy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-expands-hardware-chief-role-185859457.html</link><description>Cook, who has led Apple since 2011 and turned 65 in November, quietly tapped Ternus to manage the company’s design teams at the end of last year, according to people with knowledge of the matter.  The responsibilities have special significance at Apple.  The role was held by Jony Ive, Jobs’ longtime design partner, until his departure in 2019.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-expands-hardware-chief-role-185859457.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Advanced Micro Devices’ Winning Streak Continues. How High Can the Chip Stock Go?</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/advanced-micro-devices-ai-chip-stock-7d9318d0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AMD shares are up 25% over that eight-day period and have soared more than 100% over the past year.  The iShares Semiconductor exchange-traded fund is up 51% over the past 12 months, bolstered in recent weeks by Intel’s sudden surge.  Intel is getting love for its new processors and positive comments from President Donald Trump, while AMD has, in comparison, flown under the radar to start 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/advanced-micro-devices-ai-chip-stock-7d9318d0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Wine, Water and No Chairs: Inside Trump’s Private Reception With CEOs in Davos</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/inside-trumps-private-reception-with-ceos-in-davos-543ef7d8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Apple’s Tim Cook, BlackRock’s Larry Fink and dozens more CEOs stood and waited for over an hour for a meet and greet with the president.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/inside-trumps-private-reception-with-ceos-in-davos-543ef7d8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Retains Smartphone Leadership as Its Chinese Shipments Soared Over 28% in Q4</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-retains-smartphone-leadership-chinese-180853910.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Stocks to Look For in 2026. On January 12, Reuters reported that Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) led the smartphone market with a 20% share worldwide. Apple’s iPhone 17 series had strong sales and gained demand in emerging and mid-sized markets, according to Counterpoint analyst Varun […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-retains-smartphone-leadership-chinese-180853910.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock In Focus -- Goldman Sees a Buying Opportunity Ahead of Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-focus-goldman-sees-175831784.html</link><description>Goldman Says Product Cycles Still Favor a Rebound</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-focus-goldman-sees-175831784.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today, Jan. 22: Strong U.S. GDP data, earnings lead stocks higher</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/latest-news/stock-market-today-jan-22</link><description>This live blog is refreshed periodically throughout the day with the latest updates from the market.To find the latest Stock Market Today threads, click here. Happy Thursday. This is TheStreet’s Stock Market Today for Jan. 22, 2026. You can follow the latest updates on the ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/latest-news/stock-market-today-jan-22</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Can PayPal’s Latest AI Bet Spark a Stock Revival?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/can-paypals-latest-ai-bet-spark-a-stock-revival/</link><description>PayPal (NASDAQ:PYPL) stock has declined 39% over the past year, reflecting investor worries about its competitive position as payment alternatives like Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) Pay and Stripe proliferate. The company faces pressure from fintech rivals offering seamless integrations and lower fees, eroding PayPal’s market share in digital transactions. Trading at around $57 per share, it hovers ... Can PayPal’s Latest AI Bet Spark a Stock Revival?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/can-paypals-latest-ai-bet-spark-a-stock-revival/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Michael O'Leary Promises To 'Undress' Elon Musk's Tantrum On X As Ryanair Launches Sale: Airline Wonders If Tesla CEO Needs A 'Break'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-oleary-promises-undress-elon-173119600.html</link><description>Irish airliner Ryanair Holdings PLC (NASDAQ:RYAAY) is turning its recent clashes with Elon Musk into a marketing spectacle, with the company’s CEO, Michael O'Leary, calling a press conference to discuss the billionaire entrepreneur’s “tantrum” on X. The ‘Great Idiots’ Sale On Tuesday, in a post on X, the carrier announced that its CEO will “Address/undress” Musk’s latest tantrum on the platform, in a press conference in Dublin on Wednesday morning. O’Leary also took a swipe at Musk’s understandi</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-oleary-promises-undress-elon-173119600.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Pushes Lunar New Year Discounts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-pushes-lunar-discounts-171942490.html</link><description>China promotion targets older iPhones and devices</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-pushes-lunar-discounts-171942490.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] KHC Is Low-Hanging Fruit for Greg Abel: Which Warren Buffett Stock Will He Sell Next?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37178066/khc-is-low-hanging-fruit-for-greg-abel-which-warren-buffett-stock-will-he-sell-next</link><description>KHC might not be the only mistake made by Warren Buffet that Berkshire Hathaway’s new CEO might try and rectify.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37178066/khc-is-low-hanging-fruit-for-greg-abel-which-warren-buffett-stock-will-he-sell-next</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Warren Buffett Retires: Here’s the Money Advice He’s Giving Americans for 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-retires-money-advice-164403383.html</link><description>Learn the investing and money advice Warren Buffett is sharing with Americans as he retires, including smart financial moves to prepare for 2026 and beyond.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-retires-money-advice-164403383.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Bucks Market’s Tumble as Wall Street Warms to Chipmaker</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/intel-bucks-markets-tumble-as-wall-street-warms-to-chipmaker/</link><description>Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) shares climbed more than 3% yesterday even as broader markets plunged after Japan had a weaker than expected 20-year bond market sale. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped almost 900 points, marking its worst day since October. Combined with President Trump’s threats of tariffs on eight European countries opposing U.S. attempts to acquire ... Intel Bucks Market’s Tumble as Wall Street Warms to Chipmaker</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/intel-bucks-markets-tumble-as-wall-street-warms-to-chipmaker/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The ‘Trump Effect’ Makes Intel’s Earnings Report Tonight Very Special. Why You Should Brace for a Double-Digit Move in INTC Stock.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37177799/the-trump-effect-makes-intels-earnings-report-tonight-very-special-why-you-should-brace-for-a-double-digit-move-in-intc-stock</link><description>Intel has a long way to fall back to its pre-Trump investment levels.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37177799/the-trump-effect-makes-intels-earnings-report-tonight-very-special-why-you-should-brace-for-a-double-digit-move-in-intc-stock</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 Stocks to Watch as Stock Markets Plummet Over Greenland</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/2-stocks-to-watch-as-stock-markets-plummet-over-greenland/</link><description>The situation over in Greenland caused a bit of a market shock on Tuesday, with just about everything marching lower over fears of tariffs and related uncertainties. Undoubtedly, in the heat of the panic, it really felt as though Greenland-linked tariffs on numerous European countries would derail the market rally in its tracks. With Trump ... 2 Stocks to Watch as Stock Markets Plummet Over Greenland</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/2-stocks-to-watch-as-stock-markets-plummet-over-greenland/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Mobileye Global Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/mobileye-global-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Mobileye Global (NASDAQ:MBLY) executives struck an upbeat tone on the company’s fourth-quarter and full-year 2025 earnings call, pointing to stronger-than-expected demand trends through the year, expanding engagement on next-generation ADAS programs, and what they described as rising momentum for ro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/mobileye-global-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Has Barclays (LSE:BARC) Run Too Far After A 66% One Year Share Price Gain?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Barclays shares still offer value after a strong run, this article walks through how the current price stacks up against several valuation checks. The stock has been relatively steady in the near term, with a 0.9% decline over the last 7 days and a 1.6% gain over the last 30 days. The 1 year return of 66.2% and 3 year return of 194.8% put recent moves in a much longer context for anyone thinking about risk and reward. That 1 year return of 66.2% and a 5 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock's Torrid Rally Is About to Face Its Latest Test. Here's What You Need to Know.</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/intel-stock-s-torrid-rally-is-about-to-face-its-latest-test-here-s-what-you-need-to-know-earnings-intc-11890223</link><description>Intel is slated to report fourth-quarter results after the market closes today, after a strong run for the struggling chipmaker's stock in recent weeks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/intel-stock-s-torrid-rally-is-about-to-face-its-latest-test-here-s-what-you-need-to-know-earnings-intc-11890223</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Susquehanna Lifts Semiconductor Targets as AI, Lead Times Support Earnings Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/susquehanna-lifts-semiconductor-targets-ai-155355135.html</link><description>Analysts see modest upside into 4Q and 1Q, driven by AI demand and improving semiconductor lead times.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/susquehanna-lifts-semiconductor-targets-ai-155355135.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] HSBC Just Doubled Its Price Target on Intel Stock. Should You Buy INTC Ahead of Earnings?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37176834/hsbc-just-doubled-its-price-target-on-intel-stock-should-you-buy-intc-ahead-of-earnings</link><description>Analysts sharp target hike puts Intel back in focus as AI-driven server demand builds ahead of earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37176834/hsbc-just-doubled-its-price-target-on-intel-stock-should-you-buy-intc-ahead-of-earnings</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] ChatGPT Thinks Intel Stock Will Close At This Price In The Next 60 Days</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-intel-stock-close-153120913.html</link><description>Shares of Intel have shown signs of renewed investor interest as the company's push to ramp semiconductor production and expand its AI foundry ambitions intersects with broader demand for compute and deeper strategic positioning versus rivals like Nvidia and TSMC....</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-intel-stock-close-153120913.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018945.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018945.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Chip Stocks Are Rising. Nvidia's Huang Reignites the AI Trade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-rising-nvidias-huang-152326038.html</link><description>Global Semiconductor Shares Jump as Davos Fuels AI Optimism.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-rising-nvidias-huang-152326038.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Should CrowdStrike’s Identity Security and AI Governance Push Require Action From CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-identity-security-ai-governance-150945571.html</link><description>CrowdStrike recently moved to acquire identity-security specialist SGNL for about US$740 million, advanced its Global Data Sovereignty initiative with new regional clouds in Saudi Arabia, India and the UAE, and secured ISO/IEC 42001:2023 certification for responsible AI across its Falcon platform. Taken together, these steps extend CrowdStrike’s platform beyond endpoint protection into identity, AI governance and regulated-market deployments, potentially reshaping how enterprises consolidate...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-identity-security-ai-governance-150945571.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Falls Back from 4-Year High Ahead of Earnings. What Has the Market Excited.”</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was cooling off Thursday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report but remains at multiyear highs.  Intel was down 1% at $53.77 in early trading.  Intel is expected to report adjusted earnings of eight cents a share on revenue of $13.42 billion for the fourth quarter of 2025, according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL) Reports Next Week: Wall Street Expects Earnings Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-reports-next-week-150013834.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-reports-next-week-150013834.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Launches Lunar New Year Discounts in China</title><link>https://tech.yahoo.com/ai/apple-intelligence/articles/apple-launches-lunar-discounts-china-145545066.html</link><description>Promotion aims to boost sales ahead of key holiday shopping period.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tech.yahoo.com/ai/apple-intelligence/articles/apple-launches-lunar-discounts-china-145545066.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Holdings' Quarterly Earnings Preview: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37175118/crowdstrike-holdings-quarterly-earnings-preview-what-you-need-to-know</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings is set to release its fourth-quarter results soon, and analysts predict a triple-digit surge in the company’s bottom-line figure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37175118/crowdstrike-holdings-quarterly-earnings-preview-what-you-need-to-know</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise after Trump backpedals on Greenland tariffs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-greenland-tariffs-143627517.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-greenland-tariffs-143627517.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock tumbles as company's Q1 outlook falls short of Wall Street expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-tumbles-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143443764.html</link><description>Intel reported fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-tumbles-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143443764.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel earnings set to test stock rally as Wall Street grows bullish on chipmaker’s AI position</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-earnings-set-to-test-stock-rally-as-wall-street-grows-bullish-on-chipmakers-ai-position-143443999.html</link><description>Intel is set to report fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-earnings-set-to-test-stock-rally-as-wall-street-grows-bullish-on-chipmakers-ai-position-143443999.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s Huge Surge in China</title><link>https://247wallst.com/consumer-electronics/2026/01/22/apples-huge-surge-in-china/</link><description>Apple led in smartphone market share and shipment growth in China in the fourth quarter of 2025, despite it not having an artificial intelligence product in the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/consumer-electronics/2026/01/22/apples-huge-surge-in-china/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says High Price to Earnings Multiples Are Hurting Spotify Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-high-price-141021559.html</link><description>Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about, along with market froth. Highlighting that the company faces competition from Apple and YouTube, a caller inquired if the stock is a buy, sell, or hold. In response, Cramer said: I have been watching the stock just shed points and shed points […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-high-price-141021559.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Earnings live: GE Aerospace orders surge, Procter &amp; Gamble and Abbott stocks dip</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-ge-aerospace-orders-surge-procter--gamble-and-abbott-stocks-dip-131910594.html</link><description>A broader set of sectors will be represented when 35 more S&amp;amp;P 500 companies report earnings this week, including Netflix, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-ge-aerospace-orders-surge-procter--gamble-and-abbott-stocks-dip-131910594.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] NatWest and Halifax cut mortgage costs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-halifax-bank-england-131529096.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-halifax-bank-england-131529096.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Price Target Shifts Are Rewriting The Story For NatWest Group (LSE:NWG)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-price-target-shifts-rewriting-130943619.html</link><description>Why the NatWest Group price target has changed NatWest Group has seen its price target updated, reflecting a fresh look at the bank's current position and what that might mean for investors following the story closely. This shift in expectations is rooted in recent commentary around the stock, which has prompted analysts to reassess how they frame its prospects and risks. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of these price target moves and the wider narrative as it evolves. Analyst Price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-price-target-shifts-rewriting-130943619.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Corp. (INTC) Soars to 52-Week High Ahead of Thursday Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-corp-intc-soars-52-130831414.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names Leaving Wall Street Behind; 7 Are Hitting Record Highs. Intel Corp. (NASDAQ:INTC) was one of the worst performers on Wednesday. Intel Corp. rallied to a new 52-week high on Wednesday, as investors loaded portfolios ahead of the results of its earnings performance for the full year and fourth quarter […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-corp-intc-soars-52-130831414.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Self-Driving Stock Mobileye Plunged After Earnings. Here’s Why.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/mobileye-stock-price-earnings-7046c190?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Mobileye announced fourth-quarter adjusted earnings per share of 6 cents from sales of $446 million. Wall Street was looking for 6 cents and $432 million, respectively.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/mobileye-stock-price-earnings-7046c190?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Okta’s Profits Are Up, But Its Credibility Still Hasn’t Recovered</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/oktas-profits-are-up-but-its-credibility-still-hasnt-recovered/</link><description>You want to talk about irony? Okta Inc (NASDAQ:OKTA) sells identity security to enterprises worldwide, and in 2023, hackers breached its own systems. Twice. That’s like hiring a locksmith who leaves your front door wide open. The question isn’t whether those headlines hurt the stock. They did. The question is whether they’ll haunt it forever. ... Okta’s Profits Are Up, But Its Credibility Still Hasn’t Recovered</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/oktas-profits-are-up-but-its-credibility-still-hasnt-recovered/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel price target raised to $36 from $35 at Bernstein</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-price-target-raised-36-122042694.html</link><description>Bernstein analyst Stacy Rasgon raised the firm’s price target on Intel (INTC) to $36 from $35 and keeps a Market Perform rating on the shares ahead of quarterly results. The firm is upping its server market assumptions but lowering its PC assumptions going forward.Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper decisions Stay ahead of the market with the latest news and analysis and maximize your portfolio's potential Published first o</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-price-target-raised-36-122042694.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Hidden Winner in Nvidia's AI Chip Boom Isn't Who You'd Expect</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</link><description>Nvidia is now outspending Apple at TSMC. Intel may benefit the most from the shift.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Moderna, Intel, GameStop, Micron, Venture Global, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-fd84ffe4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel shares are climbing again ahead of the chip maker’s fourth-quarter earnings, due out after the close of trading Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-fd84ffe4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] “I’d Like to be as Incompetent,” As Apple (AAPL)’s CEO, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/d-incompetent-apple-aapl-ceo-114828610.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Tech giant Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)’s shares are up by 12% over the past year. Ahead of the firm’s upcoming earnings report, Evercore and Goldman Sachs discussed the stock. The former kept an Outperform rating […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/d-incompetent-apple-aapl-ceo-114828610.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Discusses Alphabet (GOOGL) &amp; OpenAI’s Rivalry</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Over the past couple of months, Jim Cramer has turned increasingly optimistic on Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL). Several factors have driven his optimism. Early on, these included enthusiasm for YouTube and the firm’s dominance in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Jumps 11% as Chip Stocks Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</link><description>AI optimism lifts semiconductors across the board</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why Berkshire Put Its Kraft Stake on the Block</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/why-berkshire-put-its-kraft-stake-on-the-block-0861b16f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Warren Buffett’s  explanation of why the conglomerate held on to businesses that more “Darwinian” investors might have cut loose made sense—it engendered valuable goodwill.  New CEO Greg Abel might favor survival of the fittest.  Exhibit A is  Kraft Heinz  : The food giant has struggled mightily.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/why-berkshire-put-its-kraft-stake-on-the-block-0861b16f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple asks Indian court to stop antitrust body from seeking its financials</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-asks-indian-court-stop-105630793.html</link><description>NEW DELHI, Jan 22 (Reuters) - Apple has asked an Indian court to stop the country's antitrust watchdog from seeking its global financial records as part of an investigation into its app store policies</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-asks-indian-court-stop-105630793.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] US Stock Market Today S&amp;P 500 Futures Climb As Traders Await Key PCE Data</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-stock-market-today-p-101016352.html</link><description>The Morning Bull - US Market Morning Update Thursday, Jan, 22 2026 US stock futures are higher this morning, with contracts linked to the broad market up about 0.5%, as investors focus on fresh inflation clues and interest rate expectations. The key inflation gauge the Federal Reserve watches, the PCE index, is expected to rise 0.2% in November, with yearly inflation seen at 2.8%. Put simply, prices are still rising, just not rapidly. At the same time, the 10 year US government bond yield is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-stock-market-today-p-101016352.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Thursday: Intel, P&amp;G, Volkswagen</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-thursday-intel-p-g-volkswagen-AkT24v7VSScFpwtlYwxY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↗️ Intel (INTC): The chip company, in which the government has invested, is due to post earnings on Thursday afternoon. Shares were up around 1.5% in premarket trading, after surging 12% in Wednesday's regular session following an analyst upgrade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-thursday-intel-p-g-volkswagen-AkT24v7VSScFpwtlYwxY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trending tickers: AMD, Intel, Moderna, Associated British Foods and Young &amp; Co's Brewery</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AI power and infrastructure needs boomed in 2025. At Davos, the AI story for 2026 remains the same.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</link><description>The AI industry's greatest bottleneck, power, drove a boom in infrastructure throughout 2025. At Davos, leaders signal that 2026 is likely to see more of the same.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bitcoin price rises as Trump backtracks on Greenland tariff threat</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-crypto-095355676.html</link><description>Bitcoin traded higher after Donald Trump walked back his plan to impose new tariffs on European allies amid his push to acquire Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-crypto-095355676.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bitcoin price rises with stocks as Trump backtracks on tariff threat</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-095355156.html</link><description>Bitcoin traded higher after Trump walked back his plan to impose new tariffs on European allies amid his push to acquire Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-095355156.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] My Top 5 Predictions for the Magnificent Seven Stocks in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</link><description>Investors may continue to closely watch the Magnificent Seven this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Gold price to hit $5,400 this year, says Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-price-trump-greenland-oil-pound-davos-092535662.html</link><description>Gold prices stabilised after US president Donald Trump retreated from using tariffs to pressure Denmark over Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-price-trump-greenland-oil-pound-davos-092535662.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Davos, Intel Earnings, Inflation Data: Still to Come This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/davos-intel-earnings-inflation-data-still-to-come-this-week-47eXdmnsojFralFdpQmY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season kicked up a gear this week, with results still due from Intel, among other companies. Plus, the World Economic Forum continues in Davos, Switzerland, and the Federal Reserve's preferred inflation gauge is due.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/davos-intel-earnings-inflation-data-still-to-come-this-week-47eXdmnsojFralFdpQmY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] FTSE 100 LIVE: Stocks climb as Trump cancels European tariffs amid 'framework' Greenland deal</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-trump-european-tariffs-greenland-deal-090740451.html</link><description>Donald Trump cited agreement on “the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland”.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-trump-european-tariffs-greenland-deal-090740451.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Nvidia Stock Is Lagging Behind Other AI Names. Why the Boom’s Darling Is Out of Favor.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-today-ai-chips-4f4ddb9d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock is hovering near the same levels it was at last August, while other companies involved in the artificial-intelligence boom have surged.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-today-ai-chips-4f4ddb9d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Nvidia Stock -- 100% of His Portfolio Is Now Invested in 3 AI Stocks</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</link><description>Billionaire Peter Thiel has his entire portfolio invested in Tesla, Microsoft, and Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Is Bullish on UiPath, Inc. (PATH) Amid Stable IT Spending Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 15 High Growth Mid-Cap Stocks to Buy. The second stock on our list of high growth stocks is UiPath, Inc. TheFly reported on January 12 that Barclays raised its price target on PATH to $18 from $16 and maintained an Equal Weight rating. As part of its 2026 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer on Ares Capital: “I Want to Be Very Careful There”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</link><description>Ares Capital Corporation (NASDAQ:ARCC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. When a caller mentioned that their top five holdings are AAPL, ARCC, HSY, KMB, and NVDA, Cramer remarked: Wow, okay. Well, you got some yield there. You got some growth. I don’t like the Ares because I can’t really tell what […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Market’s Hottest Active ETF Has Yet to Meet Its Biggest Test</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/hottest-active-etf-biggest-test-mag-7-ea23e58b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The iShares U.S. Equity Factor Rotation Active ETF has taken huge bets on tech and communications stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/hottest-active-etf-biggest-test-mag-7-ea23e58b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Is Intel (INTC) Getting Ahead Of Itself After A 148% One Year Share Price Surge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-getting-ahead-itself-070717403.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Intel's current share price reflects a fair deal or is getting ahead of itself, you are in the right place for a clear, valuation focused look at the stock. Intel shares last closed at US$54.25, with returns of 11.4% over the past week, 49.2% over the past month, 37.8% year to date, 148.2% over the past year, 89.4% over three years, and 12.0% over five years. These moves raise questions about how much of the story is already in the price. Recent news flow around...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-getting-ahead-itself-070717403.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] The Age of AI Agents Brings a Risk No One Is Prepared For</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence companies have promised that 2026 will be the year of agents: Software that can use AI language models to autonomously execute a complex series of tasks from simple instructions.  The most prevalent use for agents today is for making software.  With enough of a budget, a single developer can orchestrate teams of agents to work on existing codebases or even to start a project from scratch.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Franklin Resources (BEN) Target Raised as Barclays Updates Asset Manager Models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</link><description>Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 15, Barclays raised its price target on Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) to $25 from $22, while still keeping an Underweight rating on the stock. The firm said the adjustment was mainly driven by updates to its asset manager […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Q4 Preview: Kimberly-Clark (KMB) Target Cut, “enthusiasm” Not Driven by Fundamentals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</link><description>Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 16, Barclays cut its price target on Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) to $102 from $132, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The move was part of the firm’s Q4 earnings preview for the consumer staples sector, where […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] CubeSmart (CUBE) Target Cut as Barclays Updates 2026 REIT Sector View</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</link><description>CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 13, Barclays analyst Brendan Lynch trimmed his price target on CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) to $43 from $45, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change came as part of Barclays’ broader 2026 outlook update for the REIT sector. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>