<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[BARC.L] Colgate-Palmolive (CL) Valuation Check After Defensive Rotation And Upgraded Analyst Views</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</link><description>Recent commentary from Barclays and Wells Fargo has pushed Colgate-Palmolive (CL) into focus, as both banks highlight growing investor interest in the stock as a defensive option while maintaining a cautious stance on fundamentals. See our latest analysis for Colgate-Palmolive. The recent analyst comments and Colgate-Palmolive’s new four year collaboration with the WHO Foundation come as the shares trade at US$85.44. The 30 day share price return is 9.04% and the year to date share price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Elon Musk Confirms AI4-Powered Cars Can Achieve Unsupervised Self-Driving Without Additional Upgrades</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has confirmed that the automaker's vehicles equipped with the AI4 (HW4) chip will be able to achieve unsupervised autonomous driving without requiring upgrades. AI4 Will Be Capable Of Self-Driving On Monday, user @iliketeslas shared a post on the social media platform X, stating that the current AI4 chips are capable of running Unsupervised FSD without "better hardware." Anyone using AI4 right now knows that better hardware is not needed for unsupervised dr</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq Climb as Trump Seeks Negotiations on Greenland</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dow-p-500-nasdaq-climb-185410493.html</link><description>Trump's Greenland Remarks Ease Tariff Fears; Stocks Surge Across Sectors</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dow-p-500-nasdaq-climb-185410493.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Is Climbing -- Foundry Customer Optimism Sparks Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-climbing-foundry-customer-185408304.html</link><description>Wall Street Turns Cautiously Optimistic on Intel as Q4 Results Loom</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-climbing-foundry-customer-185408304.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Results in Focus as Investors Bet on AI Fueled Comeback</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-focus-investors-bet-184835993.html</link><description>Shares surge ahead of earnings as CEO Lip-Bu Tan's turnaround gains traction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-focus-investors-bet-184835993.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] This Super Semiconductor Stock Crushed Nvidia in 2025, and Jan. 28 Could Be a Very Big Day for Its Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</link><description>This semiconductor equipment powerhouse could be set for another strong year in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Is Intel (INTC) Stock Rocketing Higher Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-rocketing-172536853.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) jumped 9.5% in the afternoon session after its positive momentum continued as recent analyst upgrades completely reshaped the market narrative.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-rocketing-172536853.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Big Tech earnings put spotlight on AI and memory shortage as Trump tariff threats loom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</link><description>Big Tech earnings will put a spotlight on the continued AI build-out, memory shortage, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Is Micron (MU) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</link><description>Shares of memory chips maker Micron (NYSE:MU) jumped 5.9% in the afternoon session after analysts at multiple firms, including Barclays, Stifel, and TD Cowen, raised their price targets on the stock, citing strong demand for its AI-related memory chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Fluence Energy (FLNC) Stock Is Trading Lower Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</link><description>Shares of electricity storage and software provider Fluence (NASDAQ:FLNC) fell 1.8% in the afternoon session after Goldman Sachs maintained its 'Buy' rating on the stock and raised its price target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Did Intel Stock Pop on Wednesday?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/why-did-intel-stock-pop-on-wednesday/</link><description>Should you buy Intel stock before its earnings beat?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/why-did-intel-stock-pop-on-wednesday/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Is CrowdStrike (CRWD) Fairly Priced After Recent Pullback And Cybersecurity Spotlight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether CrowdStrike Holdings is still worth the price you see on your screen, the key question is how that price lines up with what the business may realistically be worth. The stock last closed at US$442.73, after a 5.4% decline over the past week and an 8.0% decline over the past month, although the 1 year return sits at 20.8% and the 3 year return is very large. Recent attention on CrowdStrike has focused on its role as a major cybersecurity provider, as investors...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple vs HP: Who Gains as AI PCs Rise and Memory Costs Surge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-vs-hp-gains-ai-170000265.html</link><description>Apple's Mac momentum and chip innovation give AAPL an edge against HPQ as PC makers face memory shortages and rising costs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-vs-hp-gains-ai-170000265.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Could This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Be a Hidden Gem for Patient Investors?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/could-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-hidden-gem/</link><description>This tech giant lagged behind rivals in AI, but its huge user base could help it capitalize on this technology's growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/could-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-hidden-gem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Market Movers: Albemarle Exploding on Lithium Supply-Demand Story</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/market-movers-albemarle-exploding-on-lithium-supply-demand-story/</link><description>With the lithium supply-demand story heating up again, Albemarle (NYSE: ALB) is still exploding higher. In fact, since Friday, ALB ran from about $162 to $179 and could see higher highs. Helping, Deutsche Bank upgraded ALB to a buy rating with a $185 price target. Analysts at Baird also upgraded ALB to a buy with ... Market Movers: Albemarle Exploding on Lithium Supply-Demand Story</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/market-movers-albemarle-exploding-on-lithium-supply-demand-story/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trump &amp; Venezuela: New Foreign Policy, New Changes for Your 401(k)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-venezuela-foreign-policy-changes-163121840.html</link><description>Learn how shifting U.S.–Venezuela foreign policy could impact markets, energy stocks and your 401(k) plan as investors adjust to new geopolitical risks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-venezuela-foreign-policy-changes-163121840.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today: Dow Jumps On Trump Assurance; Berkshire Hathaway Eyes $7 Billion Sale (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-speech-netflix-stock-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones Industrial Average and other major stock indexes added to opening gains Wednesday in late-morning trade, as President Donald Trump told a crowd in Davos, Switzerland that he ruled out the use of military force in pursuit of Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-speech-netflix-stock-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:10:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153016698.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153016698.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Will Lower Active Accounts Impact Synchrony's Q4 Earnings Potential?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lower-active-accounts-impact-synchronys-151700709.html</link><description>SYF heads into Q4 with higher margins and purchase volumes, but declining active accounts and average interest-earning assets cloud earnings upside.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lower-active-accounts-impact-synchronys-151700709.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Rises Ahead of Earnings. Why Optimism Is Growing.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report.  Intel shares were up 5.8% at $51.35 in early trading.  Intel is expected to report adjusted earnings of eight cents a share on revenue of $13.42 billion for the fourth quarter of 2025, according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Hits a 52-Week High: Time to Buy?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/intel-hits-a-52-week-high-time-to-buy/</link><description>Motley Fool analysts look at the U.S. government's backing of the business and what it might mean for future returns.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/intel-hits-a-52-week-high-time-to-buy/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Top 5 Stocks to Avoid Despite the AI Hype</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/top-5-stocks-to-avoid-despite-the-ai-hype/</link><description>The AI gold rush has created winners and losers, but the market hasn’t fully sorted them yet. While everyone chases AI exposure, some household names are getting swept up in hype despite questionable positioning. These five stocks deserve scrutiny. 5. Salesforce (CRM): Software AI vs. Infrastructure Reality Salesforce has woven AI into its CRM platform, ... Top 5 Stocks to Avoid Despite the AI Hype</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/top-5-stocks-to-avoid-despite-the-ai-hype/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:05:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Wall Street's Wild Week</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/wall-streets-wild-week/</link><description>The biggest news was the U.S. government potentially spending $1.5 trillion on defense. Of course, there are strings attached, which investors don't like, but this could be an opportunity long-term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/wall-streets-wild-week/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks making big moves yesterday: Generac, Coinbase, Forestar Group, Nova, and Intel</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-making-big-moves-yesterday-130038848.html</link><description>Check out the companies making headlines yesterday:</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-making-big-moves-yesterday-130038848.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Earnings live: Netflix stock tumbles, Johnson &amp; Johnson falls, Halliburton and United Airlines climb</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-netflix-stock-tumbles-johnson--johnson-falls-halliburton-and-united-airlines-climb-125813797.html</link><description>A broader set of sectors will be represented when 35 more S&amp;amp;P 500 companies report earnings this week, including Netflix, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-netflix-stock-tumbles-johnson--johnson-falls-halliburton-and-united-airlines-climb-125813797.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Interest rate cut hopes fade as inflation rises in December</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/interest-rate-cut-bank-of-england-inflation-december-123420372.html</link><description>Investors are now betting that an interest rate cut will not come before April.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/interest-rate-cut-bank-of-england-inflation-december-123420372.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel results to spotlight turnaround efforts as AI data centers boost chip demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-spotlight-turnaround-efforts-123156720.html</link><description>Intel shareholders are optimistic about the company's results like they have not been for many quarters, betting the turnaround CEO Lip-Bu Tan promised was taking root and that rapid data center build outs were fueling strong demand ​for its traditional server chips.  A slew of high-profile investments engineered by Tan last year piqued investor interest in a stock that ‌had crashed in 2024 following years of management missteps, including a botched AI product roadmap that led to deep competitive losses and thousands of job cuts.  Intel's stock gained 84% in 2025, ‌far outperforming the benchmark semiconductor index's 42% rise.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-spotlight-turnaround-efforts-123156720.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The Chip Technology That Finally Gives Intel an Edge Over TSMC</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-chip-technology-that-finally-gives-intel-an-ed/</link><description>Intel was first to market with backside power delivery.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-chip-technology-that-finally-gives-intel-an-ed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Treasury Yield Spike Can’t Be Ignored. Stocks Are Vulnerable to ‘Sell America’ Pressures.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/treasury-yield-spike-stock-market-sell-america-8f0d5189?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The current turmoil in global bond markets, which has triggered a spike in U.S. Treasury yields and a record slump in Japan, could have big implications for stock markets heading into a crucial early stretch of the new year.  President Donald Trump’s vow to take over Greenland “one way or the other,” as well as his new tariff threats on European allies and the ongoing pressure on Federal Reserve independence, has stoked a new phase of the so-called Sell America trade in bond markets that spilled over violently into stocks on the first day of the holiday-shortened week.  The bond market slump Tuesday, which was accelerated by a looming fiscal crisis in Japan as the country heads toward a snap national election next month, lifted benchmark  10-year Treasury note  yields just past 4.3%, the highest since August 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/treasury-yield-spike-stock-market-sell-america-8f0d5189?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Rises Again After Upgrades. Why Wall Street Is Warming to It.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-upgrade-chips-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report.  Intel shares were up 2.4% at $49.73 in premarket trading.  As Barron’s has written, several Wall Street analysts have turned more positive on Intel stock in recent weeks, after the company unveiled new processors and comments from President Donald Trump praising CEO Lip-Bu Tan.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-upgrade-chips-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 1 Magnificent Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock to Buy in 2026 and Hold Forever (Hint: It's Not Nvidia)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-magnif/</link><description>Alphabet is beginning to emerge as Wall Street's new favorite artificial intelligence (AI) growth stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-magnif/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Netflix CEO Ted Sarandos reveals where he sees the biggest value in monster Warner Bros. deal</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-ceo-ted-sarandos-reveals-where-he-sees-the-biggest-value-in-monster-warner-bros-deal-110138834.html</link><description>Netflix is trying to pull off a whopper of a deal.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-ceo-ted-sarandos-reveals-where-he-sees-the-biggest-value-in-monster-warner-bros-deal-110138834.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Netflix, Intel, United Airlines, Kraft Heinz, GameStop, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-902f7bb1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Netflix shares tumble after the video streamer issues soft margin guidance, overshadowing a fourth-quarter earnings beat.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-902f7bb1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Amazon Investors Bet on AWS to Pull the Stock Out of Its Malaise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-investors-bet-aws-pull-103914610.html</link><description>The optimism starts with demand for the Amazon Web Services cloud-computing business, which is positioned to benefit from the explosion of artificial intelligence technology.  “An improvement in AWS should help materially in terms of the perception of the stock as being the relative loser in cloud,” said Pat Burton, a portfolio manager at Winslow Capital Management, who counts Amazon as one of his biggest overweights among the Magnificent Seven tech giants.  Amazon shares were the worst performers among the Mag Seven in 2025, their seventh straight year trailing the group.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-investors-bet-aws-pull-103914610.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) To Report Earnings Tomorrow: Here Is What To Expect</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-report-earnings-tomorrow-103648685.html</link><description>Computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) will be reporting results tomorrow afternoon. Here’s what you need to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-report-earnings-tomorrow-103648685.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Average UK rent climbs to £1,368 as house prices edge higher</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rents-december-house-prices-ons-101657181.html</link><description>Average UK house prices increased by 2.5%, to £271,000 in December, according to the ONS.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rents-december-house-prices-ons-101657181.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Netflix defends Warner Bros bid as shares drop on tepid results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-101203336.html</link><description>Jan 21 (Reuters) - "YouTube is not just user-generated content and cat videos anymore," Netflix CEO Ted Sarandos said on Tuesday.  Making a compelling case for why the streaming giant wanted Warner Bros Discovery's studio and streaming assets, Sarandos noted how tech giants such ​as Alphabet's YouTube had changed what television viewing meant and forced Netflix to change tack to keep up.  Sarandos and his co-CEO Greg Peters spent a large portion of the post-earnings call talking effusively about how strong and complementary Warner Bros' services were, a sharp change from the long-held company credo: build, don't buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-101203336.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Here's How Much Traders Expect Intel Stock to Move After Earnings This Week</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/here-is-how-much-traders-expect-intel-stock-to-move-after-earnings-this-week-intc-11886771</link><description>Intel is due to report earnings after the closing bell Thursday, with traders expecting a big swing in the chipmaker's stock following the results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/here-is-how-much-traders-expect-intel-stock-to-move-after-earnings-this-week-intc-11886771</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights Apple, Walmart, JPMorgan Chase, Park Aerospace and Motorsport Games</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-apple-093400737.html</link><description>Apple headlines Zacks' latest Analyst Blog as new research highlights earnings drivers, growth catalysts and key risks across major and microcap stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-apple-093400737.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] FTSE 100 LIVE: Stocks muted as Trump heads to Davos amid Greenland standoff</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-stocks-donald-trump-davos-greenland-090636474.html</link><description>Trump has threatened to impose tariffs on European countries who oppose him buying, or even seizing, Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-stocks-donald-trump-davos-greenland-090636474.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:06:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump at Davos, Intel Earnings, Supreme Court: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/trump-at-davos-intel-earnings-supreme-court-what-to-watch-this-week-5msZk5NpuZWckBchQvar?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season kicked up a gear this week, with results still due from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and Intel, among other companies. Plus, President Trump is at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, where he is due to speak on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/trump-at-davos-intel-earnings-supreme-court-what-to-watch-this-week-5msZk5NpuZWckBchQvar?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] UK inflation rises for first time in five months in December</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-inflation-rises-december-bank-of-england-072336744.html</link><description>Increase to 3.4% suggests Bank of England will keep interest rates on hold in February.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-inflation-rises-december-bank-of-england-072336744.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] What Berkshire’s Greg Abel Should Do With All That Cash</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-greg-abel-buffett-cash-ffcbba65?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The new CEO could enhance the company’s returns on its massive cash position with a simple options strategy: cash-secured put sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-greg-abel-buffett-cash-ffcbba65?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] US futures edge higher and gold hits another record as markets swoon over Greenland dispute</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-edge-higher-gold-045146410.html</link><description>Asian shares mostly extended their losses on Wednesday and gold prices hit a record high as concerns over U.S. President Donald Trump’s tariff threats on Greenland fueled unease among investors.  U.S. futures rose after steep losses Tuesday on Wall Street.  Gold prices crossed the $4,800 mark for the first time, gaining 1.7% as money flowed into assets considered to be safe havens at times of uncertainty.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-edge-higher-gold-045146410.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] 2 Popular AI Stocks to Sell Before They Drop 70% and 60% in 2026, According to Wall Street Analysts</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/popular-ai-stocks-sell-before-drop-analysts/</link><description>Future performance could look very different from recent performance for these two tech companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/popular-ai-stocks-sell-before-drop-analysts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Oklo Stock a Buy in 2026 After Its Nuclear Deal With Meta?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oklo-stock-a-buy-after-its-nuclear-deal-with-me/</link><description>Oklo and Meta announced a partnership to support 1.2 gigawatts of power in Ohio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oklo-stock-a-buy-after-its-nuclear-deal-with-me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Elon Musk Says He Hasn't Sold Tesla Stock For Over Three Years: 'Bought A Billion Dollars...'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-hasnt-sold-013105702.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared that he has not sold any of the EV giant's stock in the past three years. Bought A Billion Dollars Worth Of Stock Responding to a now-deleted post by influencer Mario Nawfal on the social media platform X on Sunday, the billionaire shared that he hadn't "sold stock for about 3 years." Musk also added that instead, he has invested in acquiring more Tesla shares. "bought a billion dollars of Tesla stock last year," he said in the post. I have not s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-hasnt-sold-013105702.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Stock Climbed Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/why-intel-stock-is-up-today/</link><description>Wall Street is warming up to the chipmaker's AI-driven growth strategy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/why-intel-stock-is-up-today/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Will Intel Stock Keep Soaring as Q4 Earnings Approach?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-keep-soaring-q4-010400690.html</link><description>Analyst upgrades and bullish commentary have piled up ahead of Intel's Q4 results on Thursday, January 22, pushing its stock to a two-year high of $50 a share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-keep-soaring-q4-010400690.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] What Nvidia didn’t show at CES, and whether AMD should care</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/what-nvidia-didnt-show-at-ces-and-whether-amd-should-care</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) stock is trading about 3.39% lower near $180, at the time of writing, Tuesday afternoon, Jan. 20, according to Yahoo Finance. And as if the worries about the AI bubble weren’t enough, other big tech stocks, including Apple, Meta, Microsoft, Tesla, and Google, are also down, as ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/what-nvidia-didnt-show-at-ces-and-whether-amd-should-care</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] With Gemini Powering Apple's Siri, Alphabet Could Soon Be the Undisputed AI Leader</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/with-gemini-powering-apples-siri-alphabet-could-so/</link><description>The new collaboration gives Alphabet the AI momentum it needs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/with-gemini-powering-apples-siri-alphabet-could-so/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today, Jan. 20: Intel Rises on Analyst Upgrades Highlighting AI Server CPU Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-intel-rises-on-analyst-upgrades-highlighting-ai-server-cpu-growth/</link><description>On Jan. 20, 2026, Wall Street's AI server growth upgrades put this legacy chipmaker's turnaround narrative under a brighter spotlight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-intel-rises-on-analyst-upgrades-highlighting-ai-server-cpu-growth/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Why CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Dipped More Than Broader Market Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-dipped-225504568.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) closed at $442.73 in the latest trading session, marking a -2.46% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-dipped-225504568.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Big Tech Stocks Hit Hard in Selloff</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/big-tech-stocks-hit-hard-in-selloff-AwsGv5yl8bMI2P5nHa2x?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>All seven of the giant tech stocks known as the Magnificent Seven fell at least 1% Tuesday. That was the first time that has happened since October.    Microsoft was down the least, about 1.2%, with Tesla and Nvidia down 4% or more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/big-tech-stocks-hit-hard-in-selloff-AwsGv5yl8bMI2P5nHa2x?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Top Stock Reports for Apple, Walmart &amp; JPMorgan</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-stock-reports-apple-walmart-213200157.html</link><description>Apple, Walmart and JPMorgan lead today's Zacks research, highlighting services growth, omnichannel strength and banking momentum amid risks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-stock-reports-apple-walmart-213200157.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Earnings live: Netflix stock sinks, United Airlines pops as earnings pick up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-netflix-stock-sinks-united-airlines-pops-as-earnings-pick-up-212836515.html</link><description>A broader set of sectors will be represented when 35 more S&amp;amp;P 500 companies report earnings this week, including Netflix, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-netflix-stock-sinks-united-airlines-pops-as-earnings-pick-up-212836515.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Is Already Up 19% in 2026. Can Q4 Earnings Propel It Higher in 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37135682/intel-stock-is-already-up-19-in-2026-can-q4-earnings-propel-it-higher-in-2026</link><description>Intel’s Q4 earnings could determine the stock’s next move. Here's what to watch when the company reports on Jan. 22.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37135682/intel-stock-is-already-up-19-in-2026-can-q4-earnings-propel-it-higher-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] RBC Initiates Intel (INTC) at Sector Perform, Awaits Proof on Margins and Foundry Execution</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-intel-intc-sector-205239771.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage of the stock with a “Sector Perform” rating and a price target of $50. Firm analysts see strategic progress for Intel, but are awaiting proof of execution on gross margins and […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-intel-intc-sector-205239771.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia's place in AI, Apple downgrade, JPMorgan cautious on oil</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidias-place-ai-apple-downgrade-204706772.html</link><description>Market Domination Host Josh Lipton and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma track several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including Nvidia's (NVDA) position in the AI ecosystem, Citi analysts cutting their price target on Apple (AAPL), and JPMorgan's cautious outlook on the oil industry (CL=F, BZ=F). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidias-place-ai-apple-downgrade-204706772.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Himax, Broadcom, KLA Corporation, Impinj, and Qualcomm Stocks Trade Down, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/himax-broadcom-kla-corporation-impinj-204554608.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Europe over control of Greenland sparked a broad, risk-off mood in asset markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/himax-broadcom-kla-corporation-impinj-204554608.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why Nvidia (NVDA) Stock Is Down Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-nvda-stock-down-204542603.html</link><description>Shares of leading designer of graphics chips Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) fell 3.8% in the afternoon session after rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Europe over control of Greenland sparked a broad, risk-off mood in asset markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-nvda-stock-down-204542603.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Tech Earnings Are Here. Capex, Memory Prices, and Software’s Future Will Be Key Themes.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tech-earnings-ai-capex-memory-62d98816?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Wall Street is keeping an eye on several themes this tech earnings season that stand out from the past.  A major theme impacting tech hardware companies is the rising cost of memory.  Memory demand is outpacing supply as the need for memory that powers artificial intelligence increases.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tech-earnings-ai-capex-memory-62d98816?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Stock Is Up, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-stock-know-201106689.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) jumped 2.6% in the afternoon session after Wall Street signaled belief in the turnaround narrative, as the company received a dual vote of confidence from major analyst firms just days before its fourth-quarter earnings report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-stock-know-201106689.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>