<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Osborne Partners Buys Another $4 Million Worth of MercadoLibre Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/27/osborne-partners-buys-another-usd4-million-worth-of-mercadolibre-stock/</link><description>MercadoLibre is a leading Latin American e-commerce and fintech platform, linking merchants and consumers through digital services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/27/osborne-partners-buys-another-usd4-million-worth-of-mercadolibre-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Wall Street Thinks This AI Stock Is the Next Big Thing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/wall-street-thinks-this-ai-stock-is-the-next-big-t/</link><description>While AI chip stocks continue to garner outsize attention, smart analysts are looking elsewhere for growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/wall-street-thinks-this-ai-stock-is-the-next-big-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures edge up as Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-edge-up-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353553.html</link><description>Wall Street is assessing the Federal Reserve and 'magnificent seven' earnings reports in a big week for data releases.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-edge-up-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353553.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Exceeds Market Returns: Some Facts to Consider</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-exceeds-market-224505205.html</link><description>In the latest trading session, CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) closed at $476.66, marking a +1.78% move from the previous day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-exceeds-market-224505205.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Forget Intel: The Smartest Investors Are Gaining an Edge With This Mobile‑First Chip Leader</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-intel-smart-investors-mobile-chip-leader/</link><description>A name you've certainly heard of -- but probably never really considered a threat -- is democratizing some important chip markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-intel-smart-investors-mobile-chip-leader/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Earnings live: UnitedHealth stock falls 19%, American Airlines slides, Texas Instruments pops, Logitech edges higher</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-unitedhealth-stock-falls-19-american-airlines-slides-texas-instruments-pops-logitech-edges-higher-213941564.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-unitedhealth-stock-falls-19-american-airlines-slides-texas-instruments-pops-logitech-edges-higher-213941564.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How major US stock indexes fared Tuesday, 1/27/2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/major-us-stock-indexes-fared-212650648.html</link><description>Wall Street ticked to a record as stocks zigzagged underneath the market's surface following mixed profit reports from UnitedHealth, General Motors and other big companies. The S&amp;amp;P 500 rose 0.4% Tuesday, even though more stocks fell within the index than rose. It squeaked past its prior all-time high set a couple weeks ago.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/major-us-stock-indexes-fared-212650648.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip sector shifts: Nvidia to beat Apple as TSMC's top customer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/chip-sector-shifts-nvidia-to-beat-apple-as-tsmcs-top-customer-212618311.html</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) is set to surpass Apple (AAPL) as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company's (TSM) top 2026 customer.Creative Strategies CEO and principal analyst Ben Bajarin joins Market Domination host Josh Lipton to explain how the chip sector is evolving.To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/chip-sector-shifts-nvidia-to-beat-apple-as-tsmcs-top-customer-212618311.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Here's Why I Wouldn't Touch Intel Stock With a 10-Foot Pole</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/heres-why-i-wouldnt-touch-intel-stock-with-a-10-fo/</link><description>There are key questions that have yet to be answered for its valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/heres-why-i-wouldnt-touch-intel-stock-with-a-10-fo/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Being a White House VIP Thrusts Tim Cook into the Political Fray</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/being-a-white-house-vip-thrusts-tim-cook-into-the-political-fray-0bae0988?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The risk of  Tim Cook’s  strategy for navigating Washington came into clear focus Saturday night.  As the world’s attention turned to Minneapolis following the death of Alex Pretti, a nurse, at the hands of federal immigration agents, the  Apple  chief executive was at the White House feting President Trump and the first lady.  The juxtaposition couldn’t be starker: videos showing protests in the streets versus a photo of a smiling Cook in a tuxedo with  Brett Ratner,  the director of a coming documentary about Melania.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/being-a-white-house-vip-thrusts-tim-cook-into-the-political-fray-0bae0988?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500 hits fresh record with Fed decision, Big Tech earnings bonanza on deck</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-hits-fresh-record-with-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-bonanza-on-deck-210311432.html</link><description>Tech stocks are a bright spot as tariffs, healthcare names, and political insecurity weigh on investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-hits-fresh-record-with-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-bonanza-on-deck-210311432.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Tech earnings: AI spending moderation could prove detrimental</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-earnings-ai-spending-moderation-could-prove-detrimental-205430937.html</link><description>Earnings season is off to another busy week as Magnificent Seven companies prepare to release quarterly earnings results: Microsoft (MSFT), Meta Platforms (META), and Tesla (TSLA) coming out on Wednesday, and Apple (AAPL) on Thursday.The S&amp;amp;P 500 (^GSPC) inches closer to a record milestone of 7,000 amid investor anticipation.Washington Crossing Advisors Senior Portfolio Manager Chad Morganlander comes on Market Domination to talk more about the ROIC figures (Return on Invested Capital) that he expects to see from the AI hyperscalers this week.To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-earnings-ai-spending-moderation-could-prove-detrimental-205430937.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Siri settlement payments hitting bank accounts. What to know.</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2026/01/27/apple-siri-settlement-payout/88377845007/</link><description>Claimants are beginning to receive payouts for the settled Lopez v. Apple class-action lawsuit. Here's how to check if you received a payment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2026/01/27/apple-siri-settlement-payout/88377845007/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Jim Cramer Makes Contrarian Intel Call After Stock Plunges</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/jim-cramer-makes-contrarian-intel-call-after-stock-plunges/</link><description>People use many different words to describe Mad Money host Jim Cramer. Could he be characterized as a contrarian, though? The answer is yes as Cramer just made a surprisingly bullish call on shares of chip giant Intel (NASDAQ:INTC). Under the leadership of CEO Lip-Bu Tan, Intel seemingly flipped from black sheep to comeback kid ... Jim Cramer Makes Contrarian Intel Call After Stock Plunges</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/jim-cramer-makes-contrarian-intel-call-after-stock-plunges/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Weather is Freezing but Stocks Are Hot. It’s the January Effect.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-rally-2026-january-effect-9dfeeb82?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>With the U.S. digging out from Winter Storm Fern, and counting the cost of an arctic blast that could bring record cold readings as far south as the Florida Keys, investors are also taking the temperature of perhaps the most important stretch of the year for the stock market.  Labeled the “January Barometer” by famed academic Yale Hirsch, creator of the Stock Trader’s Almanac, the idea of extrapolating first- month returns over the calendar year has proven to be a winner.  Adam Turnquist, chief technical strategist at  LPL Financial  notes data showing that since 1950, the  has generated an average return of nearly 17% in years when the benchmark ends January in positive territory.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-rally-2026-january-effect-9dfeeb82?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] This Specialty Glassmaker’s Stock Is Soaring on an AI Data Center Deal With Meta</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/this-specialty-glassmaker-stock-is-soaring-on-an-ai-data-center-deal-with-meta-glw-11893239</link><description>Corning shares surged Tuesday, thanks to a $6 billion deal with Meta Platforms, in the latest piece of good news for the glass and fiber optic cable maker.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/this-specialty-glassmaker-stock-is-soaring-on-an-ai-data-center-deal-with-meta-glw-11893239</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Market Movers: Affirm Upgraded to a Buy Rating</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/market-movers-affirm-upgraded-to-a-buy-rating/</link><description>Shares of buy now, pay later stock Affirm (NASDAQ: AFRM) are gaining attention. All after analysts at Needham upgraded the stock to a buy with a $100 price target. The firm added that, “AFRM has submitted an application to establish Affirm Bank, a proposed Nevada-chartered industrial loan company,” as quoted by CNBC. We have to ... Market Movers: Affirm Upgraded to a Buy Rating</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/market-movers-affirm-upgraded-to-a-buy-rating/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bernstein Reiterates Outperform on ASML Ahead of Key Q4 Bookings Print</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-reiterates-outperform-asml-ahead-180028917.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Bernstein SocGen Group analyst David Dai reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $1,642.00 price target. The firm anticipates a robust Q4 beat, with revenue and booking strength viewed as key upside drivers. With ASML […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-reiterates-outperform-asml-ahead-180028917.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Jim Cramer Loves Intel (INTC) CEO Lip-Bu Tan</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-loves-intel-intc-174852565.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Stocks Jim Cramer Commented On. Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer commanded on. Chip manufacturing giant Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC)’s shares are among the top performers in the market. They are up by 122% over the past year and by 14% year-to-date. In January, Seaport Global Securities upgraded […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-loves-intel-intc-174852565.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Buy, Sell or Hold the Apple Stock? Key Tips Ahead of Q1 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-sell-hold-apple-stock-174500928.html</link><description>AAPL eyes 10-12% sales growth in fiscal Q1, powered by strong iPhone demand and expanding Services momentum.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-sell-hold-apple-stock-174500928.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Do Wall Street Analysts Like Apple Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37254972/do-wall-street-analysts-like-apple-stock</link><description>Apple stock has lagged behind the broader market over the past year, while analysts are moderately bullish about its prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37254972/do-wall-street-analysts-like-apple-stock</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jefferies Flags App Store and Google Ad Risks for Apple (AAPL)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-flags-app-store-google-172321219.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Jefferies analyst Edison Lee lowered the price target on the stock to $276.47 (from $283.36) while maintaining a Hold rating. The firm believes AAPL’s long-term growth is capped due to slowing App Store growth and Google ad revenue […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-flags-app-store-google-172321219.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Jumps After Investors Target AI Growth 'Buy-the-Dip' Entry</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-jumps-investors-target-165748527.html</link><description>Intel Shares Rally With Wall Street Eyeing 2026 Growth and Chip Demand</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-jumps-investors-target-165748527.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Will social media bans weigh on App Store revenue? Analyst sees limited impact</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/social-media-bans-weigh-app-164658862.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Restrictions preventing children under 16 from accessing major social media platforms in Australia, and a similar proposal now under consideration in the U.K., have prompted some to question whether Apple’s App Store and Google’s Play Store could face pressure on in-app purchase revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/social-media-bans-weigh-app-164658862.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia and Apple Stocks In Spotlight -- Pelosi Files New Disclosure</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/nvidia-apple-stocks-spotlight-pelosi-164201442.html</link><description>Pelosi Adds Tech Exposure With New Options in Alphabet and Amazon</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/nvidia-apple-stocks-spotlight-pelosi-164201442.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] ASML Stock Is Gaining Ahead of Earnings. It’s a Test for a Chip Sector Darling.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-earnings-stock-price-7f26b1a7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>ASML stock has more than doubled in the past year. Investors will be watching orders and High-NA adoption when it reports earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-earnings-stock-price-7f26b1a7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Nvidia stock is on sale</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-stock-is-on-sale-161506921.html</link><description>Time to nibble at Nvidia?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-stock-is-on-sale-161506921.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Viral AI Bot That Sent Cloudflare Stock to the Moon</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/cloudflare-stock-price-ai-bot-moltbot-fdb3e77b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The emergence of Moltbot, previously known as Clawdbot, affirms Cloudflare’s positioning as a cloud-network and security solution for the AI age.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/cloudflare-stock-price-ai-bot-moltbot-fdb3e77b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Corning Stock Jumps on Deal With Meta. Glass Maker Is an AI Darling.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/corning-stock-meta-glass-deal-ai-59b30615?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The manufacturer will supply the social-media company with cabling, optical fiber, and connectivity solutions for data centers across the U.S..</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/corning-stock-meta-glass-deal-ai-59b30615?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Should You Buy Apple Stock Before Jan. 29?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/should-you-buy-apple-stock-before-jan-29/</link><description>The tech giant may have some positive updates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/should-you-buy-apple-stock-before-jan-29/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017437.html</link><description>Nu Holdings Ltd. 6,960,728 18.38</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017437.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Analysts Expect Applied Materials Stock to Dominate in 2026. Should You Buy Shares Now?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37252145/analysts-expect-applied-materials-stock-to-dominate-in-2026-should-you-buy-shares-now</link><description>Applied Materials' stock offers upside potential, according to this investment firm.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37252145/analysts-expect-applied-materials-stock-to-dominate-in-2026-should-you-buy-shares-now</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Corning Stock Breaks Out After Striking Fiber-Optic Cable Deal With Meta Platforms</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/corning-stock-meta-stock-fiber-optics/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Corning stock jumped while Meta stock was slightly lower after the companies announced a $6 billion fiber-optic deal.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/corning-stock-meta-stock-fiber-optics/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is It Too Late To Invest In Google Stock? Here’s Why Some Experts Think It Can Still Rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-invest-google-stock-why-151707335.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) hit a $4 trillion market cap as AI fuels growth. Experts weigh the upside, risks and whether Google stock is still a smart buy for 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-invest-google-stock-why-151707335.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Here’s Why 1 Analyst Just Hiked This Monopoly’s Target to $1,642 Ahead of Earnings</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/heres-why-1-analyst-just-hiked-this-monopolys-target-to-1642-ahead-of-earnings/</link><description>ASML (NASDAQ:ASML) dominates the semiconductor equipment market with its extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography technology, essential for producing the world’s most advanced chips. No competitors can match its precision in etching circuits at nanoscale levels, creating a monopoly on tools that power the AI surge. Chipmakers like Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (NYSE:TSM), Intel (NASDAQ:INTC), and Samsung rely ... Here’s Why 1 Analyst Just Hiked This Monopoly’s Target to $1,642 Ahead of Earning</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/heres-why-1-analyst-just-hiked-this-monopolys-target-to-1642-ahead-of-earnings/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] What Intel Just Accomplished with Panther Lake Seemed Impossible 2 Years Ago</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/what-intel-just-accomplished-with-panther-lake-see/</link><description>Panther Lake is the company's best PC CPU in years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/what-intel-just-accomplished-with-panther-lake-see/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls Ahead Of Fed Meet; UnitedHealth Plunges On Medicare News (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/fed-meeting-unitedhealth-unh-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stock Market Today: The Dow Jones index fell Tuesday ahead of the Fed's policy meeting. UnitedHealth stock plunged on Medicare news.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/fed-meeting-unitedhealth-unh-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Cloudflare Stock Keeps On Surging. A Viral AI Bot Has Investors Excited.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/cloudflare-stock-moltbot-viral-ai-bot-fdb3e77b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The emergence of Moltbot, previously known as Clawdbot, affirms Cloudflare’s positioning as a cloud-network and security solution for the AI age.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/cloudflare-stock-moltbot-viral-ai-bot-fdb3e77b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] More Than 100 Blue-Chips Are Reporting Earnings This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-27-2026/card/more-than-100-blue-chips-are-reporting-earnings-this-week-gQrMcvTy3G4s3SpHmBKp?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full swing, with 102 companies in the benchmark S&amp;amp;P 500 index reporting earnings this week, according to LSEG. Tuesday's highlights includes airlines, health insurers and transportation specialists:   UnitedHealth booked charges related to a restructuring and a major cyberattack, and warned annual sales could fall.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-27-2026/card/more-than-100-blue-chips-are-reporting-earnings-this-week-gQrMcvTy3G4s3SpHmBKp?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Do Wall Street Analysts Like Intel Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37247778/do-wall-street-analysts-like-intel-stock</link><description>Intel has significantly outperformed the broader market over the past year, but analysts are cautious about the stock’s prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37247778/do-wall-street-analysts-like-intel-stock</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple and Google removing dozens of "nudity" apps in Grok-related fallout</title><link>https://tech.yahoo.com/ai/apple-intelligence/articles/apple-google-removing-dozens-nudity-131701303.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Apple has removed 28 "nudify" apps from its App Store after a report from the Tech Transparency Project (TTP) revealed dozens of applications that use AI to generate nude images of people from their photos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tech.yahoo.com/ai/apple-intelligence/articles/apple-google-removing-dozens-nudity-131701303.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Major UK banks expected to lift profitability targets – report</title><link>https://www.retailbankerinternational.com/news/uk-banks-lift-profitability-targets/</link><description>HSBC is expected to raise its ROTE guidance, while NatWest is considering a revision of its 2027 ROTE target from 15% up to 17%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.retailbankerinternational.com/news/uk-banks-lift-profitability-targets/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir and 5 More Stocks That Might Catch Trump’s Attention—in a Good Way</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/palantir-stock-price-trump-buy-apple-ionq-98f5e987?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>There is a change in the way the federal government operates that investors need to incorporate into their thinking.  If they do it right, they can get some gains by holding stocks that President Donald Trump might covet.  The White House often points out that Trump is a businessman and his second administration has demonstrated a willingness to do business directly with American companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/palantir-stock-price-trump-buy-apple-ionq-98f5e987?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel's 18A: The Angstrom Advantage and the Valuation Divide</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intels-18a-angstrom-advantage-valuation-125132662.html</link><description>Process Leadership (18A) is the Only Variable that Matters for Massive Upside</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intels-18a-angstrom-advantage-valuation-125132662.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Bank of Scotland penalised for breaching Russian sanctions law</title><link>https://www.retailbankerinternational.com/news/bank-of-scotland-penalised/</link><description>The breach stemmed from an incident in which the sanctioned person opened a personal account using a British passport.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.retailbankerinternational.com/news/bank-of-scotland-penalised/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks and Gold Near Record Highs? Maybe It’s About Trust and Verify.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-gold-record-highs-98a6fc36?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>“Trust but verify,” a Russian proverb famously used by President Ronald Reagan during nuclear disarmament negotiations with the former Soviet Union, feels like an apt description of global investor sentiment toward U.S. markets.  Stocks are poised to test new all-time highs again this week amid a parade of corporate earnings updates likely to consolidate forecasts of double-digit profit growth again this year, and a Federal Reserve interest rate decision that is likely to clear the way for further borrowing cost reductions over the next 12 months.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-gold-record-highs-98a6fc36?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] What S&amp;P Earnings Would Be Without The Magnificent Seven</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/magnificent-seven-sp-500-q4-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>As a group, the Magnificent Seven are expected to report earnings growth of 20.3% for the fourth quarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/magnificent-seven-sp-500-q4-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple's AI progress raises 'key' questions ahead of Q1 earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-ai-progress-raises-key-questions-ahead-of-q1-earnings-120000901.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) reports first quarter earnings results this Thursday, Jan. 29 after markets close.KeyBanc Capital Markets equity research analyst Brandon Nispel joins Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman to discuss the upcoming earnings print as it relates to the company's broader journey in artificial intelligence (AI) expansion.To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-ai-progress-raises-key-questions-ahead-of-q1-earnings-120000901.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks gain tracking tech, Fed and trade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asian-stocks-track-wall-st-031147315.html</link><description>Stock markets gained Tuesday as investors geared up for the US Federal Reserve's policy meeting and earnings from tech titans, which will be pored over for signs of AI momentum.Investors attention was also on the Federal Reserve's policy meeting starting Tuesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asian-stocks-track-wall-st-031147315.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] AI Stocks Still Face a China Risk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/ai-stocks-still-face-a-china-risk-73444a9f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>What knocked trillions off of the value of the U.S. market was news that a Chinese AI company, DeepSeek, had nearly matched U.S. competitors that were spending fortunes on chips and electricity.  As Heard on the Street columnist Dan Gallagher explained at the time, the reaction was excessive and DeepSeek’s claims seemed exaggerated.  JPMorgan Asset Management says in a report that 42 AI-related companies have been responsible for between 65% and 75% of the S&amp;amp;P 500’s gains, earnings and capital spending since ChatGPT was launched in November 2022.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/ai-stocks-still-face-a-china-risk-73444a9f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Tesla’s Price Target Is Rising Even as Its Profit Outlook Tanks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-price-target-rising-even-112716958.html</link><description>“Tesla is truly unique in capital markets,” said Nicholas Colas, co-founder at DataTrek Research.  Over the past 12 months, the average forecast for Tesla’s 2026 net income has tumbled 56% from $14.1 billion to $6.1 billion.  The stock is up 7% in that time after closing Tuesday at $435.20, well above Wall Street’s expectations for a year from now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-price-target-rising-even-112716958.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Tech, Media &amp; Telecom Roundup: Market Talk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/tech-media-telecom-roundup-market-talk-cdfd7e8d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Find insight on Kunlunxin’s coming IPO and more in the latest Market Talks covering technology, media and telecom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/tech-media-telecom-roundup-market-talk-cdfd7e8d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trending tickers: Apple, CoreWeave, ASML, Salesforce and Dr Martens</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-coreweave-asml-salesforce-dr-martens-trending-tickers-092822884.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Tuesday</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-coreweave-asml-salesforce-dr-martens-trending-tickers-092822884.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bitcoin Rises on Optimism Over Upcoming Big Tech Earnings</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-012726/card/bitcoin-rises-on-optimism-over-upcoming-big-tech-earnings-Sm4CsgOSYdRtRrtz3fdX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Bitcoin was edging higher following gains in U.S. stocks overnight on optimism over upcoming U.S. megacap tech earnings. Investors are positioning ahead of results from Microsoft, Apple, Meta and Tesla this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-012726/card/bitcoin-rises-on-optimism-over-upcoming-big-tech-earnings-Sm4CsgOSYdRtRrtz3fdX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Aletheia Maintains Sell on Apple (AAPL), Lowers Target Price</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aletheia-maintains-sell-apple-aapl-084000844.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching. On January 20, Aletheia Capital analyst Warren Lau lowered the price target on the stock to $205.00 (from $215.00) while maintaining a Sell rating. According to the firm, Apple’s hardware margins have peaked and face pressure until the company raises prices or pushes […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aletheia-maintains-sell-apple-aapl-084000844.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Meta Earnings, Fed Decision, Venezuela Testimony: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-27-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-what-to-watch-this-week-1vkOxKCMFzg0W0BYLXMe?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full throttle, with results expected from big-name companies including UnitedHealth, Chevron and Boeing. A quartet of tech giants—Apple, Meta Platforms, Microsoft and Tesla—will also report results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-27-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-what-to-watch-this-week-1vkOxKCMFzg0W0BYLXMe?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Forget SoundHound AI: This Tech King Is the Real Voice-and-AI Cash Cow Worth Betting On</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-soundhound-ai-this-tech-king-is-the-real-vo/</link><description>Apple offers a relatively low-risk, potentially high-reward investment proposition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-soundhound-ai-this-tech-king-is-the-real-vo/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] If You Invested $1,000 in Apple vs. Bitcoin in 2015, Here’s Which One Made You Richer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invested-1-000-apple-vs-070005240.html</link><description>Here's how a $1,000 investment in Apple stock in 2015 compares to Bitcoin and which one would have made you richer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invested-1-000-apple-vs-070005240.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Texas Instruments Reports Earnings Today. China Is a Wildcard.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/texas-instruments-earnings-stock-price-28cd11e2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The chip maker reports after the close. Analysts expect modest revenue and earnings declines and are watching China demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/texas-instruments-earnings-stock-price-28cd11e2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Sees Defensive Appeal in PepsiCo (PEP) but Flags 2026 Risks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-sees-defensive-appeal-pepsico-065916369.html</link><description>PepsiCo, Inc. (NASDAQ:PEP) is included among the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Dividend Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 16, Barclays raised PepsiCo, Inc. (NASDAQ:PEP) price target to $148 from $144 and kept an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The firm updated price targets across the consumer staples group as part of its Q4 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-sees-defensive-appeal-pepsico-065916369.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Zacks Analyst Blog Microsoft, Apple, Meta and Tesla</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-microsoft-apple-064900957.html</link><description>MSFT headlines a pivotal week as Mag 7 Q4 earnings begin alongside the first Fed meeting of 2026, with investors eyeing guidance amid AI spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-microsoft-apple-064900957.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] ASML rides Nvidia's coattails with lasers and huge chip 'printers'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145690.html</link><description>By Toby Sterling and Nathan Vifflin AMSTERDAM, Jan 27 (Reuters) - As artificial intelligence firms jostle for the Nvidia chips needed to power the AI boom, Dutch firm ASML has carved out a key niche</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145690.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] ASML rides Nvidia's coattails with lasers and huge chip 'printers'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145161.html</link><description>As artificial intelligence firms jostle for the Nvidia chips needed to power the AI boom, Dutch firm ASML has carved out a key niche in the supply chain: building the laser-using machines needed ​to print them.  ASML, which counts Taiwan's TSMC and Intel amongst its clients, makes the huge precision machines needed to print the minuscule ‌circuitry onto silicon chips, dominating the market for the high-end microprocessors needed for AI.  The Veldhoven, Netherlands-based company has seen its shares double in value since last April and rise 25% ‌this month alone amid signs that its chipmaker clients are ramping up investment as a supply crunch pushes up chip prices.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145161.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Pros and cons of downsizing when you retire</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/downsizing-house-retirement-explained-060053321.html</link><description>Downsizing your home may seem like a neat solution to your retirement challenges, but for many, the dream does not match up to reality.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/downsizing-house-retirement-explained-060053321.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir and 5 More Stocks to Play Trump’s Plan to Invest in America</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-investments-government-palantir-apple-98f5e987?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>There is a change in the way the federal government operates that investors need to incorporate into their thinking.  If they do it right, they can get some gains by holding stocks that President Donald Trump might covet.  The White House often points out that Trump is a businessman and his second administration has demonstrated a willingness to do business directly with American companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-investments-government-palantir-apple-98f5e987?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Shop price inflation 'defies expectations' to jump to 1.5% in January</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/shop-price-inflation-january-060000700.html</link><description>Shop price inflation in Britain jumped to 1.5% in January, as retailers passed on higher energy and national insurance (NI) costs to consumers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/shop-price-inflation-january-060000700.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Morgan Stanley resets Apple stock forecast ahead of earnings</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/morgan-stanley-resets-apple-stock-forecast-ahead-of-earnings</link><description>Wall Street is resetting expectations for Apple ahead of the company’s first-quarter earnings report, due Thursday, Jan 29, 2026, at 5 pm ET. Weighing resilient iPhone demand against cost pressures, increasing competition, and slightly slow growth in the services industry, analysts are ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/morgan-stanley-resets-apple-stock-forecast-ahead-of-earnings</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Expects Western Digital’s Quarter to Be “Very Positive”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-expects-western-digital-023433366.html</link><description>Western Digital Corporation (NASDAQ:WDC) is one of the stocks in focus as Jim Cramer shared his weekly game plan. Cramer mentioned the stock during his game plan, as he commented: Sandisk and Western Digital report at the same time. These are our storage plays. They’ll be very positive. I don’t think they’ll get the same […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-expects-western-digital-023433366.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says Sandisk Is “Up Huge, Way Too Much for Me”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-sandisk-huge-023323220.html</link><description>Sandisk Corporation (NASDAQ:SNDK) is one of the stocks in focus as Jim Cramer shared his weekly game plan. Cramer noted that the stock has run up significantly, as he said: Sandisk and Western Digital report at the same time. These are our storage plays. They’ll be very positive. I don’t think they’ll get the same […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-sandisk-huge-023323220.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says “I’m Not Changing My View, I Say, Own Apple, Don’t Trade It”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-m-not-023322336.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks in focus as Jim Cramer shared his weekly game plan. Cramer highlighted why the stock has been down for the past few weeks, as he stated: Apple’s stock’s been down for eight straight weeks. Quite a dry spell. Why is that? I think it’s the other side […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-m-not-023322336.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks up as earnings hopes offset Trump's Korea tariff move, dollar wobbles</title><link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-earnings-hopes-offset-trumps-020410372.html</link><description>By Stella Qiu SYDNEY, Jan 27 (Reuters) - Asian shares advanced on Tuesday as investors hoped for the best from a barrage of U.S. mega-cap earnings, though uncertainty caused by President Donald</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-earnings-hopes-offset-trumps-020410372.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>