<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Billionaire Peter Thiel Made a Big Bet on Two Stocks for 2026 (Hint: It's Not Nvidia)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/billionaire-peter-thiel-made-a-big-bet-on-two-stoc/</link><description>Thiel has sold his hedge fund's entire stake in Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/billionaire-peter-thiel-made-a-big-bet-on-two-stoc/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AI &amp; Business Newsletter | Hey Google. Make Siri Work Better</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/ai-business-newsletter-hey-google-make-siri-work-better-NQGAOAKKf4KJPjcyQZ5f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Google and Apple have long been among the more awkward relationships in tech.  The two companies announced a deal Monday that will effectively have Google’s Gemini acting as a foundation for Apple’s AI offerings, including “a more personalized Siri coming this year.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/ai-business-newsletter-hey-google-make-siri-work-better-NQGAOAKKf4KJPjcyQZ5f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nasdaq Turns Lower Amid Mag 7 Struggles</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011326/card/nasdaq-turns-lower-amid-mag-7-struggles-4vGq9hGLL286U56OCRYa?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>So much for the Nasdaq Composite’s turnaround. The tech-heavy index was back down 0.2% on Tuesday after briefly turning positive. The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.3%. The Dow sank 337 points, or 0.7%. Salesforce, down 6.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011326/card/nasdaq-turns-lower-amid-mag-7-struggles-4vGq9hGLL286U56OCRYa?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trump's credit card cap could make most of industry 'unprofitable'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trumps-credit-card-cap-could-183000666.html</link><description>JPMorgan Chase (JPM) reached a deal earlier this month to take over Goldman Sachs' (GS) Apple Card (AAPL) account; the costs related to this transfer weighed on the former's earnings figures for the fourth quarter. Additionally, President Trump suggested a 10% cap on credit card fees earlier this week. HSBC Head of US Financials Research Saul Martinez reacts to headlines of the Apple Card impacts and what Trump's policy proposal could mean for the financial sector and credit lenders. Also watch Saul Martinez discuss JPMorgan's latest earnings release. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trumps-credit-card-cap-could-183000666.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple's Services Business Was a Major Catalyst Last Year, and 2026 Will Likely Be Even Better</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/apples-services-business-was-a-major-catalyst-last/</link><description>Apple's services segment is becoming a bigger part of the story, and the company's latest updates suggest that momentum is carrying into fiscal 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/apples-services-business-was-a-major-catalyst-last/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 Growth Stocks With Big Catalysts in 2026</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/2-growth-stocks-with-big-catalysts-in-2026/</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 has been so incredibly resilient in 2026. It’s been less than two weeks since we rang in the new year, but the broad market has already been rocked with a number of macro events, which I would have thought would pave the way for greater volatility and perhaps downside to kick off ... 2 Growth Stocks With Big Catalysts in 2026</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/2-growth-stocks-with-big-catalysts-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google joins a rare valuation milestone club on Wall Street</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/markets/google-joins-a-rare-valuation-milestone-club-on-wall-street</link><description>Alphabet just joined one of the rarest clubs in markets, companies worth roughly $4 trillion or more, according to Reuters and real-time quote data. The company’s class A shares pushed its market value to around $4 trillion in intraday trading on Monday, Jan. 12, as the stock traded near a record ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/markets/google-joins-a-rare-valuation-milestone-club-on-wall-street</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] JPMorgan Chase reports mixed results as Dimon defends Fed chief</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-chase-reports-mixed-results-180643305.html</link><description>JPMorgan Chase reported lower fourth-quarter profits Tuesday as CEO Jamie Dimon endorsed Federal Reserve independence and offered an upbeat reading on the US economy.Dimon, who has struck a cautious tone in some recent quarters, characterized the United States outlook as "pretty positive," while also offering a strong defense of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, who is under investigation by President Donald Trump's Justice Department.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-chase-reports-mixed-results-180643305.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:06:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Spotify Is Fighting Listener Fatigue. AI Is Central to the Plan</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-fighting-listener-fatigue-ai-174617931.html</link><description>Spotify Turns to AI and Video as User Boredom Grows</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-fighting-listener-fatigue-ai-174617931.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Microsoft and Apple Could Join the $4 Trillion Club in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-apple-could-join-4-173405211.html</link><description>Tech Titans Eye $4 Trillion Market Value Amid Enterprise AI Boom</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-apple-could-join-4-173405211.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Partners With Google's Gemini to Power AI Version of Siri</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-partners-googles-gemini-power-171808845.html</link><description>Deal marks Apple's biggest step yet into the fast-moving artificial intelligence race.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-partners-googles-gemini-power-171808845.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia is a 'very boring idea' and could lose its market cap crown, says market veteran</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-is-a-very-boring-idea-and-could-lose-its-market-cap-crown-says-market-veteran-170753022.html</link><description>A "nasty" 15% sell-off could hit crowded trades this spring, says Tom Sosnoff.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-is-a-very-boring-idea-and-could-lose-its-market-cap-crown-says-market-veteran-170753022.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Jumps on the Subscription Software Bandwagon. Why Adobe Stock Is Dropping.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-price-new-software-adobe-71424855?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Starting Wednesday, users will be able to subscribe to the offering, dubbed  Apple  Creator Studio, for $12.99 a month or $129 a year, Apple said.  This subscription for Apple includes access to video, audio, and photo editing programs such as Final Cut Pro, Logic Pro, and Pixelmator Pro for a lower monthly payment than what each software previously cost individually.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-price-new-software-adobe-71424855?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stocks Surges. It’s Shaping Up to Be a Good Year for Chip Makers.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-upgrade-amd-chips-e1993901?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining Tuesday after getting upgraded at KeyBanc.  It’s set to be a good year for makers of central processing units, including  Advanced Micro Devices  the analysts say.  Analyst John Vinh raised his rating on both Intel and AMD to Overweight, noting the companies appear to have largely sold out their server CPUs for this year amid the boom in artificial-intelligence infrastructure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-upgrade-amd-chips-e1993901?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Predicted Apple (AAPL)’s Gemini Deal</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-predicted-apple-aapl-163640302.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of Cramer’s favorite stocks. The CNBC TV host spent most of 2025 defending the firm against its detractors as the shares struggled due to multiple news cycles, such as weak […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-predicted-apple-aapl-163640302.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel (INTC) CEO is Doing An Amazing Job, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-ceo-doing-amazing-163552285.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Chip manufacturing giant Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC)’s shares are up by 137% over the past year. In 2026, the stock is up by 19.9% year-to-date. A key catalyst for the stock came in January after the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-ceo-doing-amazing-163552285.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel stock rises on analyst upgrade citing data center AI demand, 'significant progress' in manufacturing</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-rises-on-analyst-upgrade-citing-data-center-ai-demand-significant-progress-in-manufacturing-163050036.html</link><description>KeyBanc analyst John Vinh upgraded Intel to Overweight from Sector Weight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-rises-on-analyst-upgrade-citing-data-center-ai-demand-significant-progress-in-manufacturing-163050036.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] JPMorgan's guidance seemed especially 'conservative.' Here's why.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jpmorgans-guidance-seemed-especially-conservative-161943036.html</link><description>JPMorgan Chase stock (JPM) is under some pressure in Tuesday's trading session after the major bank's earnings fell below fourth quarter estimates when accounting for the costs related to the Apple Card (AAPL) deal. HSBC Head of US Financials Research Saul Martinez discusses JPMorgan's earnings release and how it factors into his broader outlook for the major bank in 2026. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jpmorgans-guidance-seemed-especially-conservative-161943036.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google Stock Momentum Continues Amid Apple Deal. Wall Street Firms Hike Price Targets.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/google-stock-momentum-apple-siri-record-high/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Alphabet hit a record high as Wall Street firms raised their price targets on Google stock in the wake of a new AI deal with Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/google-stock-momentum-apple-siri-record-high/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] If You Invested $500 or More in Apple Stock at the Beginning of 2025, Here’s How Much You’d Have Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invested-500-more-apple-stock-151442553.html</link><description>Apple stock rose nearly 12% in 2025, but it still lagged behind the S&amp;amp;P 500. So how much would an investment in early 2025 be worth now? Find out now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invested-500-more-apple-stock-151442553.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet reaches the $4 trillion club: Can it keep up the pace?</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/next/2026/01/13/alphabet-reaches-the-4-trillion-club-can-it-keep-up-the-pace?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</link><description>Google’s parent company is the fourth firm to hit the $4tn mark, following Nvidia, Microsoft, and Apple.View on euronews</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.euronews.com/next/2026/01/13/alphabet-reaches-the-4-trillion-club-can-it-keep-up-the-pace?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays says AI eclipses macro as key market driver in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-says-ai-eclipses-macro-150421966.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Artificial intelligence is now the dominant force shaping market behaviour in 2026, surpassing traditional macro and policy catalysts, according to Barclays.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-says-ai-eclipses-macro-150421966.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:04:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Industry sounds new alarm bell over Reeves's ISA reforms</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/industry-sounds-alarm-bell-over-144100019.html</link><description>The investment industry has intensified warnings to the government over plans to limit cash ISAs, arguing that they risk undermining British investors' willingness to back listed companies.  Sky News has learnt that a meeting on Tuesday involving major industry players including Hargreaves Lansdown, HSBC and Lloyds Banking Group, along with officials from the Treasury and HM Revenue and Customs, descended into a heated exchange over the implications of the Treasury's reforms.  Under plans confirmed by Rachel Reeves at November's Budget, the cash ISA allowance will be slashed from £20,000 to £12,000 from April 2027, with the exception of savers aged under 65.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/industry-sounds-alarm-bell-over-144100019.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Brokers Suggest Investing in CrowdStrike (CRWD): Read This Before Placing a Bet</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brokers-suggest-investing-crowdstrike-crwd-143002290.html</link><description>Based on the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), CrowdStrike (CRWD) should be added to one's portfolio. Wall Street analysts' overly optimistic recommendations cast doubt on the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric. So, is the stock worth buying?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brokers-suggest-investing-crowdstrike-crwd-143002290.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple rolls out Creator Studio to boost services push, adds AI features</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-rolls-creator-studio-boost-142842572.html</link><description>Apple on Tuesday unveiled Apple Creator Studio, a new subscription bundle of ​professional creative software priced at $12.99 a month ‌or $129 a year, as the iPhone maker steps up its push ‌into paid services for creators, students and professionals. The company has used its services business, which includes its Apple Music and iCloud services, to drive growth ⁠in recent years, helping ‌counter slower hardware growth and generate recurring revenue. Apple Creator Studio bundles some of ‍the company's best-known creative tools into a single subscription, including Final Cut Pro, Logic Pro and Pixelmator Pro across ​Mac and iPad.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-rolls-creator-studio-boost-142842572.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Biggest Loser: Tim Cook of Apple</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/the-biggest-loser-tim-cook-of-apple/</link><description>Apple has fallen behind rivals in the artificial intelligence race because CEO Tim Cook failed to launch an advanced AI product of its own.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/the-biggest-loser-tim-cook-of-apple/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says  “There’s a Lot of Value in Nike”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-lot-value-140628826.html</link><description>NIKE, Inc. (NYSE:NKE) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with recent market rotation. Cramer discussed the recent downgrade by a Needham analyst, as he remarked: “Or take Nike. Oh boy, the stock of Nike. What had it been? [The house of pain]. This thing spiked when they canned the previous CEO and […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-lot-value-140628826.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] What Investors In JPMorgan’s Active Growth ETF Need To Pay Attention To Now</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/what-investors-in-jpmorgans-active-growth-etf-need-to-pay-attention-to-now/</link><description>The JPMorgan Active Growth ETF (NYSEARCA:JGRO) delivered a 14.2% return over the past year, trailing the S&amp;amp;P 500’s 17.9% gain by nearly 4 percentage points. For investors paying a 0.44% expense ratio for active management, underperformance raises a key question: what should you watch to understand whether this fund can close the gap? JGRO’s $8.5 ... What Investors In JPMorgan’s Active Growth ETF Need To Pay Attention To Now</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/what-investors-in-jpmorgans-active-growth-etf-need-to-pay-attention-to-now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] X and xAI Face Malaysia Legal Action</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/x-xai-face-malaysia-legal-133752232.html</link><description>Grok deepfake concerns trigger legal action</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/x-xai-face-malaysia-legal-133752232.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Health &amp; Fitness Stocks Positioned for Strong 2026 Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/health-fitness-stocks-positioned-strong-133200092.html</link><description>UNFI, COCO, DOCS and PTON are tapping into the $11T wellness boom with tech, nutrition, and fitness-driven growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/health-fitness-stocks-positioned-strong-133200092.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] JPMorgan, Bank of New York Mellon Diverge On Earnings Results</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/jpmorgan-chase-bank-earnings-q4-2025-jpm-stock-dow-jones-bank-of-new-york-mellon-bny-bk/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan Chase, Bank of New York Mellon trade tightly ahead of a busy week of quarterly bank earnings reports.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/jpmorgan-chase-bank-earnings-q4-2025-jpm-stock-dow-jones-bank-of-new-york-mellon-bny-bk/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google Is Now the AI Top Dog. The Stock Keeps Rising After $4 Trillion Milestone.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/alphabet-stock-google-trillion-74a8ba6b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shares hit a record high on Monday, making Alphabet the fourth company ever to pass a $4 trillion market capitalization.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/alphabet-stock-google-trillion-74a8ba6b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL): Trailing in AI Spending or Exploring a Different Path?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-trailing-ai-spending-123749841.html</link><description>Fundsmith, an investment management firm based in London, has released its annual 2025 investor letter for its “Fundsmith Equity Fund.” A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The fund focuses on investing in equities globally. The T Class Accumulation shares where the firm invested returned 0.8% in 2025, compared to 12.8% for the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-trailing-ai-spending-123749841.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] KeyBanc upgrades Intel and AMD on surging hyperscaler demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-upgrades-intel-amd-surging-120025997.html</link><description>Investing.com -- KeyBanc Capital Markets has upgraded Intel and AMD to Overweight, citing stronger-than-expected data-center demand and tightening memory supply across the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-upgrades-intel-amd-surging-120025997.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Tech Weekly: Apple and Google do a deal, Glasses for the Blind</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-weekly-apple-google-deal-112701603.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: From Apple and Google doing a deal to Glasses for the Blind, this is Tech Weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: Tech Weekly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple and Google-owner Alphabet have done a deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The iPhone maker will use Google's Gemini models for its revamped Siri coming later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It deepens their alliance in the AI era and boosts Alphabet's position in the race against OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google's technology already drives much of Samsung's Galaxy AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the Siri deal unlocks a massive market with Apple's base of more than two billion active devices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there's no sign Apple's dominance of global smartphones has let up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm led the sector with a 20% share of the market last year - just ahead of Samsung.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading analyst Counterpoint Research said the firm saw solid demand in emerging and mid-sized markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And enjoyed strong sales of the iPhone 17 series.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest innovations in the tech sector were on show at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;.lumen showed off its so-called Glasses for the Blind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The device goes on a person's head and acts in a similar way to a guide dog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm said the glasses use haptics to help people with blindness go about daily life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And employs AI to distinguish between safe and unsafe surfaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new robotaxi design was unveiled in Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's the product of a partnership between EV-maker Lucid, Uber and autonomous vehicle tech firm Nuro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The car uses Nvidia's AI driving hardware, and can drive itself in certain conditions without a human using Nuro's autonomous tech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Salguero is Nuro's Head of Communications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We use an AI autonomy foundation model that basically learns as it goes along. So as we're driving, as we are testing, both on road and in simulations, it gets better and better at driving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group plans to launch robotaxi services in the San Francisco Bay Area later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And AI wearables were on show in Vegas, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the wearable tech included rings, jewelry, exoskeletons and glasses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI jewlery company Nirva showed products it claims can track your mood and record a journal of your day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While tech firm ible demonstrated noise-cancelling headphones which they said can detect pollution and purify the air in front of your face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-weekly-apple-google-deal-112701603.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The trillion-dollar IPOs investors are watching for in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trillion-dollar-ipos-investors-watching-110019391.html</link><description>Listen and subscribe to Stocks In Translation on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you find your favorite podcast.Investors are buzzing over potential $1 trillion tech IPOs in 2026, but which giants will come out on top? In this episode of Stocks in Translation, The Futurum Group Daniel Newman joins host Jared Blikre and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma to discuss the potential $1 trillion IPOs of OpenAI and SpaceX. Newman breaks down investor hype, competitive moats, and market risks, while also exploring Google (GOOG) Gemini’s AI gains, Apple's (AAPL) innovation gap, and how Amazon (AMZN) and Meta (META) are positioned to dominate AI in 2026.Check out the full episode here. Twice a week, Stocks In Translation cuts through the market mayhem, noisy numbers and hyperbole to give you the information you need to make the right trade for your portfolio. You can find more episodes here, or watch on your favorite streaming service. This post was written by Lauren Pokedoff</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trillion-dollar-ipos-investors-watching-110019391.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trending tickers: Alphabet, UBS, Novo Nordisk, Persimmon and Whitbread</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-ubs-novo-nordisk-persimmon-whitbread-trending-tickers-100452578.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Tuesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-ubs-novo-nordisk-persimmon-whitbread-trending-tickers-100452578.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Is Barclays’ Renewed Overweight on DigitalOcean (DOCN) Reframing Its Role in AI Infrastructure?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-renewed-overweight-digitalocean-docn-091003704.html</link><description>Recently, Barclays reaffirmed its "Overweight" rating on cloud platform provider DigitalOcean Holdings and named the company one of its preferred software stocks for 2026, citing confidence in its market potential and sector backdrop. This endorsement highlights how DigitalOcean is being positioned by a major investment bank within the broader software and cloud landscape, particularly as investors reassess opportunities in smaller, AI-focused infrastructure providers. We’ll now examine how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-renewed-overweight-digitalocean-docn-091003704.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Heard on the Street Monday Recap: Central Bank Shot</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-monday-recap-central-bank-shot-5eV1swOTbuxx96X1244m?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks shrug off latest Powell threat. U.S. indexes posted mild gains despite pressure following the news that the Trump administration has launched a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-monday-recap-central-bank-shot-5eV1swOTbuxx96X1244m?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] It's Official: Apple and Alphabet Are Teaming Up for an AI-Powered Siri. Why This Is a Win for Both Companies.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/its-official-apple-and-alphabet-are-teaming-up-for/</link><description>Apple gets a faster path to a smarter Siri, while Alphabet gets Gemini in front of one of the biggest consumer audiences in the world.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/its-official-apple-and-alphabet-are-teaming-up-for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The UK areas tipped for strongest house price growth</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-house-prices-growth-2026-england-scotland-zoopla-060006009.html</link><description>UK house prices to rise by 1.5% overall in 2026, says Zoopla.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-house-prices-growth-2026-england-scotland-zoopla-060006009.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Unpacking Q3 Earnings: CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) In The Context Of Other Cybersecurity Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unpacking-q3-earnings-crowdstrike-nasdaq-033117197.html</link><description>As the Q3 earnings season wraps, let’s dig into this quarter’s best and worst performers in the cybersecurity industry, including CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) and its peers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unpacking-q3-earnings-crowdstrike-nasdaq-033117197.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Behind the Unraveling of Apple’s Credit-Card Partnership With Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/banking/apple-goldman-sachs-credit-card-what-happened-0e89749d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>After more than two years of negotiations, one of the biggest credit-card deals of all time will see Goldman replaced by JPMorgan on the Apple credit card.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/banking/apple-goldman-sachs-credit-card-what-happened-0e89749d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Heard on the Street Recap: Central Bank Shot</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-central-bank-shot-Q2K8LQAJeOeOivkpZH4U?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>What Happened in Markets Today Stocks shrug off latest Powell threat. Major U.S. stock indexes posted some mild gains Monday despite earlier pressure following news that the Trump administration has launched a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-central-bank-shot-Q2K8LQAJeOeOivkpZH4U?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Investors Are Still Waiting for an AI Siri. A New Deal With Google Could Help It Deliver</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/apple-investors-are-still-waiting-for-an-ai-siri-a-new-deal-with-google-could-help-it-deliver-11883948</link><description>Apple plans to use Google's Gemini to power future Apple Intelligence features, including an AI-enhanced Siri coming later this year, the companies said Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/apple-investors-are-still-waiting-for-an-ai-siri-a-new-deal-with-google-could-help-it-deliver-11883948</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today: Dow, S&amp;P 500 Close At Highs; Alphabet Hits $4 Trillion Mark (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-powell-nvidia-nvda-tesla-tsla/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nasdaq composite outperforms the Dow and the S&amp;amp;P 500. Alphabet crosses above $4 trillion market cap.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-powell-nvidia-nvda-tesla-tsla/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>