<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:30:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:30:07 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[CRWD] Analysts Applaud CrowdStrike Holdings’ (CRWD) SGNL Deal, Reiterate Buy Ratings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-applaud-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-115824747.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is among the best software infrastructure stocks to buy according to hedge funds. On Thursday, January 8, the company announced an agreement to acquire SGNL, an identity management startup, for $740 million, according to CNBC. The company believes the acquisition will bolster its position in the Next-Gen Identity Security space, complementing its […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-applaud-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-115824747.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Led Smartphone Market in 2025. 3 Ways It Can Defy a Market Slump in 2026.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-price-iphone-sales-2026-aecb866f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Apple took a 20% market share of the global smartphone market last year but could face declining device sales in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-price-iphone-sales-2026-aecb866f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Santander completes stake sale in Polish unit to Austria’s Erste</title><link>https://www.retailbankerinternational.com/news/santander-completes-polish-unit-sale-erste/</link><description>The Austrian lender intends to rebrand Santander Bank Polska as Erste Bank Polska during the second quarter of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.retailbankerinternational.com/news/santander-completes-polish-unit-sale-erste/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Stocks to Watch Monday: Capital One, UnitedHealth, Walmart, Exxon</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-monday-capital-one-amex-citi-walmart-cxNFLzth3IQXy8o4joFX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ Exxon Mobil (XOM): President Trump said he might block the oil company from drilling in Venezuela after Chief Executive Darren Woods described the country as "uninvestible" at present. Shares dropped about 1% in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-monday-capital-one-amex-citi-walmart-cxNFLzth3IQXy8o4joFX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Leads Global Smartphone Market With 20% Share in 2025</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-113854832.html</link><description>iPhone 17 sales and emerging-market demand lift Apple to top spot.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-113854832.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Top "Magnificent Seven" Stocks to Buy in 2026, According to Wall Street</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/the-top-magnificent-seven-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-ac/</link><description>Several of the "Magnificent Seven" stocks could deliver magnificent returns this year, if analysts are right.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/the-top-magnificent-seven-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-ac/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple leads global smartphone market in 2025, says Counterpoint</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-105756650.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Global smartphone shipments rose 2% year-on-year in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to leading analyst Counterpoint Research Monday (January 12).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It said sales were lifted by stronger demand and economic strength in emerging markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple led the market with a 20% share.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Counterpoint said the U.S. tech giant saw solid demand in emerging and mid-sized markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And it enjoyed&amp;amp;nbsp;strong sales of the iPhone 17 series.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galaxy maker Samsung came second with a 19% share on modest shipment growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While China's Xiaomi was third on a 13% share and supported by steady demand in emerging markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Counterpoint said the global smartphone market is expected to soften this year due to chip shortages and rising component costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That as chipmakers focus on AI data centers over handsets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-105756650.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Apple Stock a Buy for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/is-apple-stock-a-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Apple's stock lost to the market in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/is-apple-stock-a-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 Tech Stocks You Can Buy and Hold for the Next Decade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/2-tech-stocks-you-can-buy-and-hold-for-the-next-de/</link><description>These tech giants will almost certainly be worth a lot more 10 years from now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/2-tech-stocks-you-can-buy-and-hold-for-the-next-de/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Capital One, Synchrony Stocks Fall After Trump Calls for Cap on Credit-Card Rates</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/capital-one-synchrony-stocks-fall-after-trump-calls-for-cap-on-credit-card-rates-xkGy1foivVYa4SaMagIG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks in a range of financial companies fell after President Trump called for credit-card interest rates to be capped at 10% for a year, in his latest attempt to address voters' affordability concerns.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/capital-one-synchrony-stocks-fall-after-trump-calls-for-cap-on-credit-card-rates-xkGy1foivVYa4SaMagIG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trending tickers: Walmart, Alibaba, Novo Nordisk, BE Semiconductor and British Land</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-alibaba-novo-nordisk-be-semiconductor-british-land-trending-tickers-094445339.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-alibaba-novo-nordisk-be-semiconductor-british-land-trending-tickers-094445339.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia Stock Drifts. China AI Chips and 1 Other Thing Can Reignite It.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-china-8bfa9df6?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  stock is languishing with progress on sales in China and the health of the wider artificial-intelligence sector in focus.  The chip maker’s shares were up 0.1% at $184.98 in Friday’s after-hours trading.  The stock is down 1.8% over the past month, as a flurry of robotics and autonomous-driving related announcements at the CES trade show, formerly known as the Consumer Electronics Show, failed to provide a catalyst.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-china-8bfa9df6?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank, TSMC Earnings, Inflation Data: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/bank-tsmc-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-this-week-fggTRgyPTtK2YFZaAw0U?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Key economic data are due this week, including two inflation readings. The U.S.'s largest banks are also scheduled to report earnings, starting with JPMorgan Chase. Later this week, results from Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing, known as TSMC, will pulse-check the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/bank-tsmc-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-this-week-fggTRgyPTtK2YFZaAw0U?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 08:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction Markets Face a New Test This Earnings Season</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/prediction-markets-earnings-trade-kalshi-polymarket-6fe90538?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Event contracts are giving investors more direct ways to trade on corporate results this earnings season. The most popular bets may surprise you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/prediction-markets-earnings-trade-kalshi-polymarket-6fe90538?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple leads global smartphone market with 20% share in 2025, says Counterpoint</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-064420012.html</link><description>Global smartphone shipments rose 2% year-on-year in 2025, lifted ​by stronger demand and economic (? momentum in emerging markets, Counterpoint Research said on ‌Monday. Apple led the market with a 20% share, the largest among the top five brands, supported by solid demand in ⁠emerging and ‌mid-sized markets and strong sales of the iPhone 17 series, said ‍Counterpoint analyst Varun Mishra.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-064420012.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Savings challenges to boost your finances in 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/savings-challenges-finances-2026-060059530.html</link><description>This is a great time of year to get stuck into a savings challenge – either a fun, quick fix to get back on track or a longer-term change designed to make saving easier.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/savings-challenges-finances-2026-060059530.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC Q4 profit poised to soar 27% as AI demand drives growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-profit-poised-soar-044206683.html</link><description>TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 27% jump in fourth-quarter net profit to a record due to ​the seemingly insatiable demand for AI infrastructure.  Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co, the world's top contract chipmaker and ‌a key supplier to Nvidia and Apple, is forecast to report a net profit of T$475.2 billion ($15.02 billion) for the three months through ‌December 31, according to an LSEG SmartEstimate compiled from 19 analysts.  TSMC, Asia's most valuable listed company with a market capitalisation of around $1.38 trillion - more than twice that of South Korean rival Samsung Electronics - is due to report on Thursday and will provide first-quarter and full-year guidance ⁠in an earnings call scheduled for ‌0600 GMT.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-profit-poised-soar-044206683.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple CEO Tim Cook Could Buy 92,984 iPhone 17s With His 2025 Compensation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ceo-tim-cook-could-023108071.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) CEO Tim Cook was one of the highest-paid executives in 2024. The CEO saw a slight dip in his 2025 compensation, but still took home an impressive pay package despite Apple stock trailing several leading market indexes for the year. Tim Cook's 2025 Salary and Pay Compensation Cook, who has been CEO of Apple since 2011 when he took over for co-founder Steve Jobs, has helped usher Apple into a new era of growth and taken Apple stock to new milestones. A new filing from Appl</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ceo-tim-cook-could-023108071.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 02:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Dow Jones Futures Fall As Fed Chief Powell Under Criminal Probe; JPMorgan, Goldman, Delta, Taiwan Semi Ahead</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-fed-chief-powell-criminal-probe-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Fed chief Jerome Powell said a criminal probe is really about interest rates. JPMorgan, Goldman, Taiwan Semi, Delta loom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-fed-chief-powell-criminal-probe-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures slip with bank earnings and inflation data on deck</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-with-bank-earnings-and-inflation-data-on-deck-001621195.html</link><description>Major gauges made slight losses as Wall Street prepares for a week of major releases against a backdrop of global volatility.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-with-bank-earnings-and-inflation-data-on-deck-001621195.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Sees Lamb Weston (LW) Selloff as Overdone, Cuts Price Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-sees-lamb-weston-lw-215243663.html</link><description>Lamb Weston Holdings, Inc. (NYSE:LW) is included among the 13 Best Consumer Staples Dividend Stocks to Invest in Now. On December 23, Barclays cut its price target on Lamb Weston Holdings, Inc. (NYSE:LW) to $55 from $68 and kept an Overweight rating on the shares. The firm acknowledged investor frustration after the company posted a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-sees-lamb-weston-lw-215243663.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Dow Jones Futures Loom; JPMorgan, Goldman, Delta, Taiwan Semi Ahead</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market is at highs with JPMorgan, Goldman, Taiwan Semi and Delta earnings due. Two huge conferences, inflation data and perhaps a Trump tariffs ruling also are on tap.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 19:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Earnings Kickoff, CPI and Other Can't Miss Items this Week</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36988468/earnings-kickoff-cpi-and-other-can-t-miss-items-this-week</link><description>Markets enter a massive week marking the unofficial start of Q4 earnings season with major financial institutions including JPMorgan, Bank of America, and Goldman Sachs reporting results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36988468/earnings-kickoff-cpi-and-other-can-t-miss-items-this-week</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia CEO sends strong message on Taiwan Semiconductor</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-sends-strong-message-on-taiwan-semiconductor</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang has just cut through the big debate over AI chipmaking, saying that the future of advanced chips runs through Taiwan. By extension, it still runs through the crown jewel of the chipspace in Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (TSM), regardless of the number of ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-sends-strong-message-on-taiwan-semiconductor</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] What The Q3 Narrative Shift Means For Martin Marietta Materials's Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q3-narrative-shift-means-martin-171148582.html</link><description>What the New Fair Value Estimate Signals Analysts have nudged their modeled fair value for Martin Marietta Materials to US$676.43 from US$666.29, paired with a nearly unchanged 8.21% discount rate that keeps the core risk view steady. The forecast now blends slightly softer revenue growth of 7.22% versus 7.34% with a modestly higher implied valuation, reflecting the push and pull between optimism around Q3 themes like volume recovery and infrastructure demand, and caution around weather and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q3-narrative-shift-means-martin-171148582.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] A 2025 security breach exposed over 184 million private passwords. How to stay safe while you browse</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2025-security-breach-exposed-over-161500826.html</link><description>'This is a cybercriminal’s dream working list.'</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2025-security-breach-exposed-over-161500826.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] This Money Expert Is Sending Warning Signs About the Economy — and How To Protect Yourself</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/money-expert-sending-warning-signs-150720870.html</link><description>Several money experts have sounded the alarm, warning that today's economy isn't as strong as some headlines suggest.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/money-expert-sending-warning-signs-150720870.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 5 AI Stocks That Could Replicate NVIDIA’s Decade of Dominance</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/5-ai-stocks-that-could-replicate-nvidias-decade-of-dominance/</link><description>NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA) has delivered a 23,000% return over the past decade has become the benchmark every tech investor measures against. The company created the infrastructure that made modern AI possible. Now the question: which company pulls off the next NVIDIA-like run? We analyzed 15 AI-adjacent stocks across semiconductors, software, and quantum computing to find the ... 5 AI Stocks That Could Replicate NVIDIA’s Decade of Dominance</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/5-ai-stocks-that-could-replicate-nvidias-decade-of-dominance/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Revealed: My 2 Top AI Stock Picks for 2026</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/revealed-my-2-top-ai-stock-picks-for-2026/</link><description>With the first full trading week of 2026 now in the books, investors might be wondering if the strong early start in the S&amp;amp;P will precede even more strength. Undoubtedly, a lack of a Santa Claus rally has seemingly paved the way for a rather hot start to 2026, with some memory chip stocks really ... Revealed: My 2 Top AI Stock Picks for 2026</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/revealed-my-2-top-ai-stock-picks-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Magnificent 7’s Stock Market Dominance Shows Signs of Cracking</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stock-market-dominance-140007016.html</link><description>For the first time since 2022, when the Federal Reserve started raising interest rates, the majority of the Magnificent 7 tech giants performed worse than the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index.  While the Bloomberg Magnificent 7 Index rose 25% in 2025, compared with 16% for the S&amp;amp;P 500, that was only because of the enormous gains by Alphabet Inc. and Nvidia Corp.  Suddenly stock picking within the group is crucial.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stock-market-dominance-140007016.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Surprising Stock About to Join the Nasdaq 100</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/the-surprising-stock-about-to-join-the-nasdaq-100/</link><description>The Nasdaq 100 is an index most often associated with technology stocks like Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) and Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) due to its historical focus on innovation and high-growth companies. While it is not a “pure” technology index — there is a separate Nasdaq 100 index devoted exclusively to tech stocks — its heavy tilt towards tech-driven ... The Surprising Stock About to Join the Nasdaq 100</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/the-surprising-stock-about-to-join-the-nasdaq-100/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>