<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[INTC] Bank of America resets Intel stock forecast</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-resets-intel-stock-forecast</link><description>Intel reported its Q4 earnings on January 22. The guidance provided by the company for Q1 disappointed investors, and the stock took a tumble on the following day, closing at $45.07, or 17.03% lower, according to Yahoo Finance. During the earnings call, Lip-Bu Tan, CEO of Intel, addressed the ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-resets-intel-stock-forecast</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] This Telecom Stock Could Be a Surprising Long-Term Winner as Artificial Intelligence Adoption Accelerates</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/this-telecom-stock-could-be-a-surprising-long-term/</link><description>After years of redefining itself as a telecom equipment provider, Nokia may finally be ready for a stock price breakout.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/this-telecom-stock-could-be-a-surprising-long-term/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Dow Jones Futures Loom: New Trump Tariff Threat, Government Shutdown, Earnings Wave In Focus</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-100-canada-tariff-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>President Donald Trump threatened a 100% tariff on Canada. Government shutdown risks soared. Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, Apple learnings loom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-100-canada-tariff-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Investors Hedge China, Tech Risks Amid Trump TACO Trade Drama</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-hedge-china-tech-risks-150000906.html</link><description>For volatility markets, it’s an all-too familiar quick spike and reversal: The Cboe Volatility Index jumped Tuesday, then quickly retreated to below the level from the previous Friday, with the futures curve ending the week in an almost identical shape.  Meanwhile, away from the Trump-driven headlines that moved the broader indexes and the VIX, some investors were putting on hedges against geopolitical risks that could pressure shares of Chinese companies and against the potential for disappointing tech earnings.  Last week, investors bought about 400,000 lots of March-expiring puts in the iShares China Large-Cap ETF (FXI), along with 20,000 contracts in the KraneShares CSI China Internet ETF (KWEB) and 150,000 of Xtrackers Harvest CSI China A-Shares ETF (ASHR) puts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-hedge-china-tech-risks-150000906.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] China Opens Door to Nvidia H200 Chips But Questions Outnumber Answers</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/25/china-opens-door-to-nvidia-h200-chips-but-questions-outnumber-answers/</link><description>China has reportedly indicated willingness to approve NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA) H200 chips for import. The timing, conditions, and competitive dynamics present a complex situation for the company’s China market strategy. The Approval That Isn’t Really an Approval Jensen Huang is currently in Shanghai. China is “poised to approve” H200 imports. Questions remain about whether this represents ... China Opens Door to Nvidia H200 Chips But Questions Outnumber Answers</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/25/china-opens-door-to-nvidia-h200-chips-but-questions-outnumber-answers/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Prediction: These 2 Stocks Will Be the Biggest Winners From $500 Billion AI Spending in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/predict-stock-winner-billion-ai-spending-nvda/</link><description>Don't overthink the AI boom. This year's AI winners are sitting in plain sight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/predict-stock-winner-billion-ai-spending-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Big Tech earnings, Fed meeting feature as markets end January with busiest week of Q1: What to watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-fed-meeting-feature-as-markets-end-january-with-busiest-week-of-q1-what-to-watch-125211822.html</link><description>As geopolitical tensions simmer in the background, Big Tech earnings and the January Fed meeting take center stage this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-fed-meeting-feature-as-markets-end-january-with-busiest-week-of-q1-what-to-watch-125211822.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Every Stock in This Index Group Is Up Double-Digits in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/every-stock-in-this-index-group-is-up-double-digit/</link><description>Spending on chip fabrication equipment is soaring -- and sending these stocks higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/every-stock-in-this-index-group-is-up-double-digit/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 1 Incredible Stock Warren Buffett Bought Over 30 Years Ago Is Up 150% in 3 Years, And It's About to Overtake Apple as Berkshire Hathaway's Largest Holding</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/1-incredible-stock-warren-buffett-bought-over-30-y/</link><description>This forever holding could still keep climbing as Berkshire Hathaway cuts its Apple stake.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/1-incredible-stock-warren-buffett-bought-over-30-y/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 1 "Magnificent Seven" Stock That's a Clear Fintech Powerhouse</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/1-magnificent-seven-stock-clear-fintech-powerhouse/</link><description>Leading traditional financial institutions aren't protected from this company's innovative push.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/1-magnificent-seven-stock-clear-fintech-powerhouse/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Prediction: This Will Be the Next Artificial Intelligence (AI) Chip Stock to Join Nvidia, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Broadcom in the Trillion-Dollar Club (Hint: It's Not AMD)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/prediction-this-will-be-the-next-artificial-intell/</link><description>The trillion-dollar club features three artificial intelligence (AI) chip stocks, and another could soon join the ranks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/prediction-this-will-be-the-next-artificial-intell/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] What to Expect in Markets This Week: Fed Interest Rate Decision, Earnings From Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, Apple</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-fed-interest-rate-decision-earnings-from-microsoft-meta-tesla-apple-11890747</link><description>Coming up: A Federal Reserve interest rate decision, earnings from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, Apple, and other key firms, U.S. trade deficit data, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-fed-interest-rate-decision-earnings-from-microsoft-meta-tesla-apple-11890747</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Goldman Sticks With Apple (AAPL) Buy Rating Despite Early-2026 Weakness</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sticks-apple-aapl-buy-091152294.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Buzzing AI Stocks Analysts are Watching. On January 20, Goldman Sachs analyst Michael Ng reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $320.00 price target. The firm views APPL’s recent YTD drop as a buying opportunity, citing multi-year iPhone strength and Services mix. The investment bank noted […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sticks-apple-aapl-buy-091152294.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Bernstein Sees Structural Upside for ASML Through 2029</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-bernstein-sees-structural-upside-090221425.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the Buzzing AI Stocks Analysts are Watching. On January 16, Bernstein SocGen Group analyst David Dai reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $1,528.00 price target. The firm is strongly positive on ASML as it sees structural demand upside for the stock into 2026–2029. On January […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-bernstein-sees-structural-upside-090221425.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Seaport Global Turns Bullish on Intel (INTC), Citing Strong PC Signals and Foundry Progress</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/seaport-global-turns-bullish-intel-090047153.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the Buzzing AI Stocks Analysts are Watching. On January 20, Seaport Global Securities analyst Jay Goldberg upgraded the stock to “Buy” from Neutral with a price target of $65. The firm is cautiously optimistic on the stock, noting that INTC is back on track, but a full turnaround at […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/seaport-global-turns-bullish-intel-090047153.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Wall Street Is Wrong About Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/why-wall-street-is-wrong-about-taiwan-semiconducto/</link><description>Wall Street expects the company to gain about 25% this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/why-wall-street-is-wrong-about-taiwan-semiconducto/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Does Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) Still Offer Value After Its Strong Five-Year Rally?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-lloyds-banking-group-lse-061331166.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Lloyds Banking Group shares still offer value after the recent run, this article will walk through what the current price might be implying. The stock last closed at £1.02, with returns of a 0.4% decline over 7 days, 4.8% over 30 days, 2.4% year to date and 72.7% over the past year, as well as 126.0% over 3 years and 288.1% over 5 years. Recent headlines around Lloyds Banking Group have focused on its position as a major UK retail and commercial bank and its...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-lloyds-banking-group-lse-061331166.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet Inc. (GOOGL) Strengthens Its Position in AI and Cloud Innovation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-googl-strengthens-position-044216933.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the best stocks to buy, according to billionaire Bill Ackman. On January 12, Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL)’s market capitalization broke through the $4 trillion mark after Apple announced it would use Gemini models to power its artificial intelligence and next-generation Siri. The multiyear partnership will enable Apple to leverage Gemini […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-googl-strengthens-position-044216933.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is QUALCOMM (QCOM) One of the Best 5G Stocks to Invest In?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/qualcomm-qcom-one-best-5g-032924491.html</link><description>QUALCOMM Incorporated (NASDAQ:QCOM) is one of the 12 Best 5G Stocks to Invest in According to Hedge Funds. On January 15, Citi reiterated its Neutral rating on QUALCOMM Incorporated (NASDAQ:QCOM) with a price target of $180 following a coverage reshuffle. Citi noted that the stock is currently trading above its historical valuation levels. Earlier, on […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/qualcomm-qcom-one-best-5g-032924491.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 03:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Bernstein Names AT&amp;T (T) Top Telecom Pick for 2026, Barclays Stays Neutral</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-names-t-t-top-032913072.html</link><description>AT&amp;amp;T Inc. (NYSE:T) is one of the 12 Best 5G Stocks to Invest in According to Hedge Funds. On January 15, Bernstein named AT&amp;amp;T Inc. (NYSE:T) as its top pick in the US telecom market for 2026, even as competition in the industry is expected to grow. The research firm noted that the telecom sector […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-names-t-t-top-032913072.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] FactSet Research Systems (FDS) Valuation After New Multiyear Barclays Agreement</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-research-systems-fds-valuation-001813159.html</link><description>Barclays has entered a multiyear arrangement with FactSet Research Systems (FDS), using the company’s analytics, data and technology to support its long term market data strategy and services for global clients. See our latest analysis for FactSet Research Systems. The Barclays agreement comes after a tough stretch for shareholders, with a 1 year total shareholder return decline of 37.91% and a relatively flat pattern in recent share price returns. This suggests momentum has been subdued even...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-research-systems-fds-valuation-001813159.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] My Top 3 Chip Stocks for 2025 Crushed the Market. Here's Why They Can Repeat Again in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/my-top-3-chip-stocks-for-2025-crushed-the-market/</link><description>AI spending is expected to stay elevated in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/my-top-3-chip-stocks-for-2025-crushed-the-market/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 Reasons to Buy TSMC Stock Like There's No Tomorrow</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/reasons-to-buy-tsmc-stock-like-no-tomorrow/</link><description>The semiconductor manufacturer just reported stellar fourth-quarter results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/reasons-to-buy-tsmc-stock-like-no-tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] GM To End Production Of Its Most Affordable EV, Move Buick From China To US: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gm-end-production-most-affordable-203104675.html</link><description>General Motors Co. (NYSE:GM) will reportedly end production of its most affordable EV, the Chevrolet Bolt, as well as move Buick production out of China into Kansas. GM's Production Reshuffle The Detroit-based automaker will shift production of the Gas-powered Chevrolet Equinox and the upcoming Buick Envision away from Mexico and China, respectively, to its facility in Fairfax, Kansas, TechCrunch reported on Thursday. Don't Miss: Missed Nvidia and Tesla? RAD Intel Could Be the Next AI Powerhouse</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gm-end-production-most-affordable-203104675.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Drops After Q4 Earnings: Is INTC a Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214534/intel-stock-drops-after-q4-earnings-is-intc-a-buy-now</link><description>Intel enters 2026 facing near-term pressure, with the first quarter expected to remain challenging.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214534/intel-stock-drops-after-q4-earnings-is-intc-a-buy-now</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Could a Wearable AI Pin Be the Next Big Thing for Apple Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214375/could-a-wearable-ai-pin-be-the-next-big-thing-for-apple-stock</link><description>A wearable AI pin may be niche, but it hints at Apple's plans to weave AI deeper into its ecosystem.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37214375/could-a-wearable-ai-pin-be-the-next-big-thing-for-apple-stock</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 19:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>