<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[INTC] Surging Intel Stock, 2 Other Nasdaq 100 Giants Headline Earnings Calendar</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/intel-stock-nasdaq-100-netflix-earnings-isrg-ge-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock is holding near highs ahead of its Q4 earnings report, along with Leaderboard stock GE Aerospace.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/intel-stock-nasdaq-100-netflix-earnings-isrg-ge-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Spotify will net an eye-popping amount of money by raising prices again</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-will-net-an-eye-popping-amount-of-money-by-raising-prices-again-141750366.html</link><description>The streaming platform is raising prices across its plans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-will-net-an-eye-popping-amount-of-money-by-raising-prices-again-141750366.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Tech rally, US-Taiwan chip deal, power grid auction: 3 Things</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-rally-us-taiwan-chip-141009857.html</link><description>US stock futures (ES=F, NQ=F, YM=F) are perked up in Friday's premarket as the tech sector and bank stocks are looking to rally. Chip stocks are roaring to life this morning after the US struck a trade deal with Taiwan, which includes Taiwanese tech companies investing a total of $250 billion into US semiconductor manufacturing. Lastly, the Trump administration is teaming up with governors to hold an emergency power auction to resolve the surging power costs expected from Big Tech's AI data centers. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-rally-us-taiwan-chip-141009857.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Last Year, I Predicted That Alphabet Would Join the $3 Trillion Club. Here's Why the "Magnificent Seven" Stock Could Surpass $5 Trillion Before the End of 2027.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/alphabet-stock-all-time-high-5-trillion-club/</link><description>The Google parent's stock is roaring higher for all the right reasons.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/alphabet-stock-all-time-high-5-trillion-club/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Are you concerned about losing your job this year? How readers voted</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/job-losses-unemployment-uk-poll-results-133703725.html</link><description>Continued signs of weakness in the UK labour market have created uncertainty over the outlook for jobs for the year ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/job-losses-unemployment-uk-poll-results-133703725.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today: Dow Wavers Near Record Highs; Nvidia Regains Key Level (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-record-highs-nvidia-nvda-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Futures for the Dow Jones Industrial Average and other major stock indexes were mostly higher Friday, as Wall Street looked to finish out the week on a high note. An early winner was Nvidia, which rose on the stock market today after making a bullish move above a key level Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-record-highs-nvidia-nvda-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Rigetti Stock: Hype or Hidden Opportunity in Quantum Tech?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-stock-hype-hidden-opportunity-132733016.html</link><description>Wall Street Flags Rigetti Risks as Revenue Remains Near Zero, Cash Burn Persists</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-stock-hype-hidden-opportunity-132733016.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to watch next week: Netflix, Intel, Burberry, JD Wetherspoon and JD Sports</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-intel-burberry-jd-wetherspoon-jd-sports-stocks-to-watch-131827171.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-intel-burberry-jd-wetherspoon-jd-sports-stocks-to-watch-131827171.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Prediction: Intel Stock Will Continue Soaring in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-intel-will-continue-soaring-in-2026/</link><description>Intel's product development efforts could help the company clock faster-than-expected growth in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-intel-will-continue-soaring-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Watch February Earnings From NVIDIA and Microsoft to Predict Where This Mag7 ETF Goes Next</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/watch-february-earnings-from-nvidia-and-microsoft-to-predict-where-this-mag7-etf-goes-next/</link><description>The Roundhill Magnificent Seven ETF (NYSEARCA:MAGS) provides equal-weight exposure to the seven largest tech companies for investors seeking diversified exposure to this basket without selecting individual stocks. The fund holds NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA), Alphabet Inc (NASDAQ:GOOGL), Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT), and Meta Platforms Inc (NASDAQ:META) in equal portions alongside Apple Inc (NASDAQ:AAPL), Amazon.com Inc (NASDAQ:AMZN), and ... Watch February Earnings From NVIDIA and Mic</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/watch-february-earnings-from-nvidia-and-microsoft-to-predict-where-this-mag7-etf-goes-next/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 'The minute our love for meat goes, the business goes downhill'</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jolly-hog-sausages-bacon-meat-business-060032786.html</link><description>Bristol-based sausage firm The Jolly Hog is run by three Kohn brothers, whose relentless focus on quality has driven multimillion-pound sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jolly-hog-sausages-bacon-meat-business-060032786.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Zacks Investment Ideas feature highlights: Taiwan Semiconductor, NVIDIA, Apple, Broadcom and Meta Platforms</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-120500392.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor delivered blockbuster earnings, raised capex, and detailed AI-driven shortages that could keep demand ahead of supply for years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-120500392.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AST SpaceMobile Stock Jumps Again. Why the SpaceX Rival’s Shares Are Going Stellar.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ast-spacemobile-stock-price-spacex-d24b8d2a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AST SpaceMobile stock was rising as investors got excited about the potential for the satellite-communications company to expand in the defense sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ast-spacemobile-stock-price-spacex-d24b8d2a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Friday: J.B. Hunt, PNC, Verizon</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-j-b-hunt-pnc-verizon-keWejK8riJCb6jCEHgUB?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ J.B. Hunt Transport Services (JBHT): The logistics company recorded lower quarterly revenue, as transcontinental load volumes declined. Shares fell in off-hours trading. 🔎 M&amp;amp;T Bank (MTB), PNC Financial Services (PNC) and State Street (STT) are due to report results Friday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-j-b-hunt-pnc-verizon-keWejK8riJCb6jCEHgUB?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] President Donald Trump's Tax Policy Has Lit a Fire Under This Trillion-Dollar Trend That Apple, Alphabet, and Nvidia Are Taking Full Advantage Of</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/donald-trump-tax-policy-trillion-dollar-trend-nvda/</link><description>Hint: It has nothing to do with the rise of artificial intelligence (AI).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/donald-trump-tax-policy-trillion-dollar-trend-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Over-reliance on China supply chains could put 90,000 UK jobs at risk</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-china-car-battery-supply-chains-jobs-060031535.html</link><description>Trade wars and macroeconomic events raise questions about how resilient the UK economy would be if it couldn't import key parts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-china-car-battery-supply-chains-jobs-060031535.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AI Market Looks More Like Boom than Bubble After TSMC Earnings</title><link>https://www.thedailyupside.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-market-looks-more-like-boom-than-bubble-after-tsmc-earnings/</link><description>The foundry behind Nvidia’s and Apple’s chips predicted Thursday its capital spending would swell at least 27% this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thedailyupside.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/ai-market-looks-more-like-boom-than-bubble-after-tsmc-earnings/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Exclusive: Is Apple Late To Foldable iPhones? Ming-Chi Kuo Says Cupertino Isn't At 'Disadvantage' As Samsung Sees Foldables Go Mainstream</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-apple-foldable-iphones-ming-033130804.html</link><description>Apple Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AAPL) long-anticipated entry into the foldable iPhone market may not be as delayed — or as risky — as it appears, according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, even as Samsung Electronics Co. (OTC:SSNLF) says the category is nearing mainstream adoption. Apple's Timing May Not Be A Problem After All Apple has yet to launch a foldable iPhone, but Kuo, a TF International Securities analyst known for tracking Apple's supply chain, told Benzinga that timing alone does not put Cupertino at a</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-apple-foldable-iphones-ming-033130804.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq climb as Wall Street gets set to wrap up volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-climb-as-wall-street-gets-set-to-wrap-up-volatile-week-234227757.html</link><description>Stocks eked out gains at the end of a week packed with developments and earnings ahead of the long weekend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-climb-as-wall-street-gets-set-to-wrap-up-volatile-week-234227757.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq climb with Wall Street set to wrap up volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-climb-with-wall-street-set-to-wrap-up-volatile-week-234227487.html</link><description>Stocks eked out gains at the end of a week packed with developments and earnings ahead of the long weekend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-climb-with-wall-street-set-to-wrap-up-volatile-week-234227487.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] TSMC Seeks Narrower Tech Gap in US, Taiwan Fabs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-seeks-narrower-tech-gap-231246722.html</link><description>(Updates video to add Huang's comment that TSMC can consider collaborations on advanced packaging if it makes sense for customers and the wafer business; updates video description with additional comments.) Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Chief Financial Officer Wendell Huang said the company will try to accelerate the transfer of its advanced chipmaking expertise to the US in the future, though it will still develop and maintain its most cutting-edge fabrication techniques at home. He said TSMC can consider collaborations on advanced packaging if it makes sense for customers and the company's wafer business. There have been no discussions about potential investments in Intel Corp., Huang said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-seeks-narrower-tech-gap-231246722.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Trump Takes Credit For Intel's Surge But Hesitant To Raise Stake: 'I'll Invest More In Other Things'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-takes-credit-intels-surge-230112226.html</link><description>President Donald Trump stated that his intervention in Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) has resulted in substantial gains for the U.S. chipmaker. However, he is not sure if he would invest more in the company. “I don’t know about Intel but I’ll invest more in other things,” Trump said. Speaking to reporters at Joint Base Andrews in Maryland on Tuesday, Trump said that after he assisted Intel, the company’s valuation soared. He added that Intel’s success had attracted other major players’ investme</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-takes-credit-intels-surge-230112226.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today, Jan. 15: Nvidia Rises on Strong AI Demand and Data Center Growth Optimism</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/15/stock-market-today-jan-15-nvidia-rises-on-strong-ai-demand-and-data-center-growth-optimism/</link><description>Today, Jan. 15, 2026, investors are weighing surging AI data center demand against fresh questions about the durability of that growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/15/stock-market-today-jan-15-nvidia-rises-on-strong-ai-demand-and-data-center-growth-optimism/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Small-cap records, chip stock gains, silver: Market Takeaways</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/small-cap-records-chip-stock-221522267.html</link><description>US stocks (^DJI, ^IXIC, ^GSPC) close Thursday's session higher following AI optimism tied to the US trade deal with Taiwan. Yahoo Finance Markets and Data Editor Jared Blikre breaks down the biggest market themes from today’s trading day, including how small-cap indexes are reaching record highs, stock movements in semiconductor chip manufacturers, and price trends in silver (SI=F). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Asking for a Trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/small-cap-records-chip-stock-221522267.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) Valuation Check After Strong Recent Share Price Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-banking-group-lse-lloy-221036842.html</link><description>Event context and recent share performance Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) has attracted fresh attention after recent share price moves, with the stock showing gains over the past week, month and past 3 months that stand out against its longer term track record. See our latest analysis for Lloyds Banking Group. Set against this, Lloyds Banking Group’s recent 7.56% 1 month share price return and 23.97% 3 month share price return sit alongside a very large 5 year total shareholder return. This...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-banking-group-lse-lloy-221036842.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Is Back From the Brink, But It Only Gets Tougher From Here. How Should You Play INTC in 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37071510/intel-is-back-from-the-brink-but-it-only-gets-tougher-from-here-how-should-you-play-intc-in-2026</link><description>Intel is looking up but faces more headwinds ahead. Here's what's next for Intel as the company prepares to report earnings late next week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37071510/intel-is-back-from-the-brink-but-it-only-gets-tougher-from-here-how-should-you-play-intc-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Dell Stock Has Been a Victim of AI. These Analysts Say It’s a Winner.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-price-buy-analysts-ai-winner-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Barclays and Goldman Sachs both urged investors to buy the shares, citing AI server demand, expense discipline, and accelerating earnings growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-price-buy-analysts-ai-winner-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 5 AI Chip Stocks Most Exposed to Trump’s New 25% Tariff</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/5-ai-chip-stocks-most-exposed-to-trumps-new-25-tariff/</link><description>Trump’s 25% tariff on AI chips landed the same day Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) posted blowout earnings and dismissed AI bubble fears. TSMC’s stock surged 8% Thursday, pulling AMD up 12% and NVIDIA 3% in sympathy. Now investors face a critical question: which chip stocks are most exposed when the tariff hits? The policy ... 5 AI Chip Stocks Most Exposed to Trump’s New 25% Tariff</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/5-ai-chip-stocks-most-exposed-to-trumps-new-25-tariff/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Gene Munster Says Apple's Move From OpenAI's ChatGPT To Google Gemini Significantly Raises Chances Of New Siri Succeeding: 'Nice Job'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gene-munster-says-apples-move-213113224.html</link><description>On Tuesday, Deepwater Asset Management's managing partner Gene Munster said that Apple Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AAPL) switch from OpenAI's ChatGPT to Alphabet Inc.'s (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google Gemini gives Siri a much stronger chance of success. Apple Partners With Google Gemini To Reinvent Siri Munster took to X and said, "Odds of new Siri succeeding just went up," while praising Apple CEO Tim Cook for turning long-standing Siri shortcomings into an opportunity for future device and services gro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gene-munster-says-apples-move-213113224.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Best Dividend ETF to Invest $500 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/best-dividend-etf-to-invest-500-in-right-now/</link><description>Dividend ETFs have been getting another look as the market rotates into non-tech sectors to kick off 2026. This Vanguard ETF, in particular, looks well-positioned to benefit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/best-dividend-etf-to-invest-500-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Datadog (DDOG) Faces Competitive Pressures in 2026, Goldman Says in Sell Call</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/datadog-ddog-faces-competitive-pressures-203038399.html</link><description>Datadog, Inc. (NASDAQ:DDOG) is one of the Must-Watch AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 12, Goldman Sachs analyst Gabriela Borges assumed coverage on the stock with a Sell rating and a price target of $113.00. Firm analysts see 2026 as a pressure year for DDOG as competition intensifies and weighs on fundamentals. “We assume coverage […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/datadog-ddog-faces-competitive-pressures-203038399.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Microchip, Analog Devices target raised ahead of semiconductor earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microchip-analog-devices-target-raised-201302724.html</link><description>Investing.com --Wolfe Research raised estimates on select semiconductor names ahead of the fourth-quarter earnings season, arguing that while demand visibility remains mixed across end markets, downside risks appear limited and company-specific drivers are becoming more important.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microchip-analog-devices-target-raised-201302724.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s (AAPL) AI-Powered Siri and Foldable iPhone Are Key Catalysts, Analyst Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-powered-siri-200804438.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Must-Watch AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 12, BofA Securities analyst Wamsi Mohan reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $325.00 price target. Firm analysts anticipate upside surprises as the tech giant heads into F1Q26 earnings on January 29 after markets close, particularly driven by […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-powered-siri-200804438.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise as TSMC boosts AI hopes, bank stocks rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-tsmc-boosts-ai-hopes-bank-stocks-rally-195049176.html</link><description>Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-tsmc-boosts-ai-hopes-bank-stocks-rally-195049176.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How Apple Stock Could Add $100 Per Share in 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37068991/how-apple-stock-could-add-100-per-share-in-2026-and-beyond</link><description>Here is how Wedbush analyst Dan Ives thinks Apple could add $100 per share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37068991/how-apple-stock-could-add-100-per-share-in-2026-and-beyond</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Michael Burry Bets Against Nvidia, Says'I Do Not See How That Math Works' Amid AI Chip Boom Fears</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-burry-bets-against-nvidia-190119667.html</link><description>Investor Michael Burry, famed for predicting the 2008 housing crash, is now betting against Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA), warning that the AI-driven chip boom is vulnerable to a sharp reversal. Burry Calls Nvidia ‘Purest Play’ On AI In a Substack post over the weekend, Burry said he is shorting Nvidia because the chipmaker is "simply the purest play" on artificial intelligence and is dangerously reliant on hyperscaler spending. "I do not see how that math works," he wrote, adding that Nvidia could</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-burry-bets-against-nvidia-190119667.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Just Got a New Street-High Price Target. Should You Buy INTC Here?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37067938/intel-stock-just-got-a-new-street-high-price-target-should-you-buy-intc-here</link><description>Intel has been on an absolute tear in the past year, surging 50% during this period, as it inked partnerships with Nvidia, SoftBank, and others.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37067938/intel-stock-just-got-a-new-street-high-price-target-should-you-buy-intc-here</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Massive Corporate Layoffs Changed Everything, Says Robert Kiyosaki. Calls Going To School For Job Security An 'Obsolete Idea'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/massive-corporate-layoffs-changed-everything-183114744.html</link><description>Robert Kiyosaki says the recent wave of corporate job cuts shows that the traditional promise of stability through schooling no longer holds up in today's economy. In a recent post on X, the investor and author of “Rich Dad Poor Dad” argued that going to school for job security has become an “obsolete idea,” especially as layoffs hit industries that once symbolized safety, prestige, and high pay. His comments come amid continued workforce reductions across logistics, retail, manufacturing, and t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/massive-corporate-layoffs-changed-everything-183114744.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] India Presses Ahead With Apple Probe</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-presses-ahead-apple-probe-181600941.html</link><description>Regulators warn after year long delays</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-presses-ahead-apple-probe-181600941.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Corning (GLW) Stock Is Up, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corning-glw-stock-know-175137337.html</link><description>Shares of glass and electronic component manufacturer Corning (NYSE:GLW) jumped 3.8% in the afternoon session after BofA raised its price target on the company's shares to $110 from $95 while keeping a Buy rating.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corning-glw-stock-know-175137337.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 4 semiconductor stocks giving the AI boom 'more legs'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-semiconductor-stocks-giving-the-ai-boom-more-legs-175135867.html</link><description>Crossmark Global Investments chief market strategist Victoria Fernandez explains why a new wave of earnings from the semiconductor sector signals the AI race is just warming up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-semiconductor-stocks-giving-the-ai-boom-more-legs-175135867.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Western Digital (WDC) Stock Is Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-western-digital-wdc-stock-175042827.html</link><description>Shares of leading data storage manufacturer Western Digital (NASDAQ: WDC) jumped 6.6% in the afternoon session after positive analyst actions, including an upgrade to "Overweight" and a significant price target increase from Barclays. Barclays raised its price target on the company to $240 from $200, while keeping an "Overweight" rating. Separately, other analysts upgraded the stock to "Overweight," citing optimism about its future performance. This wave of positive sentiment from analysts was e</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-western-digital-wdc-stock-175042827.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Goldman Sachs Profit Climbs 12% as Earnings Top Estimates</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/bank-earnings-wells-fargo-bank-of-america-morgan-stanley-blackrock-goldman-sachs-citigroup/card/goldman-sachs-profit-climbs-12-as-earnings-top-estimates-XrJtIaMtKJRZ6S4uLDPI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Goldman Sachs reported fourth-quarter net earnings of $4.62 billion, up 12% from a year earlier. The firm earned $14.01 a share, topping analysts’ forecasts for $11.70, according to FactSet estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/bank-earnings-wells-fargo-bank-of-america-morgan-stanley-blackrock-goldman-sachs-citigroup/card/goldman-sachs-profit-climbs-12-as-earnings-top-estimates-XrJtIaMtKJRZ6S4uLDPI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Taiwan Semi Stock Just Hit a New All-Time High But AI Fears Remain</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37066859/taiwan-semi-stock-just-hit-a-new-all-time-high-but-ai-fears-remain</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor (TSM) shares are trading at new all-time highs. Shares are up nearly 70% over the past 52 weeks. TSM maintains a 100% technical “Buy” opinion from Barchart. The stock hit new highs Thursday after Taiwan Semi reported record profit in its fourth-quarter earnings. Today’s Featured Stock Valued at...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37066859/taiwan-semi-stock-just-hit-a-new-all-time-high-but-ai-fears-remain</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple makes high-stakes Siri change as Services growth takes center stage</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/apple-makes-high-stakes-siri-change-as-services-growth-takes-center-stage</link><description>Apple is wagering that it can resolve a long-standing problem with one of its products rapidly by using a competitor's artificial intelligence. This might lead customers to buy new iPhones and use more services, which would boost Apple's income. Apple and Google have announced a multi-year ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/apple-makes-high-stakes-siri-change-as-services-growth-takes-center-stage</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Analysts Say Dell Is Becoming an AI Winner. Buy the Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-analysts-ai-upside-buy-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Barclays and Goldman Sachs both urged investors to buy the shares, citing AI server demand, expense discipline, and accelerating earnings growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/dell-stock-analysts-ai-upside-buy-7fac5550?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Faces Final Warning From India in Antitrust Dispute</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-faces-final-warning-india-165816638.html</link><description>Regulator threatens to move ahead after yearlong delay in Apple's response.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-faces-final-warning-india-165816638.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] OpenAI seeks US hardware partners for expansion into devices and data centers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openai-seeks-us-hardware-partners-164641000.html</link><description>Investing.com -- OpenAI is searching for US-based manufacturing partners as it prepares for a major expansion into consumer devices, robotics, and cloud data centers in the coming years, according to a report Thursday from Bloomberg News.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openai-seeks-us-hardware-partners-164641000.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 3 Technology Stocks to Sell in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-technology-stocks-sell-2026-163117495.html</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Information Technology Index is down -1.75% year to date and -2.53% over the past month, signaling a sketchy outlook for tech stocks in 2026, though not for all big sector names. As usual, artificial intelligence, especially in the software realm, is using up most of the tech industry’s oxygen. “There’s a lot of optimism around AI, but also a lot of hype,” said Anthony Saglimbene, chief market strategist at Ameriprise, in a recent research note. “2026 will be more about the proof of</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-technology-stocks-sell-2026-163117495.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Nasdaq Plays Catch-Up: Is the Tech-Heavy Index Ready to Breakout?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-plays-catch-tech-heavy-161600773.html</link><description>The themes we saw last year appear to be carrying over into 2026, a positive sign that this multi-year rally still has legs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-plays-catch-tech-heavy-161600773.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Can Intel's Upgradation in AI PCs Strengthen Its Business Growth?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intels-upgradation-ai-pcs-strengthen-161400884.html</link><description>INTC is pushing deeper into AI with next-gen AI PCs, pairing powerful on-device processing, new Core Ultra chips, and key partnerships to reshape everyday computing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intels-upgradation-ai-pcs-strengthen-161400884.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock at 52-wk. high: Here's what's driving enthusiasm</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-52-wk-high-161055829.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock hit a 52-week high on Thursday as investor enthusiasm continues to grow. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley sits down with Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman to explain how Intel's high-powered laptop chip, which debuted at CES 2026, is part of what's driving investor interest in the company. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-52-wk-high-161055829.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Siri to Get Smarter With Gemini: The ETF Playbook for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/siri-smarter-gemini-etf-playbook-160500261.html</link><description>Apple teams up with Google's Gemini to supercharge Siri, creating a win-win AI deal and pointing investors toward tech ETFs for diversified exposure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/siri-smarter-gemini-etf-playbook-160500261.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dell, Intel, DraftKings: Top analyst calls today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/dell-intel-draftkings-top-analyst-155706146.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma outlines some of Wall Street's top analyst calls today: Dell Technologies (DELL), Intel (INTC), and DraftKings (DKNG). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/dell-intel-draftkings-top-analyst-155706146.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights AbbVie, Intel, Boeing and Tandy Leather Factory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-abbvie-154300644.html</link><description>AbbVie leads a Zacks Analyst Blog roundup highlighting strong pharma execution, AI-driven chip gains and an aviation rebound.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-abbvie-154300644.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights Qualcomm Technologies, Advanced Micro Devices, Intel and NVIDIA</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-qualcomm-153800690.html</link><description>Qualcomm takes a slight edge in a Zacks Analyst Blog comparison as chipmakers race to capitalize on AI-driven demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-qualcomm-153800690.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 1 Oversold Software Stock With Too Much AI Fear Priced In</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/1-oversold-software-stock-with-too-much-ai-fear-priced-in/</link><description>AI has really landed a heavy shot on some of the software names, especially the SaaS (Software as a Service) companies that have been quite slow to brace for the rise of the artificial intelligence (AI) age. Undoubtedly, with agents, robotics, and all sorts of transformative and revolutionary disruptive tech up ahead, standing pat and ... 1 Oversold Software Stock With Too Much AI Fear Priced In</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/15/1-oversold-software-stock-with-too-much-ai-fear-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153025915.html</link><description>HIVE Digital Technologies Ltd. 2,672,229 3.47</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153025915.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Soaring Memory Prices Lift Chipmakers, Pressure Apple and HP</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/soaring-memory-prices-lift-chipmakers-152001445.html</link><description>AI-driven memory shortages are boosting suppliers while rising costs weigh on hardware makers' margins and outlooks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/soaring-memory-prices-lift-chipmakers-152001445.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CRWD to Acquire Seraphic: Is Browser Security the Next Growth Engine?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-acquire-seraphic-browser-security-151400300.html</link><description>CrowdStrike agrees to acquire Seraphic to extend Falcon into browser security, targeting AI-driven risks inside browser sessions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-acquire-seraphic-browser-security-151400300.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why ASML Stock Is Climbing Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-asml-stock-climbing-today-151159957.html</link><description>ASML Shares Jump on TSMC Capex Boost, but 2026 Growth Remains Unclear</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-asml-stock-climbing-today-151159957.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>