<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[INTC] Mobileye Global Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/mobileye-global-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Mobileye Global (NASDAQ:MBLY) executives struck an upbeat tone on the company’s fourth-quarter and full-year 2025 earnings call, pointing to stronger-than-expected demand trends through the year, expanding engagement on next-generation ADAS programs, and what they described as rising momentum for ro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/mobileye-global-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Has Barclays (LSE:BARC) Run Too Far After A 66% One Year Share Price Gain?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Barclays shares still offer value after a strong run, this article walks through how the current price stacks up against several valuation checks. The stock has been relatively steady in the near term, with a 0.9% decline over the last 7 days and a 1.6% gain over the last 30 days. The 1 year return of 66.2% and 3 year return of 194.8% put recent moves in a much longer context for anyone thinking about risk and reward. That 1 year return of 66.2% and a 5 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Susquehanna Lifts Semiconductor Targets as AI, Lead Times Support Earnings Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/susquehanna-lifts-semiconductor-targets-ai-155355135.html</link><description>Analysts see modest upside into 4Q and 1Q, driven by AI demand and improving semiconductor lead times.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/susquehanna-lifts-semiconductor-targets-ai-155355135.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] ChatGPT Thinks Intel Stock Will Close At This Price In The Next 60 Days</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-intel-stock-close-153120913.html</link><description>Shares of Intel have shown signs of renewed investor interest as the company's push to ramp semiconductor production and expand its AI foundry ambitions intersects with broader demand for compute and deeper strategic positioning versus rivals like Nvidia and TSMC....</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-intel-stock-close-153120913.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018945.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018945.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Chip Stocks Are Rising. Nvidia's Huang Reignites the AI Trade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-rising-nvidias-huang-152326038.html</link><description>Global Semiconductor Shares Jump as Davos Fuels AI Optimism.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-rising-nvidias-huang-152326038.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Should CrowdStrike’s Identity Security and AI Governance Push Require Action From CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-identity-security-ai-governance-150945571.html</link><description>CrowdStrike recently moved to acquire identity-security specialist SGNL for about US$740 million, advanced its Global Data Sovereignty initiative with new regional clouds in Saudi Arabia, India and the UAE, and secured ISO/IEC 42001:2023 certification for responsible AI across its Falcon platform. Taken together, these steps extend CrowdStrike’s platform beyond endpoint protection into identity, AI governance and regulated-market deployments, potentially reshaping how enterprises consolidate...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-identity-security-ai-governance-150945571.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Falls Back from 4-Year High Ahead of Earnings. What Has the Market Excited.”</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was cooling off Thursday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report but remains at multiyear highs.  Intel was down 1% at $53.77 in early trading.  Intel is expected to report adjusted earnings of eight cents a share on revenue of $13.42 billion for the fourth quarter of 2025, according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL) Reports Next Week: Wall Street Expects Earnings Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-reports-next-week-150013834.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-reports-next-week-150013834.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Launches Lunar New Year Discounts in China</title><link>https://tech.yahoo.com/ai/apple-intelligence/articles/apple-launches-lunar-discounts-china-145545066.html</link><description>Promotion aims to boost sales ahead of key holiday shopping period.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tech.yahoo.com/ai/apple-intelligence/articles/apple-launches-lunar-discounts-china-145545066.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise after Trump backpedals on Greenland tariffs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-greenland-tariffs-143627517.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-greenland-tariffs-143627517.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel earnings set to test stock rally as Wall Street grows bullish on chipmaker’s AI position</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-earnings-set-to-test-stock-rally-as-wall-street-grows-bullish-on-chipmakers-ai-position-143443999.html</link><description>Intel is set to report fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-earnings-set-to-test-stock-rally-as-wall-street-grows-bullish-on-chipmakers-ai-position-143443999.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s Huge Surge in China</title><link>https://247wallst.com/consumer-electronics/2026/01/22/apples-huge-surge-in-china/</link><description>Apple led in smartphone market share and shipment growth in China in the fourth quarter of 2025, despite it not having an artificial intelligence product in the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/consumer-electronics/2026/01/22/apples-huge-surge-in-china/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says High Price to Earnings Multiples Are Hurting Spotify Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-high-price-141021559.html</link><description>Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about, along with market froth. Highlighting that the company faces competition from Apple and YouTube, a caller inquired if the stock is a buy, sell, or hold. In response, Cramer said: I have been watching the stock just shed points and shed points […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-high-price-141021559.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] NatWest and Halifax cut mortgage costs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-halifax-bank-england-131529096.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-halifax-bank-england-131529096.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Price Target Shifts Are Rewriting The Story For NatWest Group (LSE:NWG)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-price-target-shifts-rewriting-130943619.html</link><description>Why the NatWest Group price target has changed NatWest Group has seen its price target updated, reflecting a fresh look at the bank's current position and what that might mean for investors following the story closely. This shift in expectations is rooted in recent commentary around the stock, which has prompted analysts to reassess how they frame its prospects and risks. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of these price target moves and the wider narrative as it evolves. Analyst Price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-price-target-shifts-rewriting-130943619.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Corp. (INTC) Soars to 52-Week High Ahead of Thursday Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-corp-intc-soars-52-130831414.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names Leaving Wall Street Behind; 7 Are Hitting Record Highs. Intel Corp. (NASDAQ:INTC) was one of the worst performers on Wednesday. Intel Corp. rallied to a new 52-week high on Wednesday, as investors loaded portfolios ahead of the results of its earnings performance for the full year and fourth quarter […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-corp-intc-soars-52-130831414.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Self-Driving Stock Mobileye Plunged After Earnings. Here’s Why.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/mobileye-stock-price-earnings-7046c190?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Mobileye announced fourth-quarter adjusted earnings per share of 6 cents from sales of $446 million. Wall Street was looking for 6 cents and $432 million, respectively.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/mobileye-stock-price-earnings-7046c190?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Okta’s Profits Are Up, But Its Credibility Still Hasn’t Recovered</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/oktas-profits-are-up-but-its-credibility-still-hasnt-recovered/</link><description>You want to talk about irony? Okta Inc (NASDAQ:OKTA) sells identity security to enterprises worldwide, and in 2023, hackers breached its own systems. Twice. That’s like hiring a locksmith who leaves your front door wide open. The question isn’t whether those headlines hurt the stock. They did. The question is whether they’ll haunt it forever. ... Okta’s Profits Are Up, But Its Credibility Still Hasn’t Recovered</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/oktas-profits-are-up-but-its-credibility-still-hasnt-recovered/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel price target raised to $36 from $35 at Bernstein</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-price-target-raised-36-122042694.html</link><description>Bernstein analyst Stacy Rasgon raised the firm’s price target on Intel (INTC) to $36 from $35 and keeps a Market Perform rating on the shares ahead of quarterly results. The firm is upping its server market assumptions but lowering its PC assumptions going forward.Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper decisions Stay ahead of the market with the latest news and analysis and maximize your portfolio's potential Published first o</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-price-target-raised-36-122042694.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Hidden Winner in Nvidia's AI Chip Boom Isn't Who You'd Expect</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</link><description>Nvidia is now outspending Apple at TSMC. Intel may benefit the most from the shift.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Moderna, Intel, GameStop, Micron, Venture Global, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-fd84ffe4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel shares are climbing again ahead of the chip maker’s fourth-quarter earnings, due out after the close of trading Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-fd84ffe4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] “I’d Like to be as Incompetent,” As Apple (AAPL)’s CEO, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/d-incompetent-apple-aapl-ceo-114828610.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Tech giant Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)’s shares are up by 12% over the past year. Ahead of the firm’s upcoming earnings report, Evercore and Goldman Sachs discussed the stock. The former kept an Outperform rating […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/d-incompetent-apple-aapl-ceo-114828610.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Discusses Alphabet (GOOGL) &amp; OpenAI’s Rivalry</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Over the past couple of months, Jim Cramer has turned increasingly optimistic on Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL). Several factors have driven his optimism. Early on, these included enthusiasm for YouTube and the firm’s dominance in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Jumps 11% as Chip Stocks Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</link><description>AI optimism lifts semiconductors across the board</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why Berkshire Put Its Kraft Stake on the Block</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/why-berkshire-put-its-kraft-stake-on-the-block-0861b16f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Warren Buffett’s  explanation of why the conglomerate held on to businesses that more “Darwinian” investors might have cut loose made sense—it engendered valuable goodwill.  New CEO Greg Abel might favor survival of the fittest.  Exhibit A is  Kraft Heinz  : The food giant has struggled mightily.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/why-berkshire-put-its-kraft-stake-on-the-block-0861b16f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple asks Indian court to stop antitrust body from seeking its financials</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-asks-indian-court-stop-105630793.html</link><description>NEW DELHI, Jan 22 (Reuters) - Apple has asked an Indian court to stop the country's antitrust watchdog from seeking its global financial records as part of an investigation into its app store policies</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-asks-indian-court-stop-105630793.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] US Stock Market Today S&amp;P 500 Futures Climb As Traders Await Key PCE Data</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-stock-market-today-p-101016352.html</link><description>The Morning Bull - US Market Morning Update Thursday, Jan, 22 2026 US stock futures are higher this morning, with contracts linked to the broad market up about 0.5%, as investors focus on fresh inflation clues and interest rate expectations. The key inflation gauge the Federal Reserve watches, the PCE index, is expected to rise 0.2% in November, with yearly inflation seen at 2.8%. Put simply, prices are still rising, just not rapidly. At the same time, the 10 year US government bond yield is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-stock-market-today-p-101016352.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Thursday: Intel, P&amp;G, Volkswagen</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-thursday-intel-p-g-volkswagen-AkT24v7VSScFpwtlYwxY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↗️ Intel (INTC): The chip company, in which the government has invested, is due to post earnings on Thursday afternoon. Shares were up around 1.5% in premarket trading, after surging 12% in Wednesday's regular session following an analyst upgrade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-thursday-intel-p-g-volkswagen-AkT24v7VSScFpwtlYwxY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trending tickers: AMD, Intel, Moderna, Associated British Foods and Young &amp; Co's Brewery</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AI power and infrastructure needs boomed in 2025. At Davos, the AI story for 2026 remains the same.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</link><description>The AI industry's greatest bottleneck, power, drove a boom in infrastructure throughout 2025. At Davos, leaders signal that 2026 is likely to see more of the same.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bitcoin price rises as Trump backtracks on Greenland tariff threat</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-crypto-095355676.html</link><description>Bitcoin traded higher after Donald Trump walked back his plan to impose new tariffs on European allies amid his push to acquire Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-crypto-095355676.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bitcoin price rises with stocks as Trump backtracks on tariff threat</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-095355156.html</link><description>Bitcoin traded higher after Trump walked back his plan to impose new tariffs on European allies amid his push to acquire Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-stocks-trump-tariff-greenland-davos-095355156.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] My Top 5 Predictions for the Magnificent Seven Stocks in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</link><description>Investors may continue to closely watch the Magnificent Seven this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Gold price to hit $5,400 this year, says Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-price-trump-greenland-oil-pound-davos-092535662.html</link><description>Gold prices stabilised after US president Donald Trump retreated from using tariffs to pressure Denmark over Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-price-trump-greenland-oil-pound-davos-092535662.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Davos, Intel Earnings, Inflation Data: Still to Come This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/davos-intel-earnings-inflation-data-still-to-come-this-week-47eXdmnsojFralFdpQmY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season kicked up a gear this week, with results still due from Intel, among other companies. Plus, the World Economic Forum continues in Davos, Switzerland, and the Federal Reserve's preferred inflation gauge is due.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/davos-intel-earnings-inflation-data-still-to-come-this-week-47eXdmnsojFralFdpQmY?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] FTSE 100 LIVE: Stocks climb as Trump cancels European tariffs amid 'framework' Greenland deal</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-trump-european-tariffs-greenland-deal-090740451.html</link><description>Donald Trump cited agreement on “the framework of a future deal with respect to Greenland”.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-trump-european-tariffs-greenland-deal-090740451.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Nvidia Stock Is Lagging Behind Other AI Names. Why the Boom’s Darling Is Out of Favor.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-today-ai-chips-4f4ddb9d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock is hovering near the same levels it was at last August, while other companies involved in the artificial-intelligence boom have surged.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-today-ai-chips-4f4ddb9d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Nvidia Stock -- 100% of His Portfolio Is Now Invested in 3 AI Stocks</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</link><description>Billionaire Peter Thiel has his entire portfolio invested in Tesla, Microsoft, and Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Is Bullish on UiPath, Inc. (PATH) Amid Stable IT Spending Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 15 High Growth Mid-Cap Stocks to Buy. The second stock on our list of high growth stocks is UiPath, Inc. TheFly reported on January 12 that Barclays raised its price target on PATH to $18 from $16 and maintained an Equal Weight rating. As part of its 2026 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer on Ares Capital: “I Want to Be Very Careful There”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</link><description>Ares Capital Corporation (NASDAQ:ARCC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. When a caller mentioned that their top five holdings are AAPL, ARCC, HSY, KMB, and NVDA, Cramer remarked: Wow, okay. Well, you got some yield there. You got some growth. I don’t like the Ares because I can’t really tell what […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Market’s Hottest Active ETF Has Yet to Meet Its Biggest Test</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/hottest-active-etf-biggest-test-mag-7-ea23e58b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The iShares U.S. Equity Factor Rotation Active ETF has taken huge bets on tech and communications stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/hottest-active-etf-biggest-test-mag-7-ea23e58b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Is Intel (INTC) Getting Ahead Of Itself After A 148% One Year Share Price Surge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-getting-ahead-itself-070717403.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Intel's current share price reflects a fair deal or is getting ahead of itself, you are in the right place for a clear, valuation focused look at the stock. Intel shares last closed at US$54.25, with returns of 11.4% over the past week, 49.2% over the past month, 37.8% year to date, 148.2% over the past year, 89.4% over three years, and 12.0% over five years. These moves raise questions about how much of the story is already in the price. Recent news flow around...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-getting-ahead-itself-070717403.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] The Age of AI Agents Brings a Risk No One Is Prepared For</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence companies have promised that 2026 will be the year of agents: Software that can use AI language models to autonomously execute a complex series of tasks from simple instructions.  The most prevalent use for agents today is for making software.  With enough of a budget, a single developer can orchestrate teams of agents to work on existing codebases or even to start a project from scratch.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Franklin Resources (BEN) Target Raised as Barclays Updates Asset Manager Models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</link><description>Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 15, Barclays raised its price target on Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) to $25 from $22, while still keeping an Underweight rating on the stock. The firm said the adjustment was mainly driven by updates to its asset manager […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Q4 Preview: Kimberly-Clark (KMB) Target Cut, “enthusiasm” Not Driven by Fundamentals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</link><description>Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 16, Barclays cut its price target on Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) to $102 from $132, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The move was part of the firm’s Q4 earnings preview for the consumer staples sector, where […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] CubeSmart (CUBE) Target Cut as Barclays Updates 2026 REIT Sector View</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</link><description>CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 13, Barclays analyst Brendan Lynch trimmed his price target on CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) to $43 from $45, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change came as part of Barclays’ broader 2026 outlook update for the REIT sector. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Surging memory chip prices dim outlook for consumer electronics makers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-memory-chip-prices-dim-001756209.html</link><description>Global demand for smartphones, personal computers and gaming consoles is expected to shrink this year as companies from Britain's Raspberry Pi to HP Inc raise sticker prices to offset surging memory chip costs.  The rapid build-out of artificial intelligence infrastructure by U.S. tech firms such ​as OpenAI, Alphabet-owned  Google and Microsoft has absorbed much of the world's memory chip supply, pushing up prices as manufacturers prioritize components for higher-margin data ‌centers over consumer devices.  Samsung, SK Hynix and Micron, the world's three largest producers of memory chips, have said in recent months that they were struggling to keep up with demand as they reported rosy quarterly ‌earnings on the back of surging prices for their semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-memory-chip-prices-dim-001756209.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump EU meeting, Intel earnings, December PCE: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-eu-meeting-intel-earnings-000023754.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come tomorrow, Thursday, January 22, including President Trump's meeting with European Union (EU) leadership; corporate earnings results from Procter &amp;amp; Gamble (PG), GE Aerospace (GE), and Intel (INTC); and December's Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) index. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-eu-meeting-intel-earnings-000023754.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures rise after Trump backpedals on tariffs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-tariffs-234947394.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-tariffs-234947394.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures inch up after Trump's Greenland whiplash</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-inch-up-after-trumps-greenland-whiplash-234947096.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-inch-up-after-trumps-greenland-whiplash-234947096.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures climb after Trump's Greenland whiplash</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-climb-after-trumps-greenland-whiplash-234947137.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-climb-after-trumps-greenland-whiplash-234947137.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] 2025 Was a Record Year for Activism: Barclays</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/2025-record-activism-barclays-234806819.html</link><description>Jim Rossman, global head of shareholder advisory at Barclays Capital, says 2025 set a record with 255 activist campaigns. He tells Romaine Bostick and Katie Greifeld on "The Close" that M&amp;amp;A demands were the top focus of these activists.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/2025-record-activism-barclays-234806819.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Jefferies Raises Intel (INTC) Price Target to $45 but Cites Structural Constraints</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-raises-intel-intc-price-232821685.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 16, Jefferies analyst Blayne Curtis raised the price target on the stock to $45.00 (from $40.00) while maintaining a Hold rating. The firm is cautiously negative on INTC despite strong server demand, due to structural constraints. The firm noted that Intel […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-raises-intel-intc-price-232821685.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Citizens Reiterates Bullish View on CrowdStrike (CRWD) With $550 Price Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citizens-reiterates-bullish-view-crowdstrike-232102207.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 20, Citizens analyst reiterated a Market Outperform rating on the stock with a $550.00 price target. According to the firm, CrowdStrike’s recent acquisitions in identity governance and secure browser space help the company close potential functional gaps and limit competitors’ […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citizens-reiterates-bullish-view-crowdstrike-232102207.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How Apple’s Gemini-Powered Siri Deal Will Impact Alphabet (GOOGL) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-powered-siri-deal-231107182.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, Apple announced a multi-year partnership with Google to base its next generation of Apple Foundation Models on Google’s Gemini AI and cloud technology, bringing more personalized, AI-powered Siri features while keeping Apple Intelligence workloads on-device and within its Private Cloud Compute framework. The deal effectively places Google’s Gemini at the heart of Apple’s core AI experience, turning a long-time ecosystem rival into a large-scale customer for...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-powered-siri-deal-231107182.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Rallies Ahead of Earnings. Here's What Analysts Are Saying That's Boosting the Stock.</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/intel-rallies-ahead-of-earnings-here-is-what-analysts-are-saying-that-is-boosting-the-stock-intc-11889769</link><description>Intel shares popped Wednesday, adding to their recent gains amid growing optimism about demand ahead of the chipmaker's earnings report due Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/intel-rallies-ahead-of-earnings-here-is-what-analysts-are-saying-that-is-boosting-the-stock-intc-11889769</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] A timeline of the US semiconductor market in 2025</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/timeline-us-semiconductor-market-2025-110649518.html</link><description>From leadership changes at legacy semiconductor companies to wishy washy policy around chip exports, a lot happened last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/timeline-us-semiconductor-market-2025-110649518.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] This Analyst Calls Tesla 7 Times More 'Capital Efficient' Than Rivals: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analyst-calls-tesla-7-times-223109335.html</link><description>NewStreet Research analyst Pierre Ferragu has hailed Tesla Inc.'s (NASDAQ:TSLA) Robotaxi efforts compared to the likes of Alphabet Inc.-backed (NASDAQ:GOOGL) (NASDAQ:GOOG) Waymo. Tesla ‘Seven Times More Capital Efficient' Than Rivals, Says Pierre Ferragu In an interview with influencer Farzad Mesbahi on Saturday, Ferragu shared his thoughts on the company's Robotaxi efforts. "Tesla is seven times more capital efficient than competitors," Ferragu said, adding that Waymo still faced issues related</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analyst-calls-tesla-7-times-223109335.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trading Day: Relief on Greenland deal hopes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trading-day-relief-greenland-deal-220147030.html</link><description>ORLANDO, Florida, Jan 21 (Reuters) - U.S. stocks jumped and Treasury yields fell on Wednesday after President Donald Trump said a framework of an agreement over Greenland had been reached, and that</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trading-day-relief-greenland-deal-220147030.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Just Claimed the Top Spot in the Chinese Smartphone Market. What Does That Mean for AAPL Stock in 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37160908/apple-just-claimed-the-top-spot-in-the-chinese-smartphone-market-what-does-that-mean-for-aapl-stock-in-2026</link><description>Despite competition concerns, Apple had the top market share in Q4 in China, per Counterpoint Research.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37160908/apple-just-claimed-the-top-spot-in-the-chinese-smartphone-market-what-does-that-mean-for-aapl-stock-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Earnings live: Netflix stock tumbles, Johnson &amp; Johnson falls, Charles Schwab climbs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-netflix-stock-tumbles-johnson--johnson-falls-charles-schwab-climbs-212631402.html</link><description>A broader set of sectors will be represented when 35 more S&amp;amp;P 500 companies report earnings this week, including Netflix, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-netflix-stock-tumbles-johnson--johnson-falls-charles-schwab-climbs-212631402.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Dear Apple Stock Fans, Mark Your Calendars for January 29</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37159215/dear-apple-stock-fans-mark-your-calendars-for-january-29</link><description>Apple's earnings are coming soon. Here's what investors should expect.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37159215/dear-apple-stock-fans-mark-your-calendars-for-january-29</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple to revamp Siri as a built-in chatbot, Bloomberg News reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-chatbot-202957790.html</link><description>Apple plans to revamp Siri later this year by turning the digital assistant into the ​company's first artificial intelligence chatbot, Bloomberg News reported on ‌Wednesday.  The chatbot, code named Campos, will be embedded deeply into the iPhone, ‌iPad and Mac operating systems and will replace the current Siri interface, the report said, citing people familiar with the plan.  Siri's revamp is a crucial part of Apple's strategy to catch up ⁠to its Big Tech ‌peers in the AI race after its initial "Apple Intelligence" rollout in 2024 met with lukewarm reception.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-chatbot-202957790.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock spikes after report of Siri revamp into chatbot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-spikes-report-siri-202356243.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) stock spiked as much as 1.6% Wednesday afternoon following a Bloomberg News report that the company plans to transform Siri into a built-in chatbot, marking its entry into the generative AI race currently led by OpenAI and Google.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-spikes-report-siri-202356243.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s new Siri runs on Gemini, and there’s an invisible catch</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apples-new-siri-runs-on-gemini-and-theres-an-invisible-catch</link><description>Apple and Google describe their Gemini deal as a multi‑year collaboration that will put Google’s models and cloud technology at the core of Apple’s next generation of foundation models, including a more personalized Siri arriving later this year. In their joint statement, the companies stress that ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apples-new-siri-runs-on-gemini-and-theres-an-invisible-catch</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple to Revamp Siri as a Built-In iPhone, Mac Chatbot to Fend Off OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-iphone-195739657.html</link><description>The chatbot — code-named Campos — will be embedded deeply into the iPhone, iPad and Mac operating systems and replace the current Siri interface, according to people familiar with the plan.  Users will be able to summon the new service the same way they open Siri now, by speaking the “Siri” command or holding down the side button on their iPhone or iPad.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-iphone-195739657.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Colgate-Palmolive (CL) Valuation Check After Defensive Rotation And Upgraded Analyst Views</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</link><description>Recent commentary from Barclays and Wells Fargo has pushed Colgate-Palmolive (CL) into focus, as both banks highlight growing investor interest in the stock as a defensive option while maintaining a cautious stance on fundamentals. See our latest analysis for Colgate-Palmolive. The recent analyst comments and Colgate-Palmolive’s new four year collaboration with the WHO Foundation come as the shares trade at US$85.44. The 30 day share price return is 9.04% and the year to date share price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Wednesday: Netflix, Schwab, J&amp;J, United Airlines</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-netflix-united-airlines-kraft-heinz-MdlTaZKD0ZhN2pyHDTCH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ Netflix (NFLX): The streaming company posted better-than-expected quarterly results, but its cash flow and outlook disappointed, as did the news that it would pause buybacks. The stock dropped 4%. ↗️ARM Holdings (ARM): The chip design firm's stock rose 6% after shares were upgraded by Susquehanna.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-netflix-united-airlines-kraft-heinz-MdlTaZKD0ZhN2pyHDTCH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Elon Musk Confirms AI4-Powered Cars Can Achieve Unsupervised Self-Driving Without Additional Upgrades</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has confirmed that the automaker's vehicles equipped with the AI4 (HW4) chip will be able to achieve unsupervised autonomous driving without requiring upgrades. AI4 Will Be Capable Of Self-Driving On Monday, user @iliketeslas shared a post on the social media platform X, stating that the current AI4 chips are capable of running Unsupervised FSD without "better hardware." Anyone using AI4 right now knows that better hardware is not needed for unsupervised dr</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Should You Buy Apple Stock Before Earnings on January 29? This Analyst Says ‘Yes.’</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37157419/should-you-buy-apple-stock-before-earnings-on-january-29-this-analyst-says-yes</link><description>Apple stock has lagged the market, but improving fundamentals and upbeat analyst forecasts suggest earnings may reset investor expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37157419/should-you-buy-apple-stock-before-earnings-on-january-29-this-analyst-says-yes</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq Climb as Trump Seeks Negotiations on Greenland</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dow-p-500-nasdaq-climb-185410493.html</link><description>Trump's Greenland Remarks Ease Tariff Fears; Stocks Surge Across Sectors</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dow-p-500-nasdaq-climb-185410493.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Is Climbing -- Foundry Customer Optimism Sparks Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-climbing-foundry-customer-185408304.html</link><description>Wall Street Turns Cautiously Optimistic on Intel as Q4 Results Loom</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-climbing-foundry-customer-185408304.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Results in Focus as Investors Bet on AI Fueled Comeback</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-focus-investors-bet-184835993.html</link><description>Shares surge ahead of earnings as CEO Lip-Bu Tan's turnaround gains traction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-focus-investors-bet-184835993.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] This Super Semiconductor Stock Crushed Nvidia in 2025, and Jan. 28 Could Be a Very Big Day for Its Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</link><description>This semiconductor equipment powerhouse could be set for another strong year in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Is Intel (INTC) Stock Rocketing Higher Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-rocketing-172536853.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) jumped 9.5% in the afternoon session after its positive momentum continued as recent analyst upgrades completely reshaped the market narrative.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-rocketing-172536853.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Big Tech earnings put spotlight on AI and memory shortage as Trump tariff threats ease for now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-ease-for-now-172319457.html</link><description>Big Tech earnings will put a spotlight on the continued AI build-out, memory shortage, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-ease-for-now-172319457.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Big Tech earnings put spotlight on AI and memory shortage as Trump tariff threats loom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</link><description>Big Tech earnings will put a spotlight on the continued AI build-out, memory shortage, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Is Micron (MU) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</link><description>Shares of memory chips maker Micron (NYSE:MU) jumped 5.9% in the afternoon session after analysts at multiple firms, including Barclays, Stifel, and TD Cowen, raised their price targets on the stock, citing strong demand for its AI-related memory chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Fluence Energy (FLNC) Stock Is Trading Lower Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</link><description>Shares of electricity storage and software provider Fluence (NASDAQ:FLNC) fell 1.8% in the afternoon session after Goldman Sachs maintained its 'Buy' rating on the stock and raised its price target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Did Intel Stock Pop on Wednesday?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/why-did-intel-stock-pop-on-wednesday/</link><description>Should you buy Intel stock before its earnings beat?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/why-did-intel-stock-pop-on-wednesday/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Is CrowdStrike (CRWD) Fairly Priced After Recent Pullback And Cybersecurity Spotlight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether CrowdStrike Holdings is still worth the price you see on your screen, the key question is how that price lines up with what the business may realistically be worth. The stock last closed at US$442.73, after a 5.4% decline over the past week and an 8.0% decline over the past month, although the 1 year return sits at 20.8% and the 3 year return is very large. Recent attention on CrowdStrike has focused on its role as a major cybersecurity provider, as investors...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>