<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:29:04 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Dumped Nvidia and Bought This Other Magnificent Stock Instead -- Even as Warren Buffett Was Selling It Before Retiring</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-dumped-nvidia-and/</link><description>Peter Thiel's hedge fund recently exited his entire stake in Nvidia stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-dumped-nvidia-and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stock Market Week Ahead: Key Health Care, Retail, Aerospace Conferences</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/investing-action-plan/stock-market-week-ahead-health-care-retail-aerospace-conferences/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan and Goldman Sachs launch the Q4 reporting season, in a mix of inflation data and key industry conferences.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/investing-action-plan/stock-market-week-ahead-health-care-retail-aerospace-conferences/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] The Smartest Growth Stock to Buy With $1,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor is a great choice for playing the AI race in a neutral way.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva plc's (LON:AV.) Has Been On A Rise But Financial Prospects Look Weak: Is The Stock Overpriced?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-plcs-lon-av-rise-092601062.html</link><description>Aviva's (LON:AV.) stock is up by a considerable 5.1% over the past month. However, we decided to pay close attention to...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-plcs-lon-av-rise-092601062.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] BofA Reiterates Buy on Apple (AAPL) With $325 Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-reiterates-buy-apple-aapl-082011878.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 6, BofA Securities analyst Wamsi Mohan reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $325.00 price target. Analysts are optimistic about the stock driven by steady App Store momentum, strong capital returns, and long-term AI leadership potential. The firm […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-reiterates-buy-apple-aapl-082011878.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia Soared by 39% in 2025, but Here's Another Super Semiconductor Stock to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/nvidia-soared-39-2025-semiconductor-stock-buy-2026/</link><description>This under-the-radar semiconductor equipment supplier crushed Nvidia last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/nvidia-soared-39-2025-semiconductor-stock-buy-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank earnings, CPI inflation data, Fed comments: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-cpi-inflation-data-000021240.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come next week, including earnings results reported by the Big Banks, December's Consumer Price Index (CPI) inflation data, and a slew of commentary from Federal Reserve officials. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-cpi-inflation-data-000021240.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Senator Dumps Apple, Google, Microsoft To End 2025—But Refuses To Sell This Mag 7 Underperformer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senator-dumps-apple-google-microsoft-223108948.html</link><description>When it comes to members of Congress’s trading activity, there is a strong focus on what's being bought and when stocks are sold. One senator recently disclosed the sale of three Magnificent Seven stocks sold in December, but a Mag7 stock that wasn't sold could be more telling. Senator Ditches Magnificent Seven Stocks Sen. Shelley Moore Capito (R-W.Va.) recently disclosed selling multiple stocks, including several Magnificent Seven stocks, according to the Benzinga Government Trades page. Here w</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senator-dumps-apple-google-microsoft-223108948.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Score: Constellation, Chevron, Lockheed Martin and More Stocks That Defined the Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/the-score-constellation-chevron-lockheed-martin-ventyx-biosciences-paramount-jpmorganstocks-that-defined-the-week-58662721?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Modelo and Corona importer reported lower quarterly sales and profit as customers, particularly Hispanic consumers, continue to buy less beer.  Constellation cited weak consumer sentiment and rising unemployment rates, as well as a downturn in “4,000-calorie jobs,” or physically demanding jobs such as construction, that typically boost beer sales.  Constellation shares rose 5.3% Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/the-score-constellation-chevron-lockheed-martin-ventyx-biosciences-paramount-jpmorganstocks-that-defined-the-week-58662721?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Dow Jones Futures: Stock Market Runs To Highs; JPMorgan, Goldman, Delta, Taiwan Semi Lead Big Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market is at highs with JPMorgan, Goldman, Taiwan Semi and Delta earnings due. Two huge conferences, inflation data and perhaps a Trump tariffs ruling also are on tap.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today, Jan. 9: S&amp;P 500 Sets New High and Intel Rallies</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/09/stock-market-today-jan-9-s-and-p-500-sets-new-high-and-intel-rallies/</link><description>Positive jobs data and high-profile political backing for Intel pushed major U.S. indexes toward new highs, today, Jan. 9, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/09/stock-market-today-jan-9-s-and-p-500-sets-new-high-and-intel-rallies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank Earnings, Inflation Data: What to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-09-2026/card/bank-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-next-week-0OSTVh9i8cZCv4LVvaWQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Next week will be busy as 2026 launches into full swing. Key economic data are due, including the consumer-price index for December and producer-price index for November. Meanwhile, the nation’s largest banks are scheduled to report earnings, starting with JPMorgan Chase Tuesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-09-2026/card/bank-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-next-week-0OSTVh9i8cZCv4LVvaWQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] It’s the End of the World as We Know It—and the Market Feels Fine</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-bubble-tech-small-caps-ce55f11d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>It seems tech can take a breather and stocks can still gain. So far this year, areas like materials and industrials are far outpacing tech names. And small-caps are doing the best of all.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-bubble-tech-small-caps-ce55f11d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] These Stocks Are Moving the Most Today: Oklo, Vistra, Opendoor, Intel, GM, Revolution Medicines, Tilray, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks were rising modestly Friday after fresh jobs data showed U.S. unemployment ticked down in December and a potential Supreme Court ruling on tariffs failed to pan out.  Vistra  stock surged 11% and  Oklo  jumped 7.4% after the nuclear energy companies unveiled separate agreements to provide power to  Meta Platforms  in order to support the hyperscaler’s data-center campus in Ohio.  Meta inched up 0.8%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bell, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at Mizuho Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>