<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AV.L] AI-driven inflation is 2026's most overlooked risk, investors say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</link><description>Global stock markets, riding high on AI euphoria at the start of 2026 may be disregarding one of the biggest threats that could spoil the party: a surge in inflation driven partly by the tech investment boom.  U.S. stock indexes, where seven tech groups ​contributed half of all market earnings this year, made double-digit gains in 2025 to hit record highs as exuberance about AI and monetary easing also propelled European and ‌Asian equities to record peaks.  Expectations for further rate cuts have buoyed bonds too, handing U.S. Treasury investors the best annual performance for five years as inflation retreated, although it remains above the Federal Reserve's average 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Is Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) Starting To Look Fully Priced After Strong Five Year Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-banking-group-lse-lloy-091039184.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Lloyds Banking Group at around £0.99 is still reasonably priced or starting to look stretched, you are not alone. The stock shows returns of 2.0% over the last 7 days, 3.6% over the last 30 days, 0.0% year to date, 86.9% over 1 year, 140.5% over 3 years and 245.7% over 5 years. This naturally raises questions about how much value is already reflected in the current price. Recent moves in the share price have kept Lloyds on many investors' watchlists, with ongoing...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-banking-group-lse-lloy-091039184.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Best Income Stocks to Buy for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</link><description>LGGNY, BAP and CCBG made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) income stocks list on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] New Strong Buy Stocks for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</link><description>KVYO, MMS, CCBG, BAP and LGGNY have been added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Why The Narrative Around HSBC Holdings LSE HSBA Is Shifting After Recent Analyst And Boardroom Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</link><description>HSBC Holdings’ latest price target work has not led to a shift in model fair value, which stays at £10.88 per share. Some of the building blocks behind that valuation have been fine tuned. The discount rate has edged down to 10.44% and revenue growth assumptions remain at 8.52%, reflecting how recent mixed research, capital allocation debates and boardroom headlines are feeding into a steadier rather than radically different narrative around the stock. Stay with this article to see how you...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:04:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for January 7th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</link><description>AVVIY, CAE and CHMG have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on January 7th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank completes UK’s first gilt purchase using tokenized deposits</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</link><description>Lloyds enlisted the help of Archax and Canton Network to carry out the transaction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Invests in US Stablecoin Startup Ubyx</title><link>https://decrypt.co/353838/barclays-invests-in-us-stablecoin-start-up-ubyx</link><description>The investment shows UK institutions are taking ‘practical steps’ to bring digital money into regulated frameworks, CryptoUK told Decrypt.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://decrypt.co/353838/barclays-invests-in-us-stablecoin-start-up-ubyx</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank, Archax and Canton Network Complete UK’s First Gilt Purchase Using Tokenised Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</link><description>Lloyds Banking Group has completed a landmark digital finance transaction executing the first-ever Gilt purchase using tokenised deposits. The transaction, carried out in partnership with Archax and the Canton Network, marks the first time tokenised deposits have been issued on a public blockchain in the UK — and the first ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] ‘High-stakes’ frauds and fake texts among scammers’ tactics, Barclays warns</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/high-stakes-frauds-fake-texts-150847392.html</link><description>The bank said it is ‘seeing a shift in the nature of scams reported by our customers’ and made suggestions to help people stay safe.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/high-stakes-frauds-fake-texts-150847392.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Backs Ubyx as Banks Race to Control Stablecoin Rails</title><link>https://99bitcoins.com/news/altcoins/barclays-ubyx-stablecoin-infrastructure/</link><description>Barclays invested in Ubyx, a U.S.-based clearing firm that connects banks to stablecoins and tokenized deposits. Crypto markets barely moved on the news, but stablecoin volumes already push close to $3 trillion a month, which shows where banks focus their energy. Big institutions now treat blockchain payment rails as plumbing, ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://99bitcoins.com/news/altcoins/barclays-ubyx-stablecoin-infrastructure/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva-backed altnet Truespeed in merger talks with rival</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</link><description>A fibre broadband network provider backed by an arm of Aviva, the FTSE-100 insurer, is in merger talks with a rival amid growing financial pressure on the heavily indebted industry.  Sky News has learnt that Truespeed, which has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, is in discussions about a tie-up with Freedom Fibre.  Truespeed, which is concentrated in the west of England, in areas such as Bath, Somerset and south Gloucestershire, had connected 28,000 customers to its network as of last summer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Developments Are Shaping The NatWest Group LSE NWG Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</link><description>NatWest Group’s latest valuation update keeps fair value anchored at £6.63 while making only small tweaks to the inputs behind that number, including a slightly lower discount rate and unchanged revenue growth assumptions at around 6.28%. Together with full year 2025 guidance, recent deal discussions and a completed share buyback, these moves indicate that analysts are refining their models rather than rewriting the story. Stay with this article to see how you can track these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Assessing Lowe’s (LOW) Valuation After Barclays Upgrade And Housing Market Optimism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-lowe-low-valuation-barclays-121548071.html</link><description>Barclays' decision to raise its rating on Lowe's Companies (LOW) to overweight has refocused attention on the home improvement retailer, as investors weigh potential benefits from an improving housing market and possible pent up demand. See our latest analysis for Lowe's Companies. The latest move comes after a period of relatively steady share price gains, with a 90 day share price return of 5.31% and a 1 year total shareholder return of 2.10%. This suggests only modest momentum despite the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-lowe-low-valuation-barclays-121548071.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Hikes BofA (BAC) PT To $71 on Expectations of Sustained Earnings Momentum in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-hikes-bofa-bac-pt-141303263.html</link><description>Bank of America Corporation (NYSE:BAC) is one of the most buzzing stocks to invest in according to hedge funds. On January 5, Barclays raised the firm’s price target on Bank of America to $71 from $59 while maintaining an Overweight rating on the shares. As part of its 2026 sector forecast, Barclays updated its ratings […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-hikes-bofa-bac-pt-141303263.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet overtakes Apple as world's second-most-valuable company behind Nvidia</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-overtakes-apple-as-worlds-second-most-valuable-company-behind-nvidia-154751861.html</link><description>Alphabet notched a market capitalization of roughly $4 trillion on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-overtakes-apple-as-worlds-second-most-valuable-company-behind-nvidia-154751861.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] JPMorgan takes over Apple card, Paramount reaffirms WBD bid</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jpmorgan-takes-over-apple-card-160149117.html</link><description>Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman tracks several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including Goldman Sachs (GS) reaching a deal to sell its Apple credit card (AAPL) to JPMorgan Chase (JPM), Paramount Skydance (PSKY) reaffirming its offer to acquire Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD), and CrowdStrike's (CRWD) $740 million purchase of SGNL. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jpmorgan-takes-over-apple-card-160149117.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] JPMorgan takes over Apple card, Paramount reaffirms WBD bid</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jpmorgan-takes-over-apple-card-160149117.html</link><description>Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman tracks several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including Goldman Sachs (GS) reaching a deal to sell its Apple credit card (AAPL) to JPMorgan Chase (JPM), Paramount Skydance (PSKY) reaffirming its offer to acquire Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD), and CrowdStrike's (CRWD) $740 million purchase of SGNL. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jpmorgan-takes-over-apple-card-160149117.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Bets Identity Is The Next AI Risk</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-bets-identity-next-ai-165603257.html</link><description>Identity security takes center stage</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-bets-identity-next-ai-165603257.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Mortgage rates tick up, Alphabet's market cap overtakes Apple</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mortgage-rates-tick-alphabets-market-181016837.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance's John Hyland tracks today's top moving stocks and biggest market stories in this Market Minute, including the 30-year fixed rate mortgages ticking up to 6.16%, homebuilder stocks receiving downgrades due to headwinds tied to President Trump's policy proposals, and Alphabet's (GOOG, GOOGL) market cap overtaking Apple (AAPL) to become the second most valuable company in the world. Stay up to date on the latest market action, minute-by-minute, with&amp;nbsp;Yahoo Finance's Market Minute.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mortgage-rates-tick-alphabets-market-181016837.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to buy identity security startup SGNL for $740 million to tackle AI threats</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-buy-identity-security-startup-190902189.html</link><description>CrowdStrike said on Thursday it would buy identity security startup SGNL in a deal valued at $740 million ​aiming to enhance its cybersecurity tools to help customers counter artificial ‌intelligence-powered threats.  The cybersecurity company looks to benefit from SGNL's "continuous identity" technology to prevent hackers from exploiting ‌user identities as entry points for data theft with constant evaluations at a time when businesses are increasingly granting autonomous access to AI agents.  CrowdStrike entered the identity security market with its acquisition of Preempt Security in 2020.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-buy-identity-security-startup-190902189.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike To Acquire Identity Security Firm Amid Cybersecurity Platform Race</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/crowdstrike-stock-sgnl-acquisition-cybersecurity-platform-building-race/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>CrowdStrike announced the acquisition of identity security firm SGNL in a deal valued at about $740 million. CrowdStrike stock dipped on news.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/crowdstrike-stock-sgnl-acquisition-cybersecurity-platform-building-race/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Recent Shifts Are Reframing The Story For Equitable Holdings (EQH)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-shifts-reframing-story-equitable-211214767.html</link><description>Equitable Holdings has just seen a small reset to its fair value estimate, with the price target nudged from US$64.27 to US$64.00 per share as analysts fine tune their core valuation model. That tweak sits alongside a slightly higher discount rate and a modest uplift in expected revenue growth, reflecting a careful balance between stronger recent sector earnings and more cautious assumptions across insurance peers. Stay with this article to see how you can keep on top of these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-shifts-reframing-story-equitable-211214767.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Stock Declines While Market Improves: Some Information for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-stock-declines-224503955.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) concluded the recent trading session at $463.87, signifying a -3.14% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-stock-declines-224503955.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] This Cybersecurity Leader Is Poised to Capture a $300 Billion Market by 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/08/cybersecurity-leader-capture-300-billion-market/</link><description>This company is angling to dominate a $300 billion cybersecurity market by 2030 with its one-of-a-kind software.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/08/cybersecurity-leader-capture-300-billion-market/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Turns More Confident on Goldman Sachs (GS) as Bank Earnings Stay Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</link><description>The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) is included among the 12 Best DOW Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 5, Barclays raised its price target on The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) to $1,048 from $850 and kept an Overweight rating. The move followed updates across the large-cap bank group as part of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK Dividend Stocks To Consider For Your Portfolio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</link><description>The United Kingdom's FTSE 100 index has recently experienced a downturn, influenced by weak trade data from China and declining commodity prices, impacting several major companies within the index. In this challenging market environment, investors may find value in dividend stocks which can provide a steady income stream and potential stability amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to enhance AI-era identity security with SGNL acquisition</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</link><description>CrowdStrike aims to enhance its dynamic authorisation across cloud platforms by integrating SGNL's technology with the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Looking At The Cisco Systems (CSCO) Narrative As Networking And AI Redefine The Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</link><description>Cisco Systems’ latest fair value estimate has edged to US$85.43 from US$85.24, with the discount rate assumption now 8.32% versus 8.26% previously and long term revenue growth essentially unchanged at about 5.87%. These fine tuned inputs reflect how recent research is weighing solid networking execution and growing artificial intelligence related orders against questions about security and the durability of the product mix. Continue with this article to see how you can keep tracking these...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia’s Go-To Chipmaker TSMC Sees Revenue Top Estimates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-chipmaker-tsmc-sees-revenue-053720561.html</link><description>The go-to chipmaker for Nvidia Corp. reported a roughly 20% rise in December-quarter revenue to NT$1.05 trillion ($33.1 billion), based on calculations off monthly figures.  Shares in ASML Holding NV, which supplies chipmaking machines to TSMC, rose about 6% to a record high.  TSMC’s ADRs gained about 1% in premarket US trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-chipmaker-tsmc-sees-revenue-053720561.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading modestly higher as we get set to wrap up the first complete trading week of 2026, which could finish with a bang today. With market-moving data on the way this morning in the form of the December non-farm payrolls report, and a slew of economic reports plus the ... Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Dow Jones Futures Rise Before Jobs Data, Trump Tariffs Ruling; Oklo, Revolution Medicines Soar</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-small-caps-jobs-data-trump-tariffs-ruling/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The December jobs report and a possible Trump tariffs ruling loom. Oklo, Vistra, Revolution Medicines are early winners.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-small-caps-jobs-data-trump-tariffs-ruling/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays: Trump’s 2026 challenge is America First without market fallout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays said in a note to clients that President Trump has become a central driver of market sentiment only a week into 2026, as investors weigh his effort to balance “America First policies and affordability measures aimed at Main Street, without undermining Wall Street performance.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:06:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Gets Downgraded. The Chip Maker Still Has an Apple Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus  Apple  manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semiconductor Started 2nm Chip Production. Time to Buy?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/taiwan-semiconductor-started-2nm-chip-production-time-to-buy/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (NYSE:TSM) shares have been unstoppable in the past year, gaining more than 52%, thanks in part to a handful of incredible quarters. The big 2025 winner has what it takes to keep on winning in the new year, so say analysts over at JP Morgan. With 2nm chip production kicking off just ... Taiwan Semiconductor Started 2nm Chip Production. Time to Buy?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/taiwan-semiconductor-started-2nm-chip-production-time-to-buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] These Stocks Are Moving the Most Today: Oklo, Vistra, Rocket Cos., Opendoor, GM, Revolution Medicines, Tilray, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Vistra and Oklo surge after the nuclear energy companies unveil separate agreements to provide power to Meta Platforms in order to support the hyperscaler’s data center campus in Ohio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stocks to watch next week: JPMorgan, Goldman Sachs, TSMC, Persimmon and Vistry</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-goldman-sachs-tsmc-persimmon-vistry-stocks-to-watch-145906564.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-goldman-sachs-tsmc-persimmon-vistry-stocks-to-watch-145906564.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks to watch next week: JPMorgan, Goldman Sachs, TSMC, Persimmon and Vistry</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-goldman-sachs-tsmc-persimmon-vistry-stocks-to-watch-145906564.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-goldman-sachs-tsmc-persimmon-vistry-stocks-to-watch-145906564.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What Are 3 Great Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/what-are-3-great-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>Tech stocks look poised to lead the market again in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/what-are-3-great-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC Stock Rises After Bumper Sales. What That Says About a Potential AI Bubble.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-taiwan-semi-chip-sales-ai-bubble-5dc1377f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing stock has risen strongly on the AI boom and its latest sales figures should support the rally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-taiwan-semi-chip-sales-ai-bubble-5dc1377f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC Stock Rises After Posting Double-Digit December Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-stock-rises-posting-double-151419254.html</link><description>TSMC Stock Moves Higher on Strong Year-End Revenue Growth</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-stock-rises-posting-double-151419254.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel CEO Meets With Trump, Who Hails Chipmaker’s Progress</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-ceo-meets-trump-hails-155209165.html</link><description>In a post to his Truth Social network, Trump hailed what he called progress at Santa Clara, California-based Intel, whose shares are up more than 70% since plans emerged last year for the federal government to buy as much as 10% of the company.  “I just finished a great meeting with the very successful Intel CEO, Lip-Bu Tan,” Trump wrote.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-ceo-meets-trump-hails-155209165.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] JPM Raises PT on Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (TSM), Keeps a Buy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpm-raises-pt-taiwan-semiconductor-155431616.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) is one of the Best Unstoppable Growth Stocks to Buy Right Now. The share price of TSM rose more than 54% last year, and Wall Street sees further growth with an analyst 12-month price target suggesting around 10% upside from the current level. Recently, on December 7, JPMorgan raised […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpm-raises-pt-taiwan-semiconductor-155431616.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] These Stocks Are Moving the Most Today: Oklo, Vistra, Opendoor, Intel, GM, Revolution Medicines, Tilray, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks were rising modestly Friday after fresh jobs data showed U.S. unemployment ticked down in December and a potential Supreme Court ruling on tariffs failed to pan out.  Vistra  stock surged 14% and  Oklo  jumped 13% after the nuclear energy companies unveiled separate agreements to provide power to  Meta Platforms  in order to support the hyperscaler’s data center campus in Ohio.  Meta inched up 0.4%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] JPMorgan Stock, This AI Chip Leader Kick Off Earnings Season</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/jp-morgan-stock-taiwan-semiconductor-ai-stock-earnings-season/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan stock headlines a busy week of earnings reports in the financial sector. Results are also due from AI leader Taiwan Semiconductor.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/jp-morgan-stock-taiwan-semiconductor-ai-stock-earnings-season/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] JPMorgan Stock, This AI Chip Leader Kick Off Earnings Season</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/jp-morgan-stock-taiwan-semiconductor-ai-stock-earnings-season/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan stock headlines a busy week of earnings reports in the financial sector. Results are also due from AI leader Taiwan Semiconductor.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/jp-morgan-stock-taiwan-semiconductor-ai-stock-earnings-season/?src=A00220&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Corning (GLW)’s a “Potential Winner,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corning-glw-potential-winner-says-170348462.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Corning Incorporated (NYSE:GLW) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Corning Incorporated (NYSE:GLW) is a glassworks company with a presence in the data center, consumer electronics, and other industries. It performed well in 2025, and the shares are up by 84% over the past year. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corning-glw-potential-winner-says-170348462.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet (GOOGL) Has a Special Relationship With Apple, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-special-relationship-apple-170412043.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL)’s shares have gained 66% over the past year to solidify its lead as one of the largest technology companies in the world. Recently, debate has focused on the firm’s custom AI chips […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-special-relationship-apple-170412043.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says “Apple Deserves a Premium Multiple Given How Great It Is”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-apple-deserves-170635064.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Magnificent Seven stocks Jim Cramer recently reviewed. Cramer noted how the company proved the doubters wrong, as he remarked: “Apple’s next up… It only went up about 9% last year. This one’s different. Apple stock was beaten down in early 2025 because of the same worries we always […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-apple-deserves-170635064.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:06:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL)’s “the Winner With Gemini,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-winner-gemini-says-170715385.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)’s shares are up by a modest 7% over the past year. Throughout 2025, Cramer maintained an upbeat tone about the firm. He continues to believe that Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-winner-gemini-says-170715385.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:07:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says Insider Buying in Nike Signals “That the Business Is Indeed Turning”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-insider-buying-170738209.html</link><description>NIKE, Inc. (NYSE:NKE) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his takes on. Cramer discussed the insider buying in the stock, as he remarked: “Then there are the hope-spring-eternal buyers. I see a bunch of these stories, and I’m involved in some of them for the Charitable Trust, stocks like Nike, like Starbucks, which […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-insider-buying-170738209.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Rises After Trump Meeting as Markets Await Jobs Data</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rises-trump-meeting-markets-173050153.html</link><description>Chipmaker gains premarket; GM slides on $7.1B charge tied to EV pullback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rises-trump-meeting-markets-173050153.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] These Stocks Are Moving the Most Today: Oklo, Vistra, Opendoor, Intel, GM, Revolution Medicines, Tilray, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks were rising modestly Friday after fresh jobs data showed U.S. unemployment ticked down in December and a potential Supreme Court ruling on tariffs failed to pan out.  Vistra  stock surged 11% and  Oklo  jumped 9.3% after the nuclear energy companies unveiled separate agreements to provide power to  Meta Platforms  in order to support the hyperscaler’s data-center campus in Ohio.  UWM Holdings  and  Rocket Cos.  advanced 15% and 9.1%, respectively, as the mortgage lenders got a boost from President Donald Trump’s plan to buy $200 billion in mortgage bonds in a bid to make housing more affordable.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-16d62d29?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] XAI Limits Grok Images After Uproar Over Sexualized Content</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xai-limits-grok-images-uproar-175153383.html</link><description>As of Friday, Grok replied to users on the X that they’d need a paid subscription to generate and edit images.  The standalone Grok app, which operates separately from the social network, still allows users to generate pictures without subscribing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xai-limits-grok-images-uproar-175153383.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] xAI limits Grok images after uproar over sexualized content</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xai-limits-grok-images-uproar-175153383.html</link><description>As of Friday, Grok replied to users on the X that they’d need a paid subscription to generate and edit images.  The standalone Grok app, which operates separately from the social network, still allows users to generate pictures without subscribing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xai-limits-grok-images-uproar-175153383.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple CEO Pay Dips as Board Opposes China Audit</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ceo-pay-dips-board-175609175.html</link><description>Shareholders to weigh China supply-chain proposal at February meeting.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ceo-pay-dips-board-175609175.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] CIO survey ranks Microsoft and OpenAI as AI leaders, Apple in top 10</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Microsoft and OpenAI are viewed as the strongest artificial intelligence players among major technology vendors, according to Bernstein’s latest survey of 105 U.S. and European chief information officers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bells, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[0P00018XAR.L] The most popular stocks and funds investors bought in May</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</link><description>Signs of progress on US tariff deals in early May offered some reprieve around trade tensions, helping drive stock markets higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] CIO survey ranks Microsoft and OpenAI as AI leaders, Apple in top 10</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Microsoft and OpenAI are viewed as the strongest artificial intelligence players among major technology vendors, according to Bernstein’s latest survey of 105 U.S. and European chief information officers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva-backed altnet Truespeed in merger talks with rival</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</link><description>A fibre broadband network provider backed by an arm of Aviva, the FTSE-100 insurer, is in merger talks with a rival amid growing financial pressure on the heavily indebted industry.  Sky News has learnt that Truespeed, which has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, is in discussions about a tie-up with Freedom Fibre.  Truespeed, which is concentrated in the west of England, in areas such as Bath, Somerset and south Gloucestershire, had connected 28,000 customers to its network as of last summer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for January 7th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</link><description>AVVIY, CAE and CHMG have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on January 7th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] AI-driven inflation is 2026's most overlooked risk, investors say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</link><description>Global stock markets, riding high on AI euphoria at the start of 2026 may be disregarding one of the biggest threats that could spoil the party: a surge in inflation driven partly by the tech investment boom.  U.S. stock indexes, where seven tech groups ​contributed half of all market earnings this year, made double-digit gains in 2025 to hit record highs as exuberance about AI and monetary easing also propelled European and ‌Asian equities to record peaks.  Expectations for further rate cuts have buoyed bonds too, handing U.S. Treasury investors the best annual performance for five years as inflation retreated, although it remains above the Federal Reserve's average 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for December 31st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</link><description>ADM, AVVIY and EMN have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on December 31, 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for Dec. 24</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</link><description>AVTR, AVVIY and BAH have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on Dec.24, 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays: Trump’s 2026 challenge is America First without market fallout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays said in a note to clients that President Trump has become a central driver of market sentiment only a week into 2026, as investors weigh his effort to balance “America First policies and affordability measures aimed at Main Street, without undermining Wall Street performance.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Turns More Confident on Goldman Sachs (GS) as Bank Earnings Stay Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</link><description>The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) is included among the 12 Best DOW Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 5, Barclays raised its price target on The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) to $1,048 from $850 and kept an Overweight rating. The move followed updates across the large-cap bank group as part of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading modestly higher as we get set to wrap up the first complete trading week of 2026, which could finish with a bang today. With market-moving data on the way this morning in the form of the December non-farm payrolls report, and a slew of economic reports plus the ... Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to enhance AI-era identity security with SGNL acquisition</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</link><description>CrowdStrike aims to enhance its dynamic authorisation across cloud platforms by integrating SGNL's technology with the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Looking At The Cisco Systems (CSCO) Narrative As Networking And AI Redefine The Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</link><description>Cisco Systems’ latest fair value estimate has edged to US$85.43 from US$85.24, with the discount rate assumption now 8.32% versus 8.26% previously and long term revenue growth essentially unchanged at about 5.87%. These fine tuned inputs reflect how recent research is weighing solid networking execution and growing artificial intelligence related orders against questions about security and the durability of the product mix. Continue with this article to see how you can keep tracking these...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Why The Narrative Around HSBC Holdings LSE HSBA Is Shifting After Recent Analyst And Boardroom Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</link><description>HSBC Holdings’ latest price target work has not led to a shift in model fair value, which stays at £10.88 per share. Some of the building blocks behind that valuation have been fine tuned. The discount rate has edged down to 10.44% and revenue growth assumptions remain at 8.52%, reflecting how recent mixed research, capital allocation debates and boardroom headlines are feeding into a steadier rather than radically different narrative around the stock. Stay with this article to see how you...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] How Shifting Segment Margins Are Reshaping Siemens Valuation Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</link><description>Analysts have inched their fair value estimate for Siemens up from about €253 to roughly €255 per share, even as they trim their revenue growth outlook from approximately 6.28% to about 6.23% and nudge the discount rate down from around 5.84% to about 5.80%. This subtle recalibration reflects a more balanced view of Siemens' portfolio, where robust industrial automation is increasingly weighed against softer expectations for electrification and mobility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] What Analysts Think Is Shifting the Story for Alior Bank Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</link><description>Alior Bank's latest update reveals a slightly higher fair value of PLN 126.68 along with a modestly lower discount rate of 10.70%, reflecting a more finely balanced view of risk and reward. At the same time, analysts have pared back revenue growth expectations to 4.04%, signaling a more cautious stance despite improving fundamentals and capital strength. Investors can follow these shifts in fair value and risk assumptions as the bank's narrative continues to evolve. Analyst Price Targets...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Spotify Technology (SPOT) Experiences Soft Sentiment From Analysts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Best ADR Stocks to Invest In. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the best ADR stocks. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the largest audio streaming platforms in the world. On December 5th, Erste Group downgraded its shares to Hold from Buy and cited growth concerns as the reason. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] New Strong Buy Stocks for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</link><description>KVYO, MMS, CCBG, BAP and LGGNY have been added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Best Income Stocks to Buy for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</link><description>LGGNY, BAP and CCBG made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) income stocks list on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Did Legal &amp; General Group Plc (LON:LGEN) Use Debt To Deliver Its ROE Of 12%?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</link><description>Many investors are still learning about the various metrics that can be useful when analysing a stock. This article is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Insiders Continue to Buy Shares In Legal &amp; General Group</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</link><description>Those following along with Legal &amp; General Group Plc ( LON:LGEN ) will no doubt be intrigued by the recent purchase of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Legal &amp; General plots swoop for NatWest pensions arm Cushon</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</link><description>Legal &amp; General (L&amp;G) is plotting a swoop on the workplace pensions provider owned by NatWest Group, the FTSE-100 lender, as its chief executive seeks to grow its share of the UK retirement market.  Sky News has learnt that L&amp;G is among a handful of suitors which have expressed an interest in acquiring Cushon from NatWest.  This weekend, City sources said there was "significant" competition to buy the business and L&amp;G was not certain to be the eventual buyer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK Dividend Stocks To Consider For Your Portfolio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</link><description>The United Kingdom's FTSE 100 index has recently experienced a downturn, influenced by weak trade data from China and declining commodity prices, impacting several major companies within the index. In this challenging market environment, investors may find value in dividend stocks which can provide a steady income stream and potential stability amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank, Archax and Canton Network Complete UK’s First Gilt Purchase Using Tokenised Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</link><description>Lloyds Banking Group has completed a landmark digital finance transaction executing the first-ever Gilt purchase using tokenised deposits. The transaction, carried out in partnership with Archax and the Canton Network, marks the first time tokenised deposits have been issued on a public blockchain in the UK — and the first ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank completes UK’s first gilt purchase using tokenized deposits</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</link><description>Lloyds enlisted the help of Archax and Canton Network to carry out the transaction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Developments Are Shaping The NatWest Group LSE NWG Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</link><description>NatWest Group’s latest valuation update keeps fair value anchored at £6.63 while making only small tweaks to the inputs behind that number, including a slightly lower discount rate and unchanged revenue growth assumptions at around 6.28%. Together with full year 2025 guidance, recent deal discussions and a completed share buyback, these moves indicate that analysts are refining their models rather than rewriting the story. Stay with this article to see how you can track these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Goldman Sachs Sees New Drivers for European Banks, Adjusts NatWest (NWG) Stance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</link><description>NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) is included among the 15 Global Dividend Stocks to Diversify Your Portfolio. On December 4, Goldman Sachs downgraded NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) to Neutral from Buy. It lifted the price target to 685 GBp from 665 GBp. The change came as part of the firm’s 2026 outlook for European banks. Goldman […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bells, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[0P00018XAR.L] The most popular stocks and funds investors bought in May</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</link><description>Signs of progress on US tariff deals in early May offered some reprieve around trade tensions, helping drive stock markets higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] CIO survey ranks Microsoft and OpenAI as AI leaders, Apple in top 10</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Microsoft and OpenAI are viewed as the strongest artificial intelligence players among major technology vendors, according to Bernstein’s latest survey of 105 U.S. and European chief information officers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva-backed altnet Truespeed in merger talks with rival</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</link><description>A fibre broadband network provider backed by an arm of Aviva, the FTSE-100 insurer, is in merger talks with a rival amid growing financial pressure on the heavily indebted industry.  Sky News has learnt that Truespeed, which has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, is in discussions about a tie-up with Freedom Fibre.  Truespeed, which is concentrated in the west of England, in areas such as Bath, Somerset and south Gloucestershire, had connected 28,000 customers to its network as of last summer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for January 7th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</link><description>AVVIY, CAE and CHMG have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on January 7th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] AI-driven inflation is 2026's most overlooked risk, investors say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</link><description>Global stock markets, riding high on AI euphoria at the start of 2026 may be disregarding one of the biggest threats that could spoil the party: a surge in inflation driven partly by the tech investment boom.  U.S. stock indexes, where seven tech groups ​contributed half of all market earnings this year, made double-digit gains in 2025 to hit record highs as exuberance about AI and monetary easing also propelled European and ‌Asian equities to record peaks.  Expectations for further rate cuts have buoyed bonds too, handing U.S. Treasury investors the best annual performance for five years as inflation retreated, although it remains above the Federal Reserve's average 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for December 31st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</link><description>ADM, AVVIY and EMN have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on December 31, 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for Dec. 24</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</link><description>AVTR, AVVIY and BAH have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on Dec.24, 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays: Trump’s 2026 challenge is America First without market fallout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays said in a note to clients that President Trump has become a central driver of market sentiment only a week into 2026, as investors weigh his effort to balance “America First policies and affordability measures aimed at Main Street, without undermining Wall Street performance.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Turns More Confident on Goldman Sachs (GS) as Bank Earnings Stay Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</link><description>The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) is included among the 12 Best DOW Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 5, Barclays raised its price target on The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) to $1,048 from $850 and kept an Overweight rating. The move followed updates across the large-cap bank group as part of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading modestly higher as we get set to wrap up the first complete trading week of 2026, which could finish with a bang today. With market-moving data on the way this morning in the form of the December non-farm payrolls report, and a slew of economic reports plus the ... Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to enhance AI-era identity security with SGNL acquisition</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</link><description>CrowdStrike aims to enhance its dynamic authorisation across cloud platforms by integrating SGNL's technology with the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Looking At The Cisco Systems (CSCO) Narrative As Networking And AI Redefine The Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</link><description>Cisco Systems’ latest fair value estimate has edged to US$85.43 from US$85.24, with the discount rate assumption now 8.32% versus 8.26% previously and long term revenue growth essentially unchanged at about 5.87%. These fine tuned inputs reflect how recent research is weighing solid networking execution and growing artificial intelligence related orders against questions about security and the durability of the product mix. Continue with this article to see how you can keep tracking these...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Why The Narrative Around HSBC Holdings LSE HSBA Is Shifting After Recent Analyst And Boardroom Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</link><description>HSBC Holdings’ latest price target work has not led to a shift in model fair value, which stays at £10.88 per share. Some of the building blocks behind that valuation have been fine tuned. The discount rate has edged down to 10.44% and revenue growth assumptions remain at 8.52%, reflecting how recent mixed research, capital allocation debates and boardroom headlines are feeding into a steadier rather than radically different narrative around the stock. Stay with this article to see how you...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] How Shifting Segment Margins Are Reshaping Siemens Valuation Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</link><description>Analysts have inched their fair value estimate for Siemens up from about €253 to roughly €255 per share, even as they trim their revenue growth outlook from approximately 6.28% to about 6.23% and nudge the discount rate down from around 5.84% to about 5.80%. This subtle recalibration reflects a more balanced view of Siemens' portfolio, where robust industrial automation is increasingly weighed against softer expectations for electrification and mobility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] What Analysts Think Is Shifting the Story for Alior Bank Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</link><description>Alior Bank's latest update reveals a slightly higher fair value of PLN 126.68 along with a modestly lower discount rate of 10.70%, reflecting a more finely balanced view of risk and reward. At the same time, analysts have pared back revenue growth expectations to 4.04%, signaling a more cautious stance despite improving fundamentals and capital strength. Investors can follow these shifts in fair value and risk assumptions as the bank's narrative continues to evolve. Analyst Price Targets...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Spotify Technology (SPOT) Experiences Soft Sentiment From Analysts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Best ADR Stocks to Invest In. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the best ADR stocks. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the largest audio streaming platforms in the world. On December 5th, Erste Group downgraded its shares to Hold from Buy and cited growth concerns as the reason. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] New Strong Buy Stocks for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</link><description>KVYO, MMS, CCBG, BAP and LGGNY have been added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Best Income Stocks to Buy for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</link><description>LGGNY, BAP and CCBG made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) income stocks list on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Did Legal &amp; General Group Plc (LON:LGEN) Use Debt To Deliver Its ROE Of 12%?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</link><description>Many investors are still learning about the various metrics that can be useful when analysing a stock. This article is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Insiders Continue to Buy Shares In Legal &amp; General Group</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</link><description>Those following along with Legal &amp; General Group Plc ( LON:LGEN ) will no doubt be intrigued by the recent purchase of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Legal &amp; General plots swoop for NatWest pensions arm Cushon</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</link><description>Legal &amp; General (L&amp;G) is plotting a swoop on the workplace pensions provider owned by NatWest Group, the FTSE-100 lender, as its chief executive seeks to grow its share of the UK retirement market.  Sky News has learnt that L&amp;G is among a handful of suitors which have expressed an interest in acquiring Cushon from NatWest.  This weekend, City sources said there was "significant" competition to buy the business and L&amp;G was not certain to be the eventual buyer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK Dividend Stocks To Consider For Your Portfolio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</link><description>The United Kingdom's FTSE 100 index has recently experienced a downturn, influenced by weak trade data from China and declining commodity prices, impacting several major companies within the index. In this challenging market environment, investors may find value in dividend stocks which can provide a steady income stream and potential stability amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank, Archax and Canton Network Complete UK’s First Gilt Purchase Using Tokenised Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</link><description>Lloyds Banking Group has completed a landmark digital finance transaction executing the first-ever Gilt purchase using tokenised deposits. The transaction, carried out in partnership with Archax and the Canton Network, marks the first time tokenised deposits have been issued on a public blockchain in the UK — and the first ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank completes UK’s first gilt purchase using tokenized deposits</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</link><description>Lloyds enlisted the help of Archax and Canton Network to carry out the transaction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Developments Are Shaping The NatWest Group LSE NWG Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</link><description>NatWest Group’s latest valuation update keeps fair value anchored at £6.63 while making only small tweaks to the inputs behind that number, including a slightly lower discount rate and unchanged revenue growth assumptions at around 6.28%. Together with full year 2025 guidance, recent deal discussions and a completed share buyback, these moves indicate that analysts are refining their models rather than rewriting the story. Stay with this article to see how you can track these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Goldman Sachs Sees New Drivers for European Banks, Adjusts NatWest (NWG) Stance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</link><description>NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) is included among the 15 Global Dividend Stocks to Diversify Your Portfolio. On December 4, Goldman Sachs downgraded NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) to Neutral from Buy. It lifted the price target to 685 GBp from 665 GBp. The change came as part of the firm’s 2026 outlook for European banks. Goldman […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bells, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[0P00018XAR.L] The most popular stocks and funds investors bought in May</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</link><description>Signs of progress on US tariff deals in early May offered some reprieve around trade tensions, helping drive stock markets higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] CIO survey ranks Microsoft and OpenAI as AI leaders, Apple in top 10</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Microsoft and OpenAI are viewed as the strongest artificial intelligence players among major technology vendors, according to Bernstein’s latest survey of 105 U.S. and European chief information officers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva-backed altnet Truespeed in merger talks with rival</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</link><description>A fibre broadband network provider backed by an arm of Aviva, the FTSE-100 insurer, is in merger talks with a rival amid growing financial pressure on the heavily indebted industry.  Sky News has learnt that Truespeed, which has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, is in discussions about a tie-up with Freedom Fibre.  Truespeed, which is concentrated in the west of England, in areas such as Bath, Somerset and south Gloucestershire, had connected 28,000 customers to its network as of last summer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for January 7th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</link><description>AVVIY, CAE and CHMG have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on January 7th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] AI-driven inflation is 2026's most overlooked risk, investors say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</link><description>Global stock markets, riding high on AI euphoria at the start of 2026 may be disregarding one of the biggest threats that could spoil the party: a surge in inflation driven partly by the tech investment boom.  U.S. stock indexes, where seven tech groups ​contributed half of all market earnings this year, made double-digit gains in 2025 to hit record highs as exuberance about AI and monetary easing also propelled European and ‌Asian equities to record peaks.  Expectations for further rate cuts have buoyed bonds too, handing U.S. Treasury investors the best annual performance for five years as inflation retreated, although it remains above the Federal Reserve's average 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for December 31st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</link><description>ADM, AVVIY and EMN have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on December 31, 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for Dec. 24</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</link><description>AVTR, AVVIY and BAH have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on Dec.24, 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays: Trump’s 2026 challenge is America First without market fallout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays said in a note to clients that President Trump has become a central driver of market sentiment only a week into 2026, as investors weigh his effort to balance “America First policies and affordability measures aimed at Main Street, without undermining Wall Street performance.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Turns More Confident on Goldman Sachs (GS) as Bank Earnings Stay Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</link><description>The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) is included among the 12 Best DOW Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 5, Barclays raised its price target on The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) to $1,048 from $850 and kept an Overweight rating. The move followed updates across the large-cap bank group as part of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading modestly higher as we get set to wrap up the first complete trading week of 2026, which could finish with a bang today. With market-moving data on the way this morning in the form of the December non-farm payrolls report, and a slew of economic reports plus the ... Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to enhance AI-era identity security with SGNL acquisition</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</link><description>CrowdStrike aims to enhance its dynamic authorisation across cloud platforms by integrating SGNL's technology with the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Looking At The Cisco Systems (CSCO) Narrative As Networking And AI Redefine The Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</link><description>Cisco Systems’ latest fair value estimate has edged to US$85.43 from US$85.24, with the discount rate assumption now 8.32% versus 8.26% previously and long term revenue growth essentially unchanged at about 5.87%. These fine tuned inputs reflect how recent research is weighing solid networking execution and growing artificial intelligence related orders against questions about security and the durability of the product mix. Continue with this article to see how you can keep tracking these...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Why The Narrative Around HSBC Holdings LSE HSBA Is Shifting After Recent Analyst And Boardroom Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</link><description>HSBC Holdings’ latest price target work has not led to a shift in model fair value, which stays at £10.88 per share. Some of the building blocks behind that valuation have been fine tuned. The discount rate has edged down to 10.44% and revenue growth assumptions remain at 8.52%, reflecting how recent mixed research, capital allocation debates and boardroom headlines are feeding into a steadier rather than radically different narrative around the stock. Stay with this article to see how you...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] How Shifting Segment Margins Are Reshaping Siemens Valuation Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</link><description>Analysts have inched their fair value estimate for Siemens up from about €253 to roughly €255 per share, even as they trim their revenue growth outlook from approximately 6.28% to about 6.23% and nudge the discount rate down from around 5.84% to about 5.80%. This subtle recalibration reflects a more balanced view of Siemens' portfolio, where robust industrial automation is increasingly weighed against softer expectations for electrification and mobility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] What Analysts Think Is Shifting the Story for Alior Bank Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</link><description>Alior Bank's latest update reveals a slightly higher fair value of PLN 126.68 along with a modestly lower discount rate of 10.70%, reflecting a more finely balanced view of risk and reward. At the same time, analysts have pared back revenue growth expectations to 4.04%, signaling a more cautious stance despite improving fundamentals and capital strength. Investors can follow these shifts in fair value and risk assumptions as the bank's narrative continues to evolve. Analyst Price Targets...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Spotify Technology (SPOT) Experiences Soft Sentiment From Analysts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Best ADR Stocks to Invest In. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the best ADR stocks. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the largest audio streaming platforms in the world. On December 5th, Erste Group downgraded its shares to Hold from Buy and cited growth concerns as the reason. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] New Strong Buy Stocks for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</link><description>KVYO, MMS, CCBG, BAP and LGGNY have been added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Best Income Stocks to Buy for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</link><description>LGGNY, BAP and CCBG made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) income stocks list on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Did Legal &amp; General Group Plc (LON:LGEN) Use Debt To Deliver Its ROE Of 12%?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</link><description>Many investors are still learning about the various metrics that can be useful when analysing a stock. This article is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Insiders Continue to Buy Shares In Legal &amp; General Group</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</link><description>Those following along with Legal &amp; General Group Plc ( LON:LGEN ) will no doubt be intrigued by the recent purchase of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Legal &amp; General plots swoop for NatWest pensions arm Cushon</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</link><description>Legal &amp; General (L&amp;G) is plotting a swoop on the workplace pensions provider owned by NatWest Group, the FTSE-100 lender, as its chief executive seeks to grow its share of the UK retirement market.  Sky News has learnt that L&amp;G is among a handful of suitors which have expressed an interest in acquiring Cushon from NatWest.  This weekend, City sources said there was "significant" competition to buy the business and L&amp;G was not certain to be the eventual buyer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK Dividend Stocks To Consider For Your Portfolio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</link><description>The United Kingdom's FTSE 100 index has recently experienced a downturn, influenced by weak trade data from China and declining commodity prices, impacting several major companies within the index. In this challenging market environment, investors may find value in dividend stocks which can provide a steady income stream and potential stability amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank, Archax and Canton Network Complete UK’s First Gilt Purchase Using Tokenised Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</link><description>Lloyds Banking Group has completed a landmark digital finance transaction executing the first-ever Gilt purchase using tokenised deposits. The transaction, carried out in partnership with Archax and the Canton Network, marks the first time tokenised deposits have been issued on a public blockchain in the UK — and the first ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank completes UK’s first gilt purchase using tokenized deposits</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</link><description>Lloyds enlisted the help of Archax and Canton Network to carry out the transaction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Developments Are Shaping The NatWest Group LSE NWG Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</link><description>NatWest Group’s latest valuation update keeps fair value anchored at £6.63 while making only small tweaks to the inputs behind that number, including a slightly lower discount rate and unchanged revenue growth assumptions at around 6.28%. Together with full year 2025 guidance, recent deal discussions and a completed share buyback, these moves indicate that analysts are refining their models rather than rewriting the story. Stay with this article to see how you can track these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Goldman Sachs Sees New Drivers for European Banks, Adjusts NatWest (NWG) Stance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</link><description>NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) is included among the 15 Global Dividend Stocks to Diversify Your Portfolio. On December 4, Goldman Sachs downgraded NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) to Neutral from Buy. It lifted the price target to 685 GBp from 665 GBp. The change came as part of the firm’s 2026 outlook for European banks. Goldman […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bells, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[0P00018XAR.L] The most popular stocks and funds investors bought in May</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</link><description>Signs of progress on US tariff deals in early May offered some reprieve around trade tensions, helping drive stock markets higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] CIO survey ranks Microsoft and OpenAI as AI leaders, Apple in top 10</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Microsoft and OpenAI are viewed as the strongest artificial intelligence players among major technology vendors, according to Bernstein’s latest survey of 105 U.S. and European chief information officers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva-backed altnet Truespeed in merger talks with rival</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</link><description>A fibre broadband network provider backed by an arm of Aviva, the FTSE-100 insurer, is in merger talks with a rival amid growing financial pressure on the heavily indebted industry.  Sky News has learnt that Truespeed, which has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, is in discussions about a tie-up with Freedom Fibre.  Truespeed, which is concentrated in the west of England, in areas such as Bath, Somerset and south Gloucestershire, had connected 28,000 customers to its network as of last summer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for January 7th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</link><description>AVVIY, CAE and CHMG have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on January 7th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] AI-driven inflation is 2026's most overlooked risk, investors say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</link><description>Global stock markets, riding high on AI euphoria at the start of 2026 may be disregarding one of the biggest threats that could spoil the party: a surge in inflation driven partly by the tech investment boom.  U.S. stock indexes, where seven tech groups ​contributed half of all market earnings this year, made double-digit gains in 2025 to hit record highs as exuberance about AI and monetary easing also propelled European and ‌Asian equities to record peaks.  Expectations for further rate cuts have buoyed bonds too, handing U.S. Treasury investors the best annual performance for five years as inflation retreated, although it remains above the Federal Reserve's average 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for December 31st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</link><description>ADM, AVVIY and EMN have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on December 31, 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for Dec. 24</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</link><description>AVTR, AVVIY and BAH have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on Dec.24, 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays: Trump’s 2026 challenge is America First without market fallout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays said in a note to clients that President Trump has become a central driver of market sentiment only a week into 2026, as investors weigh his effort to balance “America First policies and affordability measures aimed at Main Street, without undermining Wall Street performance.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Turns More Confident on Goldman Sachs (GS) as Bank Earnings Stay Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</link><description>The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) is included among the 12 Best DOW Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 5, Barclays raised its price target on The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) to $1,048 from $850 and kept an Overweight rating. The move followed updates across the large-cap bank group as part of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading modestly higher as we get set to wrap up the first complete trading week of 2026, which could finish with a bang today. With market-moving data on the way this morning in the form of the December non-farm payrolls report, and a slew of economic reports plus the ... Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to enhance AI-era identity security with SGNL acquisition</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</link><description>CrowdStrike aims to enhance its dynamic authorisation across cloud platforms by integrating SGNL's technology with the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Looking At The Cisco Systems (CSCO) Narrative As Networking And AI Redefine The Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</link><description>Cisco Systems’ latest fair value estimate has edged to US$85.43 from US$85.24, with the discount rate assumption now 8.32% versus 8.26% previously and long term revenue growth essentially unchanged at about 5.87%. These fine tuned inputs reflect how recent research is weighing solid networking execution and growing artificial intelligence related orders against questions about security and the durability of the product mix. Continue with this article to see how you can keep tracking these...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Why The Narrative Around HSBC Holdings LSE HSBA Is Shifting After Recent Analyst And Boardroom Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</link><description>HSBC Holdings’ latest price target work has not led to a shift in model fair value, which stays at £10.88 per share. Some of the building blocks behind that valuation have been fine tuned. The discount rate has edged down to 10.44% and revenue growth assumptions remain at 8.52%, reflecting how recent mixed research, capital allocation debates and boardroom headlines are feeding into a steadier rather than radically different narrative around the stock. Stay with this article to see how you...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] How Shifting Segment Margins Are Reshaping Siemens Valuation Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</link><description>Analysts have inched their fair value estimate for Siemens up from about €253 to roughly €255 per share, even as they trim their revenue growth outlook from approximately 6.28% to about 6.23% and nudge the discount rate down from around 5.84% to about 5.80%. This subtle recalibration reflects a more balanced view of Siemens' portfolio, where robust industrial automation is increasingly weighed against softer expectations for electrification and mobility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] What Analysts Think Is Shifting the Story for Alior Bank Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</link><description>Alior Bank's latest update reveals a slightly higher fair value of PLN 126.68 along with a modestly lower discount rate of 10.70%, reflecting a more finely balanced view of risk and reward. At the same time, analysts have pared back revenue growth expectations to 4.04%, signaling a more cautious stance despite improving fundamentals and capital strength. Investors can follow these shifts in fair value and risk assumptions as the bank's narrative continues to evolve. Analyst Price Targets...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Spotify Technology (SPOT) Experiences Soft Sentiment From Analysts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Best ADR Stocks to Invest In. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the best ADR stocks. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the largest audio streaming platforms in the world. On December 5th, Erste Group downgraded its shares to Hold from Buy and cited growth concerns as the reason. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] New Strong Buy Stocks for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</link><description>KVYO, MMS, CCBG, BAP and LGGNY have been added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Best Income Stocks to Buy for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</link><description>LGGNY, BAP and CCBG made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) income stocks list on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Did Legal &amp; General Group Plc (LON:LGEN) Use Debt To Deliver Its ROE Of 12%?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</link><description>Many investors are still learning about the various metrics that can be useful when analysing a stock. This article is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Insiders Continue to Buy Shares In Legal &amp; General Group</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</link><description>Those following along with Legal &amp; General Group Plc ( LON:LGEN ) will no doubt be intrigued by the recent purchase of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Legal &amp; General plots swoop for NatWest pensions arm Cushon</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</link><description>Legal &amp; General (L&amp;G) is plotting a swoop on the workplace pensions provider owned by NatWest Group, the FTSE-100 lender, as its chief executive seeks to grow its share of the UK retirement market.  Sky News has learnt that L&amp;G is among a handful of suitors which have expressed an interest in acquiring Cushon from NatWest.  This weekend, City sources said there was "significant" competition to buy the business and L&amp;G was not certain to be the eventual buyer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK Dividend Stocks To Consider For Your Portfolio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</link><description>The United Kingdom's FTSE 100 index has recently experienced a downturn, influenced by weak trade data from China and declining commodity prices, impacting several major companies within the index. In this challenging market environment, investors may find value in dividend stocks which can provide a steady income stream and potential stability amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank, Archax and Canton Network Complete UK’s First Gilt Purchase Using Tokenised Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</link><description>Lloyds Banking Group has completed a landmark digital finance transaction executing the first-ever Gilt purchase using tokenised deposits. The transaction, carried out in partnership with Archax and the Canton Network, marks the first time tokenised deposits have been issued on a public blockchain in the UK — and the first ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank completes UK’s first gilt purchase using tokenized deposits</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</link><description>Lloyds enlisted the help of Archax and Canton Network to carry out the transaction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Developments Are Shaping The NatWest Group LSE NWG Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</link><description>NatWest Group’s latest valuation update keeps fair value anchored at £6.63 while making only small tweaks to the inputs behind that number, including a slightly lower discount rate and unchanged revenue growth assumptions at around 6.28%. Together with full year 2025 guidance, recent deal discussions and a completed share buyback, these moves indicate that analysts are refining their models rather than rewriting the story. Stay with this article to see how you can track these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Goldman Sachs Sees New Drivers for European Banks, Adjusts NatWest (NWG) Stance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</link><description>NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) is included among the 15 Global Dividend Stocks to Diversify Your Portfolio. On December 4, Goldman Sachs downgraded NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) to Neutral from Buy. It lifted the price target to 685 GBp from 665 GBp. The change came as part of the firm’s 2026 outlook for European banks. Goldman […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bells, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[0P00018XAR.L] The most popular stocks and funds investors bought in May</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</link><description>Signs of progress on US tariff deals in early May offered some reprieve around trade tensions, helping drive stock markets higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-bought-popular-stocks-funds-may-080435623.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jamie Dimon's Grip On US Credit Card Dominance Grows As JPMorgan Wins Apple Card Business From Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) has chosen JPMorgan Chase (NYSE:JPM) as the new issuer of the Apple Card, ending Goldman Sachs' (NYSE:GS) role in a move that significantly reshapes the consumer finance ambitions of all three companies. JPMorgan Chase Takes Over Apple Card From Goldman Sachs On Wednesday, JPMorgan Chase announced that it has reached an agreement with Apple to become the new issuer of the Apple Card, replacing Goldman Sachs. The deal expands the largest U.S. bank's already massive credit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimons-grip-us-credit-193113884.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Qualcomm Stock Falls After Downgrade. The Apple Supplier Has an iPhone Problem.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Qualcomm  shares have had a strong start to the year but a decline in spending from longtime customer  Apple  could knock the chip maker off course, according to analysts at  Mizuho  Securities.  The firm downgraded Qualcomm stock to Neutral from Outperform and lowered its price target to $175 from $200 in a research note Friday.  A weak smartphone market, plus Apple manufacturing more components in-house, could weigh on the company over the next few years, Mizuho argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/qualcomm-stock-downgrade-apple-a8d9d429?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock Set to Break Brutal Losing Streak. Why It Remains Evercore’s ‘Top Pick.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company is at risk of extending its losing run to eight sessions, but analysts at Evercore ISI remain bullish on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-stock-is-on-a-brutal-losing-streak-why-evercore-is-upbeat-a622245e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] CIO survey ranks Microsoft and OpenAI as AI leaders, Apple in top 10</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Microsoft and OpenAI are viewed as the strongest artificial intelligence players among major technology vendors, according to Bernstein’s latest survey of 105 U.S. and European chief information officers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cio-survey-ranks-microsoft-openai-180752661.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva-backed altnet Truespeed in merger talks with rival</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</link><description>A fibre broadband network provider backed by an arm of Aviva, the FTSE-100 insurer, is in merger talks with a rival amid growing financial pressure on the heavily indebted industry.  Sky News has learnt that Truespeed, which has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, is in discussions about a tie-up with Freedom Fibre.  Truespeed, which is concentrated in the west of England, in areas such as Bath, Somerset and south Gloucestershire, had connected 28,000 customers to its network as of last summer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-backed-altnet-truespeed-merger-101800100.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for January 7th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</link><description>AVVIY, CAE and CHMG have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on January 7th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-january-7th-094800108.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] AI-driven inflation is 2026's most overlooked risk, investors say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</link><description>Global stock markets, riding high on AI euphoria at the start of 2026 may be disregarding one of the biggest threats that could spoil the party: a surge in inflation driven partly by the tech investment boom.  U.S. stock indexes, where seven tech groups ​contributed half of all market earnings this year, made double-digit gains in 2025 to hit record highs as exuberance about AI and monetary easing also propelled European and ‌Asian equities to record peaks.  Expectations for further rate cuts have buoyed bonds too, handing U.S. Treasury investors the best annual performance for five years as inflation retreated, although it remains above the Federal Reserve's average 2% target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysis-ai-driven-inflation-2026s-060212201.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for December 31st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</link><description>ADM, AVVIY and EMN have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on December 31, 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-december-31st-072800317.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] New Strong Sell Stocks for Dec. 24</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</link><description>AVTR, AVVIY and BAH have been added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List on Dec.24, 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-sell-stocks-dec-24-093200509.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays: Trump’s 2026 challenge is America First without market fallout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays said in a note to clients that President Trump has become a central driver of market sentiment only a week into 2026, as investors weigh his effort to balance “America First policies and affordability measures aimed at Main Street, without undermining Wall Street performance.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-trump-2026-challenge-america-130608575.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Turns More Confident on Goldman Sachs (GS) as Bank Earnings Stay Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</link><description>The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) is included among the 12 Best DOW Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 5, Barclays raised its price target on The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. (NYSE:GS) to $1,048 from $850 and kept an Overweight rating. The move followed updates across the large-cap bank group as part of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-turns-more-confident-goldman-231606152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading modestly higher as we get set to wrap up the first complete trading week of 2026, which could finish with a bang today. With market-moving data on the way this morning in the form of the December non-farm payrolls report, and a slew of economic reports plus the ... Here Are Friday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Adobe, Airbnb, Altria, CrowdStrike, GE Vernova, Flutter Entertainment, Robinhood, Southwest Airlines, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/here-are-fridays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-adobe-airbnb-altria-crowdstrike-ge-vernova-flutter-entertainment-robinhood-southwest-airlines-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to enhance AI-era identity security with SGNL acquisition</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</link><description>CrowdStrike aims to enhance its dynamic authorisation across cloud platforms by integrating SGNL's technology with the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Looking At The Cisco Systems (CSCO) Narrative As Networking And AI Redefine The Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</link><description>Cisco Systems’ latest fair value estimate has edged to US$85.43 from US$85.24, with the discount rate assumption now 8.32% versus 8.26% previously and long term revenue growth essentially unchanged at about 5.87%. These fine tuned inputs reflect how recent research is weighing solid networking execution and growing artificial intelligence related orders against questions about security and the durability of the product mix. Continue with this article to see how you can keep tracking these...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-cisco-systems-csco-narrative-120930917.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Why The Narrative Around HSBC Holdings LSE HSBA Is Shifting After Recent Analyst And Boardroom Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</link><description>HSBC Holdings’ latest price target work has not led to a shift in model fair value, which stays at £10.88 per share. Some of the building blocks behind that valuation have been fine tuned. The discount rate has edged down to 10.44% and revenue growth assumptions remain at 8.52%, reflecting how recent mixed research, capital allocation debates and boardroom headlines are feeding into a steadier rather than radically different narrative around the stock. Stay with this article to see how you...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-narrative-around-hsbc-holdings-180408825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] How Shifting Segment Margins Are Reshaping Siemens Valuation Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</link><description>Analysts have inched their fair value estimate for Siemens up from about €253 to roughly €255 per share, even as they trim their revenue growth outlook from approximately 6.28% to about 6.23% and nudge the discount rate down from around 5.84% to about 5.80%. This subtle recalibration reflects a more balanced view of Siemens' portfolio, where robust industrial automation is increasingly weighed against softer expectations for electrification and mobility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shifting-segment-margins-reshaping-siemens-231307496.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] What Analysts Think Is Shifting the Story for Alior Bank Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</link><description>Alior Bank's latest update reveals a slightly higher fair value of PLN 126.68 along with a modestly lower discount rate of 10.70%, reflecting a more finely balanced view of risk and reward. At the same time, analysts have pared back revenue growth expectations to 4.04%, signaling a more cautious stance despite improving fundamentals and capital strength. Investors can follow these shifts in fair value and risk assumptions as the bank's narrative continues to evolve. Analyst Price Targets...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-think-shifting-story-alior-130634333.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Spotify Technology (SPOT) Experiences Soft Sentiment From Analysts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Best ADR Stocks to Invest In. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the best ADR stocks. Spotify Technology S.A. (NYSE:SPOT) is one of the largest audio streaming platforms in the world. On December 5th, Erste Group downgraded its shares to Hold from Buy and cited growth concerns as the reason. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-technology-spot-experiences-soft-123505676.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] New Strong Buy Stocks for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</link><description>KVYO, MMS, CCBG, BAP and LGGNY have been added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-buy-stocks-january-5th-120800357.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Best Income Stocks to Buy for January 5th</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</link><description>LGGNY, BAP and CCBG made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) income stocks list on January 5th, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-income-stocks-buy-january-110100632.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Did Legal &amp; General Group Plc (LON:LGEN) Use Debt To Deliver Its ROE Of 12%?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</link><description>Many investors are still learning about the various metrics that can be useful when analysing a stock. This article is...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-legal-general-group-plc-052936825.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Insiders Continue to Buy Shares In Legal &amp; General Group</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</link><description>Those following along with Legal &amp; General Group Plc ( LON:LGEN ) will no doubt be intrigued by the recent purchase of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-spends-uk-974k-buying-052820724.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LGEN.L] Legal &amp; General plots swoop for NatWest pensions arm Cushon</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</link><description>Legal &amp; General (L&amp;G) is plotting a swoop on the workplace pensions provider owned by NatWest Group, the FTSE-100 lender, as its chief executive seeks to grow its share of the UK retirement market.  Sky News has learnt that L&amp;G is among a handful of suitors which have expressed an interest in acquiring Cushon from NatWest.  This weekend, City sources said there was "significant" competition to buy the business and L&amp;G was not certain to be the eventual buyer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-general-plots-swoop-natwest-100100048.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK Dividend Stocks To Consider For Your Portfolio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</link><description>The United Kingdom's FTSE 100 index has recently experienced a downturn, influenced by weak trade data from China and declining commodity prices, impacting several major companies within the index. In this challenging market environment, investors may find value in dividend stocks which can provide a steady income stream and potential stability amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-dividend-stocks-consider-portfolio-063152802.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank, Archax and Canton Network Complete UK’s First Gilt Purchase Using Tokenised Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</link><description>Lloyds Banking Group has completed a landmark digital finance transaction executing the first-ever Gilt purchase using tokenised deposits. The transaction, carried out in partnership with Archax and the Canton Network, marks the first time tokenised deposits have been issued on a public blockchain in the UK — and the first ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/lloyds-bank-archax-and-canton-network-complete-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenised-deposits/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds Bank completes UK’s first gilt purchase using tokenized deposits</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</link><description>Lloyds enlisted the help of Archax and Canton Network to carry out the transaction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/business/2026/01/07/lloyds-bank-completes-uk-s-first-gilt-purchase-using-tokenized-deposits</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best savings account deals for 2026</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</link><description>Check the best savings accounts to find a top-rated deal that works for you.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-savings-accounts-deals-inflation-rates-130148742.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] How Recent Developments Are Shaping The NatWest Group LSE NWG Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</link><description>NatWest Group’s latest valuation update keeps fair value anchored at £6.63 while making only small tweaks to the inputs behind that number, including a slightly lower discount rate and unchanged revenue growth assumptions at around 6.28%. Together with full year 2025 guidance, recent deal discussions and a completed share buyback, these moves indicate that analysts are refining their models rather than rewriting the story. Stay with this article to see how you can track these kinds of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-developments-shaping-natwest-group-121324116.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] UK mortgage rates unlikely to fall much further despite expected interest rate cuts</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-bank-of-england-115823340.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Best credit card deals of the week</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</link><description>Discover the best credit cards to save money, earn rewards and travel smarter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/best-credit-card-deals-093401129.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWG.L] Goldman Sachs Sees New Drivers for European Banks, Adjusts NatWest (NWG) Stance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</link><description>NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) is included among the 15 Global Dividend Stocks to Diversify Your Portfolio. On December 4, Goldman Sachs downgraded NatWest Group plc (NYSE:NWG) to Neutral from Buy. It lifted the price target to 685 GBp from 665 GBp. The change came as part of the firm’s 2026 outlook for European banks. Goldman […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-sees-drivers-european-075000722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bells, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>