<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] YouTuber MKBHD Hails Tesla Model Y Performance, Calls EV Giant's Self-Driving Technology 'The Best'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</link><description>YouTuber Marques Brownlee, aka MKBHD, has shared his thoughts on the Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) Model Y Performance trim, as well as the company's self-driving technology. Tesla Self-Driving Is The Best Ever, MKBHD Says The YouTuber, in a review of the Model Y Performance on Thursday, hailed the crossover's software on the 16-inch touchscreen infotainment display, which is also a real-time representation of the car. "This is the best software in a car that is not Android Auto or Apple CarPlay," bo</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bank of America revamps Alphabet stock after Google enters two key partnerships</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</link><description>Investors are taking a fresh look at Google, as new partnerships tied to its Gemini models help push the stock higher. On Jan. 11, Google and Walmart (WMT) said they plan to roll out a new shopping experience inside Google’s Gemini chatbot, highlighting a potential new revenue path for Google. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s (AAPL) AI Roadmap Strengthens With Google Deal, Says Evercore</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-roadmap-strengthens-174853486.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Hot AI Stocks to Keep on Your Radar. On January 12, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $330.00 price target. Firm analysts highlight Apple’s new AI partnership with Google Gemini, citing monetization upside and custom AI experiences ahead. The firm […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-roadmap-strengthens-174853486.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] KeyBanc Turns Bullish on Intel (INTC), Citing Server CPU Tightness and Foundry Yield Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-turns-bullish-intel-intc-173853702.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the Trending AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 13, KeyBanc analyst John Vinh upgraded the stock from Sector Weight to Overweight with a price target of $60.00. Firm analysts see improving foundry yield gains and robust hyperscaler-driven data center demand. Despite several headwinds in the server CPU market, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-turns-bullish-intel-intc-173853702.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] TSMC Says 'No More' To Nvidia: Why That Is Intel's Golden Ticket</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-says-no-more-nvidia-161151468.html</link><description>The AI boom just hit a constraint investors don't talk about enough: you can't ship what you can't build. Demand for AI chips is still surging, but the world's leading foundry, Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd (NYSE:TSM), or TSMC, is starting to run out of room. That matters — because when supply, not demand, becomes the bottleneck, the entire power structure of the AI trade begins to shift. When The Kingmaker Runs Out Of Capacity According to a report first published by The Information</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-says-no-more-nvidia-161151468.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Investors Worried About Large Cap Concentration Risk Have a Great Option in MDY</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/investors-worried-about-large-cap-concentration-risk-have-a-great-option-in-mdy/</link><description>The SPDR S&amp;amp;P 500 ETF Trust (NYSEARCA:SPY) tells a story of increasing concentration. The S&amp;amp;P 500 has become a technology-dominated index, with information technology representing over a third of its weight. This concentration intensifies at the top, where just three mega-cap tech companies control more than a fifth of the entire index’s value—creating a portfolio ... Investors Worried About Large Cap Concentration Risk Have a Great Option in MDY</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/investors-worried-about-large-cap-concentration-risk-have-a-great-option-in-mdy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Wall Street Is Starting to Like Intel Stock Again</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/wall-street-is-starting-to-like-intel-stock-again/</link><description>The once-hated stock is starting to win some fans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/wall-street-is-starting-to-like-intel-stock-again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] As Trump's deadline for a cap on credit card rates looms, banks have only questions and no answers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-deadline-cap-credit-card-134909277.html</link><description>President Donald Trump a week ago told the credit card industry it had until Jan. 20 to comply with his demand for a 10% cap on interest rates.  With just days to go, consumer groups, politicians, and bankers alike remain unclear on what the White House has planned and whether Trump even remains serious about the idea.  White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt said the president has “an expectation” that credit card companies will accede to his demand that they cap interest rates on credit cards at 10%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-deadline-cap-credit-card-134909277.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Insiders Sold US$23m Of Shares Suggesting Hesitancy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-insiders-sold-us-23m-130031482.html</link><description>Many Apple Inc. ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) insiders ditched their stock over the past year, which may be of interest to the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-insiders-sold-us-23m-130031482.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: Nvidia Will Become the First $6 Trillion Company in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-nvidia-will-become-the-first-6-trillion/</link><description>High demand marches on for Nvidia's AI products and services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-nvidia-will-become-the-first-6-trillion/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The 1 Vanguard ETF That Warren Buffett's Recent Remarks Suggest He Would Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-vanguard-etf-warren-buffett-recent-remarks/</link><description>There's one Vanguard bond ETF that Buffett would love.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-vanguard-etf-warren-buffett-recent-remarks/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 Quantum Computing Stocks That Could Make a Millionaire</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/2-quantum-computing-stocks-that-could-make-a-milli/</link><description>These players may help you along the path to wealth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/2-quantum-computing-stocks-that-could-make-a-milli/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Nvidia and Buys 2 Other Magnificent Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks Instead</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-nvidia-and/</link><description>Peter Thiel recently sold his stake in Nvidia and rotated capital into Apple and Microsoft.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-nvidia-and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Does a $21 Million Exit Amid a 43% Drop in Share Prices Raise Questions About This Packaging Stock?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/16/does-a-usd21-million-exit-amid-a-43-drop-in-share-prices-raise-questions-about-this-packaging-stock/</link><description>Graphic Packaging provides fiber-based packaging for food, beverage, and consumer goods firms, emphasizing sustainable solutions worldwide.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/16/does-a-usd21-million-exit-amid-a-43-drop-in-share-prices-raise-questions-about-this-packaging-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Assessing Barclays (LSE:BARC) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-barclays-lse-barc-valuation-010935217.html</link><description>What Barclays’ recent performance data tells you right now Barclays (LSE:BARC) has drawn attention after a period of strong share price moves, with a 1-year total return of 73.47% and a past 3-month total return of 36.65%. This has prompted fresh interest in its valuation. See our latest analysis for Barclays. Recent trading suggests momentum is building, with a 30 day share price return of 6.72% and a 90 day share price return of 36.65%. The 1 year total shareholder return of 73.47%, along...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-barclays-lse-barc-valuation-010935217.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>