<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Nvidia vs. Alphabet: Which Is the Better AI Growth Stock for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidia-vs-alphabet-which-is-the-better-ai-growth-s/</link><description>Both companies are riding the AI wave, but one stock offers a better mix of growth momentum and valuation today.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidia-vs-alphabet-which-is-the-better-ai-growth-s/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] A Look At monday.com (MNDY) Valuation After Barclays Target Cut And Revenue Guidance Concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/look-monday-com-mndy-valuation-021624640.html</link><description>monday.com (MNDY) has drawn fresh attention after Barclays cut its price target, citing softer revenue guidance that fell short of expectations and coincided with a single-day drop of about 5%. See our latest analysis for monday.com. The recent 6.39% one day share price decline and 13.72% 30 day share price return extend a weaker trend, with a 26.34% 90 day share price pullback and a 44.34% 1 year total shareholder return loss suggesting fading momentum despite a modestly positive 3 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/look-monday-com-mndy-valuation-021624640.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Review &amp; Preview: Not So Magnificent</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-today-rotation-mag-7-selloff-318554f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>FEATURE S&amp;amp;P 493. A wave of selling in technology stocks overshadowed an otherwise decent day on Wall Street. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1%. The S&amp;amp;P 500 fell 0.5%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 42 points, or 0.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-today-rotation-mag-7-selloff-318554f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today, Jan. 14: Intel Jumps on Sold Out 2026 Server CPU Capacity</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/14/stock-market-today-jan-14-intel-jumps-on-sold-out-2026-server-cpu-capacity/</link><description>On Jan. 14, 2026, investors weighed fresh AI server demand signals and foundry wins that sharpen the stakes of Intel’s turnaround.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/14/stock-market-today-jan-14-intel-jumps-on-sold-out-2026-server-cpu-capacity/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here's Why CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Fell More Than Broader Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-224503871.html</link><description>In the closing of the recent trading day, CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) stood at $460.63, denoting a -1.58% move from the preceding trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-224503871.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] TSMC likely to post fourth-quarter profit leap driven by AI boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-221545201.html</link><description>TAIPEI, Jan 15 () - TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 28% jump in fourth-quarter net profit to a ​record high on Thursday driven by ongoing strong demand for AI infrastructure. Taiwan Semiconductor ‌Manufacturing Co, the world's top contract chipmaker and a key supplier to Nvidia and Apple, is forecast to report a ‌net profit of T$479.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-221545201.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Top Research Reports for AbbVie, Intel &amp; Boeing</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-research-reports-abbvie-intel-215500484.html</link><description>Today's Research Daily features new research reports on 16 major stocks, including AbbVie Inc. (ABBV), Intel Corp. (INTC) and The Boeing Company (BA), as well as a micro-cap stock Tandy Leather Factory, Inc. (TLF).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-research-reports-abbvie-intel-215500484.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Apple's AI partnership with Google a major loss for OpenAI?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-ai-partnership-google-major-214700767.html</link><description>OpenAI (OPAI.PVT) is reportedly taking early steps to go public, according to the New York Times, setting up 2026 to be the "Year of the Mega IPO." While co-founder and CEO Sam Altman is "zero percent" interested in leading a public company, he stated that OpenAI needed to continue raising more funds. Yahoo Finance Tech and Markets Reporter Laura Bratton comes on Market Domination Overtime to discuss OpenAI's spending forecasts, going into detail how Apple's (AAPL) partnership with Alphabet's Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL) is a major loss for OpenAI. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-ai-partnership-google-major-214700767.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Elon Musk Slams Google, Apple Deal: 'Unreasonable Concentration Of Power'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-slams-google-apple-213106434.html</link><description>Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla, Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) and xAI, voiced criticism of the AI partnership between Apple, Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) and Alphabet, Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) announced on Monday. In a post on X replying to the News from Google account, Musk questioned the partnership as possibly allowing Google too much "power," considering it owns the Android operating system and Chrome browser. "This seems like an unreasonable concentration of power for Google, given that the[y] also have Andro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-slams-google-apple-213106434.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Bank of America, Wells Fargo, Citigroup, Tesla, Rivian, Intel, AppLovin, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-5199a1f2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shares of Bank of America, Citigroup, and Wells Fargo tumble after reporting earnings, a day after JPMorgan Chase posted a decline in quarterly profit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-5199a1f2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google vs. Apple: Which Magnificent 7 Stock is a Better Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37047986/google-vs-apple-which-magnificent-7-stock-is-a-better-buy-right-now</link><description>After these two Mag 7 rivals finally partnered on AI, which stock is worth the investment?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37047986/google-vs-apple-which-magnificent-7-stock-is-a-better-buy-right-now</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Nasdaq Drops 1%. Small Stocks Take Lead From Big Tech.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/nasdaq-drops-1-small-stocks-take-lead-from-big-tech--4SP73wyThk4PhB7mspng?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A rotation away from large technology stocks dragged down the major indexes on Wednesday. The Nasdaq Composite fell 1%. The S&amp;amp;P 500 dropped 0.6%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 66 points, or 0.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/nasdaq-drops-1-small-stocks-take-lead-from-big-tech--4SP73wyThk4PhB7mspng?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why the Nasdaq Composite Is Lagging the S&amp;P 500 and Dow</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/why-the-nasdaq-composite-is-lagging-the-s-p-500-and-dow-J9b196YXOLfheNb7RmC4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A rotation away from Big Tech and into smaller stocks was a big drag on the Nasdaq Composite on Wednesday.  The tech-heavy index fell 1.2%, while the S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.7%.  The Dow was down just 100 points, or 0.2%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/why-the-nasdaq-composite-is-lagging-the-s-p-500-and-dow-J9b196YXOLfheNb7RmC4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Microsoft Stock Ready to Rebound After Recent Slide</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-stock-ready-rebound-recent-201023104.html</link><description>The security is trading near a historically bullish trendline</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-stock-ready-rebound-recent-201023104.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Amid the AI boom, Intel is focusing on the basics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amid-the-ai-boom-intel-is-focusing-on-the-basics-192933560.html</link><description>Intel's Core Ultra Series 3 could be the key to the company's turnaround effort.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amid-the-ai-boom-intel-is-focusing-on-the-basics-192933560.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Return of CPUs | INTC Stock, AMD Stock, NVDA Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-return-of-cpus-intc-stock-amd-stock-nvda-stock/</link><description>24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are kicking the New Year off in style with 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. Over the course of 12 videos, the two will share their thoughts on everything from the memory explosion to software stocks to robotics. In this video, Eric focuses on the unexpected return of CPUs in 2026. The rise of AI agents and Reinforcement Learning Environments is creating enormous demand for CPUs. That could lead to significant pricing power for leading CPU companies like Intel (Nasdaq: INTC) and AMD (Nasdaq: AMD).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-return-of-cpus-intc-stock-amd-stock-nvda-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AMD stock bets shift after analyst drops $15 billon message</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/amd-stock-shifts-after-analyst-drops-comments-before-earnings</link><description>AMD(Advanced Micro Devices) is set to announce its Q4 and full fiscal year 2025 report on February 3, 2026, after the market close. Ahead of this, the semiconductor company's shares are reacting to new research from analysts at KeyBanc. The company, under the leadership of CEO Lisa Su, has grown ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/amd-stock-shifts-after-analyst-drops-comments-before-earnings</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] India’s security plan could create a new headache for iPhone and Android users</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/indias-security-plan-could-create-a-new-headache-for-iphone-and-android-users</link><description>India is talking about a set of 83 smartphone security rules that Reuters said would oblige big phone makers to update their software and, in certain cases, let government-approved labs look into the source code. The ideas are part of the Indian Telecom Security Assurance Requirements framework and ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/indias-security-plan-could-create-a-new-headache-for-iphone-and-android-users</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike CEO says AI agents are unpredictable as company snaps up more cybersecurity startups</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-ceo-says-ai-agents-are-unpredictable-as-company-snaps-up-more-cybersecurity-startups-165836482.html</link><description>CrowdStrike has come out swinging in 2026 with some key deals. Here's why.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-ceo-says-ai-agents-are-unpredictable-as-company-snaps-up-more-cybersecurity-startups-165836482.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple aims to capture creator market with software bundle</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aims-to-capture-creator-market-with-software-bundle-165532120.html</link><description>Apple is launching its Creator Studio later this month.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aims-to-capture-creator-market-with-software-bundle-165532120.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Keeps an Overweight Rating on Shake Shack Inc. (SHAK)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-keeps-overweight-rating-shake-165221562.html</link><description>Shake Shack Inc. (NYSE:SHAK) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. The Fly reported on January 7, 2026, that Barclays kept its Overweight rating on Shake Shack Inc. (NYSE:SHAK) and lowered the price goal to $110 from $115. The change reflects outlooks for the restaurant industry in 2026, where sales difficulties […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-keeps-overweight-rating-shake-165221562.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Big banks push back on Trump's credit card cap, warning of 'significant' economic slowdown</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-push-back-on-trumps-credit-card-cap-warning-of-significant-economic-slowdown-165046195.html</link><description>Some of America’s top bankers are warning that the president’s cap on credit card interest rates would prove disastrous for lower-income consumers and the US economy — not to mention their profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-push-back-on-trumps-credit-card-cap-warning-of-significant-economic-slowdown-165046195.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AppLovin Stock Just Got a New Buy Rating. Its Shares Are Tanking.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/applovin-stock-price-buy-rating-b3e198a3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Buzzy, high-growth stocks like  AppLovin  often get a boost when sell-side analysts counsel investors to buy.  Evercore ISI initiated coverage of  AppLovin  stock with an Outperform rating and an $835 price target on Wednesday, forecasting a 25% jump from Tuesday’s closing price of $668.63.  The company has momentum across its gaming and e-commerce ad businesses, and investors should expect a big quarterly earnings print next month, Evercore argued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/applovin-stock-price-buy-rating-b3e198a3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The AI Boom Gets Its First Earnings Test of the Year. Watch TSMC Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-taiwan-semi-earnings-stock-price-8ccafaeb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>When  Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing  reports fourth-quarter earnings on Thursday, investors will be watching for the company’s comments on revenue and capital expenditure for clarity on where the boom in artificial-intelligence processors goes from here.  TSMC is expected to report a net profit of 469.13 billion New Taiwan dollars ($14.86 billion), according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates, up 25% from the same period a year ago.  The Taiwanese chip manufacturer releases monthly revenue figures, which makes it easier for investors to calculate fourth-quarter revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-taiwan-semi-earnings-stock-price-8ccafaeb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] These 2 "Magnificent Seven" Stocks May Announce Stock Splits in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/these-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-may-announce-stoc/</link><description>Stock splits can cause a stock to rally in the short term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/these-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-may-announce-stoc/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Citi Retains a Neutral Rating on Sysco Corporation (SYY)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-retains-neutral-rating-sysco-161618895.html</link><description>Sysco Corporation (NYSE:SYY) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. According to TheFly, on January 7, 2026, Citi reduced its price target for Sysco Corporation (NYSE:SYY) from $82 to $81. It kept a neutral rating on the stock. The revision was part of Citi’s overall 2026 projection upgrade for the food […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-retains-neutral-rating-sysco-161618895.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Deutsche Bank is Bullish on The Kroger Co. (KR)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/deutsche-bank-bullish-kroger-co-161552290.html</link><description>The Kroger Co. (NYSE:KR) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. The Fly reported on January 8, 2026, that Deutsche Bank has resumed coverage of The Kroger Co. (NYSE: KR), with a $75 price target and a Buy rating. The firm anticipates 2026 to be a mixed year and has restored […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/deutsche-bank-bullish-kroger-co-161552290.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bank of America delivers sharp take on Apple stock after major shift</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-delivers-sharp-take-on-apple-stock-after-major-shift</link><description>Bank of America is leaning bullish on Apple (AAPL) stock ahead of a critical earnings test on Jan. 29. The sharper take comes right after a major shift in Apple’s AI future, following a breakthrough deal for Siri with Google, a unit of Alphabet (GOOGL). The bank sees multiple potent near-term ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-delivers-sharp-take-on-apple-stock-after-major-shift</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] President Donald Trump Says, “The United States Government Is Proud to Be a Shareholder of Intel.” Should You?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37043034/president-donald-trump-says-the-united-states-government-is-proud-to-be-a-shareholder-of-intel-should-you</link><description>Trump’s endorsement of Intel has ignited a powerful stock rally. Should you follow this bold bet?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37043034/president-donald-trump-says-the-united-states-government-is-proud-to-be-a-shareholder-of-intel-should-you</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says Apple is “Humming Along, Making a Lot of Money”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-apple-humming-155728797.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Cramer showed optimism around the company’s stock, as he remarked: “We’ve seen breathtaking rallies in the data storage stocks. We also have some stocks that simply can’t lift, and I gotta mention them, Apple and NVIDIA. I know you want to know […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-apple-humming-155728797.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Sold-Out AI Chips and Growing Foundry Buzz: Is Intel’s Rally Just Getting Started?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/sold-out-ai-chips-and-growing-foundry-buzz-is-intels-rally-just-getting-started/</link><description>Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) is experiencing a notable rally already in 2026, with the stock up 28% year-to-date, building on last year’s 84% rise. While the surge first gained traction after the U.S. government took a 9.9% stake in the chipmaker through an $8.9 billion equity investment last August, its advance lately has been driven more by ... Sold-Out AI Chips and Growing Foundry Buzz: Is Intel’s Rally Just Getting Started?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/sold-out-ai-chips-and-growing-foundry-buzz-is-intels-rally-just-getting-started/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike defeats shareholder lawsuit over huge software outage</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-155130284.html</link><description>A federal judge dismissed a lawsuit by CrowdStrike shareholders who said the cybersecurity company defrauded them by concealing its inadequate ​software testing and quality assurance procedures, before a July 2024 outage crashed more ‌than 8 million Microsoft Windows-based computers worldwide.  In a decision made public on Tuesday, U.S. District Judge Robert Pitman ‌in Austin, Texas said shareholders failed to plausibly allege that a large number of statements by CrowdStrike and top executives in regulatory filings, on earnings calls and on the company's website were materially false and misleading, or motivated by an intent to defraud.  Led by New York State ⁠Comptroller Thomas DiNapoli, the shareholders ‌alleged that CrowdStrike had "no test plans and no quality assurance team," citing former employees, and that executives at the Austin-based company prioritized "speed over ‍everything else" to maximize profit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-155130284.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike CEO on M&amp;A: Identity security is the 'new perimeter'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/crowdstrike-ceo-m-identity-security-155100218.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has closed a deal valued at $420 million to acquire Seraphic Security; this comes after acquiring identity security platform SGNL last week for $740 million. CrowdStrike also bought Pangea and Onum in 2025. CrowdStrike Co-Founder and CEO George Kurtz joins Yahoo Finance Executive Editor Brian Sozzi on Opening Bid to talk about the cybersecurity operator's goals to expand its identity security portfolio and the value these companies add to CrowdStrike. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/crowdstrike-ceo-m-identity-security-155100218.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple and Qualcomm Stocks Falls -- Report Says Companies Facing Potential Supply Issues</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-stocks-falls-report-153353729.html</link><description>The AI Supply Chain Has a New Choke Point. Apple and Qualcomm Are Exposed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-stocks-falls-report-153353729.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why Google stock is on fire in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-google-stock-is-on-fire-in-2026-142253886.html</link><description>Google's stock has picked up where it left off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-google-stock-is-on-fire-in-2026-142253886.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to acquire Seraphic Security, terms undisclosed</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-acquire-seraphic-security-terms-141633279.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) announced it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire Seraphic Security. The purchase price is contemplated to be paid predominantly in cash and includes a portion to be delivered in the form of stock subject to vesting conditions. The proposed acquisition is expected to close during CrowdStrike’s first quarter of FY’27, subject to customary closing conditions. Claim 70% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper deci</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-acquire-seraphic-security-terms-141633279.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The Intel Turnaround No One Saw Coming: Sold-Out Server CPUs and Apple Knocking at the Door</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/the-intel-turnaround-no-one-saw-coming-sold-out-se/</link><description>Multiple tailwinds are lifting Intel stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/the-intel-turnaround-no-one-saw-coming-sold-out-se/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet Just Hit a $4T Market Cap. This Bull Sees More Gains Ahead</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-just-hit-a-4t-market-cap-this-bull-sees-more-gains-ahead/</link><description>Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOGL) surpassed the $4 trillion market cap mark and could be headed to a $5 trillion valuation at some point in 2026, especially if the latest parabolic move has gas in the tank. With shares of Alphabet hitting new highs on Tuesday’s session, effectively leaving many of its Magnificent Seven peers behind, questions linger ... Alphabet Just Hit a $4T Market Cap. This Bull Sees More Gains Ahead</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-just-hit-a-4t-market-cap-this-bull-sees-more-gains-ahead/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Airbnb Appoints Former Meta AI Executive CTO</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/airbnb-appoints-former-meta-ai-executive-cto-03620990?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Airbnb named Ahmad Al-Dahle, a former leader of AI at Meta, as the company’s new chief technology officer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/airbnb-appoints-former-meta-ai-executive-cto-03620990?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Airbnb Taps Meta GenAI Leader as CTO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-taps-meta-genai-leader-134040489.html</link><description>Ahmad Al-Dahle joins as Airbnb sharpens its AI push</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-taps-meta-genai-leader-134040489.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet Tops $4 Trillion With Apple AI Deal -- Is GOOGL Stock Still a Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-apple-133509931.html</link><description>Google's AI Push Expands Through Apple Partnership</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-apple-133509931.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock, Part II: How To Find &amp; Own America's Greatest Opportunities</title><link>https://www.investors.com/how-to-invest/apple-aapl-stock-americas-greatest-opportunities/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Last week, we looked at moves by Apple stock early on in this century. Here's another run it staged just a few years later.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/how-to-invest/apple-aapl-stock-americas-greatest-opportunities/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Opinion: Why It’s Time to Follow Tim Cook and CEO Elliott Hill Into Nike Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/opinion-why-its-time-to-follow-tim-cook-and-ceo-elliott-hill-into-nike-stock/</link><description>Shares of Nike (NASDAQ:NKE) have been flying higher ever since Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) CEO Tim Cook, who’s also on Nike’s board of directors (and has been for quite some time), backed up the truck on shares of the sneaker giant, picking up around $3 million worth of shares. Undoubtedly, doubling one’s position in a company on ... Opinion: Why It’s Time to Follow Tim Cook and CEO Elliott Hill Into Nike Stock</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/opinion-why-its-time-to-follow-tim-cook-and-ceo-elliott-hill-into-nike-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Stock Surges Further Toward 2-Year High. What the Excitement’s About.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-chips-4ce48217?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday.  The chip company’s shares are on the brink of levels not seen for several years as investors bet President Donald Trump’s support for the company will boost its chip-manufacturing ambitions.  Intel was up 1.6% at $48.06 in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-chips-4ce48217?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] RBC checks suggest OpenAI device coming as early as September</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-checks-suggest-openai-device-120545660.html</link><description>Investing.com -- RBC Capital said new supply chain checks point to a potential OpenAI hardware debut as early as September, a move the firm believes could signal the company’s push toward creating “a 3rd mobile ecosystem.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-checks-suggest-openai-device-120545660.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Women's, advocacy groups call on Apple, Google to drop X and Grok from app stores</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/womens-advocacy-groups-call-apple-110255271.html</link><description>By Raphael Satter WASHINGTON, Jan 14 (Reuters) - A coalition of women's groups, tech watchdogs, and progressive activists is calling on Alphabet owner Google and Apple to remove the social media site</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/womens-advocacy-groups-call-apple-110255271.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google's Apple AI deal marks 'huge loss' for OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-apple-ai-deal-marks-huge-loss-for-openai-110002996.html</link><description>Google and Apple announced a multi-year collaboration on AI Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-apple-ai-deal-marks-huge-loss-for-openai-110002996.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] JPMorgan Stock Rises After Sharp Drop on Earnings. What Spooked Markets.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/jpmorgan-stock-price-earnings-markets-c482c4f0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan Chase  stock was showing signs of recovery in Wednesday’s premarket following a sharp fall the previous session on disappointing fourth-quarter results.  While the bank’s adjusted earnings beat analysts’ estimates, profits fell 7% from a year earlier on the back of lower-than-expected investment banking fees.  The banking giant had to set up a $2.2 billion credit reserve as part of agreeing to buy the iPhone maker’s card portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/jpmorgan-stock-price-earnings-markets-c482c4f0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to acquire Seraphic Security for browser security boost</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acqusition-seraphic-security/</link><description>The acquisition will boost CrowdStrike's Falcon platform by integrating Seraphic’s protection, enabling advanced security in popular browsers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acqusition-seraphic-security/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] FTSE 100 LIVE: Stocks rise as China trade surplus hits record high</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-stocks-rise-china-trade-surplus-hits-record-high-despite-trump-tariffs-090947550.html</link><description>Beijing revealed the world's largest-ever trade surplus at $1.19tn (£890bn) year-on-year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/ftse-100-live-stocks-rise-china-trade-surplus-hits-record-high-despite-trump-tariffs-090947550.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Morgan Stanley flags further upside for UK banks as new targets come into focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-flags-further-upside-090213740.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Morgan Stanley said UK banks still have scope for further upside as new return targets, earnings forecasts and capital metrics come into focus, even after a period of strong share price performance, according to a recent note.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-flags-further-upside-090213740.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] This Unstoppable Stock Has 4 Catalysts to Fuel Its Membership in the $5 Trillion Club in 2026, According to 1 Wall Street Analyst.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/this-unstoppable-stock-has-4-catalysts-to-fuel-its/</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) and market share gains could catapult this tech titan to new heights.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/this-unstoppable-stock-has-4-catalysts-to-fuel-its/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Heard on the Street Tuesday Recap: Powered Down</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-tuesday-recap-powered-down-k5ZmTwenwSq6epivJo0m?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan gave a bum start to bank earnings. The Dow industrials component slid 4.2% after results showed a surprise slip in investment-banking fees and a significant charge for taking over the Apple credit-card program.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-tuesday-recap-powered-down-k5ZmTwenwSq6epivJo0m?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How Investing In Apple in 1995 Could Have Made You Rich Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-apple-1995-could-made-070007212.html</link><description>Here's a look at how investing in Apple back in 1995 could have made you rich -- and the lessons you can learn from that enviable track record.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-apple-1995-could-made-070007212.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>