<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Does a $21 Million Exit Amid a 43% Drop in Share Prices Raise Questions About This Packaging Stock?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/16/does-a-usd21-million-exit-amid-a-43-drop-in-share-prices-raise-questions-about-this-packaging-stock/</link><description>Graphic Packaging provides fiber-based packaging for food, beverage, and consumer goods firms, emphasizing sustainable solutions worldwide.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/16/does-a-usd21-million-exit-amid-a-43-drop-in-share-prices-raise-questions-about-this-packaging-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Assessing Barclays (LSE:BARC) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-barclays-lse-barc-valuation-010935217.html</link><description>What Barclays’ recent performance data tells you right now Barclays (LSE:BARC) has drawn attention after a period of strong share price moves, with a 1-year total return of 73.47% and a past 3-month total return of 36.65%. This has prompted fresh interest in its valuation. See our latest analysis for Barclays. Recent trading suggests momentum is building, with a 30 day share price return of 6.72% and a 90 day share price return of 36.65%. The 1 year total shareholder return of 73.47%, along...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-barclays-lse-barc-valuation-010935217.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump at Davos, Netflix earnings, SCOTUS hearing: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-davos-netflix-earnings-scotus-000054604.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come next week, including earnings results from companies like Netflix (NFLX), Procter &amp;amp; Gamble (PG), and United Airlines (UAL); President Trump's attendance at the 2026 World Economic Forum (WEF) in Davos, Switzerland; the US Supreme Court's (SCOTUS) hearing on whether the Trump administration has the power to remove Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook; and November's reading on the Personal Consumption Expenditures index (PCE). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-davos-netflix-earnings-scotus-000054604.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google to Appeal US Court Ruling of Illegal Monopoly in Search</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-appeal-us-court-ruling-224756049.html</link><description>The notice of Google’s appeal was filed Friday in Washington federal court, along with a request to put the lower-court ruling on hold while the appeal is pending.  The DC Circuit Court of Appeals will likely hear the case later this year.  The court, which hears many appeals related to the federal government, takes about a year to issue a decision after an appeal notice is filed, according to statistics compiled by the US Courts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-appeal-us-court-ruling-224756049.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL) Declines More Than Market: Some Information for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-declines-more-market-224504998.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) reached $255.52 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a -1.04% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-declines-more-market-224504998.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: This Stock Will Join the $3 Trillion Club by the End of 2026. You're Going to Want to Buy It Now.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-this-stock-will-join-the-3-trillion-clu/</link><description>Broadcom is primed to deliver explosive growth this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-this-stock-will-join-the-3-trillion-clu/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 AI Stocks to Buy in 2026, and 1 to Avoid</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/2-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-1-to-avoid/</link><description>Some AI-focused companies are not worth the trouble.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/2-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-1-to-avoid/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Reports Earnings on January 22. Here Is Where Options Data Says INTC Stock Could Be Trading Next.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37090544/intel-reports-earnings-on-january-22-here-is-where-options-data-says-intc-stock-could-be-trading-next</link><description>Intel shares have soared heading into the firm’s earnings release on Jan. 22. But a Citi analyst and options traders believe INTC stock will push higher from here in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37090544/intel-reports-earnings-on-january-22-here-is-where-options-data-says-intc-stock-could-be-trading-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Earnings live: PNC rounds out bank earnings this week as attention shifts to Netflix, Intel</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-pnc-rounds-out-bank-earnings-this-week-as-attention-shifts-to-netflix-intel-214153842.html</link><description>A broader set of sectors will be represented when 35 more S&amp;amp;P 500 companies report earnings next week, including Netflix, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-pnc-rounds-out-bank-earnings-this-week-as-attention-shifts-to-netflix-intel-214153842.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How Apple TV Is Quietly Becoming a Threat to Netflix's Growth Story</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/apple-is-quietly-becoming-a-threat-to-netflix-in-s/</link><description>The tech giant is starting to show real momentum in streaming, and it has some structural advantages.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/apple-is-quietly-becoming-a-threat-to-netflix-in-s/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] An AI Smart Pen from OpenAI Sounds Weird—Until You Consider These Use Cases</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/an-ai-smart-pen-from-openai-sounds-weird-until-you-consider-these-use-cases/</link><description>There’s been a lot of buzz around OpenAI and the secret device(s) it’s been working on behind the scenes with the expertise of an industry veteran like former Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) chief design officer Jony Ive. While Ive is arguably the undisputed king of device design, there’s no guarantee that OpenAI’s AI gadgets will hit the ... An AI Smart Pen from OpenAI Sounds Weird—Until You Consider These Use Cases</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/an-ai-smart-pen-from-openai-sounds-weird-until-you-consider-these-use-cases/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Leaders Head to Davos, Earnings Heat Up: What to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/leaders-head-to-davos-earnings-heat-up-what-to-watch-next-week-WafuDV6W06uawgDUha5p?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>President Trump will lead the U.S. delegation to the annual meeting of the World Economic Forum next week in Davos, Switzerland, along with other government and business leaders. Meanwhile, earnings season is also kicking into gear, with announcements expected from companies including Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, Intel and Netflix.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/leaders-head-to-davos-earnings-heat-up-what-to-watch-next-week-WafuDV6W06uawgDUha5p?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] 3 Key Earnings Releases to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-key-earnings-releases-watch-201900118.html</link><description>The 2025 Q4 earnings season is in full swing, with results from the big banks this week kicking the period into a much higher gear.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-key-earnings-releases-watch-201900118.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Vanguard’s $10.8B ETF Made 19% Betting on AI Infrastructure</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/vanguards-10-8b-etf-made-19-betting-on-ai-infrastructure/</link><description>If you want to bet that Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL), NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA), and Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) will continue dominating the market, Vanguard Mega Cap Index Fund ETF Shares (NYSEARCA:MGC) offers a straightforward way to do it. MGC takes a concentrated approach to mega-cap technology, with Apple, NVIDIA, and Microsoft representing nearly a quarter of the fund’s assets. This ... Vanguard’s $10.8B ETF Made 19% Betting on AI Infrastructure</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/vanguards-10-8b-etf-made-19-betting-on-ai-infrastructure/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Memory Explosion | MU Stock, SNDK Stock, SK Hynix, CAMT Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-memory-explosion-mu-stock-sndk-stock-sk-hynix-camt-stock/</link><description>Summary: To ring in 2026, our 24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are counting down 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. The first trend the two will be discussing is the AI-driven “memory explosion” that has been emerging as a core investment theme as inference, larger context windows, and ... 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Memory Explosion | MU Stock, SNDK Stock, SK Hynix, CAMT Stock</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-memory-explosion-mu-stock-sndk-stock-sk-hynix-camt-stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] The Pressure on Memory Chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/pressure-memory-chips-191256217.html</link><description>HP was hit with back-to-back downgrades. Barclays turns bearish, warning of structural PC weakness, rising memory costs, and no clear catalysts ahead. CFRA flags margin pressure from unprecedented inflation. New Street Research analyst Antoine Chkaiban joined Bloomberg Open Interest with his take on the sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/pressure-memory-chips-191256217.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Cathie Wood's ARK Invest Says Apple's Reliance On Google For AI Signals Deeper Trouble</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-says-190119374.html</link><description>Apple Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AAPL) decision to outsource its artificial intelligence (AI) foundation to Alphabet Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google is not a strategic masterstroke but a sign of a company in “huge, hairy trouble,” according to the research team at Cathie Wood's ARK Invest. ‘Strategic Disaster’ During the latest episode of ARK’s “The Brainstorm,” Chief Futurist Brett Winton offered a scathing critique of the newly announced partnership that will see Google's Gemini models power Si</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-says-190119374.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why Is Meta Platforms Priced 36% Cheaper Than Its Hyperscaler Peers?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/why-is-meta-platforms-priced-36-cheaper-than-its-hyperscaler-peers/</link><description>Meta Platforms (NASDAQ:META) has delivered outstanding performance compared its hyperscaler peers such as Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL), Amazon (NASDAQ:AMZN), Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOG)(NASDAQ:GOOGL), and Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT). Over the last 12 months, revenue growth hit 21.3%, far exceeding the low- to mid-teens rates for the others, such as with Alphabet at 13.4% and Amazon below that. And in the past ... Why Is Meta Platforms Priced 36% Cheaper Than Its Hyperscaler Peers?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/why-is-meta-platforms-priced-36-cheaper-than-its-hyperscaler-peers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL)’s The Place to Go If You Want to Make Some Money, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-place-want-money-182444686.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer talked about. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)’s been in the news as the year starts to settle. The firm made the news earlier this week after it announced that it would use Google’s Gemini to power an […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-place-want-money-182444686.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Fall Despite Citi Upgrade Amid Foundry Hopes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-fall-despite-citi-182235864.html</link><description>Analysts See Window Against TSMC Tightness</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-fall-despite-citi-182235864.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Being Down is “Just Plain Stupid,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-shares-being-down-181831619.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer talked about. Within a year, Jim Cramer has turned increasingly optimistic and bullish about technology giant Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL). Early last year, he sold the shares on the back of worries about the Justice Department’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-shares-being-down-181831619.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Chipmaker TSMC Adds Fuel To AI Megatrend Hype With Q4 Report</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/tsm-stock-record-high-tsmc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing is basking in the glow of strong sales of advanced chips for AI data centers. TSM stock notched a record high.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/tsm-stock-record-high-tsmc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Rally Extends as Analyst Upgrades Spotlight Foundry Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rally-extends-analyst-upgrades-175817741.html</link><description>Shares climb early in 2026 as Wall Street upgrades and foundry optimism build ahead of fourth-quarter earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rally-extends-analyst-upgrades-175817741.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Calls This 1 AI Server Stock ‘Best in Class’ Amid Upgrade to ‘Overweight’ Rating</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37086735/barclays-calls-this-1-ai-server-stock-best-in-class-amid-upgrade-to-overweight-rating</link><description>Dell Technologies' stock offers significant upside potential in 2026, given its widening AI moat, according to Barclays.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37086735/barclays-calls-this-1-ai-server-stock-best-in-class-amid-upgrade-to-overweight-rating</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says “Alphabet Increasingly Looks Like the Only Winner in AI for the Moment”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-alphabet-increasingly-171317205.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar recently. Cramer mentioned the company during the episode and said: “Hey, you want hate? I’ll give you hate. All you have to do is declare you’re going for clean energy to power your data centers. If Microsoft and Meta Platforms were to abandon […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-alphabet-increasingly-171317205.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Don’t Go Chasing Semis (Yet). What the Charts Say About Entry Points for 3 Chip Stocks.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/semiconductor-stocks-rally-entry-points-amd-marvell-texas-instruments-stocks-9c4ba532?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>FEATURE  The last three months have seen investors clearly sour on technology stocks and move into value-oriented plays. The three best-performing S&amp;amp;P sectors, and the only ones to have delivered double digit gains over that time frame, are energy, materials, and healthcare, reflected in their ETF proxies and   One notable exception to this tech exodus is the robust action in the semiconductor segment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/semiconductor-stocks-rally-entry-points-amd-marvell-texas-instruments-stocks-9c4ba532?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Erste Group Bank (EBKDY) Upgraded to Buy: Here's What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/erste-group-bank-ebkdy-upgraded-170004568.html</link><description>Erste Group Bank (EBKDY) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company's earnings prospects. This might drive the stock higher in the near term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/erste-group-bank-ebkdy-upgraded-170004568.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Sprout Social (SPT) Stock Is Nosediving</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-sprout-social-spt-stock-162541553.html</link><description>Shares of social media management platform Sprout Social (NASDAQ:SPT) fell 5.9% in the morning session after analysts at Morgan Stanley lowered their price target on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-sprout-social-spt-stock-162541553.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel: A Policy-Driven Boom or Hidden Bubble?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-policy-driven-boom-hidden-153828782.html</link><description>AI and Semiconductor Buildout: What Intel Investors Should Watch</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-policy-driven-boom-hidden-153828782.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153028184.html</link><description>Nu Holdings Ltd. 2,640,111 16.59</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153028184.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Here’s What the Wall Street Thinks About ​​Barclays PLC (BCS)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-thinks-barclays-plc-152637977.html</link><description>​Barclays PLC (NYSE:BCS) is one of the Best Performing Affordable Stocks Under $40. On January 13, Kepler Cheuvreux maintained a Buy rating on Barclays PLC (NYSE:BCS) and raised the price target from GBP4.60 to GBP5.40. Earlier, on January 6, Jonathan Pierce from Jefferies also reiterated a Buy rating on the stock and raised the price […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-thinks-barclays-plc-152637977.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: This Will Be the First Dividend Champion from the "Magnificent Seven"</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-this-will-be-first-dividend-champion/</link><description>One "Magnificent Seven" company has raised payouts by 600% since 2010.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-this-will-be-first-dividend-champion/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays cuts HPQ on secular challenges and a ’lack of catalyst’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-cuts-hpq-secular-challenges-151809573.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Barclays has downgraded HP Inc., warning that a combination of secular headwinds, a weakening memory cycle and limited catalysts will likely keep the stock under pressure through 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-cuts-hpq-secular-challenges-151809573.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Intel Stock a Buy at New 52-Week Highs?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37084328/is-intel-stock-a-buy-at-new-52-week-highs</link><description>Intel (INTC) is trading at a new two-year high. Shares are up a whopping 145% over the past 52 weeks. INTC maintains a 100% technical “Buy” opinion from Barchart. The stock hit new highs coming out of CES 2026 and amid rumors that it could be partnering with Apple. Today’s...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37084328/is-intel-stock-a-buy-at-new-52-week-highs</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] INTC Stock Before Q4 Earnings: Is It a Smart Buy or Risky Move?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intc-stock-q4-earnings-smart-150600290.html</link><description>Intel's Q4 earnings preview includes AI chip launches, rising estimates and geopolitical headwinds. What's next for the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intc-stock-q4-earnings-smart-150600290.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] TSMC Stock Rises as It Plans $56 Billion Splurge on AI Chip Making. What Really Matters.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsm-stock-price-tsmc-spending-ai-intel-323b808f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing will spend up to $56 billion on capital expenditures this year. It was taken as a vote of confidence in AI but it could be influenced by a U.S.-Taiwan trade deal.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsm-stock-price-tsmc-spending-ai-intel-323b808f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Extends Comeback as Investors Bet on Foundry Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-extends-comeback-investors-bet-145824938.html</link><description>After an 84% rally in 2025, the shares are near their highest level in two years, recovering from a 60% drop in 2024 when Intel appeared to be falling behind its rivals who were capitalizing on the AI boom.  “It’s back from the dead,” said Kim Forrest, chief investment officer at Bokeh Capital Partners and a long-time Intel shareholder.  A range of catalysts are driving the optimism: an improving financial outlook, new confidence from Wall Street as seen in recent analyst upgrades, speculation about new foundry customers, and even enthusiasm around the company’s potential to be a winner in President Trump’s “America First” campaign.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-extends-comeback-investors-bet-145824938.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Surging Intel Stock, 2 Other Nasdaq 100 Giants Headline Earnings Calendar</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/intel-stock-nasdaq-100-netflix-earnings-isrg-ge-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock is holding near highs ahead of its Q4 earnings report, along with Leaderboard stock GE Aerospace.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/intel-stock-nasdaq-100-netflix-earnings-isrg-ge-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Spotify will net an eye-popping amount of money by raising prices again</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-will-net-an-eye-popping-amount-of-money-by-raising-prices-again-141750366.html</link><description>The streaming platform is raising prices across its plans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-will-net-an-eye-popping-amount-of-money-by-raising-prices-again-141750366.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Amazon Will Be America’s First $1T Revenue Company</title><link>https://247wallst.com/companies-and-brands/2026/01/16/amazon-will-be-americas-first-1t-revenue-company/</link><description>At is current pace of growth, Amazon will have over $1 trillion in revenue by 2028. Its growth is likely to be supercharged by artificial intelligence.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/companies-and-brands/2026/01/16/amazon-will-be-americas-first-1t-revenue-company/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Exploring Analyst Estimates for Intel (INTC) Q4 Earnings, Beyond Revenue and EPS</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exploring-analyst-estimates-intel-intc-141504635.html</link><description>Beyond analysts' top-and-bottom-line estimates for Intel (INTC), evaluate projections for some of its key metrics to gain a better insight into how the business might have performed for the quarter ended December 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exploring-analyst-estimates-intel-intc-141504635.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Tech rally, US-Taiwan chip deal, power grid auction: 3 Things</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-rally-us-taiwan-chip-141009857.html</link><description>US stock futures (ES=F, NQ=F, YM=F) are perked up in Friday's premarket as the tech sector and bank stocks are looking to rally. Chip stocks are roaring to life this morning after the US struck a trade deal with Taiwan, which includes Taiwanese tech companies investing a total of $250 billion into US semiconductor manufacturing. Lastly, the Trump administration is teaming up with governors to hold an emergency power auction to resolve the surging power costs expected from Big Tech's AI data centers. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-rally-us-taiwan-chip-141009857.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Want Better Returns? Don't Ignore These 2 Computer and Technology Stocks Set to Beat Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/want-better-returns-dont-ignore-140006405.html</link><description>Why investors should use the Zacks Earnings ESP tool to help find stocks that are poised to top quarterly earnings estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/want-better-returns-dont-ignore-140006405.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Cathie Wood Is Selling Meta Platforms Stock. Should You?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37082721/cathie-wood-is-selling-meta-platforms-stock-should-you</link><description>Even as Wood trims her position, Meta’s accelerating AI infrastructure buildout, strong cash generation, and consensus analyst rating make META stock appear solid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37082721/cathie-wood-is-selling-meta-platforms-stock-should-you</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Last Year, I Predicted That Alphabet Would Join the $3 Trillion Club. Here's Why the "Magnificent Seven" Stock Could Surpass $5 Trillion Before the End of 2027.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/alphabet-stock-all-time-high-5-trillion-club/</link><description>The Google parent's stock is roaring higher for all the right reasons.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/alphabet-stock-all-time-high-5-trillion-club/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Are Options Traders Betting on a Big Move in Apple Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/options-traders-betting-big-move-135700857.html</link><description>Investors need to pay close attention to AAPL stock based on the movements in the options market lately.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/options-traders-betting-big-move-135700857.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Implied Volatility Surging for Barclays Stock Options</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/implied-volatility-surging-barclays-stock-133800509.html</link><description>Investors need to pay close attention to Barclays stock based on the movements in the options market lately.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/implied-volatility-surging-barclays-stock-133800509.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Are you concerned about losing your job this year? How readers voted</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/job-losses-unemployment-uk-poll-results-133703725.html</link><description>Continued signs of weakness in the UK labour market have created uncertainty over the outlook for jobs for the year ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/job-losses-unemployment-uk-poll-results-133703725.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today: Dow Wavers Near Record Highs; Nvidia Regains Key Level (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-record-highs-nvidia-nvda-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Futures for the Dow Jones Industrial Average and other major stock indexes were mostly higher Friday, as Wall Street looked to finish out the week on a high note. An early winner was Nvidia, which rose on the stock market today after making a bullish move above a key level Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-record-highs-nvidia-nvda-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Rigetti Stock: Hype or Hidden Opportunity in Quantum Tech?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-stock-hype-hidden-opportunity-132733016.html</link><description>Wall Street Flags Rigetti Risks as Revenue Remains Near Zero, Cash Burn Persists</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-stock-hype-hidden-opportunity-132733016.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to watch next week: Netflix, Intel, Burberry, JD Wetherspoon and JD Sports</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-intel-burberry-jd-wetherspoon-jd-sports-stocks-to-watch-131827171.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-intel-burberry-jd-wetherspoon-jd-sports-stocks-to-watch-131827171.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Prediction: Intel Stock Will Continue Soaring in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-intel-will-continue-soaring-in-2026/</link><description>Intel's product development efforts could help the company clock faster-than-expected growth in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-intel-will-continue-soaring-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Watch February Earnings From NVIDIA and Microsoft to Predict Where This Mag7 ETF Goes Next</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/watch-february-earnings-from-nvidia-and-microsoft-to-predict-where-this-mag7-etf-goes-next/</link><description>The Roundhill Magnificent Seven ETF (NYSEARCA:MAGS) provides equal-weight exposure to the seven largest tech companies for investors seeking diversified exposure to this basket without selecting individual stocks. The fund holds NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA), Alphabet Inc (NASDAQ:GOOGL), Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT), and Meta Platforms Inc (NASDAQ:META) in equal portions alongside Apple Inc (NASDAQ:AAPL), Amazon.com Inc (NASDAQ:AMZN), and ... Watch February Earnings From NVIDIA and Mic</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/watch-february-earnings-from-nvidia-and-microsoft-to-predict-where-this-mag7-etf-goes-next/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 'The minute our love for meat goes, the business goes downhill'</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jolly-hog-sausages-bacon-meat-business-060032786.html</link><description>Bristol-based sausage firm The Jolly Hog is run by three Kohn brothers, whose relentless focus on quality has driven multimillion-pound sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/jolly-hog-sausages-bacon-meat-business-060032786.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Zacks Investment Ideas feature highlights: Taiwan Semiconductor, NVIDIA, Apple, Broadcom and Meta Platforms</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-120500392.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor delivered blockbuster earnings, raised capex, and detailed AI-driven shortages that could keep demand ahead of supply for years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-120500392.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] AST SpaceMobile Stock Jumps Again. Why the SpaceX Rival’s Shares Are Going Stellar.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ast-spacemobile-stock-price-spacex-d24b8d2a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AST SpaceMobile stock was rising as investors got excited about the potential for the satellite-communications company to expand in the defense sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ast-spacemobile-stock-price-spacex-d24b8d2a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Friday: J.B. Hunt, PNC, Verizon</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-j-b-hunt-pnc-verizon-keWejK8riJCb6jCEHgUB?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ J.B. Hunt Transport Services (JBHT): The logistics company recorded lower quarterly revenue, as transcontinental load volumes declined. Shares fell in off-hours trading. 🔎 M&amp;amp;T Bank (MTB), PNC Financial Services (PNC) and State Street (STT) are due to report results Friday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-j-b-hunt-pnc-verizon-keWejK8riJCb6jCEHgUB?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] President Donald Trump's Tax Policy Has Lit a Fire Under This Trillion-Dollar Trend That Apple, Alphabet, and Nvidia Are Taking Full Advantage Of</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/donald-trump-tax-policy-trillion-dollar-trend-nvda/</link><description>Hint: It has nothing to do with the rise of artificial intelligence (AI).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/donald-trump-tax-policy-trillion-dollar-trend-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>