<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[CRWD] Bank stock picks, crypto trajectory, dealmaking appetite, and more takes from top execs this past week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bank-stock-picks-crypto-trajectory-dealmaking-appetite-and-more-takes-from-top-execs-this-past-week-133010645.html</link><description>Your new investing ideas think sheet, with comments from recent guests on Yahoo Finance's Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bank-stock-picks-crypto-trajectory-dealmaking-appetite-and-more-takes-from-top-execs-this-past-week-133010645.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] 3 Reasons to Buy Intel Stock Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/3-reasons-to-buy-intel-stock-right-now/</link><description>Panther Lake, booming demand for server CPUs, and the foundry opportunity line up to make Intel a strong buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/3-reasons-to-buy-intel-stock-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump in Davos, Netflix and Intel results on deck earnings season ramps: What to watch this week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-in-davos-netflix-and-intel-results-on-deck-earnings-season-ramps-what-to-watch-this-week-123046356.html</link><description>A holiday-shortened trading week will bring investors the start of tech earnings and a key speech from President Trump in Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-in-davos-netflix-and-intel-results-on-deck-earnings-season-ramps-what-to-watch-this-week-123046356.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] These 2 AI Stocks Could Join the $2 Trillion Club in 2026, According to Wall Street</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/these-2-ai-stocks-could-join-the-2-trillion-club-i/</link><description>These AI leaders could soon join a highly exclusive group.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/these-2-ai-stocks-could-join-the-2-trillion-club-i/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Taiwan’s Flagship Chip Maker Charts a Future Beyond Taiwan</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/taiwan-semiconductor-tscm-us-investment-d96f77f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>TSMC has for decades provided a “Silicon Shield” to its namesake island. Now it sees both business and geopolitical reasons for going big in the U.S.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/taiwan-semiconductor-tscm-us-investment-d96f77f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] What to Expect in Markets This Week: Trump Davos Speech, MLK Holiday,
PCE Inflation, Netflix, Intel Earnings</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-trump-davos-speech-mlk-holiday-pce-inflation-netflix-intel-earnings-11886065</link><description>Coming up: Trump speech at Davos, Martin Luther King Jr. holiday, PCE inflation report, GDP update, and earnings from Netflix, Intel, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-trump-davos-speech-mlk-holiday-pce-inflation-netflix-intel-earnings-11886065</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Will humanoids be the growth engine of the 21st century?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/humanoids-growth-engine-21st-century-093005481.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Humanoid robots are moving rapidly from experimental prototypes to real-world workers, a shift Barclays says could redefine global labor markets and industrial supply chains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/humanoids-growth-engine-21st-century-093005481.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] YouTuber MKBHD Hails Tesla Model Y Performance, Calls EV Giant's Self-Driving Technology 'The Best'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</link><description>YouTuber Marques Brownlee, aka MKBHD, has shared his thoughts on the Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) Model Y Performance trim, as well as the company's self-driving technology. Tesla Self-Driving Is The Best Ever, MKBHD Says The YouTuber, in a review of the Model Y Performance on Thursday, hailed the crossover's software on the 16-inch touchscreen infotainment display, which is also a real-time representation of the car. "This is the best software in a car that is not Android Auto or Apple CarPlay," bo</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Bank of America revamps Alphabet stock after Google enters two key partnerships</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</link><description>Investors are taking a fresh look at Google, as new partnerships tied to its Gemini models help push the stock higher. On Jan. 11, Google and Walmart (WMT) said they plan to roll out a new shopping experience inside Google’s Gemini chatbot, highlighting a potential new revenue path for Google. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple’s (AAPL) AI Roadmap Strengthens With Google Deal, Says Evercore</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-roadmap-strengthens-174853486.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Hot AI Stocks to Keep on Your Radar. On January 12, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $330.00 price target. Firm analysts highlight Apple’s new AI partnership with Google Gemini, citing monetization upside and custom AI experiences ahead. The firm […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-roadmap-strengthens-174853486.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] KeyBanc Turns Bullish on Intel (INTC), Citing Server CPU Tightness and Foundry Yield Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-turns-bullish-intel-intc-173853702.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the Trending AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 13, KeyBanc analyst John Vinh upgraded the stock from Sector Weight to Overweight with a price target of $60.00. Firm analysts see improving foundry yield gains and robust hyperscaler-driven data center demand. Despite several headwinds in the server CPU market, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-turns-bullish-intel-intc-173853702.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] TSMC Says 'No More' To Nvidia: Why That Is Intel's Golden Ticket</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-says-no-more-nvidia-161151468.html</link><description>The AI boom just hit a constraint investors don't talk about enough: you can't ship what you can't build. Demand for AI chips is still surging, but the world's leading foundry, Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd (NYSE:TSM), or TSMC, is starting to run out of room. That matters — because when supply, not demand, becomes the bottleneck, the entire power structure of the AI trade begins to shift. When The Kingmaker Runs Out Of Capacity According to a report first published by The Information</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-says-no-more-nvidia-161151468.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Investors Worried About Large Cap Concentration Risk Have a Great Option in MDY</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/investors-worried-about-large-cap-concentration-risk-have-a-great-option-in-mdy/</link><description>The SPDR S&amp;amp;P 500 ETF Trust (NYSEARCA:SPY) tells a story of increasing concentration. The S&amp;amp;P 500 has become a technology-dominated index, with information technology representing over a third of its weight. This concentration intensifies at the top, where just three mega-cap tech companies control more than a fifth of the entire index’s value—creating a portfolio ... Investors Worried About Large Cap Concentration Risk Have a Great Option in MDY</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/investors-worried-about-large-cap-concentration-risk-have-a-great-option-in-mdy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>