<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[AAPL] Wall Street Is Starting to Like Intel Stock Again</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/wall-street-is-starting-to-like-intel-stock-again/</link><description>The once-hated stock is starting to win some fans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/wall-street-is-starting-to-like-intel-stock-again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] As Trump's deadline for a cap on credit card rates looms, banks have only questions and no answers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-deadline-cap-credit-card-134909277.html</link><description>President Donald Trump a week ago told the credit card industry it had until Jan. 20 to comply with his demand for a 10% cap on interest rates.  With just days to go, consumer groups, politicians, and bankers alike remain unclear on what the White House has planned and whether Trump even remains serious about the idea.  White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt said the president has “an expectation” that credit card companies will accede to his demand that they cap interest rates on credit cards at 10%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-deadline-cap-credit-card-134909277.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Insiders Sold US$23m Of Shares Suggesting Hesitancy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-insiders-sold-us-23m-130031482.html</link><description>Many Apple Inc. ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) insiders ditched their stock over the past year, which may be of interest to the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-insiders-sold-us-23m-130031482.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: Nvidia Will Become the First $6 Trillion Company in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-nvidia-will-become-the-first-6-trillion/</link><description>High demand marches on for Nvidia's AI products and services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-nvidia-will-become-the-first-6-trillion/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] The 1 Vanguard ETF That Warren Buffett's Recent Remarks Suggest He Would Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-vanguard-etf-warren-buffett-recent-remarks/</link><description>There's one Vanguard bond ETF that Buffett would love.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-vanguard-etf-warren-buffett-recent-remarks/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 Quantum Computing Stocks That Could Make a Millionaire</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/2-quantum-computing-stocks-that-could-make-a-milli/</link><description>These players may help you along the path to wealth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/2-quantum-computing-stocks-that-could-make-a-milli/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Nvidia and Buys 2 Other Magnificent Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks Instead</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-nvidia-and/</link><description>Peter Thiel recently sold his stake in Nvidia and rotated capital into Apple and Microsoft.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-sells-nvidia-and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Does a $21 Million Exit Amid a 43% Drop in Share Prices Raise Questions About This Packaging Stock?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/16/does-a-usd21-million-exit-amid-a-43-drop-in-share-prices-raise-questions-about-this-packaging-stock/</link><description>Graphic Packaging provides fiber-based packaging for food, beverage, and consumer goods firms, emphasizing sustainable solutions worldwide.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/16/does-a-usd21-million-exit-amid-a-43-drop-in-share-prices-raise-questions-about-this-packaging-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Assessing Barclays (LSE:BARC) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-barclays-lse-barc-valuation-010935217.html</link><description>What Barclays’ recent performance data tells you right now Barclays (LSE:BARC) has drawn attention after a period of strong share price moves, with a 1-year total return of 73.47% and a past 3-month total return of 36.65%. This has prompted fresh interest in its valuation. See our latest analysis for Barclays. Recent trading suggests momentum is building, with a 30 day share price return of 6.72% and a 90 day share price return of 36.65%. The 1 year total shareholder return of 73.47%, along...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-barclays-lse-barc-valuation-010935217.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Dividend Investor Earns $30K a Month After 37 Years, Says He Started Investing in 1988 With Student Loans</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dividend-investor-earns-30k-month-000137613.html</link><description>Many investors underestimate the power of staying invested. Riding out market volatility and uncertainty while holding quality stocks can lead to dramatic long-term results. In May, a dividend investor posted in a Reddit community that he reached $1,000 per day in dividend income after 37 years of investing. The portfolio screenshots shared by the investor on the social platform showed his monthly dividend income stood at $30,417. Don't Miss: Missed Nvidia and Tesla? RAD Intel Could Be the Next</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dividend-investor-earns-30k-month-000137613.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trump at Davos, Netflix earnings, SCOTUS hearing: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-davos-netflix-earnings-scotus-000054604.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come next week, including earnings results from companies like Netflix (NFLX), Procter &amp;amp; Gamble (PG), and United Airlines (UAL); President Trump's attendance at the 2026 World Economic Forum (WEF) in Davos, Switzerland; the US Supreme Court's (SCOTUS) hearing on whether the Trump administration has the power to remove Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook; and November's reading on the Personal Consumption Expenditures index (PCE). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-davos-netflix-earnings-scotus-000054604.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Google to Appeal US Court Ruling of Illegal Monopoly in Search</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-appeal-us-court-ruling-224756049.html</link><description>The notice of Google’s appeal was filed Friday in Washington federal court, along with a request to put the lower-court ruling on hold while the appeal is pending.  The DC Circuit Court of Appeals will likely hear the case later this year.  The court, which hears many appeals related to the federal government, takes about a year to issue a decision after an appeal notice is filed, according to statistics compiled by the US Courts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-appeal-us-court-ruling-224756049.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL) Declines More Than Market: Some Information for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-declines-more-market-224504998.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) reached $255.52 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a -1.04% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-declines-more-market-224504998.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: This Stock Will Join the $3 Trillion Club by the End of 2026. You're Going to Want to Buy It Now.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-this-stock-will-join-the-3-trillion-clu/</link><description>Broadcom is primed to deliver explosive growth this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/prediction-this-stock-will-join-the-3-trillion-clu/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 AI Stocks to Buy in 2026, and 1 to Avoid</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/2-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-1-to-avoid/</link><description>Some AI-focused companies are not worth the trouble.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/2-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-1-to-avoid/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Reports Earnings on January 22. Here Is Where Options Data Says INTC Stock Could Be Trading Next.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37090544/intel-reports-earnings-on-january-22-here-is-where-options-data-says-intc-stock-could-be-trading-next</link><description>Intel shares have soared heading into the firm’s earnings release on Jan. 22. But a Citi analyst and options traders believe INTC stock will push higher from here in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37090544/intel-reports-earnings-on-january-22-here-is-where-options-data-says-intc-stock-could-be-trading-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Earnings live: PNC rounds out bank earnings this week as attention shifts to Netflix, Intel</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-pnc-rounds-out-bank-earnings-this-week-as-attention-shifts-to-netflix-intel-214153842.html</link><description>A broader set of sectors will be represented when 35 more S&amp;amp;P 500 companies report earnings next week, including Netflix, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-pnc-rounds-out-bank-earnings-this-week-as-attention-shifts-to-netflix-intel-214153842.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How Apple TV Is Quietly Becoming a Threat to Netflix's Growth Story</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/apple-is-quietly-becoming-a-threat-to-netflix-in-s/</link><description>The tech giant is starting to show real momentum in streaming, and it has some structural advantages.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/16/apple-is-quietly-becoming-a-threat-to-netflix-in-s/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] An AI Smart Pen from OpenAI Sounds Weird—Until You Consider These Use Cases</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/an-ai-smart-pen-from-openai-sounds-weird-until-you-consider-these-use-cases/</link><description>There’s been a lot of buzz around OpenAI and the secret device(s) it’s been working on behind the scenes with the expertise of an industry veteran like former Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) chief design officer Jony Ive. While Ive is arguably the undisputed king of device design, there’s no guarantee that OpenAI’s AI gadgets will hit the ... An AI Smart Pen from OpenAI Sounds Weird—Until You Consider These Use Cases</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/an-ai-smart-pen-from-openai-sounds-weird-until-you-consider-these-use-cases/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Leaders Head to Davos, Earnings Heat Up: What to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/leaders-head-to-davos-earnings-heat-up-what-to-watch-next-week-WafuDV6W06uawgDUha5p?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>President Trump will lead the U.S. delegation to the annual meeting of the World Economic Forum next week in Davos, Switzerland, along with other government and business leaders. Meanwhile, earnings season is also kicking into gear, with announcements expected from companies including Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, Intel and Netflix.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-16-2026/card/leaders-head-to-davos-earnings-heat-up-what-to-watch-next-week-WafuDV6W06uawgDUha5p?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] 3 Key Earnings Releases to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-key-earnings-releases-watch-201900118.html</link><description>The 2025 Q4 earnings season is in full swing, with results from the big banks this week kicking the period into a much higher gear.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-key-earnings-releases-watch-201900118.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Vanguard’s $10.8B ETF Made 19% Betting on AI Infrastructure</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/vanguards-10-8b-etf-made-19-betting-on-ai-infrastructure/</link><description>If you want to bet that Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL), NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA), and Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) will continue dominating the market, Vanguard Mega Cap Index Fund ETF Shares (NYSEARCA:MGC) offers a straightforward way to do it. MGC takes a concentrated approach to mega-cap technology, with Apple, NVIDIA, and Microsoft representing nearly a quarter of the fund’s assets. This ... Vanguard’s $10.8B ETF Made 19% Betting on AI Infrastructure</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/vanguards-10-8b-etf-made-19-betting-on-ai-infrastructure/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Memory Explosion | MU Stock, SNDK Stock, SK Hynix, CAMT Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-memory-explosion-mu-stock-sndk-stock-sk-hynix-camt-stock/</link><description>Summary: To ring in 2026, our 24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are counting down 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. The first trend the two will be discussing is the AI-driven “memory explosion” that has been emerging as a core investment theme as inference, larger context windows, and ... 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Memory Explosion | MU Stock, SNDK Stock, SK Hynix, CAMT Stock</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-memory-explosion-mu-stock-sndk-stock-sk-hynix-camt-stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] The Pressure on Memory Chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/pressure-memory-chips-191256217.html</link><description>HP was hit with back-to-back downgrades. Barclays turns bearish, warning of structural PC weakness, rising memory costs, and no clear catalysts ahead. CFRA flags margin pressure from unprecedented inflation. New Street Research analyst Antoine Chkaiban joined Bloomberg Open Interest with his take on the sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/pressure-memory-chips-191256217.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Cathie Wood's ARK Invest Says Apple's Reliance On Google For AI Signals Deeper Trouble</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-says-190119374.html</link><description>Apple Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AAPL) decision to outsource its artificial intelligence (AI) foundation to Alphabet Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google is not a strategic masterstroke but a sign of a company in “huge, hairy trouble,” according to the research team at Cathie Wood's ARK Invest. ‘Strategic Disaster’ During the latest episode of ARK’s “The Brainstorm,” Chief Futurist Brett Winton offered a scathing critique of the newly announced partnership that will see Google's Gemini models power Si</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-says-190119374.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Why Is Meta Platforms Priced 36% Cheaper Than Its Hyperscaler Peers?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/why-is-meta-platforms-priced-36-cheaper-than-its-hyperscaler-peers/</link><description>Meta Platforms (NASDAQ:META) has delivered outstanding performance compared its hyperscaler peers such as Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL), Amazon (NASDAQ:AMZN), Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOG)(NASDAQ:GOOGL), and Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT). Over the last 12 months, revenue growth hit 21.3%, far exceeding the low- to mid-teens rates for the others, such as with Alphabet at 13.4% and Amazon below that. And in the past ... Why Is Meta Platforms Priced 36% Cheaper Than Its Hyperscaler Peers?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/16/why-is-meta-platforms-priced-36-cheaper-than-its-hyperscaler-peers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple (AAPL)’s The Place to Go If You Want to Make Some Money, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-place-want-money-182444686.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer talked about. Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL)’s been in the news as the year starts to settle. The firm made the news earlier this week after it announced that it would use Google’s Gemini to power an […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-place-want-money-182444686.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Fall Despite Citi Upgrade Amid Foundry Hopes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-fall-despite-citi-182235864.html</link><description>Analysts See Window Against TSMC Tightness</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-fall-despite-citi-182235864.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Alphabet (GOOGL) Shares Being Down is “Just Plain Stupid,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-shares-being-down-181831619.html</link><description>We recently published 9 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer talked about. Within a year, Jim Cramer has turned increasingly optimistic and bullish about technology giant Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL). Early last year, he sold the shares on the back of worries about the Justice Department’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-shares-being-down-181831619.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Chipmaker TSMC Adds Fuel To AI Megatrend Hype With Q4 Report</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/tsm-stock-record-high-tsmc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing is basking in the glow of strong sales of advanced chips for AI data centers. TSM stock notched a record high.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/tsm-stock-record-high-tsmc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Rally Extends as Analyst Upgrades Spotlight Foundry Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rally-extends-analyst-upgrades-175817741.html</link><description>Shares climb early in 2026 as Wall Street upgrades and foundry optimism build ahead of fourth-quarter earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-rally-extends-analyst-upgrades-175817741.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Calls This 1 AI Server Stock ‘Best in Class’ Amid Upgrade to ‘Overweight’ Rating</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37086735/barclays-calls-this-1-ai-server-stock-best-in-class-amid-upgrade-to-overweight-rating</link><description>Dell Technologies' stock offers significant upside potential in 2026, given its widening AI moat, according to Barclays.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37086735/barclays-calls-this-1-ai-server-stock-best-in-class-amid-upgrade-to-overweight-rating</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Jim Cramer Says “Alphabet Increasingly Looks Like the Only Winner in AI for the Moment”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-alphabet-increasingly-171317205.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar recently. Cramer mentioned the company during the episode and said: “Hey, you want hate? I’ll give you hate. All you have to do is declare you’re going for clean energy to power your data centers. If Microsoft and Meta Platforms were to abandon […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-alphabet-increasingly-171317205.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Don’t Go Chasing Semis (Yet). What the Charts Say About Entry Points for 3 Chip Stocks.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/semiconductor-stocks-rally-entry-points-amd-marvell-texas-instruments-stocks-9c4ba532?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>FEATURE  The last three months have seen investors clearly sour on technology stocks and move into value-oriented plays. The three best-performing S&amp;amp;P sectors, and the only ones to have delivered double digit gains over that time frame, are energy, materials, and healthcare, reflected in their ETF proxies and   One notable exception to this tech exodus is the robust action in the semiconductor segment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/semiconductor-stocks-rally-entry-points-amd-marvell-texas-instruments-stocks-9c4ba532?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[EBS.VI] Erste Group Bank (EBKDY) Upgraded to Buy: Here's What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/erste-group-bank-ebkdy-upgraded-170004568.html</link><description>Erste Group Bank (EBKDY) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company's earnings prospects. This might drive the stock higher in the near term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/erste-group-bank-ebkdy-upgraded-170004568.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Sprout Social (SPT) Stock Is Nosediving</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-sprout-social-spt-stock-162541553.html</link><description>Shares of social media management platform Sprout Social (NASDAQ:SPT) fell 5.9% in the morning session after analysts at Morgan Stanley lowered their price target on the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-sprout-social-spt-stock-162541553.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>