<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Personal Stock News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news from yfinance for my portfolio</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/stocks_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[INTC] Why Advanced Micro Devices Stock Popped Friday</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-advanced-micro-devices-stock-popped-friday/</link><description>Intel's troubles may be AMD's opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-advanced-micro-devices-stock-popped-friday/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks to watch next week: Tesla, Meta, Microsoft, Apple and Lloyds</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-meta-microsoft-apple-lloyds-stocks-to-watch-153735797.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-meta-microsoft-apple-lloyds-stocks-to-watch-153735797.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017784.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017784.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Boeing Stock Rips Higher Ahead Of Q4 Results; 3 Data Storage Stocks In Earnings Spotlight</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/boeing-stock-rips-higher-q4-earnings-data-storage-western-digital-seagate-sandisk-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Boeing stock has been on a tear ahead of its Q4 report as Wall Street bets on clearer skies ahead for the aerospace giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/boeing-stock-rips-higher-q4-earnings-data-storage-western-digital-seagate-sandisk-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Q4 2025 Earnings Call Transcript</title><link>https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/23/intel-intc-q4-2025-earnings-call-transcript/</link><description>Over the last 10 months, we established the foundation for new Intel, a more focus and execution-driven company.  Along with our next-generation Nova Lake coming at the end of 2026, we now have a client road map that combines best-in-class performance with cost-optimized solutions giving me confidence that we are on the path to fortify market share and profitability in both notebooks and desktops over the next several years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/23/intel-intc-q4-2025-earnings-call-transcript/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds set to see annual profits rise despite motor finance hit</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-set-see-annual-profits-144621947.html</link><description>Most analysts expect the lender to deliver a 7% rise in pre-tax profits for the year, with the City pencilling in £6.38 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-set-see-annual-profits-144621947.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel stock sinks as company's Q1 outlook falls short of Wall Street expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-sinks-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143343615.html</link><description>Intel reported fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-sinks-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143343615.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Andrew Ng Thinks AI Apps are “Underinvested”—Here are the Stocks I’d Buy in Response</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/andrew-ng-thinks-ai-apps-are-underinvested-here-are-the-stocks-id-buy-in-response/</link><description>While others see an inflating AI bubble that could burst and lose investors a boatload of money, others see underinvestment in some specific parts of the theme. Undoubtedly, it’s hard to know with any degree of certainty where the AI trade goes next, especially as other volatility drivers (think Trump tariffs) are thrown into the ... Andrew Ng Thinks AI Apps are “Underinvested”—Here are the Stocks I’d Buy in Response</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/andrew-ng-thinks-ai-apps-are-underinvested-here-are-the-stocks-id-buy-in-response/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Intel, AMD, Tesla, Capital One, Booz Allen, BitGo, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-c4ed1582?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel shares plummet following disappointing guidance, while rival AMD is poised to add to an eight-day winning streak.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-c4ed1582?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock sinks on weak guidance: Q4 earnings takeaways</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-sinks-weak-guidance-141418133.html</link><description>Intel stock (INTC) continues to fall lower in Friday's pre-market trading after the hardware and chip manufacturer released disappointing first quarter guidance. Yahoo Finance Tech and Markets Reporter Laura Bratton comes on Morning Brief to break down the biggest takeaways from Intel's earnings release, examining the company's foundry business in terms of AI data center demands and its outlook on its Panther Lake processors. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-sinks-weak-guidance-141418133.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel's stock falls 13% in premarket trading, after missing Wall Street estimates</title><link>https://qz.com/intel-stock-ai-chipmaker-shares-semiconductor</link><description>The chipmaker issued a softer-than-expected outlook for the first quarter, reigniting concerns about its turnaround</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://qz.com/intel-stock-ai-chipmaker-shares-semiconductor</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike (CRWD) Is a Trending Stock: Facts to Know Before Betting on It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-trending-stock-facts-140005624.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Therefore, it is wise to be aware of the facts that can impact the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-trending-stock-facts-140005624.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Most-Watched Stock Apple Inc. (AAPL) Worth Betting on Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-apple-inc-140002795.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately. So, it is worth exploring what lies ahead for the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-apple-inc-140002795.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel shares tumble as supply chain snarls hamper turnaround</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-shares-tumble-supply-chain-135036641.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Intel shares plunged 12% on Friday (January 23).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors sold off after the company struggled to meet strong AI demand for data center chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It blamed that on supply constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm had also forecast quarterly revenue and profit below market estimates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market watchers were disappointed as many had bet on Intel's turnaround.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm is a latecomer to the AI boom and has finally enjoyed a demand surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers want its traditional server chips which are used alongside AI processors in data centers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investor interest also grew due to investments in the firm from the U.S. government, Softbank and Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intel's stock outpaced most semiconductor firms last year with an 84% gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It extended its rally into this year - and was up close to half this month so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the company couldn't keep up with the demand surge even as it runs factories at capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also warned a spike in memory chip prices could hurt sales in the PC market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its new "Panther Lake" PC chips were expected to spark a comeback after years of market share losses to AMD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The memory chip surge is driven by growing AI demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Intel said it expects available memory supply to improve in the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That after hitting its lowest levels in the first quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-shares-tumble-supply-chain-135036641.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple, Microsoft, and Tesla Earnings Loom as Stocks Stall and Risks Mount. Something’s Got to Give.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-microsoft-tesla-earnings-stock-market-risk-eed32393?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>With U.S. stocks stuck in their worst rut since the summer, Treasury bonds in a slump, gold testing $5,000 for the first time on record, and geopolitical risks dominating, the stakes couldn’t be higher for the first round of mega tech earnings coming up next week.  Four of the so-called Magnificent Seven tech giants—  Microsoft Meta Platforms Tesla  and  Apple  —are slated to post quarterly earnings next week.  Outside of the Mag 7 updates, just over 100 companies are expected to post fourth-quarter updates over the coming week, as well as near-term outlooks that will either test or consolidate that current investor rotation away from tech and growth stocks into so-called value names.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/apple-microsoft-tesla-earnings-stock-market-risk-eed32393?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls In Wake Of Greenland Deal Rally; Intel Plunges After Earnings (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Friday following two days of gains from the Greenland deal rally. Intel plunged on earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Shares Drop 12% on AI Supply Constraints</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-drop-12-ai-125949151.html</link><description>Shortfall in data-center chip supply weighs on turnaround hopes.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-drop-12-ai-125949151.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dow Jones Futures Fall As Intel Dives, Nvidia Gets H200 China Boost; Tesla Self-Driving In Focus</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-intel-dives-nvidia-h200-chips-china-tesla-self-driving/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Futures fell after as Intel dived, but Nvidia H200 chip sales may be close in China. Tesla has big self-driving robotaxi news..</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-intel-dives-nvidia-h200-chips-china-tesla-self-driving/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Faces Memory-Price Crunch. Why Apple Will Be the Next Victim.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-memory-8b5df4e5?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock was falling as it faces headwinds from soaring memory-chip prices, which could hit other companies such as Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-memory-8b5df4e5?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] BTIG Remains a Buy on CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (CRWD)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/btig-remains-buy-crowdstrike-holdings-123952313.html</link><description>​CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the Best Cybersecurity Stocks to Buy in 2026. Wall Street is bullish on the stock, with analysts’ 12-month price targets suggesting more than 26% upside from current levels. Recently, on January 20, Gray Powell from BTIG reiterated a Buy rating on CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) with a $640 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/btig-remains-buy-crowdstrike-holdings-123952313.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Slid After Supply Shortages Hit Its Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-slid-supply-shortages-123453421.html</link><description>Supply shortages weigh on guidance, manufacturing execution in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-slid-supply-shortages-123453421.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is It Too Late to Sell Lucid Motors Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37193765/is-it-too-late-to-sell-lucid-motors-stock</link><description>Lucid Motors stock fell to a record low and briefly plunged below $10. Is it too late to sell the struggling startup EV stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37193765/is-it-too-late-to-sell-lucid-motors-stock</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Gold Has Shone. How Trump, Fed Can Keep It Surging in a Turbulent Market.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/gold-prices-trump-fed-things-to-know-today-e48324fb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel is still facing supply constraints, Trump vows retaliation as ‘Sell America’ list grows, airlines brace for chaos ahead of winter storm, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/gold-prices-trump-fed-things-to-know-today-e48324fb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Shares Slide After Weak Forecast, Manufacturing Issues Resurface</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slide-weak-forecast-113556797.html</link><description>First-quarter revenue outlook misses estimates as CEO warns low yields and supply constraints will take time to fix.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slide-weak-forecast-113556797.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Shares Nosedive On Disappointing Outlook Despite Q4 Beat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-nosedive-disappointing-outlook-113235121.html</link><description>Intel Stock Slides After Outlook Disappoints. Why Investors Looked Past the Q4 Beat</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-nosedive-disappointing-outlook-113235121.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Greg Abel's First Significant Move Since Warren Buffett's Retirement Was Likely Just Revealed by One of Berkshire Hathaway's Largest Holdings</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/greg-abel-first-move-since-warren-buffett-retired/</link><description>Although everyone is waiting for Abel's first stock purchase as CEO, it's his selling activity that could leave an indelible mark.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/greg-abel-first-move-since-warren-buffett-retired/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Lenovo looking to partner with multiple AI models, CFO says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lenovo-looking-partner-multiple-ai-110900834.html</link><description>Lenovo is seeking partnerships with multiple large language models around the world to power its ​devices as it aims to establish itself as a global AI ‌player, the company's chief financial officer said.  Lenovo, the world's largest personal computer maker, plans to equip its ‌broad range of products - from PCs to smartphones and wearables - with AI technology.  "We are the only company besides Apple with significant market share across both ⁠PCs and mobiles, and in ‌the open Android and Windows ecosystems," Lenovo CFO Winston Cheng told Reuters on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum in ‍Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lenovo-looking-partner-multiple-ai-110900834.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[PHNX.L] Aegon attracts bidders for $2.7bn UK insurance business</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/aegon-uk-insurance-business-bidders/</link><description>Since late last year, the Netherlands-based insurer has been reviewing options for its UK insurance and workplace business.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/aegon-uk-insurance-business-bidders/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple and Dell supplier Pegatron expects US plant to be completed by end of March</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230142.html</link><description>TAIPEI, Jan 23 () - Taiwanese ​contract electronics ‌manufacturer Pegatron's first ‌U. factory is expected to be ⁠completed ‌by the end of ‍March, with trial production to ​begin around ‌then or April, President and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng said ⁠on Friday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230142.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stocks to Watch Friday: Intel, Capital One, CSX</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-intel-capital-one-csx-9Goek52ChmE0WrX9mR8l?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ Intel (INTC): The chip maker swung to a bigger-than-expected loss and forecast more losses this quarter. It said it hadn’t adequately anticipated demand from AI data centers. Shares slid more than 12% in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-friday-intel-capital-one-csx-9Goek52ChmE0WrX9mR8l?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple supplier Pegatron expects US plant to be completed by end-March</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230268.html</link><description>Taiwanese contract electronics manufacturer Pegatron's first U.S. factory, in Texas, is expected ​to be completed by the end of March, with ‌trial production to begin around then or April, President and CEO Kuang-Chih Cheng ‌said on Friday.  The company, a supplier to Apple, Microsoft and Tesla, said in October it had acquired an industrial building and land in Texas, joining other Taiwanese tech manufacturers investing in the state ⁠including Foxconn, Inventec and ‌Wistron.  "It is currently scheduled to be completed by the end of ​March, and we should be able to begin trial ‌production in late March or April."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-dell-supplier-pegatron-expects-093230268.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Falls After Loss Exceeds Forecasts</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-stock-falls-after-loss-exceeds-forecasts-FbF4fVVxIbHSiWm2Uo72?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock dropped offhours, after the chip maker swung to a larger-than-expected quarterly loss.  Shares slid 13% in recent premarket trading.   Intel forecast further losses to start 2026, as it spends heavily to ramp up production of its latest chips and contends with an inventory shortage.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-stock-falls-after-loss-exceeds-forecasts-FbF4fVVxIbHSiWm2Uo72?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Trending tickers: Tesla, Intel, Ericsson, Ubisoft and Oracle</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-intel-ericsson-ubisoft-oracle-trending-tickers-092310095.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Friday</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-intel-ericsson-ubisoft-oracle-trending-tickers-092310095.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Prediction: 4 Stocks That'll Be Worth More Than Apple 5 Years From Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/prediction-x-stocks-thatll-be-worth-more-than-writ/</link><description>Apple's lack of growth will allow others to catch up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/prediction-x-stocks-thatll-be-worth-more-than-writ/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] How to navigate market swings as Trump's Greenland pivot gives investors whiplash</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-swings-trump-greenland-investing-060049008.html</link><description>The first few weeks of the year have been marked by rapid shifts in geopolitical relations, which has driven some major moves in markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-swings-trump-greenland-investing-060049008.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Pensions system ‘built for men’ leaves women facing retirement crisis</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/pensions-system-woman-retirement-crisis-060025959.html</link><description>Nearly 15 million people in the UK are not saving enough for retirement, according to DWP, with women disproportionately affected.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/pensions-system-woman-retirement-crisis-060025959.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Corp (INTC) Q4 2025 Earnings Call Highlights: Surpassing Expectations and Navigating ...</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-corp-intc-q4-2025-050123928.html</link><description>Intel Corp (INTC) reports strong financial performance and technological advancements, while addressing supply constraints and strategic growth plans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-corp-intc-q4-2025-050123928.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 05:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Gets Slammed. Is This a Buy-the-Dip Moment?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/intel-stock-gets-slammed-is-this-a-buy-the-dip-mom/</link><description>Intel's quarter was fine, but its near-term outlook is still being held back by supply -- and the stock does not look cheap enough to ignore that.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/intel-stock-gets-slammed-is-this-a-buy-the-dip-mom/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Is Now the Time to Move Away From the "Magnificent Seven" and Into Small-Cap Stocks?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/is-now-the-time-to-move-away-from-the-magnificent/</link><description>Many of the "Magnificent Seven" stocks have been losing steam over the past year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/is-now-the-time-to-move-away-from-the-magnificent/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] The Age of AI Agents Brings a Risk No One Is Prepared For</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence companies have promised that 2026 will be the year of agents: Software that can use AI language models to autonomously execute a complex series of tasks from simple instructions.  The most prevalent use for agents today is for making software.  With enough of a budget, a single developer can orchestrate teams of agents to work on existing codebases or even to start a project from scratch.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] How The Latest Price Target Shift Is Rewriting The Story For Aviva (LSE:AV.)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-price-target-shift-rewriting-010715321.html</link><description>Why Aviva’s latest price target shift matters now The latest change in the price target for Aviva puts fresh focus on how analysts are reassessing the story behind the stock, even without a clear, published rationale attached to the move. With no detailed commentary provided on what is driving this revision, you are left reading between the lines and weighing what it might signal about expectations for the business. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of future price target updates and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-price-target-shift-rewriting-010715321.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:07:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Podcast: Stocks Rise as Tariff Tensions Cool</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/podcast-stocks-rise-as-tariff-tensions-cool-tDi4j8GoDf8BPnjJawUX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The gains occur as investors look for more details about President Trump's desire to annex Greenland. Plus, Intel predicts further losses next quarter in an after-hours earnings report. And shares in Abbott Laboratories fall after the company misses sales expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-22-2026/card/podcast-stocks-rise-as-tariff-tensions-cool-tDi4j8GoDf8BPnjJawUX?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Returns to Losses as Supply Shortages and Spending Weigh on Q4 Results and Forecast</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/intel-intl-q4-earnings-report-2025-9271b096?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The troubled chip maker has seen its shares rise with AI demand and new investors, but revenue sagged 3.9% year-over-year to $13.7 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/intel-intl-q4-earnings-report-2025-9271b096?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/intel-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) executives used the company’s fourth-quarter 2025 earnings call to highlight progress on an internal reset, improving execution on new process technologies, and accelerating efforts to meet what management described as intense AI-driven demand that remains constrained by supply.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/intel-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow leads S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq waver after volatile week as Intel earnings fall short</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-leads-sp-500-nasdaq-waver-after-volatile-week-as-intel-earnings-fall-short-234147579.html</link><description>Wall Street is faltering as it heads into the end of holiday shortened but rollercoaster week defined by Trump's moves on Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-leads-sp-500-nasdaq-waver-after-volatile-week-as-intel-earnings-fall-short-234147579.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow leads S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq lower after volatile week as Intel earnings fall short</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-leads-sp-500-nasdaq-lower-after-volatile-week-as-intel-earnings-fall-short-234147356.html</link><description>Wall Street is faltering as it heads into the end of holiday shortened but rollercoaster week defined by Trump's moves on Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-leads-sp-500-nasdaq-lower-after-volatile-week-as-intel-earnings-fall-short-234147356.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures stall after volatile week as Intel earnings fall short</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-stall-after-volatile-week-as-intel-earnings-fall-short-234147705.html</link><description>Wall Street is regrouping after a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off messages regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-stall-after-volatile-week-as-intel-earnings-fall-short-234147705.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures falter as Trump Greenland drama marks latest volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-falter-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147093.html</link><description>Wall Street is regrouping after a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off messages regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-falter-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147093.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures muted as Trump Greenland drama marks latest volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-muted-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147406.html</link><description>Wall Street hit pause following a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off behaviour regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-muted-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147406.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures inch up as Trump Greenland drama marks latest volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-inch-up-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147076.html</link><description>Wall Street is taking a breather following a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off behaviour regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-inch-up-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147076.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures slip as Trump Greenland drama marks latest volatile week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147947.html</link><description>Wall Street is taking a breather following a rollercoaster week defined by Trump's on-and-off behaviour regarding Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-as-trump-greenland-drama-marks-latest-volatile-week-234147947.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Markets Up on Decent PCE &amp; Earnings. Q4 After the Close: INTC, COF, CSX</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-decent-pce-earnings-q4-230100566.html</link><description>Year over year PCE moved back up to +2.8% after dipping 10 bps the prior month, and Intel sells off even after beating estimates in Q4.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-decent-pce-earnings-q4-230100566.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Reports Q4 Earnings: What Key Metrics Have to Say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-reports-q4-earnings-230001051.html</link><description>The headline numbers for Intel (INTC) give insight into how the company performed in the quarter ended December 2025, but it may be worthwhile to compare some of its key metrics to Wall Street estimates and the year-ago actuals.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-reports-q4-earnings-230001051.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Sinks on Weak Outlook. CFO Says Chip Supply Will Improve Later This Year.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-1c25d034?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel stock fell sharply on Thursday after the chip maker offered disappointing guidance for its first-quarter revenue.  The company reported adjusted earnings per share of 15 cents in the quarter versus Wall Street’s consensus estimate for 8 cents, according to FactSet.  Intel shares fell as much as 10.9% following the company’s earnings release Thursday evening.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-1c25d034?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Dow Jones Futures Fall After Stocks Extend Rebound, Tesla Rallies On Self-Driving News; Intel Dives Late</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-greenland-tesla-rallies-self-driving-news-intel-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market extended its Greenland bounce, with Tesla rallying on big self-driving robotaxi news. Intel tumbled late.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-greenland-tesla-rallies-self-driving-news-intel-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel shares plunge on earnings expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-plunge-earnings-expectations-223932017.html</link><description>Intel shares dove more than 10 percent Thursday despite the struggling US chip maker doing better than expected in the recently ended quarter, as its revenue forecast disappointed investors.While the depth of losses beat market expectations, Intel's revenue forecast for the current quarter fell far short of what Wall Street analysts were predicting amid recently raised expectations for the company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-plunge-earnings-expectations-223932017.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel (INTC) Beats Q4 Earnings and Revenue Estimates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-beats-q4-earnings-222003648.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) delivered earnings and revenue surprises of +86.10% and +2.29%, respectively, for the quarter ended December 2025. Do the numbers hold clues to what lies ahead for the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-intc-beats-q4-earnings-222003648.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Why Intel Stock Is Crashing in After-Hours Trading</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/why-intel-stock-is-crashing-in-after-hours-trading/</link><description>Intel exceeded analysts' Q4 2025 expectations, so what's driving the after-hours sell-off?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/why-intel-stock-is-crashing-in-after-hours-trading/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Struggles to Meet Demand, CEO Says After Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-struggles-meet-demand-ceo-215440905.html</link><description>Intel Corp.&amp;amp;nbsp;gave a lackluster forecast for the current quarter because supply shortages are making it harder to meet customer demand. Chief Executive Officer Lip-Bu Tan told Bloomberg's Ed Ludlow that demand is "quite strong." Ludlow reports on "Bloomberg The Close."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-struggles-meet-demand-ceo-215440905.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple's reported moves could mean John Ternus will be next CEO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-reported-moves-could-mean-214431755.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) reportedly quietly expanded the role of the company's hardware chief John Ternus, who is seen as a top contender to succeed Apple CEO Tim Cook, according to reporting from Bloomberg. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley sits down with Market Domination host Josh Lipton to take a closer look at what the report means for the iPhone maker and investors. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-reported-moves-could-mean-214431755.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel shares slip 4% as weak guidance overshadows Q4 earnings beat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slip-4-weak-213829898.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) shares fell 4% Thursday after the chipmaker issued disappointing first-quarter guidance that overshadowed better-than-expected fourth-quarter results, as the company continues to navigate supply constraints while transitioning to new technologies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-slip-4-weak-213829898.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stocks Settle Higher as Global Tensions Cool and the Economy Expands</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37183261/stocks-settle-higher-as-global-tensions-cool-and-the-economy-expands</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Index ($SPX ) (SPY ) on Thursday closed up +0.55%, the Dow Jones Industrials Index ($DOWI ) (DIA ) closed up +0.63%, and the Nasdaq 100 Index ($IUXX ) (QQQ ) closed up +0.76%. March E-mini S&amp;amp;P futures (ESH26 ) rose +0.52%, and March E-mini Nasdaq futures...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37183261/stocks-settle-higher-as-global-tensions-cool-and-the-economy-expands</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock drops on weak outlook: Analyst reacts to Q4 earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-drops-weak-outlook-213310075.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) stock is under pressure after the company's weak outlook overshadowed its fourth quarter results that beat on the top and bottom lines. TECHnalysis Research president Bob O'Donnell joins Market Domination Overtime to share his instant reaction to the legacy chipmaker's earnings print. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-drops-weak-outlook-213310075.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] US stocks rally again after Trump backs off Greenland tariff threat</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</link><description>Global stocks rallied Thursday, lifting US indices for a second straight day after President Donald Trump dialed back tariff threats on Europe over their opposition to a US takeover of Greenland.But relief came Wednesday when Trump backed down on threats to seize the Arctic island by force from ally Denmark and retracted his tariff threat.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock Drops On Weak First-Quarter Guidance After Q4 Beat</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/intel-stock-intc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Chipmaker Intel beat estimates for the fourth quarter but badly missed with its guidance for the current quarter. Intel stock fell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/intel-stock-intc-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel: Q4 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-q4-earnings-snapshot-212044392.html</link><description>The average estimate of 16 analysts surveyed by Zacks Investment Research was for earnings of 8 cents per share. The world's largest chipmaker posted revenue of $13.67 billion in the period, which also beat Street forecasts. Fourteen analysts surveyed by Zacks expected $13.37 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-q4-earnings-snapshot-212044392.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel stock falls after Q1 outlook disappoints</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-falls-q1-outlook-211218296.html</link><description>Intel (INTC) reported fourth quarter adjusted earnings of $0.15 per share versus an estimate of $0.09. However, it's first quarter earnings and revenue outlook were shy of Wall Street estimates. Market Domination Overtime Anchor Josh Lipton reports the breaking details. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-stock-falls-q1-outlook-211218296.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise for second day in a row as Greenland drama fades</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-for-second-day-in-a-row-as-greenland-drama-fades-210027669.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-for-second-day-in-a-row-as-greenland-drama-fades-210027669.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:02:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple further expands role of rumored CEO candidate John Ternus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-further-expands-role-rumored-200012255.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Apple Inc. has expanded hardware chief John Ternus’s responsibilities to include design work, according to a Bloomberg report Thursday, further positioning him as a potential successor to Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-further-expands-role-rumored-200012255.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Elon Musk Drops Major Cybercab, Optimus Production Update: 'Insanely Fast'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-drops-major-cybercab-190110898.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared an update regarding the upcoming Cybercab, as well as the Optimus Humanoid Robot's production timelines. Elon Musk Says Tesla Has Revamped Cybercab Production In a response to influencer Sawyer Merritt's post on the social media platform X, Musk, on Tuesday, shared that the initial production for any product "is always very slow and follows an S-curve." Merritt's post shared a video that showcased the Tesla Cybercab being produced with the "unbox</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-drops-major-cybercab-190110898.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Expands Hardware Chief’s Role in Latest Sign of CEO Candidacy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-expands-hardware-chief-role-185859457.html</link><description>Cook, who has led Apple since 2011 and turned 65 in November, quietly tapped Ternus to manage the company’s design teams at the end of last year, according to people with knowledge of the matter.  The responsibilities have special significance at Apple.  The role was held by Jony Ive, Jobs’ longtime design partner, until his departure in 2019.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-expands-hardware-chief-role-185859457.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Advanced Micro Devices’ Winning Streak Continues. How High Can the Chip Stock Go?</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/advanced-micro-devices-ai-chip-stock-7d9318d0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AMD shares are up 25% over that eight-day period and have soared more than 100% over the past year.  The iShares Semiconductor exchange-traded fund is up 51% over the past 12 months, bolstered in recent weeks by Intel’s sudden surge.  Intel is getting love for its new processors and positive comments from President Donald Trump, while AMD has, in comparison, flown under the radar to start 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/advanced-micro-devices-ai-chip-stock-7d9318d0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Wine, Water and No Chairs: Inside Trump’s Private Reception With CEOs in Davos</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/inside-trumps-private-reception-with-ceos-in-davos-543ef7d8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Apple’s Tim Cook, BlackRock’s Larry Fink and dozens more CEOs stood and waited for over an hour for a meet and greet with the president.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/inside-trumps-private-reception-with-ceos-in-davos-543ef7d8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Retains Smartphone Leadership as Its Chinese Shipments Soared Over 28% in Q4</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-retains-smartphone-leadership-chinese-180853910.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Stocks to Look For in 2026. On January 12, Reuters reported that Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) led the smartphone market with a 20% share worldwide. Apple’s iPhone 17 series had strong sales and gained demand in emerging and mid-sized markets, according to Counterpoint analyst Varun […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-retains-smartphone-leadership-chinese-180853910.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Stock In Focus -- Goldman Sees a Buying Opportunity Ahead of Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-focus-goldman-sees-175831784.html</link><description>Goldman Says Product Cycles Still Favor a Rebound</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-focus-goldman-sees-175831784.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Stock Market Today, Jan. 22: Strong U.S. GDP data, earnings lead stocks higher</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/latest-news/stock-market-today-jan-22</link><description>This live blog is refreshed periodically throughout the day with the latest updates from the market.To find the latest Stock Market Today threads, click here. Happy Thursday. This is TheStreet’s Stock Market Today for Jan. 22, 2026. You can follow the latest updates on the ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/latest-news/stock-market-today-jan-22</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Can PayPal’s Latest AI Bet Spark a Stock Revival?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/can-paypals-latest-ai-bet-spark-a-stock-revival/</link><description>PayPal (NASDAQ:PYPL) stock has declined 39% over the past year, reflecting investor worries about its competitive position as payment alternatives like Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) Pay and Stripe proliferate. The company faces pressure from fintech rivals offering seamless integrations and lower fees, eroding PayPal’s market share in digital transactions. Trading at around $57 per share, it hovers ... Can PayPal’s Latest AI Bet Spark a Stock Revival?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/can-paypals-latest-ai-bet-spark-a-stock-revival/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Michael O'Leary Promises To 'Undress' Elon Musk's Tantrum On X As Ryanair Launches Sale: Airline Wonders If Tesla CEO Needs A 'Break'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-oleary-promises-undress-elon-173119600.html</link><description>Irish airliner Ryanair Holdings PLC (NASDAQ:RYAAY) is turning its recent clashes with Elon Musk into a marketing spectacle, with the company’s CEO, Michael O'Leary, calling a press conference to discuss the billionaire entrepreneur’s “tantrum” on X. The ‘Great Idiots’ Sale On Tuesday, in a post on X, the carrier announced that its CEO will “Address/undress” Musk’s latest tantrum on the platform, in a press conference in Dublin on Wednesday morning. O’Leary also took a swipe at Musk’s understandi</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-oleary-promises-undress-elon-173119600.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Apple Pushes Lunar New Year Discounts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-pushes-lunar-discounts-171942490.html</link><description>China promotion targets older iPhones and devices</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-pushes-lunar-discounts-171942490.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] KHC Is Low-Hanging Fruit for Greg Abel: Which Warren Buffett Stock Will He Sell Next?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37178066/khc-is-low-hanging-fruit-for-greg-abel-which-warren-buffett-stock-will-he-sell-next</link><description>KHC might not be the only mistake made by Warren Buffet that Berkshire Hathaway’s new CEO might try and rectify.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37178066/khc-is-low-hanging-fruit-for-greg-abel-which-warren-buffett-stock-will-he-sell-next</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Warren Buffett Retires: Here’s the Money Advice He’s Giving Americans for 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-retires-money-advice-164403383.html</link><description>Learn the investing and money advice Warren Buffett is sharing with Americans as he retires, including smart financial moves to prepare for 2026 and beyond.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-retires-money-advice-164403383.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] Intel Bucks Market’s Tumble as Wall Street Warms to Chipmaker</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/intel-bucks-markets-tumble-as-wall-street-warms-to-chipmaker/</link><description>Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) shares climbed more than 3% yesterday even as broader markets plunged after Japan had a weaker than expected 20-year bond market sale. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped almost 900 points, marking its worst day since October. Combined with President Trump’s threats of tariffs on eight European countries opposing U.S. attempts to acquire ... Intel Bucks Market’s Tumble as Wall Street Warms to Chipmaker</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/intel-bucks-markets-tumble-as-wall-street-warms-to-chipmaker/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] The ‘Trump Effect’ Makes Intel’s Earnings Report Tonight Very Special. Why You Should Brace for a Double-Digit Move in INTC Stock.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37177799/the-trump-effect-makes-intels-earnings-report-tonight-very-special-why-you-should-brace-for-a-double-digit-move-in-intc-stock</link><description>Intel has a long way to fall back to its pre-Trump investment levels.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37177799/the-trump-effect-makes-intels-earnings-report-tonight-very-special-why-you-should-brace-for-a-double-digit-move-in-intc-stock</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AAPL] 2 Stocks to Watch as Stock Markets Plummet Over Greenland</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/2-stocks-to-watch-as-stock-markets-plummet-over-greenland/</link><description>The situation over in Greenland caused a bit of a market shock on Tuesday, with just about everything marching lower over fears of tariffs and related uncertainties. Undoubtedly, in the heat of the panic, it really felt as though Greenland-linked tariffs on numerous European countries would derail the market rally in its tracks. With Trump ... 2 Stocks to Watch as Stock Markets Plummet Over Greenland</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/2-stocks-to-watch-as-stock-markets-plummet-over-greenland/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Mobileye Global Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/mobileye-global-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Mobileye Global (NASDAQ:MBLY) executives struck an upbeat tone on the company’s fourth-quarter and full-year 2025 earnings call, pointing to stronger-than-expected demand trends through the year, expanding engagement on next-generation ADAS programs, and what they described as rising momentum for ro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/mobileye-global-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-22/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Has Barclays (LSE:BARC) Run Too Far After A 66% One Year Share Price Gain?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Barclays shares still offer value after a strong run, this article walks through how the current price stacks up against several valuation checks. The stock has been relatively steady in the near term, with a 0.9% decline over the last 7 days and a 1.6% gain over the last 30 days. The 1 year return of 66.2% and 3 year return of 194.8% put recent moves in a much longer context for anyone thinking about risk and reward. That 1 year return of 66.2% and a 5 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[INTC] Intel Stock's Torrid Rally Is About to Face Its Latest Test. Here's What You Need to Know.</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/intel-stock-s-torrid-rally-is-about-to-face-its-latest-test-here-s-what-you-need-to-know-earnings-intc-11890223</link><description>Intel is slated to report fourth-quarter results after the market closes today, after a strong run for the struggling chipmaker's stock in recent weeks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/intel-stock-s-torrid-rally-is-about-to-face-its-latest-test-here-s-what-you-need-to-know-earnings-intc-11890223</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>