<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[GOOG] How Will Dow Jones Futures React To Trump's Greenland Tariffs On NATO Nations?</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-tariffs-nato-nations-greenland-google/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>President Donald Trump will impose escalating tariffs on eight NATO members unless a deal is struck for the U.S. buying Greenland. How will markets react?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-tariffs-nato-nations-greenland-google/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Jim Cramer Says: “J&amp;J Deserves to Be Going Higher, But Not at This Speed, Not at This Pace”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-j-j-174852644.html</link><description>Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (NYSE:JNJ) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his thoughts on. Cramer noted how money managers are betting on an economic slowdown and remarked: “So let’s talk about Procter &amp;amp; Gamble and then let’s talk about a pharma company, J&amp;amp;J. Now, here are two companies that have products that you buy, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-j-j-174852644.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on NVIDIA: “It’s Meant to Be Owned, Not Traded”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-nvidia-meant-owned-174848604.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his thoughts on. Cramer emphasized owning and not trading the stock, as he said: “What about the amazing secular growth stocks that I talk about, the ones that are supposed to do well regardless of the economy? What do you do with those? Well, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-nvidia-meant-owned-174848604.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Says “Once They Cleaned Up the Balance Sheet, Intel Instantly Became a Much Better Story”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-once-cleaned-174842427.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his thoughts on. During the episode, Cramer highlighted the company’s comeback. He remarked: “Finally, let’s talk Intel, which has been way too hot… last year’s most surprising comeback story. The chipmaker seemed like it was being eaten alive by NVIDIA and AMD. The former […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-once-cleaned-174842427.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Jim Cramer Says “Lately, Though, Cisco’s Gotten Its Act Together”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-lately-though-174840590.html</link><description>Cisco Systems, Inc. (NASDAQ:CSCO) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his thoughts on. Cramer noted the company’s ups and downs during the episode, as he commented: “How about, and this one makes me so happy because it’s a Charitable Trust name, Cisco? Yes, the online networking play is a little different. Cisco spent […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-lately-though-174840590.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Jim Cramer on International Business Machines: “It’s Inexpensive Relative to Its Growth Rate”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-international-business-machines-174839988.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer shared his thoughts on. Cramer praised the company’s CEO, as he said: “Let’s take them one by one, starting with IBM, which has become an incredibly strong performer with a stock that’s nearly tripled since late 2022 when it broke free from its… […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-international-business-machines-174839988.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] US-Taiwan tariff deal boosts TSMC, will help iPhone, AI PC shoppers</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/us-taiwan-tariff-deal-boosts-tsmc-will-help-iphone-ai-pc-shoppers</link><description>The most important chipmaker in the world recently got caught up in another big change. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing is riding the AI wave, but the latest news isn't only about demand. The latest talk on Wall Street concerns where chips are created, how they get across borders, and what it ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/us-taiwan-tariff-deal-boosts-tsmc-will-help-iphone-ai-pc-shoppers</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Jefferies Remains Bullish on NVIDIA Corporation (NVDA)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-remains-bullish-nvidia-corporation-172942359.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the best stocks to buy in 2026 for beginners. On January 16, Jefferies lifted the price target on NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) to $275 from $250 and reiterated a Buy rating, telling investors that the stock “remains pretty cheap”, trading at mid-teens multiple to its bottom-up implied calendar year 2027 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-remains-bullish-nvidia-corporation-172942359.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 1 Hidden Reason Alphabet May Be a Brilliant Stock to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/1-hidden-reason-alphabet-may-be-a-brilliant-stock/</link><description>The tech giant's investment in SpaceX could provide a serious catalyst for the stock later this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/1-hidden-reason-alphabet-may-be-a-brilliant-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 'A broadening playbook': Wall Street sees stock market gains beyond tech</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/a-broadening-playbook-wall-street-sees-stock-market-gains-beyond-tech-160556466.html</link><description>Enthusiasm for artificial intelligence's prospects will continue to drive the market higher in 2026. The gains won't be limited to tech stocks, strategists say.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/a-broadening-playbook-wall-street-sees-stock-market-gains-beyond-tech-160556466.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia stock's next move hinges on Q4 earnings, Blackwell ramp</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/nvidia-stocks-next-move-hinges-on-q4-earnings-blackwell-ramp</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) enters its Q4 earnings cycle in a unique position. The stock has spent the last year riding AI's "Hardware Wave," but 2026 marks the beginning of the "Execution Era." Investors are no longer just asking how many chips Nvidia can sell, but how fast those chips can deliver real-world ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/nvidia-stocks-next-move-hinges-on-q4-earnings-blackwell-ramp</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mark Cuban Pushes Back On The Idea That Success Was Easier In The Past. Says He Graduated Into 20% Unemployment And 15% Interest Rates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-cuban-pushes-back-idea-153115015.html</link><description>Mark Cuban is no stranger to tough beginnings. In a recent exchange on Bluesky, the billionaire entrepreneur reminded followers that his path to wealth wasn't paved with ideal conditions. “When I graduated from college the unemployment rate in the state was 20pct and interest rates were 15pct,” he wrote. “I slept on the floor for almost 2 years.” Cuban Says Class Mobility Has Never Been Easy The conversation kicked off when a user challenged Cuban's claim that he could still build wealth today b</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-cuban-pushes-back-idea-153115015.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Alphabet Stock Before Feb. 4?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/should-you-buy-alphabet-stock-before-february-4/</link><description>The $4 trillion enterprise is ready to give investors a fresh update on its financial performance.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/should-you-buy-alphabet-stock-before-february-4/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] I Predicted Nvidia Was a Better Dow Stock Than Amazon in 2025, and I Was Right. But Which Is the Better "Magnificent Seven" Stock for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/prediction-amazon-nvidia-buy-growth-stock-2026/</link><description>Wall Street is underestimating the growth potential of Nvidia's Rubin architecture.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/prediction-amazon-nvidia-buy-growth-stock-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Where Meta's metaverse vision went wrong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/where-metas-metaverse-vision-went-wrong-150053527.html</link><description>Meta is pivoting away from the metaverse. Here's where it went wrong.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/where-metas-metaverse-vision-went-wrong-150053527.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You'd Invested $1,000 in Nvidia 5 Years Ago, Here's How Much You'd Have Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/you-invest-1000-nvidia-stock-5-years-ago-how-much/</link><description>Dominating the infrastructure layer of the AI boom has proved to be a very lucrative position to be in.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/you-invest-1000-nvidia-stock-5-years-ago-how-much/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dear Intel Stock Fans, Mark Your Calendars for January 22</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37102654/dear-intel-stock-fans-mark-your-calendars-for-january-22</link><description>Investors may want to keep Intel on their radar as the chip giant gears up to unveil its fourth-quarter earnings later this month.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37102654/dear-intel-stock-fans-mark-your-calendars-for-january-22</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ‘No Reasons to Own’: Software Stocks Sink on Fear of New AI Tool</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/no-reasons-own-software-stocks-140000103.html</link><description>The release of a new artificial intelligence tool from startup Anthropic on Jan. 12 rekindled fears about disruption that weighed on software makers in 2025.  TurboTax owner Intuit Inc. tumbled 16% last week, its worst since 2022, while Adobe Inc. and Salesforce Inc., which makes customer relationship management software, both sank more than 11%.  All told, a group of software-as-a-service stocks tracked by Morgan Stanley is down 15% so far this year, following a drop of 11% in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/no-reasons-own-software-stocks-140000103.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Bank stock picks, crypto trajectory, dealmaking appetite, and more takes from top execs this past week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bank-stock-picks-crypto-trajectory-dealmaking-appetite-and-more-takes-from-top-execs-this-past-week-133010645.html</link><description>Your new investing ideas think sheet, with comments from recent guests on Yahoo Finance's Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bank-stock-picks-crypto-trajectory-dealmaking-appetite-and-more-takes-from-top-execs-this-past-week-133010645.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump Eyes Plan To Make Big Tech Shoulder Their Own Data Center Power Costs: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-eyes-plan-big-tech-130523267.html</link><description>The Donald Trump administration will reportedly propose that PJM Interconnection, the largest power grid operator in the U.S., hold an emergency auction allowing tech giants and hyperscalers to bid on 15-year contracts for building new power plants. The grid spans 13 states across the mid-Atlantic, Midwest, and South, including northern Virginia. The directive is expected to be signed on Friday at the White House by the National Energy Dominance Council in the presence of Josh Shapiro, Governor</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-eyes-plan-big-tech-130523267.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Elon Musk's Grok 4.20 Beats OpenAI, Google Models In Live Stock Trading Contest — xAI CEO Jokes About Paying For GPUs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musks-grok-4-20-123855766.html</link><description>Elon Musk's xAI has scored an early win for real-world AI monetization after its Grok 4.20 model outperformed rivals from OpenAI and Alphabet Inc.'s (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google in a live stock trading competition. Grok 4.20 Tops Alpha Arena Live Trading Leaderboard Grok 4.20, an artificial intelligence model developed byMusk-led xAI, emerged as the top performer in Alpha Arena Season 1.5, a competition that pits AI models against each other in live stock trading using the same starting c</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musks-grok-4-20-123855766.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Quantum Computing Stock Plummeted 38% Last Year but Is Soaring in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-quantum-computing-stock-plummeted-38-last-year/</link><description>Quantum Computing stock surged more than 1,700% in 2024, but it suffered a significant pullback last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-quantum-computing-stock-plummeted-38-last-year/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Trump in Davos, Netflix and Intel results on deck as earnings season ramps: What to watch this week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-in-davos-netflix-and-intel-results-on-deck-as-earnings-season-ramps-what-to-watch-this-week-123046447.html</link><description>A holiday-shortened trading week will bring investors the start of tech earnings and a key speech from President Trump in Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-in-davos-netflix-and-intel-results-on-deck-as-earnings-season-ramps-what-to-watch-this-week-123046447.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Trump in Davos, Netflix and Intel results on deck earnings season ramps: What to watch this week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-in-davos-netflix-and-intel-results-on-deck-earnings-season-ramps-what-to-watch-this-week-123046356.html</link><description>A holiday-shortened trading week will bring investors the start of tech earnings and a key speech from President Trump in Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-in-davos-netflix-and-intel-results-on-deck-earnings-season-ramps-what-to-watch-this-week-123046356.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Waymo, Tesla Robotaxi Rival WeRide's Fleet Surpasses 1,000 AVs, Boasts Driverless Operations In 3 Cities: 'Tens Of Thousands…'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-tesla-robotaxi-rival-werides-121441091.html</link><description>Chinese robotaxi company WeRide Inc. (NASDAQ:WRD) has announced an expansion of its global autonomous cab fleet amid expansion. WeRide Now Has Over 1,000 Robotaxis In a post on the social media platform X on Thursday, the company announced the 1,000 Robotaxi feat, sharing that it has "reached 1,023 Robotaxis globally!" WeRide also announced that it had achieved driverless operations in Beijing, Guangzhou &amp;amp; Abu Dhabi. The company also shared that the milestone was an important step in its vision</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-tesla-robotaxi-rival-werides-121441091.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump Administration Offers Tariff Relief In Exchange For $250 Billion Taiwan Chip Investment — TSMC Weighs Arizona Expansion, Says Howard Lutnick</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-administration-offers-tariff-relief-121440194.html</link><description>On Thursday, the Donald Trump administration struck a trade agreement with Taiwan aimed at pulling hundreds of billions of dollars in semiconductor investment onto U.S. soil while easing tariff pressure on key Taiwanese exports. US–Taiwan Deal Targets Domestic Chip Manufacturing The Department of Commerce said Taiwanese chip and technology companies will invest at least $250 billion to expand semiconductor production capacity in the U.S. The Taiwanese government will provide $250 billion in cred</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-administration-offers-tariff-relief-121440194.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] The World's Most Important Chipmaker Just Confirmed the AI Megatrend Is Real</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/the-worlds-most-important-chipmaker-just-confirmed/</link><description>TSMC is finally ramping up capital spending in response to incredible demand for AI accelerators.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/the-worlds-most-important-chipmaker-just-confirmed/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Continues Its Massive Power Grab</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/google-continues-its-massive-power-grab/</link><description>Google continues to lock in new power supplies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/google-continues-its-massive-power-grab/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Snowflake (SNOW) Eyes AI Data Cloud Expansion with Strategic Acquisition of Observe</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-snow-eyes-ai-data-111628707.html</link><description>Snowflake Inc. (NYSE:SNOW) is one of the best stocks to buy right now. On January 8, 2026, Snowflake Inc. (NYSE:SNOW) announced its acquisition of Observe, a leader in AI-powered observability. The move marks a strategic expansion of the company’s AI Data Cloud, enabling enterprises to combine telemetry and business data and apply analytics and agentic […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-snow-eyes-ai-data-111628707.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Strong Analyst Sentiment on Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) Amid CES AI Processor Launches Despite Nvidia Competition</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-analyst-sentiment-advanced-micro-111619431.html</link><description>Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD) is included in our list of the best stocks to buy right now. As of January 12, 2026, 75% of analysts are bullish on Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMD). The consensus price target of $281.50 implies a 38.60% upside. Recent analyst commentaries reinforce the positive trend, with Jefferies reiterating a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-analyst-sentiment-advanced-micro-111619431.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Analysts Bullish on Broadcom (AVGO) Amid Strong AI Chip Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-bullish-broadcom-avgo-amid-111607957.html</link><description>Broadcom Inc. (NASDAQ:AVGO) is one of the best stocks to buy right now. On January 11, 2026, Mizuho revisited semiconductor stocks and shared its revised 2026 outlook. The firm expects continued demand for the sector, driven by artificial intelligence. It projects AI-related chips and equipment to continue to support the sector. However, it sees smaller […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-bullish-broadcom-avgo-amid-111607957.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sequoia to join GIC, Coatue in Anthropic investment, FT reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sequoia-join-gic-coatue-anthropic-111210461.html</link><description>Venture capital firm Sequoia is joining Singapore's GIC and U.S. ​investor Coatue in a funding round ‌for Anthropic which aims to raise $25 billion at a $350 ‌billion valuation, the Financial Times reported on Sunday, citing sources familiar with the matter. Singapore's sovereign wealth fund GIC, and Coatue will contribute $1.5 ⁠billion each for ‌the Claude chatbot-maker, the newspaper said. Sequoia, Anthropic, GIC and Coatue did ‍not immediately respond to a Reuters request for comment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sequoia-join-gic-coatue-anthropic-111210461.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 2 AI Stocks Could Join the $2 Trillion Club in 2026, According to Wall Street</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/these-2-ai-stocks-could-join-the-2-trillion-club-i/</link><description>These AI leaders could soon join a highly exclusive group.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/these-2-ai-stocks-could-join-the-2-trillion-club-i/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Is Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:ADI) Potentially Undervalued?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-inc-nasdaq-adi-110015597.html</link><description>Let's talk about the popular Analog Devices, Inc. ( NASDAQ:ADI ). The company's shares received a lot of attention from...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-inc-nasdaq-adi-110015597.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Says, "The Race Is On for AI." Here's What It Means for Nvidia Stock.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-the-race-is-on-for-ai/</link><description>AI development hit an inflection point that will power Nvidia into the future.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-the-race-is-on-for-ai/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What If SpaceX Does Not IPO in 2026? 1 Surprise Trick Elon Musk Might Have Up His Sleeve</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/what-if-spacex-does-not-ipo-in-2026/</link><description>SpaceX might not actually IPO in 2026. Can I interest you in a Starlink IPO instead?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/what-if-spacex-does-not-ipo-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Taiwan’s Flagship Chip Maker Charts a Future Beyond Taiwan</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/taiwan-semiconductor-tscm-us-investment-d96f77f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>TSMC has for decades provided a “Silicon Shield” to its namesake island. Now it sees both business and geopolitical reasons for going big in the U.S.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/taiwan-semiconductor-tscm-us-investment-d96f77f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] This Is My No. 1 Recommended Vanguard ETF to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/this-is-my-no-1-recommended-vanguard-etf-to-buy-in/</link><description>The stars could be aligning for healthcare stocks this year. This Vanguard ETF is a great way to play it.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/this-is-my-no-1-recommended-vanguard-etf-to-buy-in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] 5 big analyst AI moves: Nvidia top 2026 pick, ASML gets big price target hike</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-big-analyst-ai-moves-093006427.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Here are the biggest analyst moves in the area of artificial intelligence (AI) for this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-big-analyst-ai-moves-093006427.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Will humanoids be the growth engine of the 21st century?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/humanoids-growth-engine-21st-century-093005481.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Humanoid robots are moving rapidly from experimental prototypes to real-world workers, a shift Barclays says could redefine global labor markets and industrial supply chains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/humanoids-growth-engine-21st-century-093005481.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Street Calls of the Week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/street-calls-week-091530595.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Here is your Pro Recap of the top takeaways from Wall Street analysts for the past week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/street-calls-week-091530595.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Smartest Quantum Computing Stock to Buy for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/the-smartest-quantum-computing-stock-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Alphabet's Willow chip addresses a key challenge with advancing quantum computing technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/the-smartest-quantum-computing-stock-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is quantum the next great tech revolution?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/quantum-next-great-tech-revolution-083002166.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Quantum computing could achieve "quantum advantage,” where quantum systems significantly outperform classical computers, around 2033, according to UBS Global Research in a recent note. However, the technology "has consistently been ’5 years away’ for the last 20 years," the report cautions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/quantum-next-great-tech-revolution-083002166.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 08:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: 1 Unstoppable Stock to Buy Before It Soars 976%, According to 1 World-Renowned Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/prediction-1-unstoppable-stock-to-buy-before-it-so/</link><description>Strong secular tailwinds, a track record of innovation, and a market-leading position could drive this tech titan to new heights.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/prediction-1-unstoppable-stock-to-buy-before-it-so/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why the iShares Semiconductor ETF (SOXX) Jumped 40% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-the-ishares-semiconductor-etf-soxx-jumped-40/</link><description>AI stocks continued to soar last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-the-ishares-semiconductor-etf-soxx-jumped-40/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Global X Artificial Intelligence and Technology ETF (AIQ) Jumped 31% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-global-x-artificial-intelligence-and-technolog/</link><description>The AIQ ETF outpaced the Nasdaq for nearly the whole year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-global-x-artificial-intelligence-and-technolog/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Analysts Bullish on Lam Research Corporation (LRCX) as Semiconductor Capex and Memory Investments Rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-bullish-lam-research-corporation-055506724.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 10 Best Investments During A Recession. The fourth stock on our list of best investments is Lam Research Corporation. TheFly reported on January 9 that Goldman Sachs analyst James Schneider raised the LRCX price target to $180 from $160 while maintaining a Buy rating. Improved semiconductor industry circumstances, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-bullish-lam-research-corporation-055506724.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. (TMO) and NVIDIA Partner to Bring Advanced AI to Lab Workflows</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/thermo-fisher-scientific-inc-tmo-055425606.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 10 Best Investments During A Recession. Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. is placed second on our list. TheFly reported on January 9 that Stifel analyst Daniel Arias maintained a Buy rating on TMO and significantly raised the price target to $700 from $583, an increase of $117. According to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/thermo-fisher-scientific-inc-tmo-055425606.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Predicted That Nvidia Would Beat the S&amp;P 500 for the 3rd Consecutive Year in 2025. Here's Why the Streak Can Continue in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/nvidia-outperform-sp-500-2025-2026-buy-stock/</link><description>Nvidia continues to be a fundamentals-led growth story rather than one of hype and hot air.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/nvidia-outperform-sp-500-2025-2026-buy-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 04:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Clearway Energy (CWEN.A) Is Up 12.7% After Major New Google PPAs - Has The Bull Case Changed?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearway-energy-cwen-12-7-041040158.html</link><description>In January 2026, Clearway Energy Group announced that in 2025 it executed three long-term PPAs with Google totaling 1.17 GW of carbon-free energy projects across Missouri, Texas, and West Virginia, representing over US$2.40 billions in planned investment and expected to begin construction this year with initial operations in 2027 and 2028. This expansion lifts the Google–Clearway partnership to 1.24 GW and underscores Big Tech’s growing role in supporting large-scale, long-duration clean...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearway-energy-cwen-12-7-041040158.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 04:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Once-in-a-Generation Investment Opportunity: Here's My Top AI Stock for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/a-once-in-a-generation-investment-opportunity-here/</link><description>AI is a once-in-a-generation investment opportunity investors cannot afford to miss.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/a-once-in-a-generation-investment-opportunity-here/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Silicon Valley is really talking about fleeing California (it’s not the 5%)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-silicon-valley-really-talking-011711652.html</link><description>If you’ve been following the billionaire exodus from California with some confusion, here’s what’s actually driving the nervousness: it’s not the 5% rate. As highlighted Friday in the New York Post, the proposed wealth tax would hit founders on their voting shares rather than the actual equity they own. Take Larry Page, who about 3% […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-silicon-valley-really-talking-011711652.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Is SoftBank (TSE:9984) Quietly Pivoting Into an AI and Energy Infrastructure Powerhouse?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-tse-9984-quietly-pivoting-010658065.html</link><description>BofA Securities recently downgraded Arm Holdings to Neutral ahead of its fiscal third-quarter 2026 results, citing near-term smartphone-related headwinds that could weigh on Arm’s client royalty revenue. At the same time, SoftBank Group is drawing fresh attention as it steps up high-profile AI and energy commitments tied to OpenAI and SB Energy, which are reshaping how investors view its role as an AI and infrastructure holding company. We’ll now examine how SoftBank’s heightened AI and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-tse-9984-quietly-pivoting-010658065.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You'd Invested $500 in Nvidia Stock 10 Years Ago, Here's How Much You'd Have Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/if-youd-invested-500-in-nvidia-stock-10-years-ago/</link><description>Nvidia has delivered life-changing returns for long-term shareholders.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/if-youd-invested-500-in-nvidia-stock-10-years-ago/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Memory Shortage Threatens Nvidia's China AI Chip Ambitions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/memory-shortage-threatens-nvidias-china-003139128.html</link><description>Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA) faces a fresh constraint on its China business as a global shortage of advanced memory chips threatens to limit U.S. export licenses for its H200 AI processors, raising near-term risks to sales growth just as demand for AI hardware remains red-hot. Tight supplies of advanced memory are likely to cap how many export licenses Nvidia can obtain to sell its H200 artificial intelligence processors to customers in China, according to Rep. John Moolenaar, the top Republican o</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/memory-shortage-threatens-nvidias-china-003139128.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Gary Black Likes Elon Musk's Tesla But Not TSLA, Draws Comparison With Amazon—Says Nvidia 'Democratizes Autonomy'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gary-black-likes-elon-musks-235124088.html</link><description>Investor Gary Black, managing director of The Future Fund LLC, has shared that Tesla Inc.'s (NASDAQ:TSLA) stock valuation has caused him to exit his position in the automaker. Gary Black Offers Insight Into Tesla Valuation Criticism The investor, in a post on the social media platform X, offered an insight into his outlook on Tesla, drawing comparisons with Amazon.com Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AMZN) stock during the e-commerce giant's early days. Black shared that he held Amazon stock before it was profita</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gary-black-likes-elon-musks-235124088.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Loses Fight To Block Saks Bankruptcy Financing, Says Report: Company Warns Of 'Drastic Remedies'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-loses-fight-block-saks-235124308.html</link><description>A U.S. bankruptcy judge has dismissed Amazon.com Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:AMZN) attempt to block a proposed financing deal to aid Saks Global Enterprises during its Chapter 11 bankruptcy. On Thursday, Judge Alfredo Perez approved a preliminary $400 million financing package for Saks following a courtroom battle between the retailer and several creditors, including Amazon, reported Reuters. Saks is seeking $1.75 billion to continue operations, but will need further approvals from the U.S. District &amp;amp; Bankru</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-loses-fight-block-saks-235124308.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] YouTuber MKBHD Hails Tesla Model Y Performance, Calls EV Giant's Self-Driving Technology 'The Best'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</link><description>YouTuber Marques Brownlee, aka MKBHD, has shared his thoughts on the Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) Model Y Performance trim, as well as the company's self-driving technology. Tesla Self-Driving Is The Best Ever, MKBHD Says The YouTuber, in a review of the Model Y Performance on Thursday, hailed the crossover's software on the 16-inch touchscreen infotainment display, which is also a real-time representation of the car. "This is the best software in a car that is not Android Auto or Apple CarPlay," bo</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 Growth Stocks to Invest $1,000 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/3-growth-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</link><description>Nvidia, Amazon, and Dutch Bros are top growth stocks to invest in now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/3-growth-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Reason Why Now Is a Great Time to Buy Vistra</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-reason-why-now-is-a-great-time-to-buy-vistra/</link><description>Vistra is ready to capitalize as tech and AI giants search for more electricity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-reason-why-now-is-a-great-time-to-buy-vistra/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: This Will Be Alphabet's Stock Price by the End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-this-will-be-alphabets-stock-price-by-t/</link><description>The primary factors that were boosting Alphabet's stock price last year are gone.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-this-will-be-alphabets-stock-price-by-t/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bank of America revamps Alphabet stock after Google enters two key partnerships</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</link><description>Investors are taking a fresh look at Google, as new partnerships tied to its Gemini models help push the stock higher. On Jan. 11, Google and Walmart (WMT) said they plan to roll out a new shopping experience inside Google’s Gemini chatbot, highlighting a potential new revenue path for Google. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 203 Billion Reasons Why Microsoft Is a Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/203-billion-reasons-why-microsoft-is-a-buy-in-2026/</link><description>Microsoft's OpenAI investment could infuse cash into its business at the right time.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/203-billion-reasons-why-microsoft-is-a-buy-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jamie Dimon Rules Out Fed Chair Role, But Would Consider 'Secretary of The Treasury' If The President Asks: 'I Like Being My Own Boss'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimon-rules-fed-chair-193104450.html</link><description>Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co.’s (NYSE:JPM) CEO, Jamie Dimon, firmly ruled out any possibility of leading the Federal Reserve in the near future, but is open to serving as the Secretary of the Treasury, if asked by the President. Dimon Might Consider Treasury Secretary Role Dimon said there was “positively no chance” that he would serve as the Chairman of the Federal Reserve, even if he were asked by “a President” of the U.S., in an interview with Bloomberg’s David Rubenstein on Thursday. Wh</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimon-rules-fed-chair-193104450.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>