<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NVDA] 2 Artificial Intelligence Stocks to Buy in 2026 That Could Be Better Picks Than Nvidia</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-artificial-intelligence-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-th/</link><description>Nvidia's massive size could lead investors to seek gains in these comparatively smaller stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-artificial-intelligence-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-th/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Will Caterpillar’s AI-Enabled Fleet and Factory Upgrades Change Caterpillar's (CAT) Narrative</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-ai-enabled-fleet-factory-061101101.html</link><description>Caterpillar Inc. recently unveiled a suite of Industrial AI advances, including the Cat AI Assistant and expanded NVIDIA collaboration, aimed at bringing AI-enabled autonomy and intelligent in-cab experiences to construction, mining and power equipment, while also using digital twins and AI to reshape its manufacturing and supply chain operations. These moves suggest Caterpillar is working to turn its installed base of heavy machinery into a connected, AI-ready platform that could embed the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-ai-enabled-fleet-factory-061101101.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] How Investors May Respond To NVIDIA (NVDA) Expanding Its AI Platform From Gaming To Drug Discovery</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-nvidia-nvda-061051894.html</link><description>NVIDIA and its partners have, over recent days, unveiled a wave of new AI hardware and collaborations, from Blackwell-based GeForce RTX 5090 gaming cards and Vera Rubin data center systems to deep-life-sciences tie‑ups with Eli Lilly, Natera, Thermo Fisher and others built on the NVIDIA AI platform. Together, these launches and alliances extend NVIDIA’s AI reach from gaming and autonomous vehicles to drug discovery, industrial automation and privacy-first cloud infrastructure, reinforcing...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-nvidia-nvda-061051894.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] The Bull Case For Illumina (ILMN) Could Change Following Its Billion Cell Atlas Pharma Alliance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-illumina-ilmn-could-060959095.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, Illumina announced the Billion Cell Atlas alliance with AstraZeneca, Merck, and Eli Lilly, alongside new AI‑enabled genomics and multiomics platforms that integrate CRISPR, single-cell sequencing, and cloud analytics to support drug discovery and precision medicine. This push into large-scale genomics datasets and multiomic software marks a shift toward data-driven services that could reshape how Illumina works with pharmaceutical partners across the drug development...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-illumina-ilmn-could-060959095.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Down 40%, Should You Buy the Dip on IonQ?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/down-40-should-you-buy-the-dip-on-ionq/</link><description>Should investors be betting on this nascent quantum computing leader?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/down-40-should-you-buy-the-dip-on-ionq/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Surrounded by billionaires in Davos, Trump plans to lay out how he'll make housing more affordable</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surrounded-billionaires-davos-trump-plans-052008766.html</link><description>President Donald Trump plans to use a key address Wednesday to try to convince Americans he can make housing more affordable, but he's picked a strange backdrop for the speech: a Swiss mountain town where ski chalets for vacations cost a cool $4.4 million.  On the anniversary of his inauguration, Trump is flying to the World Economic Forum in Davos — an annual gathering of the global elite — where he may see many of the billionaires he has surrounded himself with during his first year back in the White House.  Trump had campaigned on lowering the cost of living, painting himself as a populist while serving fries at a McDonald's drive-thru.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surrounded-billionaires-davos-trump-plans-052008766.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Top Quantum Computing Stocks to Buy in January</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-top-quantum-computing-stocks-to-buy-in-january/</link><description>Alphabet and Microsoft have the tech chops and cash to win in quantum computing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-top-quantum-computing-stocks-to-buy-in-january/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays on Rupiah's Record Low</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/barclays-rupiahs-record-low-043507055.html</link><description>The Indonesian rupiah has hit a record low against the U.S. dollar over concerns around central bank independence and policy direction. Mitul Kotecha, Head of Asia FX at Barclays, shares why he expects some stabilization ahead for the currency.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/barclays-rupiahs-record-low-043507055.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Assessing IBM (NYSE:IBM) Valuation After Recent Share Price Strength And Long Term Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-ibm-nyse-ibm-valuation-042614742.html</link><description>International Business Machines (IBM) is drawing investor attention after its recent trading session, with the stock closing at $305.67. You might be weighing that price against the company’s current fundamentals and recent return profile. See our latest analysis for International Business Machines. The latest 2.59% 1 day share price return comes after a mixed few weeks, with a 7 day share price decline but a 90 day gain of 8.37%. At the same time, the 1 year total shareholder return of...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-ibm-nyse-ibm-valuation-042614742.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] India's Lodha Developers to invest $11 billion in 2.5 GW data centre park in Maharashtra</title><link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/indias-lodha-developers-invest-11-035111674.html</link><description>BENGALURU, Jan 20 (Reuters) - India's Lodha Developers said on Tuesday that it will invest an additional 1 trillion rupees ($11 billion) to build a 2.5-gigawatt data centre park in the state of</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/indias-lodha-developers-invest-11-035111674.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Vs. Ryanair's CEO Just Turned Into A Betting Game — And Traders Are Now Wagering On A Full-Blown Takeover</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-vs-ryanairs-ceo-033109532.html</link><description>A public war of words between Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk and Ryanair Holdings plc (NASDAQ:RYAAY) CEO Michael O'Leary has spilled into prediction markets. Polymarket Weighs Musk-Ryanair Takeover Odds On Friday, Bettors on Polymarket, a crypto-based prediction platform, are mullying the chances of Musk buying Ryanair. 🚨 NEW POLYMARKET: Will Elon Musk buy Ryan Air?https://t.co/8zLAql3WU4— Polymarket (@Polymarket) January 17, 2026 Don't Miss: Missed Nvidia and Tesla? RAD Intel</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-vs-ryanairs-ceo-033109532.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How Investors May Respond To Wayfair (W) Partnering With Google On AI-Enabled In-Search Checkout Integration</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-wayfair-w-031443316.html</link><description>In January 2026, Google announced that Wayfair had served as a foundational partner in co-developing its Universal Commerce Protocol, enabling customers to complete secure Wayfair checkouts directly within Google Search’s AI Mode and theemini app while Wayfair remains the merchant of record. By pairing this AI-enabled checkout integration with high-profile exposure such as HGTV’s 2026 Dream Home and deep home-furnishings promotions, Wayfair is pushing its brand and product discovery tools...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-wayfair-w-031443316.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan says it will lead 'democratic' high-tech supply chain with US</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-says-lead-democratic-high-030604545.html</link><description>TAIPEI, Jan 20 (Reuters) - Taiwan aims to build a "democratic" high-tech supply chain with the United States and form a strategic AI partnership under the new tariffs deal it sealed with Washington</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-says-lead-democratic-high-030604545.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Visits Palantir — Wall Street Meets The War Room</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-visits-023103539.html</link><description>JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) CEO Jamie Dimon visited Palantir Technologies' (NASDAQ:PLTR) office in Washington, D.C. on Thursday. Although the exact nature of the engagement is unknown, Palantir acknowledged Dimon’s visit and the ensuing discussion in a social media post. "Thank you @jpmorgan CEO Jamie Dimon for stopping by our DC office earlier today, and for the discussion with @ChairmanG," Palantir said in the post that also highlighted photos of Dimon and Palantir's head of defense Mike G</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-visits-023103539.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] 3 Stocks to Buy in 2026 Before They Skyrocket</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/3-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-before-they-skyrocket/</link><description>2026 could be a banner year for these stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/3-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-before-they-skyrocket/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bitdeer Technologies (BTDR) Climbs 37.6% on AI Computing Expansion</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitdeer-technologies-btdr-climbs-37-020637958.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stock Winners Shocking Wall Street. Bitdeer Technologies Group (NASDAQ:BTDR) was one of the top performers last week. Bitdeer Technologies soared by 37.6 percent week-on-week following its adoption of NVIDIA GB200 NVL72 deployment in Malaysia, strengthening its mission to simplify and scale AI computing globally. In a statement, Bitdeer Technologies Group (NASDAQ:BTDR) […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitdeer-technologies-btdr-climbs-37-020637958.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Ultra Clean (UCTT) Soars 28% as Chip Expansion Sparks Rosy Prospects</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-uctt-soars-28-013630142.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stock Winners Shocking Wall Street. Ultra Clean Holdings Inc. (NASDAQ:UCTT) was one of the top performers last week. Ultra Clean Holdings saw its share prices jump by 27.89 percent week-on-week to hit a 52-week high as investors increased their positions in the company after highlighting its role in the AI industry, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-uctt-soars-28-013630142.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 01:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Should You Buy Dividend Aristocrats in 2026?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-dividend-aristocrats-2026-012700753.html</link><description>Dividend-paying stocks provide many clear benefits. But should you bother with them in the fresh year?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-dividend-aristocrats-2026-012700753.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] P&amp;G Gets Target Hike as Barclays Calls Move a “Flight to Safety”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/p-g-gets-target-hike-012142208.html</link><description>The Procter &amp;amp; Gamble Company (NYSE:PG) is included among the 13 Best Dividend Kings to Buy in 2026. On January 16, Barclays analyst Lauren Lieberman raised the firm’s price target on The Procter &amp;amp; Gamble Company (NYSE:PG) to $155 from $151 and maintained an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change was part of […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/p-g-gets-target-hike-012142208.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 01:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave (CRWV) Soars 26% as Chip Giant Raises AI Bets</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-soars-26-chip-011857550.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stock Winners Shocking Wall Street. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) was one of the top performers last week. CoreWeave surged by 26.3 percent week-on-week to claw back to the $101 level—a two-month high—as investors loaded positions in stocks riding the artificial intelligence wave, buoyed by a semiconductor giant’s strong earnings performance last year […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-soars-26-chip-011857550.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 01:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia Stock Will Be Worth This Much By Year-End 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-nvidia-stock-will-be-worth-this-much-by/</link><description>Nvidia's market cap has soared more than tenfold over the last three years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-nvidia-stock-will-be-worth-this-much-by/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Assessing Eli Lilly (LLY) Valuation After Recent Choppy Trading And GLP 1 Growth Expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-eli-lilly-lly-valuation-001126638.html</link><description>Stock performance context for Eli Lilly (LLY) Eli Lilly (LLY) has drawn fresh attention after recent price moves, with the share closing at $1,038.40. Short term returns have been mixed, while longer periods show stronger total return figures. See our latest analysis for Eli Lilly. Recent trading has been choppy, with a 7 day share price return of a 3.94% decline and a 30 day share price return of a 3.08% decline, while the 90 day share price return of 29.87% and 1 year total shareholder...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-eli-lilly-lly-valuation-001126638.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds to put all 67,000 staff through AI training in fresh digital push</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-put-67-000-staff-000100242.html</link><description>All employees of the banking group will be expected to complete the course by the end of the year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-put-67-000-staff-000100242.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Stocks to Buy in 2026 and Hold Forever</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/2-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-hold-forever/</link><description>Alphabet and Taiwan Semiconductor have nearly unstoppable businesses.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/2-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-hold-forever/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Valuation Check After Recent Pullback And Strong Long Term Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-valuation-check-recent-231120330.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) has drawn investor attention after recent share price moves, with the stock showing mixed short term performance and relatively stronger gains over the past month and the past 3 months. See our latest analysis for Alphabet. Alphabet's recent pullback over the last week sits against a much stronger backdrop, with a 30 day share price return of 7.44% and a 90 day share price return of 31.76%, while the 1 year total shareholder return of 69.03% and 5 year total shareholder...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-valuation-check-recent-231120330.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Assessing Snowflake (SNOW) Valuation After Mixed Short And Long Term Share Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-snowflake-snow-valuation-mixed-230955058.html</link><description>Evaluating Snowflake after recent price moves Snowflake (SNOW) has seen mixed share performance lately, with a 1 day gain of 1.27% contrasting with declines over the past week, month and past 3 months. This puts recent trading firmly on investors’ radar. See our latest analysis for Snowflake. At around $210 per share, Snowflake’s recent 1 day share price gain contrasts with weaker multi month share price returns. However, the 1 year and 3 year total shareholder returns of 23.18% and 39.97%...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-snowflake-snow-valuation-mixed-230955058.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm Holdings plc (ARM): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-plc-arm-bull-223326655.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on Arm Holdings plc on r/valueinvesting by Significant-Foot3928. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on ARM. Arm Holdings plc’s share was trading at $105.11 as of January 15th. ARM’s trailing and forward P/E were 134.60 and 46.08 respectively according to Yahoo Finance. ARM Holdings sits at the center of the global […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-plc-arm-bull-223326655.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Is Taiwan Semiconductor a Better Buy Than Intel for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/is-taiwan-semiconductor-a-better-buy-than-intel-fo/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor and Intel are two of the biggest names in semiconductors, but if you can only buy one of them this year, Taiwan Semiconductor is looking much more attractive than Intel.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/is-taiwan-semiconductor-a-better-buy-than-intel-fo/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia's Stock Hasn't Been This Cheap in Over a Year. Here's What History Suggests Will Happen Next.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/nvidias-stock-hasnt-been-this-cheap-in-over-a-year/</link><description>The chipmaker rallied during the second half of 2025, but can it sustain its momentum in 2026?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/nvidias-stock-hasnt-been-this-cheap-in-over-a-year/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Top Research Reports for GE Aerospace, KLA &amp; Parker-Hannifin</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-research-reports-ge-aerospace-212700547.html</link><description>GE Aerospace outpaces peers as commercial engine demand and defense budgets lift results, even as costs, supply-chain issues and FX pressures loom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-research-reports-ge-aerospace-212700547.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 1 Unstoppable Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock to Buy Before It Soars More Than 30% in 2026, According to a Wall Street Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/1-unstoppable-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-to/</link><description>Palantir stock has been one of the top performers of the AI wave for three years and counting.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/1-unstoppable-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Tariff Impact Seen as Limited, Wolfe Research Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-tariff-impact-seen-205336181.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 15, Wolfe Research analyst Chris Caso reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $250.00 price target. Firm analysts see minimal impact from newly announced tariffs, calling it a mechanism for pre-agreed payments. The White House recently announced a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-tariff-impact-seen-205336181.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] RBC Raises Alphabet (GOOGL) Target on AI Advertising Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-raises-alphabet-googl-target-205225839.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 15, RBC Capital analyst Brad Erickson raised the price target on the stock to $375.00 (from $315.00) while maintaining an “Outperform” rating. Firm analysts see AI ad rollout momentum, an expanding SMB total addressable market, and expectations that Olympics-specific CTV […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-raises-alphabet-googl-target-205225839.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Wall Street Gets More Bullish on TSMC’s AI Dominance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-gets-more-bullish-204824703.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 15, BofA Securities analyst Brad Lin raised the price target on the stock to $470.00 (from $430.00) while maintaining a “Buy” rating. Firm analysts are confident in TSM’s tech leadership, underpinned by strong pricing power, capacity stability, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-gets-more-bullish-204824703.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Down 55%, Should You Buy the Dip on Pfizer?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/down-55-should-you-buy-the-dip-on-pfizer/</link><description>Pfizer's stock has started to turn higher, but it is still down massively; is now the time to jump aboard?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/down-55-should-you-buy-the-dip-on-pfizer/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 Stocks You'll Regret Not Buying in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/5-stocks-youll-regret-not-buying-in-2026/</link><description>Artificial intelligence is set to have another huge year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/5-stocks-youll-regret-not-buying-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Quantum Enablers Set for 2026 Breakout: AMD, AVGO, TER in Focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/quantum-enablers-set-2026-breakout-200000863.html</link><description>Quantum enablers like AMD, AVGO and TER are poised for 2026 gains as enterprise spending and post-quantum security drive near-term revenue growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/quantum-enablers-set-2026-breakout-200000863.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Nvidia Stock a Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/is-nvidia-stock-a-buy-now/</link><description>The chipmaker's history of success will strengthen its investment case for some types of investors while weakening it with others.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/is-nvidia-stock-a-buy-now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Cathie Wood Goes Shopping: 3 Stocks She Just Bought</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/cathie-wood-goes-bargain-hunting-3-stocks-she-just/</link><description>The ascending growth investor went hunting for deals ahead of the holiday weekend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/cathie-wood-goes-bargain-hunting-3-stocks-she-just/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Rigetti Computing: Quantum Leader or Overhyped Stock?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/rigetti-computing-quantum-leader-or-overhyped/</link><description>After nearly tripling over the last year, what comes next for Rigetti Computing stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/rigetti-computing-quantum-leader-or-overhyped/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk drops a surprise curveball on Nvidia</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/elon-musk-drops-a-surprise-curveball-on-nvidia</link><description>Tesla (TSLA) just delivered a rare double whammy to Nvidia (NVDA) over the past weekend. CEO Elon Musk revealed that Tesla’s much-talked-about AI5 self-driving chips are nearly complete, and that the next one, A16, is already underway. With the AI inference part covered, Musk said Sunday on X ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/elon-musk-drops-a-surprise-curveball-on-nvidia</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Cathie Wood Buys AI Chips, Sells Tesla</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-buys-ai-chips-182740393.html</link><description>ARK shifts deeper into future-tech bets</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-buys-ai-chips-182740393.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia H200 Shipments Hit China Roadblock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-h200-shipments-hit-china-175929567.html</link><description>Customs move forces suppliers to pause</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-h200-shipments-hit-china-175929567.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar vs. Volvo: Which Heavy Equipment Stock is the Better Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-vs-volvo-heavy-equipment-174900681.html</link><description>CAT and VLVLY face slowing demand and tariff pressures, but both are investing in technology and capacity to position for long-term infrastructure growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-vs-volvo-heavy-equipment-174900681.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] IBN's Q3 Earnings Dip on Higher Provision &amp; Expenses, NII Rises Y/Y</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibns-q3-earnings-dip-higher-172900554.html</link><description>ICICI Bank's Q3 FY26 earnings fall 4% due to higher provisions, costs and treasury loss, even as NII, fee income and loans post solid growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibns-q3-earnings-dip-higher-172900554.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] RDDT vs. GOOGL: Which Digital Advertising Stock Has an Edge Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rddt-vs-googl-digital-advertising-171000050.html</link><description>Reddit highlights fast ad growth and rising engagement, but Alphabet's AI-driven ad tools and stronger performance give it an edge now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rddt-vs-googl-digital-advertising-171000050.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Assessing KLA (KLAC) Valuation After Broker Upgrades On AI Chip Equipment Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-kla-klac-valuation-broker-170705312.html</link><description>Several brokerages have just upgraded KLA (KLAC) after pointing to strong demand for foundry-led wafer fabrication equipment and the company’s role in process control for advanced, AI focused chips. See our latest analysis for KLA. That backdrop of upgrades and AI focused foundry spending has gone hand in hand with strong price momentum, with a 30 day share price return of 25.86% and a 1 year total shareholder return of 108.75% off the current US$1,567.82 share price. At the same time, the 5...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-kla-klac-valuation-broker-170705312.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Husband, 32, With 'Months To Live' Has $1.2M Life Insurance And Asks If He Should Put 50% Of It In Annuity So His Wife Doesn't Blow It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/husband-32-months-live-1-170114945.html</link><description>He's dying at 32. His wife is getting $1.2 million. And he's terrified she'll waste it. In a blunt Reddit post, a terminally ill man shared his financial dilemma with the r/personalfinance community. "I'm dying in a few months," he wrote. "I have a $1,200,000 life insurance [policy] w/ my wife as beneficiary… What should I do to ensure my wife gets the money w/o difficulty? Also, she's terrible w/money…" There were no savings, no 401(k), and $90,000 in combined tax and creditor debt. The couple</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/husband-32-months-live-1-170114945.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Rise and Fall of the American Monoculture</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/media/american-pop-culture-history-ce8672f1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>For most of the 20th century, pop culture was the glue that held the U.S. together. But what will it mean now that everything has splintered?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/media/american-pop-culture-history-ce8672f1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC Jumps on Strong Q4 as AI Chip Demand Surges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-jumps-strong-q4-ai-165640626.html</link><description>The chip giant tops expectations and signals another strong year ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-jumps-strong-q4-ai-165640626.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Top AI Stocks to Boost Returns and Reignite Portfolio Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-ai-stocks-boost-returns-162000203.html</link><description>Here, we have picked three AI stocks, MSFT, MU and ADI, which are well-poised to benefit from AI's growing use and ability to solve complex problems.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-ai-stocks-boost-returns-162000203.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron Warns AI Demand Is Overwhelming Supply</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-warns-ai-demand-overwhelming-161850739.html</link><description>Memory tightness spills into PCs, phones</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-warns-ai-demand-overwhelming-161850739.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Magnificent 7 is Over: What Stocks Will Replace It?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-over-stocks-replace-161400706.html</link><description>Amazon and Tesla have underperformed for 5 years. Is it time to give them the boot?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-over-stocks-replace-161400706.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] ElevenLabs Talks New Funding at $11 Billion</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elevenlabs-talks-funding-11-billion-161328360.html</link><description>AI voice startup's growth draws big money</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elevenlabs-talks-funding-11-billion-161328360.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] The Best Healthcare Stocks to Buy With $5,000 in 2026 and Hold Forever</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/best-healthcare-stocks-to-buy-with-5000-in-2026/</link><description>All three of these healthcare giants are leaders in their niches.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/best-healthcare-stocks-to-buy-with-5000-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA (KLAC) Is Up 9.8% After Analyst Upgrades On AI Chip Demand Narrative Shift?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-9-8-analyst-160631530.html</link><description>In recent days, KLA Corporation, a leading supplier of semiconductor process control and inspection equipment, has attracted increased attention after several major banks and analysts upgraded their views, citing strong demand for advanced chips and better-than-expected quarterly results. These upgrades highlight how KLA’s exposure to AI-driven chip complexity and leading-edge foundry spending is becoming central to its role in the semiconductor equipment ecosystem. Now we’ll examine how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-9-8-analyst-160631530.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Well, there goes the metaverse!</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/well-goes-metaverse-160000767.html</link><description>The metaverse is on its last legs as VR is eclipsed by AI. But that's not the only thing that went wrong for Meta's VR ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/well-goes-metaverse-160000767.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 3 Giant Tech Stocks Are Poised for Explosive Quantum Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/tech-stocks-poised-explosive-quantum-growth/</link><description>Quantum computing is the next big thing in tech, but you don't need to invest in any risky start-ups to profit from it.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/tech-stocks-poised-explosive-quantum-growth/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Transformative arrival of oral weight loss medicines in the US</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/pricing-and-market-access/transformative-arrival-of-oral-weight-loss-medicines-in-us/</link><description>While GlobalData does not expect oral Wegovy to substantially displace sales of injectable versions in 2026, some sales cannibalisation in the medium-term outlook is inevitable.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/pricing-and-market-access/transformative-arrival-of-oral-weight-loss-medicines-in-us/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Compounder sues Lilly and Novo for suppressing GLP-1RA competition</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/compounder-sues-lilly-and-novo-for-suppressing-glp-1ra-competition/</link><description>Strive Compounding Pharmacy alleges the two pharma companies are coordinating an effort to restrict compounded access.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/compounder-sues-lilly-and-novo-for-suppressing-glp-1ra-competition/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Suppliers Pause Output After China Blocks H200 Chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-suppliers-pause-output-china-151839971.html</link><description>Export suspension underscores rising trade tension over AI hardware.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-suppliers-pause-output-china-151839971.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] ADI's Consumer Revenues Rise 19% Y/Y in FY25: More Growth Ahead?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adis-consumer-revenues-rise-19-151700790.html</link><description>Analog Devices is riding on surging demand for premium audio, hearables and wearables, gaming, AR and VR.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adis-consumer-revenues-rise-19-151700790.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Podcast: JPM26’s dealmaking falls short of expectations</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/comment/podcast-jpm26s-dealmaking-falls-short-of-expectations/</link><description>Despite lacklustre dealmaking, there were still trends identified from company presentations, such as pharma's upcoming patent cliff and AI's growth in medtech.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/comment/podcast-jpm26s-dealmaking-falls-short-of-expectations/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Can Hit $1,500, According to Pro</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/19/asml-stock-can-hit-1500-according-to-pro/</link><description>The semiconductor stocks have enjoyed another big leg higher to start the year. With unprecedented AI demand and aggressive AI data center builds pushing the fabs to ramp up on capacity expansions, it should be no surprise to see the broader basket of semiconductor names making up for lost time. With the iShares Semiconductor ETF ... ASML Stock Can Hit $1,500, According to Pro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/19/asml-stock-can-hit-1500-according-to-pro/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Brilliant Growth Stocks to Buy Now and Hold for the Long Term</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/3-brilliant-growth-stocks-to-buy-now-and-hold-for/</link><description>Each one of them brings something special -- and something very necessary -- to the table.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/3-brilliant-growth-stocks-to-buy-now-and-hold-for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Kevin O'Leary Says 'I Don't Care If It's A Gift For Your Birthday'—Take 10% Of Any Money That Comes Your Way And Invest It To Get Rich</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-dont-care-150106273.html</link><description>Kevin O'Leary isn't interested in your excuses—especially the ones wrapped in a bow. In a 2020 interview with CNBC, the "Shark Tank" investor didn't just suggest setting money aside. He issued a directive. "I don't care if it's a gift for your birthday present," O'Leary said. "You have to take 10% of your paycheck every two weeks and invest it." Paychecks, birthday cards, cash from your side hustle scooping ice cream—it all counts. If it lands in your hands, O'Leary expects 10% of it to be out t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-dont-care-150106273.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is Novo Nordisk's Oral Wegovy Driving Strong Early US Demand Already?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/novo-nordisks-oral-wegovy-driving-145900933.html</link><description>NVO shares jump 9.1% as early U.S. prescriptions for oral Wegovy show strong first-week demand after its early January launch.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/novo-nordisks-oral-wegovy-driving-145900933.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semi Crushed Q4 Earnings. That Makes This 1 AI Chip Stock a Top Buy.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37111188/taiwan-semi-crushed-q4-earnings-that-makes-this-1-ai-chip-stock-a-top-buy</link><description>As Taiwan Semi reported solid Q4 results, Citi analysts upgraded Intel stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37111188/taiwan-semi-crushed-q4-earnings-that-makes-this-1-ai-chip-stock-a-top-buy</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stock Market News for Jan 19, 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-news-jan-19-143800895.html</link><description>U.S. stocks ended mostly flat on Friday as investors weighed comments on geopolitics and the Federal Reserve from President Donald Trump, as well as digested quarterly reports from some major companies, marking the start of the earnings season.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-news-jan-19-143800895.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Congresswoman Violates STOCK Act With Over 200 Late Trade Disclosures: Purchases Include Mag7, Healthcare Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/congresswoman-violates-stock-act-over-143116760.html</link><description>Rep. Julia Letlow (R-La.) reportedly violated a federal transparency law by failing to disclose her personal stock trades within the required time frame. Lawmaker Missed STOCK Act Trade Filings Letlow, a third-term Louisiana congresswoman, failed to disclose 224 stock and bond trades within the 45-day reporting window required under the Stop Trading on Congressional Knowledge (STOCK) Act, reported NOTUS on Thursday. Letlow also amended all five of her annual financial disclosures dating back to</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/congresswoman-violates-stock-act-over-143116760.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (TSM): “Enabler of the AI Era.”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-tsm-enabler-142631998.html</link><description>Wedgewood Partners, an investment management company, released its fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. The firm anticipates stronger market volatility in the coming years and has moderated its enthusiasm. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The Wedgewood Composite returned -1.8% (net) in the fourth quarter compared to the S&amp;amp;P 500’s 2.7%, the Russell 1000 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-tsm-enabler-142631998.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Want $1 Million in Retirement? Invest $100,000 in These 3 Stocks and Wait a Decade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/want-1-million-in-retirement-invest-100000-in-thes/</link><description>Broadcom, Alphabet, and UiPath have the potential to be huge winners over the next decade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/want-1-million-in-retirement-invest-100000-in-thes/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Strong Growth in Google Services Lifted Alphabet (GOOG)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-growth-google-services-lifted-141426067.html</link><description>Wedgewood Partners, an investment management company, released its fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. The firm anticipates stronger market volatility in the coming years and has moderated its enthusiasm. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The Wedgewood Composite returned -1.8% (net) in the fourth quarter compared to the S&amp;amp;P 500’s 2.7%, the Russell 1000 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-growth-google-services-lifted-141426067.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 No-Brainer AI Stocks to Buy Hand Over Fist for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/3-no-brainer-ai-stocks-to-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</link><description>Buy stakes in companies combining scale, profitability, and durable demand across the AI technology stack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/3-no-brainer-ai-stocks-to-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Drops Due to Trade War Worries. These Chip Companies Are Suffering Too.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-stock-price-stmicroelectronics-trump-tariffs-chips-cf81cc8a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>ASML Holding  and shares of other companies in the semiconductor sector were dropping Monday.  The prospect of a trade war between the European Union and the U.S. is hurting chip stocks.  Dutch company ASML was down 3.3% in trading in the Netherlands.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-stock-price-stmicroelectronics-trump-tariffs-chips-cf81cc8a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 Growth Stocks to Invest $1,000 In Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/5-growth-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</link><description>Growth stocks continue to power the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/5-growth-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Jim Cramer on Arm Holdings: “I Would Hold It”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-hold-132947594.html</link><description>Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer put under a microscope. During the episode, a caller inquired if they should hold, sell, or add more to their position, and Cramer replied: “You know, I gotta tell you, something’s going on. I mean, we gotta get Rene Haas on. I mean, the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-hold-132947594.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Jim Cramer Says “Taiwan Semi Made Mincemeat of the Skeptics Who’ve Been Doubting AI’s Staying Power”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-taiwan-semi-132939688.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer put under a microscope. Cramer highlighted the “off the charts” demand for the company’s chips, as he stated: “Do you know that the fate of today’s market was decided at 12:30 AM Eastern time? Yeah, middle of the night. That’s when Taiwan […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-taiwan-semi-132939688.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Benchmark Hikes Hut 8 Corp. (HUT) Price Target amid $7B Data Center Deal</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/benchmark-hikes-hut-8-corp-131504192.html</link><description>Hut 8 Corp (NASDAQ:HUT) is one of the best cryptocurrency and blockchain stocks to buy now. On December 19, Benchmark raised the stock’s price target to $85 from $78. The price target hike is in response to the company signing a $7 billion data center deal, which is expected to strengthen its digital infrastructure business […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/benchmark-hikes-hut-8-corp-131504192.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML) Is Up 7.4% After TSMC Unveils Higher AI-Focused Capex Plans</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-enxtam-asml-7-130933205.html</link><description>In recent days, ASML Holding has been lifted by stronger semiconductor sentiment after TSMC reported past-quarter results ahead of expectations and outlined much higher 2026 capital spending focused on advanced, AI-related chip production. Because ASML’s lithography systems are central to these advanced manufacturing plans, many analysts now see the company as a major equipment beneficiary of TSMC’s expanded investment and related US-Taiwan chip build-out initiatives. We’ll now examine how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-enxtam-asml-7-130933205.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA vs. Micron: Which AI Chip Stock Is a Better Investment Option?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-vs-micron-ai-chip-130300506.html</link><description>MU outpaces NVDA as AI demand surges, with faster EPS growth, sold-out HBM supply and a far lower valuation premium.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-vs-micron-ai-chip-130300506.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Beat the Market the Zacks Way: Amicus, Micron, Amgen in Focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beat-market-zacks-way-amicus-130100666.html</link><description>FOLD, MU and AMGN delivered sharp gains as Zacks strategies beat key benchmarks despite tariff fears, policy uncertainty and volatile markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beat-market-zacks-way-amicus-130100666.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] More AI means a higher need for cybersecurity: CrowdStrike CEO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/more-ai-means-higher-cybersecurity-110043500.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Co-Founder and CEO George Kurtz sits down with Yahoo Finance Executive Editor Brian Sozzi on Opening Bid for a conversation about the concerns around AI chatbot deployment and the role cybersecurity will have as more tech companies invest in building out AI data center infrastructure. Also watch George Kurtz discuss CrowdStrike's latest streak of acquisitions. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/more-ai-means-higher-cybersecurity-110043500.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Citi Bullish on Broadcom (AVGO) as Accelerating AI Sales Drive $480 PT</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-bullish-broadcom-avgo-accelerating-125008352.html</link><description>Broadcom Inc. (NASDAQ:AVGO) is one of the best future stocks to buy for the long term. On January 15, Citi kept a Buy rating on Broadcom with a $480 price target. Following a transfer of coverage, the firm established this new price target and issued a Buy rating, primarily driven by the company’s accelerating AI […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-bullish-broadcom-avgo-accelerating-125008352.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly’s Taltz and Zepbound Combo Delivers Superior Results in Landmark Psoriatic Arthritis Trial</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-taltz-zepbound-combo-125003769.html</link><description>Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) is one of the best future stocks to buy for the long term. On January 8, Eli Lilly announced positive topline results from the pioneering TOGETHER-PsA Phase 3b trial. This study is the first controlled pharmacologic trial to evaluate the combined use of an incretin therapy, Zepbound (tirzepatide), alongside a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-taltz-zepbound-combo-125003769.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] AstraZeneca’s Subcutaneous Saphnelo Shows Significant Disease Reduction in Landmark Lupus Trial</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/astrazeneca-subcutaneous-saphnelo-shows-significant-124953424.html</link><description>AstraZeneca (NASDAQ:AZN) is one of the best future stocks to buy for the long term. On January 6, Barclays analyst James Gordon raised the firm’s price target on AstraZeneca to 16,500 GBp from 14,000 GBp, while maintaining an Overweight rating on the shares. On the same day, AstraZeneca (NASDAQ:AZN) also published positive full results from […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/astrazeneca-subcutaneous-saphnelo-shows-significant-124953424.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] ClickHouse secures $400m in Series D led by Dragoneer</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/clickhouse-secures-400m-series-d/</link><description>The company plans further global expansion and product development after closing its latest funding round.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/clickhouse-secures-400m-series-d/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Winners &amp; Losers: The ETF Playbook to Glide Trump's Great Healthcare Plan</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/winners-losers-etf-playbook-glide-123800587.html</link><description>Trump's Great Healthcare Plan redraws healthcare winners and losers - here's how ETFs like IHE could benefit as middlemen face pressure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/winners-losers-etf-playbook-glide-123800587.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Tesla Set to Restart AI Supercomputer Project. Why Musk Has Changed His Mind.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-stock-price-musk-ai-supercomputer-8102307a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tesla is restarting its Dojo AI supercomputer project to improve its self-driving and robotics technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-stock-price-musk-ai-supercomputer-8102307a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Can IBM's Focus on the Infrastructure Segment Aid the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-focus-infrastructure-segment-aid-121500925.html</link><description>IBM's Infrastructure segment profit jumped 53% as AI, hybrid cloud and z17 demand fuel stronger enterprise adoption.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-focus-infrastructure-segment-aid-121500925.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv’s Expanded MegaMod HDX AI Pods Could Be A Game Changer For Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-expanded-megamod-hdx-ai-121242633.html</link><description>In mid-January 2026, Vertiv announced new global configurations of its prefabricated Vertiv MegaMod HDX power and liquid cooling pods, integrating direct-to-chip liquid cooling with air-cooled architectures to support AI and high‑performance computing data centers at rack densities above 100 kW. This expansion of the MegaMod HDX lineup highlights Vertiv’s effort to offer scalable, factory‑integrated AI infrastructure pods that address rising power, cooling, and deployment speed demands in...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-expanded-megamod-hdx-ai-121242633.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Best AI Energy Stocks to Buy in 2026 and Hold Forever</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-ai-energy-stocks-buy-120000236.html</link><description>Long-term investors and traders must buy stocks that are part of one of the biggest megatrends on Wall Street: the AI Energy Trade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-ai-energy-stocks-buy-120000236.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Memory Bottlenecks Cloud NVIDIA’s (NVDA) Latest China Export Approval</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/memory-bottlenecks-cloud-nvidia-nvda-115923745.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is among the best debt-free stocks to buy now. Only a few days after receiving the green light for export to China (export approval), shipments of H200 AI processors have again taken center stage. On Thursday, January 15, Bloomberg reported that House Representative John Moolenaar raised concerns on the shortage of dynamic random-access […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/memory-bottlenecks-cloud-nvidia-nvda-115923745.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Top 3 AI Stocks Dominating the Market, According to WarrenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-3-ai-stocks-dominating-114759478.html</link><description>Investing.com -- The artificial intelligence revolution continues to reshape the investment landscape, with certain companies positioned to capture outsized returns. According to a recent analysis by WarrenAI, three companies stand out as the most promising AI investments based on their market position, financial performance, and growth potential.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-3-ai-stocks-dominating-114759478.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bitcoin 'OG' Sells After 12 Years, Locking in 31,250% Profit</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-og-sells-12-years-114607600.html</link><description>A Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) whale, inactive for more than a decade, has returned to the scene, offloading half of its Bitcoin stash and securing a profit of 31,250%. The Bitcoin wallet, dubbed “5K BTC OG,” started selling its Bitcoin assets,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-og-sells-12-years-114607600.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Cathie Wood Bets Big on TSMC -- Loads Up Millions After Strong Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-bets-big-tsmc-114246476.html</link><description>Ark Invest Boosts TSMC Stake as AI Chip Demand Surges</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-bets-big-tsmc-114246476.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Latest News In AI Chips - Micron Boosts DRAM Capacity with Strategic Taiwan Acquisition</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-news-ai-chips-micron-113723442.html</link><description>Micron Technology has strategically moved to acquire Powerchip Semiconductor Manufacturing Corporation’s P5 fabrication site in Tongluo, Taiwan, for $1.8 billion, aiming to enhance its global presence in the memory solutions sector. This acquisition, including a sizable 300,000 square feet of cleanroom space, positions Micron to meet the increasing global demand for memory by boosting DRAM production capabilities. The initiative aligns with Micron's broader expansion plans and will establish...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-news-ai-chips-micron-113723442.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SEC Approves Expanded Option Expirations for Magnificent Seven Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sec-approves-expanded-option-expirations-113650138.html</link><description>Decision allows Nasdaq to list Monday and Wednesday expiries, moving single-stock options closer to a daily trading structure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sec-approves-expanded-option-expirations-113650138.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Blocks Nvidia's H200 Shipments, Output Paused</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-blocks-nvidias-h200-shipments-113514733.html</link><description>Suppliers pause output after Chinese customs halt AI chip shipments.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-blocks-nvidias-h200-shipments-113514733.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Could This Be the Most Misunderstood Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock on the Market?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/could-this-be-the-most-misunderstood-ai-stock/</link><description>This tech player has been increasing its spending on AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/could-this-be-the-most-misunderstood-ai-stock/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Analog Devices' Quarterly Earnings Preview: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37108285/analog-devices-quarterly-earnings-preview-what-you-need-to-know</link><description>Analog Devices will release its first-quarter earnings soon, and analysts anticipate a double-digit bottom-line growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37108285/analog-devices-quarterly-earnings-preview-what-you-need-to-know</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] AstraZeneca to acquire China rights for AbelZeta’s CAR-T therapy</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/astrazeneca-acquire-abelzetas-cart-therapy/</link><description>The acquisition gives AstraZeneca full global control of the therapy’s development, manufacturing and commercialisation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/astrazeneca-acquire-abelzetas-cart-therapy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike (CRWD) Valuation Check As Short Term Returns Cool And Long Term Gains Remain Strong</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-valuation-check-short-111231831.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) is back in focus after recent trading, with the stock last closing at US$453.88. Investors are weighing this price against recent returns and the company’s current fundamentals. See our latest analysis for CrowdStrike Holdings. The recent 7 day share price return of 2.81% decline and 30 day share price return of 5.69% decline contrast with a 1 year total shareholder return of 27.14% and very large 3 year total shareholder return, which indicates that long term...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-valuation-check-short-111231831.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Which Vanguard ETF Is Most Likely to Soar in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/which-vanguard-etf-is-most-likely-to-soar-in-2026/</link><description>One Vanguard ETF stands out above the rest.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/which-vanguard-etf-is-most-likely-to-soar-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia Faces Another Obstacle in China. But Wall Street Still Loves the Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-h200-sales-5efcbb2c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock trades at the same levels as it did last August. Analysts think that makes it a screaming buying opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-h200-sales-5efcbb2c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] HSBC's Roberts Says AI Won't Lead to 'Massive Layoffs'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/hsbcs-roberts-says-ai-wont-103806668.html</link><description>Michael Roberts, head of corporate and institutional banking at HSBC, discusses geopolitical risks, the bank's restructure and the impact of artificial intelligence on staffing. "I don't think it'll lead to massive layoffs," Roberts says. "I don't think it'll lead to massive change in how we do things other than as to make it more efficient," he adds. Roberts speaks on Bloomberg Television at the World Economic Forum's annual meeting in Davos, Switzerland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/hsbcs-roberts-says-ai-wont-103806668.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Will Alphabet's Cloud Division Fuel $20 Billion in Income?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/will-alphabets-cloud-division-fuel-20-billion-in/</link><description>Even if its growth slows, Google Cloud looks to be a big winner in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/will-alphabets-cloud-division-fuel-20-billion-in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] ASM International Logs Strong Orders as China Business, Advanced Tech Pick Up</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/asm-international-logs-strong-orders-as-china-business-advanced-tech-pick-up-8a832e12?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Orders climbed to roughly €800 million in the fourth quarter on strong demand from producers of integrated circuits that power smartphones and other devices.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/asm-international-logs-strong-orders-as-china-business-advanced-tech-pick-up-8a832e12?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sequoia Capital planning billon dollar investment in Claude-maker Anthropic</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/sequoia-capital-investment-anthropic/</link><description>Anthropic seeks over $25bn at a valuation of $350bn with reports of an IPO this year circulating widely.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/sequoia-capital-investment-anthropic/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Prediction: 2026 Will Be the Year of Eli Lilly</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-2026-will-be-the-year-of-eli-lilly/</link><description>A catalyst lies just ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-2026-will-be-the-year-of-eli-lilly/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron to Buy Chip Plant for $1.8 Billion. Why That Raises Market Concerns.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/micron-stock-price-buy-chips-factory-31e510a4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Micron Technology stock has surged as demand for memory-chips soars. Plans to buy a facility in Taiwan are part of a race to increase capacity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/micron-stock-price-buy-chips-factory-31e510a4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays and Wells Fargo Lift Price Targets on Micron Technology (MU)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-wells-fargo-lift-price-091921903.html</link><description>Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) is one of the best strong buy growth stocks to buy according to hedge funds. On January 15, Barclays lifted the price target on Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) to $450 from $275 and maintained an Overweight rating on the shares, telling investors that it adjusted price targets and ratings on the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-wells-fargo-lift-price-091921903.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Here’s What Analysts Are Saying About Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (TSM) Post Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-saying-taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-091916277.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) is one of the best strong buy growth stocks to buy according to hedge funds. TD Cowen lifted the price target on Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) to $370 from $325 on December 16 and maintained a Hold rating, telling investors that it updated its model after the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-saying-taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-091916277.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Where is NVIDIA Corporation (NVDA) Headed According to the Street?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/where-nvidia-corporation-nvda-headed-091915918.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the best strong buy growth stocks to buy according to hedge funds. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) received a rating update from Jefferies on January 16, with the firm lifting the price target on the stock to $275 from $250 and maintaining a Buy rating on the shares. The firm told […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/where-nvidia-corporation-nvda-headed-091915918.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: These 5 Unstoppable Stocks Could Join the $5 Trillion Club in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-these-5-unstoppable-stocks-could-join-t/</link><description>These household names have been long-term winners, and that trend appears poised to continue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/19/prediction-these-5-unstoppable-stocks-could-join-t/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>