<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia’s Huang: AI boom will create six-figure trade jobs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-ai-boom-create-125341975.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang emphasized that the artificial intelligence boom will create high-paying trade jobs while speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-ai-boom-create-125341975.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cardano Founder Slams Ripple CEO Over Clarity Act: 'You're Handing Keys To The SEC'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cardano-founder-slams-ripple-ceo-123112176.html</link><description>Cardano (CRYPTO: ADA) founder Charles Hoskinson slammed Ripple (CRYPTO: XRP) CEO Brad Garlinghouse for backing the Senate’s Clarity Act draft, warning the bill hands too much power to the SEC and locks crypto into flawed regulation that favors banks over...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cardano-founder-slams-ripple-ceo-123112176.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Analog Devices price target raised to $350 from $320 at BofA</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-price-target-raised-122609712.html</link><description>BofA raised the firm’s price target on Analog Devices (ADI) to $350 from $320 and keeps a Buy rating on the shares. The firm raised price targets for most of its diversified analog semi stock coverage, noting that it expects modest calendar Q4 beats and Q1 raises across the board led by industrial semis given ongoing rebounds across most subsegments, favorable pricing, and robust growth in strategic AI businesses.Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-price-target-raised-122609712.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Enabler Sparkles And Shines. Now Comes The Main Event.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-analysis/corning-stock-near-breakout-ai-infrastructure-collaboration-with-nvidia-broadcom-microsoft-drives-demand/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Collaboration on AI infrastructure with Nvidia, Broadcom and Microsoft has Corning stock set to light up a breakout.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-analysis/corning-stock-near-breakout-ai-infrastructure-collaboration-with-nvidia-broadcom-microsoft-drives-demand/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Shrugs Off AI Bubble Talk</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-shrugs-off-ai-121419554.html</link><description>Huang says infrastructure buildout is just starting</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-shrugs-off-ai-121419554.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI-Powered Box Extract Launch Could Be A Game Changer For Box (BOX)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-powered-box-extract-launch-120808892.html</link><description>Box, Inc. recently announced the general availability of Box Extract, an AI-driven tool that uses models from Google, Anthropic, and OpenAI to convert unstructured enterprise content into secure, actionable metadata within Box. By enabling custom “Extract Agents” that can process complex documents across sectors like finance, insurance, legal, and media, Box is positioning its platform as a central hub for automating workflows and powering metadata-driven decision-making. Next, we’ll examine...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-powered-box-extract-launch-120808892.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Hidden Winner in Nvidia's AI Chip Boom Isn't Who You'd Expect</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</link><description>Nvidia is now outspending Apple at TSMC. Intel may benefit the most from the shift.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer Discusses Alphabet (GOOGL) &amp; OpenAI’s Rivalry</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Over the past couple of months, Jim Cramer has turned increasingly optimistic on Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL). Several factors have driven his optimism. Early on, these included enthusiasm for YouTube and the firm’s dominance in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] “CoreWeave (CRWV)’s Stock is Coming Back,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-stock-coming-back-114735873.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is a key player in the AI industry. The firm provides computing infrastructure for AI software companies. It was one of the first stocks that were listed in 2025, and since […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-stock-coming-back-114735873.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] People Should Have Listened to NVIDIA (NVDA)’s CEO, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-listened-nvidia-nvda-ceo-114644985.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA)’s shares are down by 1.3% year-to-date. RBC Capital set an Outperform rating for the stock and a $240 share price target for the firm in mid-January. Some of the factors that […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-listened-nvidia-nvda-ceo-114644985.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Recalls Being Bullish on Micron (MU) a Year Ago</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-recalls-being-bullish-114637756.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) has quietly emerged as one of the top semiconductor stocks in the market. Its shares are up by a whopping 231% over the past year. Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-recalls-being-bullish-114637756.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Sun Pharma Eyes Organon In What Could Be India Pharma's Biggest Cross-Border Deal: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sun-pharma-eyes-organon-could-114606281.html</link><description>India-based Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd is reportedly evaluating a potential acquisition of Organon &amp;amp; Co (NYSE:OGN), a U.S.-based women's healthcare company. If it goes through, the deal that could become the largest cross-border transaction ever by an Indian drugmaker, according to people familiar with the matter, as cited by The Economic Times. Sun Pharmaceutical has submitted a non-binding all-cash bid and arranged $10–14 billion in acquisition financing. Why It Matters If completed, th</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sun-pharma-eyes-organon-could-114606281.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Jumps 11% as Chip Stocks Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</link><description>AI optimism lifts semiconductors across the board</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Should You 'Buy' or 'Sell' IBM Stock Ahead of Q4 Earnings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-sell-ibm-stock-ahead-113935221.html</link><description>IBM Earnings Loom. The Z17 Cycle and 2026 Outlook Are in Focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-sell-ibm-stock-ahead-113935221.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] January 2026's Stocks That May Be Trading Below Estimated Value</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/january-2026s-stocks-may-trading-113807425.html</link><description>Amid recent market volatility, the U.S. stock indices have shown resilience with a sharp rebound following geopolitical tensions and tariff threats. As investors navigate these fluctuations, identifying stocks that may be trading below their estimated value can present opportunities for those looking to capitalize on potential market inefficiencies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/january-2026s-stocks-may-trading-113807425.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] I Called Alphabet's Monster Comeback in 2025. Here's Where I Think It's Heading in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/called-alphabet-monster-comeback-2025-goog/</link><description>Alphabet's stock crushed the market in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/called-alphabet-monster-comeback-2025-goog/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Stock Markets Are Relying on the TACO Trade Again. Why That’s Not Good.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-market-trump-taco-trade-things-to-know-today-6ea34bd7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Trump cancels Greenland tariff threats, Supreme Court justices appear skeptical of Trump’s bid to fire Fed governor Lisa Cook, Amazon hits back at Walmart with planned megastore, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-market-trump-taco-trade-things-to-know-today-6ea34bd7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] TSMC Just Delivered Incredible News for ASML Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/tsmc-delivered-incredible-news-for-asml-invest/</link><description>ASML's stock price got a nice shot in the arm following TSMC's latest quarterly report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/tsmc-delivered-incredible-news-for-asml-invest/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] My Top 4 Stocks to Buy in Early 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-4-stocks-to-buy-in-early-2026/</link><description>These stocks offer impressive long-term upside with downside protection.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-4-stocks-to-buy-in-early-2026/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why 'Cheap' Software Stocks Could Be The Next Big AI Value Trap</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cheap-software-stocks-could-110112838.html</link><description>Enterprise software stocks are starting to look tempting again, at least on a chart. Adobe Inc. (NASDAQ:ADBE) is trading at November 2022 lows and has lost 55% of its value since its February 2024 peak. Salesforce Inc. (NYSE:CRM) sits near May 2024 levels, down about 40% from its January 2025 high. ServiceNow Inc. (NYSE:NOW) is at its lowest since November 2023, off roughly 45% from its January 2025 peak. To many investors, that looks like classic mean reversion. AI hardware stocks like Micron T</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cheap-software-stocks-could-110112838.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Do Its Financials Have Any Role To Play In Driving Analog Devices, Inc.'s (NASDAQ:ADI) Stock Up Recently?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financials-role-play-driving-analog-110045816.html</link><description>Analog Devices (NASDAQ:ADI) has had a great run on the share market with its stock up by a significant 25% over the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financials-role-play-driving-analog-110045816.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Taiwan Semiconductor Just Delivered Great News for Nvidia Shareholders</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductor-just-delivered-increible-news/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor has raised its growth projections.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductor-just-delivered-increible-news/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sovereign AI partners with Accenture and Palantir on EMEA data centre rollout</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/sovereign-ai-partners-accenture-palantir/</link><description>Accenture leads delivery, and Palantir optimises operations as Dell-Nvidia-powered centres target regulated, high-performance AI workloads across EMEA.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/sovereign-ai-partners-accenture-palantir/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This Magnificent Vanguard ETF Will Beat the S&amp;P 500 (Again) in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/prediction-vanguard-etf-will-beat-sp-500-in-2026/</link><description>The Vanguard Growth ETF has a stellar track record against the S&amp;amp;P 500 thanks to its unique portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/prediction-vanguard-etf-will-beat-sp-500-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trending tickers: AMD, Intel, Moderna, Associated British Foods and Young &amp; Co's Brewery</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI power and infrastructure needs boomed in 2025. At Davos, the AI story for 2026 remains the same.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</link><description>The AI industry's greatest bottleneck, power, drove a boom in infrastructure throughout 2025. At Davos, leaders signal that 2026 is likely to see more of the same.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba shares surge after report co prepares IPO of AI chip unit as demand surges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-shares-surge-report-co-094300227.html</link><description>Investing.com-- Alibaba Group Holdings (NYSE:BABA) is laying the groundwork for a potential listing of its chipmaking arm, seeking to capitalise on strong investor appetite for companies aiming to challenge Nvidia in the fast-growing AI accelerator market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-shares-surge-report-co-094300227.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] My Top 5 Predictions for the Magnificent Seven Stocks in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</link><description>Investors may continue to closely watch the Magnificent Seven this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba Is Said to Plan IPO for AI Chipmaking Unit T-Head</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-said-plan-ipo-ai-084012315.html</link><description>As a first step, Alibaba plans to restructure the unit as a business partly owned by employees, people familiar with the matter said.  The company will then explore an initial public offering, though the timing for that remains unclear, the people said, asking to remain anonymous discussing private plans.  Alibaba representatives didn’t respond to an email seeking comment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-said-plan-ipo-ai-084012315.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Motley Fool Interviews Zscaler Founder and CEO Jay Chaudhry</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-motley-fool-interviews-zscaler-founder-and-ceo/</link><description>Cloud security company Zscaler has racked up big returns for investors since going public in 2018.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-motley-fool-interviews-zscaler-founder-and-ceo/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Nvidia Stock -- 100% of His Portfolio Is Now Invested in 3 AI Stocks</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</link><description>Billionaire Peter Thiel has his entire portfolio invested in Tesla, Microsoft, and Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Is Bullish on UiPath, Inc. (PATH) Amid Stable IT Spending Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 15 High Growth Mid-Cap Stocks to Buy. The second stock on our list of high growth stocks is UiPath, Inc. TheFly reported on January 12 that Barclays raised its price target on PATH to $18 from $16 and maintained an Equal Weight rating. As part of its 2026 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Explains Why He Thinks NVIDIA’s Jensen Huang Is the “Greatest Technologist of Our Era”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-explains-why-thinks-081043024.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Cramer said that only NVIDIA saw the burgeoning demand for chips, as he commented: … NVIDIA… had much more foresight than Micron or anybody else in the industry, so its products are more plentiful… Again, only NVIDIA really saw it coming. They […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-explains-why-thinks-081043024.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on Super Micro: “Sell, I Don’t Need That”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-super-micro-sell-080925610.html</link><description>Super Micro Computer, Inc. (NASDAQ:SMCI) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Answering a caller’s query about the stock, Cramer stated: Sell. I don’t need that. And it just, you know… you gotta move on. You want to own that area, you own NVIDIA. Period. End of story. Super Micro Computer, Inc. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-super-micro-sell-080925610.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on Ares Capital: “I Want to Be Very Careful There”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</link><description>Ares Capital Corporation (NASDAQ:ARCC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. When a caller mentioned that their top five holdings are AAPL, ARCC, HSY, KMB, and NVDA, Cramer remarked: Wow, okay. Well, you got some yield there. You got some growth. I don’t like the Ares because I can’t really tell what […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on American Electric Power: “One of My Favorite Utilities for Multiple Years”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-american-electric-power-080919183.html</link><description>American Electric Power Company, Inc. (NASDAQ:AEP) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Inquiring if their portfolio is diversified enough, a club member mentioned that their top five holdings are PM, AMZN, NVDA, AEP, and UBER. In response, Cramer said: Okay, Uber, we know is transport. Amazon, we’re going to call it, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-american-electric-power-080919183.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Jim Cramer on Agnico Eagle: “This Is My Favorite Gold Company”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-agnico-eagle-favorite-080918365.html</link><description>Agnico Eagle Mines Limited (NYSE:AEM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. A caller outlined that their portfolio’s biggest five holdings are BA, AEM, MS, CAT, and TSM, and Cramer remarked: Okay, this is a terrific semiconductor manufacturing company. This is my favorite gold company. This is one of the best machinery […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-agnico-eagle-favorite-080918365.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer on Simon Property’s CEO: “We Think David Simon’s the Best Mall Operator There Is”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-simon-property-ceo-080916327.html</link><description>Simon Property Group, Inc. (NYSE:SPG) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Starting the round of “Am I Diversified,” a club member mentioned that their top five holdings are SPG, AMZN, AVGO, LNG, and VICI. Cramer replied: Wow, you’re diversified, but we may have to do some work anyway, just in terms […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-simon-property-ceo-080916327.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Jim Cramer Calls Lam Research the “Best of the Best” But Warns Against Buying Parabolic Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-lam-research-080903287.html</link><description>Lam Research Corporation (NASDAQ:LRCX) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Noting the stock’s parabolic move since September 2025, a caller asked if there is more room for it to go up or if it has reached the top. Cramer replied: Do you know that that’s got one great CEO in Tim […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-lam-research-080903287.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] The Age of AI Agents Brings a Risk No One Is Prepared For</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence companies have promised that 2026 will be the year of agents: Software that can use AI language models to autonomously execute a complex series of tasks from simple instructions.  The most prevalent use for agents today is for making software.  With enough of a budget, a single developer can orchestrate teams of agents to work on existing codebases or even to start a project from scratch.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Only 3 of My Top 10 Stocks for 2025 Lost to the Market. Here Are the Ones I Think Are Still Buys for 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/only-3-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-lost-to-the-ma/</link><description>All three of these stocks have done well; investors' perception is the only thing holding them back.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/only-3-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-lost-to-the-ma/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Is Snowflake (SNOW) Pricing Its Long Term Growth Too Richly After Recent Pullback</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-snow-pricing-long-term-043748733.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Snowflake's current share price lines up with its long term potential, this article will walk through what the numbers are actually saying about value. Snowflake last closed at US$206.50, with returns of 0.2% over 7 days, a 9.0% decline over 30 days, a 4.7% decline year to date, a 16.3% gain over 1 year and 43.0% over 3 years. Recent market conversations around Snowflake have focused on how investors are weighing its long term growth story against the price they...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-snow-pricing-long-term-043748733.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] 2 High-Flying Stocks Worth Your Attention and 1 We Avoid</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-high-flying-stocks-worth-043246981.html</link><description>Expensive stocks typically earn their valuations through superior growth rates that other companies simply can’t match. The flip side though is that these lofty expectations make them particularly susceptible to drawdowns when market sentiment shifts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-high-flying-stocks-worth-043246981.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cathie Wood's Ark Unleashes Cryptic ARKmoji Teasers To Showcase Its 'Big Ideas' For 2026: Can You Take A Guess At The Hidden Meaning?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-unleashes-cryptic-033110612.html</link><description>Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest unveiled its “big ideas” for 2025 in a cryptic list, challenging users to interpret a series of custom images called “ARKmoji” to understand their picks for the year. Ark’s ‘Big Ideas’ For 2026 On Monday, in a thread on X, the investment management firm shared six “ARKmojis” along with a poll containing options under each, allowing followers to vote on their interpretation of the idea behind each image. 1. AI Agents The first image pointed towards agentic AI, but users w</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-unleashes-cryptic-033110612.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Artificial Intelligence Stocks You Can Buy and Hold for the Next Decade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-stocks-buy-and-hold/</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) stocks still have a lot more room to run over the next decade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-stocks-buy-and-hold/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks track Wall St rally as Trump cools tariff threats in Davos</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</link><description>Asian stocks rose Thursday while safe-haven precious metals extended losses after Donald Trump rowed back on his threat to hit key European countries with tariffs over their opposition to the US takeover of Greenland.Gold and silver, which have hit multiple records this week on a push into safe havens by worried traders, both fell Wednesday, and extended their retreat in Asia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Franklin Resources (BEN) Target Raised as Barclays Updates Asset Manager Models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</link><description>Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 15, Barclays raised its price target on Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) to $25 from $22, while still keeping an Underweight rating on the stock. The firm said the adjustment was mainly driven by updates to its asset manager […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Q4 Preview: Kimberly-Clark (KMB) Target Cut, “enthusiasm” Not Driven by Fundamentals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</link><description>Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 16, Barclays cut its price target on Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) to $102 from $132, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The move was part of the firm’s Q4 earnings preview for the consumer staples sector, where […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] CubeSmart (CUBE) Target Cut as Barclays Updates 2026 REIT Sector View</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</link><description>CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 13, Barclays analyst Brendan Lynch trimmed his price target on CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) to $43 from $45, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change came as part of Barclays’ broader 2026 outlook update for the REIT sector. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Anthropic CEO goes nuclear on Nvidia</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/anthropic-ceo-goes-nuclear-on-nvidia</link><description>In November 2025, Nvidia (NVDA) said it would invest up to $10 billion in Anthropic. The company also stated it will help optimize Anthropic models for performance, efficiency, and total cost of ownership. Anthropic’s artificial intelligence models have been trained on Nvidia GPUs, Amazon Trainium ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/anthropic-ceo-goes-nuclear-on-nvidia</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Semiconductor Stock Trading at a Discount to Start the New Year</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/semiconductor-stock-trading-discount-2026-nvda/</link><description>Nvidia's stock is cheap to start the new year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/semiconductor-stock-trading-discount-2026-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta's Recent Stock Decline Is 'Self-Inflicted,' Says Analyst, Predicts Rally If Mark Zuckerberg Does This</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/metas-recent-stock-decline-self-013110659.html</link><description>Suncoast Equity managing director and co-portfolio manager Eric Lynch weighed in on Meta Platform Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:META) recent stock decline amid investor skepticism about the company’s capital expenditure (capex) guidance for the year. Capex Concerns Pressure Meta Stock Lynch, in a recent conversation with Yahoo Finance on Sunday, suggested that investors are wary of a potential increase in capex due to CEO and founder Mark Zuckerberg‘s AI push. This skepticism has led to a 4.6% drop in Meta’s s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/metas-recent-stock-decline-self-013110659.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This AI Cloud Specialist Is Poised for a Decade of Explosive Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-ai-cloud-specialist-is-poised-for-growth/</link><description>This company recently reported triple-digit revenue growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-ai-cloud-specialist-is-poised-for-growth/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Artificial Intelligence (AI) Spending Is Exploding. This Stock Stands to Benefit Most</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-ai-spending-broadcom/</link><description>Broadcom is poised to be one of the biggest beneficiaries of increasing AI infrastructure spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-ai-spending-broadcom/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] As Taiwan Semi Hikes Its Dividend 20%, Should You Buy TSM Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37163143/as-taiwan-semi-hikes-its-dividend-20-should-you-buy-tsm-stock</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor continues to increase its payout. Is the growth sustainable? Here's what to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37163143/as-taiwan-semi-hikes-its-dividend-20-should-you-buy-tsm-stock</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sovereign AI Data Center Role Could Be A Game Changer For Accenture (ACN)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sovereign-ai-data-center-role-002437639.html</link><description>Sovereign AI recently announced it has selected Accenture and Palantir to help build and scale next-generation, sovereign-grade AI data centers across EMEA, aiming to support commercial and government clients with resilient Dell AI Factory- and NVIDIA-powered infrastructure and potential future expansion into APAC. This collaboration highlights Accenture’s growing involvement in critical AI infrastructure and sovereign AI solutions, an area where its own research shows rising investment...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sovereign-ai-data-center-role-002437639.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Surging memory chip prices dim outlook for consumer electronics makers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-memory-chip-prices-dim-001756209.html</link><description>Global demand for smartphones, personal computers and gaming consoles is expected to shrink this year as companies from Britain's Raspberry Pi to HP Inc raise sticker prices to offset surging memory chip costs.  The rapid build-out of artificial intelligence infrastructure by U.S. tech firms such ​as OpenAI, Alphabet-owned  Google and Microsoft has absorbed much of the world's memory chip supply, pushing up prices as manufacturers prioritize components for higher-margin data ‌centers over consumer devices.  Samsung, SK Hynix and Micron, the world's three largest producers of memory chips, have said in recent months that they were struggling to keep up with demand as they reported rosy quarterly ‌earnings on the back of surging prices for their semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-memory-chip-prices-dim-001756209.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Truist Reiterates Buy on Meta Platforms (META), Says AI Fears Are Priced In</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/truist-reiterates-buy-meta-platforms-235455341.html</link><description>Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 14, Truist Securities reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with an $875.00 price target. While META has underperformed peers since Q3 earnings, the firm believes investor fears are already priced in. In an investor note, the firm noted how Meta […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/truist-reiterates-buy-meta-platforms-235455341.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures rise after Trump backpedals on tariffs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-tariffs-234947394.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-tariffs-234947394.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] 2025 Was a Record Year for Activism: Barclays</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/2025-record-activism-barclays-234806819.html</link><description>Jim Rossman, global head of shareholder advisory at Barclays Capital, says 2025 set a record with 255 activist campaigns. He tells Romaine Bostick and Katie Greifeld on "The Close" that M&amp;amp;A demands were the top focus of these activists.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/2025-record-activism-barclays-234806819.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] KeyBanc Raises Applied Materials (AMAT) Target to $380, Keeps Overweight Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-raises-applied-materials-amat-233441836.html</link><description>Applied Materials, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMAT) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 16, KeyBanc raised the price target on the stock to $380.00 (from $285.00) while maintaining an “Overweight” rating. The firm sees AMAT well-positioned for vertical scaling and DRAM-driven capacity growth. KeyBanc noted that AMAT’s valuation is reasonable even though it […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-raises-applied-materials-amat-233441836.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Evercore ISI Raises IBM Price Target to $330, Adds Stock to Tactical Outperform List</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-raises-ibm-price-232206297.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 20, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani raised the price target on the stock to $330 from $315 and kept an Outperform rating. The firm also added IBM to its “Tactical Outperform list” ahead of IBM’s December-end quarterly results due […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-raises-ibm-price-232206297.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Citizens Reiterates Bullish View on CrowdStrike (CRWD) With $550 Price Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citizens-reiterates-bullish-view-crowdstrike-232102207.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 20, Citizens analyst reiterated a Market Outperform rating on the stock with a $550.00 price target. According to the firm, CrowdStrike’s recent acquisitions in identity governance and secure browser space help the company close potential functional gaps and limit competitors’ […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citizens-reiterates-bullish-view-crowdstrike-232102207.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA (KLAC) Outpaces Stock Market Gains: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-outpaces-stock-market-231503506.html</link><description>KLA (KLAC) concluded the recent trading session at $1, signifying a +2.28% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-outpaces-stock-market-231503506.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How Apple’s Gemini-Powered Siri Deal Will Impact Alphabet (GOOGL) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-powered-siri-deal-231107182.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, Apple announced a multi-year partnership with Google to base its next generation of Apple Foundation Models on Google’s Gemini AI and cloud technology, bringing more personalized, AI-powered Siri features while keeping Apple Intelligence workloads on-device and within its Private Cloud Compute framework. The deal effectively places Google’s Gemini at the heart of Apple’s core AI experience, turning a long-time ecosystem rival into a large-scale customer for...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-powered-siri-deal-231107182.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire to offload Kraft Heinz: What it means in post-Buffett era</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/berkshire-offload-kraft-heinz-means-230357046.html</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway (BRK-B, BRK-A) is reportedly taking steps to offload its Kraft Heinz (KHC) investment. FBB Capital Partners senior portfolio manager Mel Casey joins Market Domination Overtime with Josh Lipton to discuss what it means for Kraft Heinz and signals about CEO Greg Abel's tenure. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/berkshire-offload-kraft-heinz-means-230357046.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) Outperforms Broader Market: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-outperforms-230002115.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) settling at $313.84, representing a +2.23% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-outperforms-230002115.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] What Bubble? Nvidia CEO Says AI Needs Trillions More in Investments</title><link>https://decrypt.co/355345/what-bubble-nvidia-ceo-says-ai-needs-trillions-more-investments</link><description>Nvidia's CEO told the World Economic Forum that AI infrastructure needs trillions more in investment to avoid a bubble collapse—even as fears mount that the industry is already overheating.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://decrypt.co/355345/what-bubble-nvidia-ceo-says-ai-needs-trillions-more-investments</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Stock Market Today, Jan. 21: Dow Rebounds After Greenland and Tariff Tensions Ease</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/21/stock-market-today-jan-21-dow-rebounds-after-greenland-and-tariff-tensions-ease/</link><description>Today, Jan. 21, 2026, U.S. stocks staged a relief rally as Trump's Davos remarks eased Greenland and tariff fears.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/21/stock-market-today-jan-21-dow-rebounds-after-greenland-and-tariff-tensions-ease/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research (LRCX) Outperforms Broader Market: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-outperforms-broader-225003307.html</link><description>Lam Research (LRCX) closed at $228.34 in the latest trading session, marking a +2.67% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-outperforms-broader-225003307.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A timeline of the US semiconductor market in 2025</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/timeline-us-semiconductor-market-2025-110649518.html</link><description>From leadership changes at legacy semiconductor companies to wishy washy policy around chip exports, a lot happened last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/timeline-us-semiconductor-market-2025-110649518.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar (CAT) Surpasses Market Returns: Some Facts Worth Knowing</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-cat-surpasses-market-returns-224505306.html</link><description>Caterpillar (CAT) closed at $645.38 in the latest trading session, marking a +2.6% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-cat-surpasses-market-returns-224505306.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Analyst Calls Tesla 7 Times More 'Capital Efficient' Than Rivals: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analyst-calls-tesla-7-times-223109335.html</link><description>NewStreet Research analyst Pierre Ferragu has hailed Tesla Inc.'s (NASDAQ:TSLA) Robotaxi efforts compared to the likes of Alphabet Inc.-backed (NASDAQ:GOOGL) (NASDAQ:GOOG) Waymo. Tesla ‘Seven Times More Capital Efficient' Than Rivals, Says Pierre Ferragu In an interview with influencer Farzad Mesbahi on Saturday, Ferragu shared his thoughts on the company's Robotaxi efforts. "Tesla is seven times more capital efficient than competitors," Ferragu said, adding that Waymo still faced issues related</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analyst-calls-tesla-7-times-223109335.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 of My Top 4 AI Stock Picks for 2025 Rose At Least 38%. Are They Still Best Buys for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-of-my-top-4-ai-stocks-for-2025-rose-at-least-39/</link><description>AI is still the prevailing theme in the stock market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-of-my-top-4-ai-stocks-for-2025-rose-at-least-39/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Cathie Wood’s ARK Invest Makes Bold Bitcoin and Nvidia Prediction</title><link>https://beincrypto.com/cathie-wood-ark-invest-bitcoin-prediction/</link><description>Cathie Wood’s ARK predicts $800,000 Bitcoin by 2030 while warning Nvidia faces rising AI competition and slower growth ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://beincrypto.com/cathie-wood-ark-invest-bitcoin-prediction/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dow Jones Futures: Stocks Jump As Trump Halts Greenland Tariffs; Google, Eli Lilly Lead 8 New Buys</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-halts-greenland-tariffs-framework-google-eli-lilly-new-buys/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks rebounded as President Donald Trump said he won't go ahead with Greenland tariffs, citing a "framework" for a future deal. Google and Eli Lilly lead new buys.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-halts-greenland-tariffs-framework-google-eli-lilly-new-buys/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Stocks Settle Sharply Higher as President Trump Claims Deal on Greenland</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37160789/stocks-settle-sharply-higher-as-president-trump-claims-deal-on-greenland</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Index ($SPX ) (SPY ) on Wednesday closed up +1.16%, the Dow Jones Industrials Index ($DOWI ) (DIA ) closed up +1.21%, and the Nasdaq 100 Index ($IUXX ) (QQQ ) closed up +1.36%. March E-mini S&amp;amp;P futures (ESH26 ) rose +1.18%, and March E-mini Nasdaq futures...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37160789/stocks-settle-sharply-higher-as-president-trump-claims-deal-on-greenland</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] My Top 2 Stocks to Buy in Early 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/my-top-2-stocks-to-buy-in-early-2026/</link><description>These two stocks are poised to outperform the S&amp;amp;P 500 as they capitalize on AI tailwinds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/my-top-2-stocks-to-buy-in-early-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Anthropic’s Revenue Run Rate Tops $9 Billion as VCs Pile In</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-revenue-run-rate-tops-191530794.html</link><description>Combined with $15 billion in total prior commitments from Nvidia Corp. and Microsoft Corp., the size of the current financing could easily surpass $20 billion, some of the people said.  The list of investors in the round is starting to take shape: Coatue Management and Singapore’s GIC, which are leading the financing, are each expected to put in about $1.5 billion, according to one of the people.  Iconiq Capital is also slated to be a major investor, with plans to put in $1 billion or more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-revenue-run-rate-tops-191530794.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO urges continued spending into AI: Top takeaways</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-urges-continued-spending-213600478.html</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang dismissed fears of an AI bubble in an interview at the World Economic Forum (WEF) in Davos, Switzerland, on Wednesday, citing the massive investments into the technology and infrastructure. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley assesses Huang's claims that artificial intelligence will create more jobs, comparing them to job loss fears coming from certain industries. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-urges-continued-spending-213600478.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] 3 Top Tech Stocks That Could Make You a Millionaire</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-top-tech-stocks-that-could-make-you-a-millionair/</link><description>Nebius, Symbotic, and Strategy could generate multibagger gains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-top-tech-stocks-that-could-make-you-a-millionair/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Johnson &amp; Johnson (JNJ) Tops Q4 Earnings and Revenue Estimates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/johnson-johnson-jnj-tops-q4-212003520.html</link><description>Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (JNJ) delivered earnings and revenue surprises of +1.05% and +1.84%, respectively, for the quarter ended December 2025. Do the numbers hold clues to what lies ahead for the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/johnson-johnson-jnj-tops-q4-212003520.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Tracking The Evolving Narrative For IBM (IBM) After The Latest Price Target Shift</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tracking-evolving-narrative-ibm-ibm-211729489.html</link><description>What the Updated Price Target Signals About IBM's Story The recent change in the price target for International Business Machines is less about a single headline event and more about how analysts now frame the story around the company. Even without a detailed breakdown of the commentary, a shift in target alone tells you that expectations about risk, opportunity and timing have been reconsidered. As you read on, you will see how to keep track of these price target moves so you can stay...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tracking-evolving-narrative-ibm-ibm-211729489.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Alphabet Rallied Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/why-alphabet-rallied-today/</link><description>Google DeepMind Co-Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Demis Hassabis explained why Alphabet should be able to maintain its lead and why AI is 10 times bigger than the industrial revolution.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/why-alphabet-rallied-today/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] House Seeks More Say in AI Chip Exports After Nvidia’s China Win</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/house-seeks-more-ai-chip-211053332.html</link><description>A House committee focused on foreign affairs approved bipartisan legislation Wednesday that calls for arms-sale style congressional oversight of advanced AI chip exports.  The text, endorsed by the panel’s Republicans and Democrats, would outright ban sales of Nvidia’s Blackwell chips to China for two years, codifying existing export controls into law.  The bill marks a response to President Donald Trump’s decision last month to ease longstanding export controls on China, a move aimed at spurring adoption of American AI technology in global markets but one that drew strenuous objections from national security hawks in Congress.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/house-seeks-more-ai-chip-211053332.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Datadog, Wix, 8x8, Akamai Technologies, and Asure Software Stocks Trade Up, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/datadog-wix-8x8-akamai-technologies-210044765.html</link><description>A number of stocks jumped in the afternoon session after President Trump cooled fears of a transatlantic trade war by calling off scheduled tariffs on European allies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/datadog-wix-8x8-akamai-technologies-210044765.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella Warns AI Could Lose 'Social Permission' If It Burns Energy Without Real-World Benefits In Health And Education</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-ceo-satya-nadella-warns-205620968.html</link><description>Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) CEO Satya Nadella says artificial intelligence faces a test: prove it improves people's lives or risk losing public trust. Speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, on Tuesday in a wide-ranging discussion with BlackRock (NYSE:BLK) CEO Larry Fink, Nadella said AI's massive energy use will only be tolerated if it delivers tangible results in areas like health care, education and productivity. “We will quickly lose even the social permission to actually tak</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-ceo-satya-nadella-warns-205620968.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Why Eli Lilly (LLY) Stock Is Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-eli-lilly-lly-stock-203040864.html</link><description>Shares of global pharmaceutical company Eli Lilly (NYSE:LLY) jumped 3.5% in the afternoon session after the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) granted a Breakthrough Therapy designation for its drug, sofetabart mipitecan, intended to treat a specific type of ovarian cancer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-eli-lilly-lly-stock-203040864.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple to revamp Siri as a built-in chatbot, Bloomberg News reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-chatbot-202957790.html</link><description>Apple plans to revamp Siri later this year by turning the digital assistant into the ​company's first artificial intelligence chatbot, Bloomberg News reported on ‌Wednesday.  The chatbot, code named Campos, will be embedded deeply into the iPhone, ‌iPad and Mac operating systems and will replace the current Siri interface, the report said, citing people familiar with the plan.  Siri's revamp is a crucial part of Apple's strategy to catch up ⁠to its Big Tech ‌peers in the AI race after its initial "Apple Intelligence" rollout in 2024 met with lukewarm reception.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-chatbot-202957790.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Better AI Chip Stock: Nvidia vs. Navitas Semiconductor</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/better-ai-chip-stock-nvidia-vs-navitas-semiconduct/</link><description>Which of these popular chip stocks is a better buy today?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/better-ai-chip-stock-nvidia-vs-navitas-semiconduct/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple stock spikes after report of Siri revamp into chatbot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-spikes-report-siri-202356243.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) stock spiked as much as 1.6% Wednesday afternoon following a Bloomberg News report that the company plans to transform Siri into a built-in chatbot, marking its entry into the generative AI race currently led by OpenAI and Google.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-spikes-report-siri-202356243.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm Stock Jumps After Top Analyst Upgrade Price Target to $150</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-stock-jumps-top-analyst-202132200.html</link><description>Arm Stock Rises on Near-Term Data Center Strength, v9 and CSS Adoption</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-stock-jumps-top-analyst-202132200.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple’s new Siri runs on Gemini, and there’s an invisible catch</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apples-new-siri-runs-on-gemini-and-theres-an-invisible-catch</link><description>Apple and Google describe their Gemini deal as a multi‑year collaboration that will put Google’s models and cloud technology at the core of Apple’s next generation of foundation models, including a more personalized Siri arriving later this year. In their joint statement, the companies stress that ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apples-new-siri-runs-on-gemini-and-theres-an-invisible-catch</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple to Revamp Siri as a Built-In iPhone, Mac Chatbot to Fend Off OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-iphone-195739657.html</link><description>The chatbot — code-named Campos — will be embedded deeply into the iPhone, iPad and Mac operating systems and replace the current Siri interface, according to people familiar with the plan.  Users will be able to summon the new service the same way they open Siri now, by speaking the “Siri” command or holding down the side button on their iPhone or iPad.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-revamp-siri-built-iphone-195739657.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Where Will TSMC Stock Be in 1 Year?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/where-will-tsmc-stock-be-in-1-year/</link><description>TSMC's latest quarterly results make it clear that the stock is poised for more gains in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/where-will-tsmc-stock-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Nvidia, Broadcom, Micron Stocks Jump -- JPMorgan Flags as Top Chip Picks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-micron-stocks-jump-192512678.html</link><description>Chip Stocks Rise After JPMorgan Names Nvidia, Broadcom, Micron Top Picks</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-micron-stocks-jump-192512678.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Links AI Expansion to Data Center Jobs Boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-links-ai-expansion-data-192041942.html</link><description>CEO Jensen Huang says AI-driven data center buildouts are boosting vocational wages as Nvidia's data center sales surge.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-links-ai-expansion-data-192041942.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] In Davos, Tech Execs Sound More Bullish Than Ever. Four Things We Learned About AI.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/davos-ai-nvidia-microsoft-amazon-stock-5f0bc8e1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tech CEOs used Davos forums to extol the future of AI, both in the enterprise and for helping better the world.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/davos-ai-nvidia-microsoft-amazon-stock-5f0bc8e1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Colgate-Palmolive (CL) Valuation Check After Defensive Rotation And Upgraded Analyst Views</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</link><description>Recent commentary from Barclays and Wells Fargo has pushed Colgate-Palmolive (CL) into focus, as both banks highlight growing investor interest in the stock as a defensive option while maintaining a cautious stance on fundamentals. See our latest analysis for Colgate-Palmolive. The recent analyst comments and Colgate-Palmolive’s new four year collaboration with the WHO Foundation come as the shares trade at US$85.44. The 30 day share price return is 9.04% and the year to date share price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Says AI Buildout Will Run Into Trillions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-buildout-191613051.html</link><description>CEO Jensen Huang forecasts trillion-dollar AI buildout at Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-buildout-191613051.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT) Valuation Check After Recent Share Price Pullbacks And Longer Term Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-valuation-191434706.html</link><description>Vertiv Holdings Co: recent performance snapshot Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT) has kept investors busy recently, with the stock showing a mix of short term pullbacks and longer term strength. This has prompted closer attention to how its fundamentals line up with its current price. Over the past day, Vertiv’s share price recorded a 0.99% decline, while the past week shows a 1.42% gain and roughly 9.61% return over the past month. This highlights uneven but positive recent momentum. See our latest...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-valuation-191434706.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How President Trump and Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang's Davos moves helped dip-buying investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/how-president-trump-and-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huangs-davos-moves-helped-dip-buying-investors-191036008.html</link><description>Welcome back, "buy the dip" fans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/how-president-trump-and-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huangs-davos-moves-helped-dip-buying-investors-191036008.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Veteran analyst revisits key semiconductor stock amid tech earnings season</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/veteran-analyst-revisits-key-chip-stock-amid-earnings-season</link><description>Shares of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM) slid 4.45% on Jan. 20, erasing most of last week’s post-earnings gains amid a broader market slump. The company is the world’s largest chip foundry and a critical manufacturer for Nvidia (NVDA), AMD (AMD), and Broadcom (AVGO). Its earnings ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/veteran-analyst-revisits-key-chip-stock-amid-earnings-season</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Confirms AI4-Powered Cars Can Achieve Unsupervised Self-Driving Without Additional Upgrades</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has confirmed that the automaker's vehicles equipped with the AI4 (HW4) chip will be able to achieve unsupervised autonomous driving without requiring upgrades. AI4 Will Be Capable Of Self-Driving On Monday, user @iliketeslas shared a post on the social media platform X, stating that the current AI4 chips are capable of running Unsupervised FSD without "better hardware." Anyone using AI4 right now knows that better hardware is not needed for unsupervised dr</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Rise of AI Factories | VRT Stock, NVT Stock, MOD Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</link><description>24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are kicking the New Year off in style with 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. Over the course of 12 videos, the two will share their thoughts on everything from the memory explosion to software stocks to robotics. In this video, Eric takes a deeper look at the rise of AI factories, massive data centers with a capacity of more than 1 gigawatt. As Eric notes, it's not just Oracle's Stargate getting into the race. There are also new super factories from Microsoft, Amazon, Meta, and many others. Companies with data center cooling portfolios like Vertiv (NYSE: VRT), nVent Electric (NYSE: NVT), Modine Manufacturing (NYSE: MOD) could be winners as the construction of this new generation of data centers takes off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Dives Deeper Into AI Inference</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dives-deeper-ai-inference-185420811.html</link><description>Inference startup draws heavyweight backing</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dives-deeper-ai-inference-185420811.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Plans China Visit as AI Chip Sales Face New Limits</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-plans-184842739.html</link><description>Trip aims to strengthen key relationships amid trade restrictions and easing H200 shipments.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-plans-184842739.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Zipline charts drone delivery expansion with $600M in new funding</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zipline-charts-drone-delivery-expansion-183333018.html</link><description>That geographic expansion in the United States has fueled Zipline’s delivery numbers. In 2024, the company completed 1 million drone deliveries to customers; this week, Zipline said it had surpassed 2 million deliveries.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zipline-charts-drone-delivery-expansion-183333018.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tom Nash Says This Energy Stock Could Solve AI's Power Crisis: Sees 7x Upside And 1,400% Revenue Growth In 5 years 'If They Execute'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tom-nash-says-energy-stock-183108000.html</link><description>Investor Tom Nash says this California-based energy company will play a pivotal role in solving AI’s “greatest bottleneck,” that is, reliable power for data centers. Sees 7x Upside Through 2030 Nash, known for earlier bullish calls on Palantir Technologies Inc. (NASDAQ:PLTR) and Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA), is now highlighting fuel-cell maker Bloom Energy Corp. (NYSE:BE) as his next major bet, projecting significant upside in the coming years. On his YouTube channel last week, Nash said that the co</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tom-nash-says-energy-stock-183108000.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Financial Advisor Told Him To Move $50K Out Of His 401(k) Into A Traditional IRA In 2021. Five Years Later, He's Only Up $2K</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financial-advisor-told-him-move-183108073.html</link><description>In 2021, a 34-year-old investor followed what sounded like standard advice. He rolled about $50,000 from his 401(k) into a Traditional IRA with the help of a local financial advisor. Then he did what many people are told to do with retirement money. “I've for the most part ignored it as that was always the advice I was given,” he wrote in Reddit’s personal finance community recently. Five years later, when he finally checked, the account balance was just over $52,000. After one of the strongest</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financial-advisor-told-him-move-183108073.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Why Eli Lilly Is The IBD Stock Of The Day — Again — As Its Novo Nordisk Rivalry Deepens</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/eli-lilly-stock-fda-weight-loss-pill-orforglipron/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Eli Lilly is Wednesday's IBD Stock Of The Day. Lilly shares are bounding off their 50-day line with a new buying opportunity in sight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/eli-lilly-stock-fda-weight-loss-pill-orforglipron/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Dave (DAVE) Quietly Recasting Its Board for an AI-Centric Fintech Strategy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dave-dave-quietly-recasting-board-181928513.html</link><description>Dave Inc. recently announced that Nima Khajehnouri, a senior artificial intelligence and data engineering leader currently serving as Vice President of Engineering at Meta and formerly at Google and Snap, has joined its Board of Directors and Audit Committee, while Imran Khan has stepped down and several board leadership roles have been reshuffled. This move signals an effort by Dave to deepen its technical governance and innovation capabilities at the board level as it applies advanced...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dave-dave-quietly-recasting-board-181928513.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Just Scored a Major Supercomputer Win. Should You Buy NBIS Stock Here?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37156902/nebius-just-scored-a-major-supercomputer-win-should-you-buy-nbis-stock-here</link><description>Nebius has multiple positive attributes, but it also has a very high valuation, while its sector is not as beloved by the Street as it once was.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37156902/nebius-just-scored-a-major-supercomputer-win-should-you-buy-nbis-stock-here</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Is Vertiv (VRT) Still Reasonably Priced After Its Strong Multi Year Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-still-reasonably-priced-181541179.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Vertiv Holdings Co at around US$175.18 is still priced reasonably after its strong run, this article walks through what the numbers are actually saying about value. The stock has returned 1.4% over the past week, 9.6% over the last 30 days, is roughly flat year to date with a 0.2% decline, and has a 22.6% return over the last year, with a very large gain over three and five years. Recent coverage has highlighted Vertiv's role as a provider of power and thermal...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-still-reasonably-priced-181541179.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] How Investors May Respond To Albemarle (ALB) After HSBC Upgrade And Stronger Balance Sheet Focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-albemarle-alb-181510476.html</link><description>Earlier this week, HSBC upgraded Albemarle, highlighting expectations of tighter lithium supply and improved company fundamentals including stronger free cash flow and a healthier balance sheet. The bank also pointed to Albemarle’s recent capital raising and operational efficiency efforts as key factors enhancing its leverage in upcoming lithium contract negotiations. Next, we’ll examine how HSBC’s focus on Albemarle’s bolstered balance sheet and lithium market backdrop shapes the company’s...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-albemarle-alb-181510476.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI-Enabled Impersonation Scams Drove Record $17B In Crypto Losses In 2025, Chainalysis Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-enabled-impersonation-scams-drove-180809657.html</link><description>A record $17 billion was lost to cryptocurrency scams last year, according to blockchain intelligence company Chainalysis. Chainalysis in a Jan. 13 report said the figure was up from $14 billion in 2024, attributing the surge to an increase in...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-enabled-impersonation-scams-drove-180809657.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron knows something the market is only starting to see</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/economy/micron-knows-something-the-market-is-only-starting-to-see</link><description>Nvidia supplier Micron Technology is airing its opinion regarding an "unprecedented" issue regarding AI, and Wall Street is standing up and taking notice. For now, the chipmaker believes the biggest issue facing the AI sector is a memory shortage that won't go away. Micron believes the issue is ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/economy/micron-knows-something-the-market-is-only-starting-to-see</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Red-Hot Growth Stocks to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-red-hot-growth-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</link><description>These companies boast different strengths that help them succeed with AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-red-hot-growth-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Scott Black's Strategic Moves: M&amp;T Bank Corp Leads the Way with 1.48% Portfolio Impact</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/scott-blacks-strategic-moves-m-180122620.html</link><description>Insight into Scott Black (Trades, Portfolio)'s Fourth Quarter 2025 Investment Strategy</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/scott-blacks-strategic-moves-m-180122620.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Did Nvidia’s CEO Just Deliver the Ultimate Buy Signal for Nebius?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/did-nvidias-ceo-just-deliver-the-ultimate-buy-signal-for-nebius/</link><description>Nebius Group (NASDAQ:NBIS) is forecasting up to 1,600% revenue growth by the end of 2026, driven by surging demand for AI compute infrastructure. The company projects an annualized run rate in revenue of $900 million to $1.1 billion for the end of 2025 and $7 billion to $9 billion by the end of 2026, as ... Did Nvidia’s CEO Just Deliver the Ultimate Buy Signal for Nebius?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/did-nvidias-ceo-just-deliver-the-ultimate-buy-signal-for-nebius/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] OpenEvidence hits $12B valuation, with new round led by Thrive, DST</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openevidence-hits-12b-valuation-round-180111298.html</link><description>The medical info database has doubled in valuation since last raise in October, despite encroachment from model makers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openevidence-hits-12b-valuation-round-180111298.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv (VRT) is an Incredible Growth Stock: 3 Reasons Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-incredible-growth-stock-174502172.html</link><description>Vertiv (VRT) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-incredible-growth-stock-174502172.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Super Semiconductor Stock Crushed Nvidia in 2025, and Jan. 28 Could Be a Very Big Day for Its Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</link><description>This semiconductor equipment powerhouse could be set for another strong year in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Her Husband Is Facing Up To 10 Years In Prison. 'Ramsey Show' Hosts Urge Her To Take Over His Business, But It's Not That Simple</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/her-husband-facing-10-years-173113681.html</link><description>A recent call to “The Ramsey Show” revealed the emotional and financial chaos one Louisiana woman is trying to navigate after her husband was arrested and could be facing years behind bars. Rental Properties, Two Kids And A Failing Business Plan Megan, a mother of two from Baton Rouge told hosts Jade Warshaw and Ken Coleman that her husband had been arrested just the week before their call. The timeline of his potential sentence isn't yet clear, but it could be anywhere from two to 10 years. Tha</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/her-husband-facing-10-years-173113681.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Registers Stake for Possible Sale After Kraft Heinz Breakup Plan</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-registers-stake-possible-sale-172520575.html</link><description>Kraft Heinz disclosed that more than 325 million Berkshire-held shares may be sold following its planned split.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-registers-stake-possible-sale-172520575.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Big Tech earnings put spotlight on AI and memory shortage as Trump tariff threats ease for now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-ease-for-now-172319457.html</link><description>Big Tech earnings will put a spotlight on the continued AI build-out, memory shortage, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-ease-for-now-172319457.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Big Tech earnings put spotlight on AI and memory shortage as Trump tariff threats loom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</link><description>Big Tech earnings will put a spotlight on the continued AI build-out, memory shortage, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Is Micron (MU) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</link><description>Shares of memory chips maker Micron (NYSE:MU) jumped 5.9% in the afternoon session after analysts at multiple firms, including Barclays, Stifel, and TD Cowen, raised their price targets on the stock, citing strong demand for its AI-related memory chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Fluence Energy (FLNC) Stock Is Trading Lower Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</link><description>Shares of electricity storage and software provider Fluence (NASDAQ:FLNC) fell 1.8% in the afternoon session after Goldman Sachs maintained its 'Buy' rating on the stock and raised its price target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why AMD (AMD) Stock Is Trading Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-amd-amd-stock-trading-172043151.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker AMD (NASDAQ:AMD) jumped 6.2% in the afternoon session after it received a series of positive developments, including upbeat analyst commentary, a new board appointment, and bullish sentiment on artificial intelligence spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-amd-amd-stock-trading-172043151.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Dear IBM Stock Fans, Mark Your Calendars for January 28</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37155591/dear-ibm-stock-fans-mark-your-calendars-for-january-28</link><description>IBM stock is heading into its January 28 earnings report with high expectations tied to the Z17 mainframe cycle, AI momentum, and guidance clarity for 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37155591/dear-ibm-stock-fans-mark-your-calendars-for-january-28</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Is CrowdStrike (CRWD) Fairly Priced After Recent Pullback And Cybersecurity Spotlight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether CrowdStrike Holdings is still worth the price you see on your screen, the key question is how that price lines up with what the business may realistically be worth. The stock last closed at US$442.73, after a 5.4% decline over the past week and an 8.0% decline over the past month, although the 1 year return sits at 20.8% and the 3 year return is very large. Recent attention on CrowdStrike has focused on its role as a major cybersecurity provider, as investors...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO's Davos message: The AI boom is a data center boom</title><link>https://qz.com/jensen-huang-nvidia-speech-davos-2026</link><description>The Nvidia CEO called AI “the largest infrastructure buildout in human history,” outlining a five-layer stack from energy to applications</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://qz.com/jensen-huang-nvidia-speech-davos-2026</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC (TSM) Is Up 5.80% in One Week: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-tsm-5-80-one-170003065.html</link><description>Does TSMC (TSM) have what it takes to be a top stock pick for momentum investors? Let's find out.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-tsm-5-80-one-170003065.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway Looks Poised to Break a Buffett Rule With Kraft-Heinz Sale</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-kraft-heinz-sale-3117c936?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Warren Buffett has famously said investors should be “fearful when others are greedy and greedy when others are fearful.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-kraft-heinz-sale-3117c936?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Takes Another Dig At Michael O'Leary Over Buying Ryanair, Says He'll Put A 'Ryan' In Charge: 'It Is Your Destiny'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-takes-another-dig-163110881.html</link><description>Billionaire entrepreneur and Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk once again joked about acquiring Irish ultra-low-cost airline, Ryanair Holdings PLC (NASDAQ:RYAAY). Will Appoint A ‘Ryan’ To Lead The Airline On Monday, in a post on X, Musk replied to Ryanair’s official X account, asking, “How much would it cost to buy you?” in response to the airline dismissing “Wi-Fi on planes” as a propaganda that it wasn’t falling for, in a subtle dig against Musk and his Starlink satellite internet service</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-takes-another-dig-163110881.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia Will Soar in 2026 Thanks to This 1 Thing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/prediction-nvidia-will-soar-in-2026-thanks-to-this/</link><description>A current trend in the AI market may boost Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/prediction-nvidia-will-soar-in-2026-thanks-to-this/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Serve Enters Healthcare With Diligent Robotics Acquisition</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/serve-enters-healthcare-diligent-robotics-161400132.html</link><description>SERV enters healthcare with a $29M stock deal for Diligent Robotics, adding Moxi hospital robots and expanding its platform into indoor environments.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/serve-enters-healthcare-diligent-robotics-161400132.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Systems (CSCO) Valuation Check After New Wi Fi 7 And AI Infrastructure Partnerships</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-valuation-check-161014228.html</link><description>Cisco Systems (CSCO) just announced two high-profile deals, a campus-wide Wi-Fi 7 buildout at Georgetown University and an AI infrastructure tie up with SharonAI and Digital Alpha in Asia Pacific, drawing fresh attention to the stock. See our latest analysis for Cisco Systems. Despite the fresh Georgetown and SharonAI announcements, Cisco’s share price has eased in the short term, with a 1 month share price return of 6.47% decline and a year to date share price return of 3.54% decline. Longer...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-valuation-check-161014228.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI startups are losing talent; Are defections the de facto?</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/ai-startups-losing-talent/</link><description>AI companies have an employee retention problem.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/ai-startups-losing-talent/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] NVTS vs. ADI: Which Semiconductor Stock Should You Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvts-vs-adi-semiconductor-stock-155400668.html</link><description>Analog Devices' AI-driven data center momentum and earnings visibility give it an edge over Navitas Semiconductor amid near-term revenue uncertainty.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvts-vs-adi-semiconductor-stock-155400668.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] 4 Stocks Guy Spier Was Selling in Q4</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-stocks-guy-spier-was-selling-in-q4/</link><description>Guy Spier of Aquamarine Capital is an incredibly intelligent value investor who’s heavily influenced by the great Warren Buffett. Just have a look at the Aquamarine portfolio, and you’ll notice many Buffett stocks as well as names that the Oracle of Omaha probably would have liked. With Buffett now retired, perhaps it’s Guy Spier and ... 4 Stocks Guy Spier Was Selling in Q4</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-stocks-guy-spier-was-selling-in-q4/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Accounting software platform Pennylane raises $205m</title><link>https://www.internationalaccountingbulletin.com/news/accounting-software-platform-pennylane/</link><description>Pennylane plans to channel the fresh capital into R&amp;amp;D.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.internationalaccountingbulletin.com/news/accounting-software-platform-pennylane/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO says AI boom is fueling the 'largest' infrastructure buildout in history</title><link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-boom-fueling-largest-infrastructure-buildout-history</link><description>AI infrastructure spending could reach $85 trillion over 15 years, creating massive job opportunities across construction, tech and manufacturing sectors, according to Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-boom-fueling-largest-infrastructure-buildout-history</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Can Vertiv's International Expansion Drive More Upside in the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertivs-international-expansion-drive-more-153800913.html</link><description>VRT's overseas momentum accelerates as AI demand lifts sales, expands backlog to $9.5B, and supports continued double-digit organic growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertivs-international-expansion-drive-more-153800913.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] FDA Grants Breakthrough Therapy Tag to LLY's Ovarian Cancer Candidate</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fda-grants-breakthrough-therapy-tag-153100294.html</link><description>Eli Lilly wins FDA Breakthrough Therapy status for sofetabart mipitecan in certain patients with platinum-resistant ovarian cancer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fda-grants-breakthrough-therapy-tag-153100294.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153016698.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153016698.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Will Lower Active Accounts Impact Synchrony's Q4 Earnings Potential?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lower-active-accounts-impact-synchronys-151700709.html</link><description>SYF heads into Q4 with higher margins and purchase volumes, but declining active accounts and average interest-earning assets cloud earnings upside.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lower-active-accounts-impact-synchronys-151700709.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is Eli Lilly (LLY) Pricing Look Stretched After A Strong Multi Year Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-pricing-look-151302414.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Eli Lilly's current share price reflects its true worth, you are not alone. This article is built to help you frame that question clearly. The stock recently closed at US$1,041.29, with returns of a 3.3% decline over 7 days, a 2.8% decline over 30 days, a 3.6% decline year to date, but a 41.3% gain over 1 year and a very large 5 year return of about 4x. Those moves come as Eli Lilly continues to be a regular focus of long term investors and large index funds...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-pricing-look-151302414.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway May Sell Stock in Kraft Heinz, Filing States</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-sell-kraft-heinz-087ba49f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway  may sell shares from its $7.8 billion equity stake in  Kraft Heinz  according to a prosepectus filed late Tuesday with the Securities and Exchange Commission.  The filing indicates Berkshire, which received the Kraft Heinz equity as part of a merger of Kraft and Heinz in 2015, may “offer to sell from time to time” shares from that stake.  Berkshire now holds a 27.5% stake in the food company, or 325.4 million shares.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-sell-kraft-heinz-087ba49f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang: 'Trillions of dollars of AI infrastructure needs to be built'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-trillions-of-dollars-of-ai-infrastructure-needs-to-be-built-144212721.html</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang told an audience at the gathering of the World Economic Forum that the world needs to build trillions of dollars of AI infrastructure to meet demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-trillions-of-dollars-of-ai-infrastructure-needs-to-be-built-144212721.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Is Greg Abel Making His First Move to Redefine Berkshire Hathaway?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-greg-abel-making-his-first-move-to-redefine-berkshire-hathaway/</link><description>Investors have long anticipated how Greg Abel, Warren Buffett’s successor as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway (NYSE:BRK-A)(NYSE:BRK-B), would influence the company following Buffett’s departure. With Abel now at the helm, we may be getting the first glimpse. Yesterday, Kraft Heinz (NASDAQ:KHC) revealed in an SEC filing a prospectus supplement registering the potential resale of up to ... Is Greg Abel Making His First Move to Redefine Berkshire Hathaway?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-greg-abel-making-his-first-move-to-redefine-berkshire-hathaway/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Intel Stock Rises Ahead of Earnings. Why Optimism Is Growing.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report.  Intel shares were up 5.8% at $51.35 in early trading.  Intel is expected to report adjusted earnings of eight cents a share on revenue of $13.42 billion for the fourth quarter of 2025, according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Kraft Heinz Spills Beans on Berkshire's Possible Share Sale; Stock Drops</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/kraft-heinz-spills-beans-on-berkshire-s-possible-share-sale-stock-drops-jJDQr87x9xukeNcLy2wZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Kraft Heinz shares dropped after the food company said in a regulatory filing that its biggest stockholder—Berkshire Hathaway—could sell nearly all of its shares.  Kraft Heinz’s Securities and Exchange Commission filing said Berkshire could sell up to 325.4 million shares.  Shares in the maker of Heinz Tomato Ketchup and Kraft Mac and Cheese fell roughly 7% Wednesday morning.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/kraft-heinz-spills-beans-on-berkshire-s-possible-share-sale-stock-drops-jJDQr87x9xukeNcLy2wZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] No One’s Talking About This AI Chip Stock That Can Easily 5X</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/no-ones-talking-about-this-ai-chip-stock-that-can-easily-5x/</link><description>Most investors on Wall Street are aware of Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA), AMD (NASDAQ:AMD), Broadcom (NASDAQ:AVGO), and the like. However, have you looked into ACM Research (NASDAQ:ACMR)? Very few will say yes, as the company is still rather under-the-radar. I called it out back in August 2023 as a stock with massive upside potential, and it has ... No One’s Talking About This AI Chip Stock That Can Easily 5X</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/no-ones-talking-about-this-ai-chip-stock-that-can-easily-5x/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm upgraded, Flutter downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-upgraded-flutter-downgraded-wall-143555244.html</link><description>Arm upgraded, Flutter downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-upgraded-flutter-downgraded-wall-143555244.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang: AI infrastructure buildout is 'sensible'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-ai-143500353.html</link><description>Speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang explains how the AI infrastructure buildout is "sensible." Hear his full comments, including on how AI is like a 5-layer cake, in the video above. Watch the full conversation with Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-ai-143500353.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Wall Street Analysts Think Vertiv (VRT) Is a Good Investment: Is It?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-analysts-think-vertiv-143004094.html</link><description>Based on the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), Vertiv (VRT) should be added to one's portfolio. Wall Street analysts' overly optimistic recommendations cast doubt on the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric. So, is the stock worth buying?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-analysts-think-vertiv-143004094.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Nvidia (NVDA) a Buy as Wall Street Analysts Look Optimistic?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-buy-wall-street-143003586.html</link><description>According to the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), one should invest in Nvidia (NVDA). It is debatable whether this highly sought-after metric is effective because Wall Street analysts' recommendations tend to be overly optimistic. Would it be worth investing in the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-buy-wall-street-143003586.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Here’s why HSBC remains bullish on global stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-hsbc-remains-bullish-global-142621932.html</link><description>Investing.com -- HSBC is staying firmly positive on global equities, arguing that rising geopolitical tensions and fresh U.S. tariffs do not alter the underlying outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-hsbc-remains-bullish-global-142621932.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] How China’s export controls, 90% ownership of metal refining threatens the AI industry: Blockspace Pod</title><link>https://blockspace.media/insight/how-chinas-export-controls-90-ownership-of-metal-refining-threatens-the-ai-industry-blockspace-pod/</link><description>With China controlling nearly 90% of critical mineral refining, Western nations face a potential supply chain guillotine that could decapitate AI and energy sectors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blockspace.media/insight/how-chinas-export-controls-90-ownership-of-metal-refining-threatens-the-ai-industry-blockspace-pod/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Sandisk the Smartest Investment You Can Make Today?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-sandisk-the-smartest-investment-you-can-make-to/</link><description>Management aims to capitalize on growth in the data center market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-sandisk-the-smartest-investment-you-can-make-to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Is Most-Watched Stock Caterpillar Inc. (CAT) Worth Betting on Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-caterpillar-inc-140005060.html</link><description>Zacks.com users have recently been watching Caterpillar (CAT) quite a bit. Thus, it is worth knowing the facts that could determine the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-caterpillar-inc-140005060.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The NYSE’s big tokenization plan is vaporware dressed up as innovation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nyse-big-tokenization-plan-vaporware-140000082.html</link><description>A Columbia business professor says the stock exchange's ambitious blockchain plan lacks details and is designed to uphold the status quo.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nyse-big-tokenization-plan-vaporware-140000082.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI robotics a "key opportunity" for Europe, says Nvidia’s Huang</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-robotics-key-opportunity-europe-135911727.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang described AI robotics as a "once-in-a-generation" opportunity for Europe during his Wednesday address at the World Economic Forum in Davos on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-robotics-key-opportunity-europe-135911727.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Q4 Earnings Loom: Buy, Sell or Hold the Stock Ahead of Results?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-q4-earnings-loom-buy-135500274.html</link><description>IBM gears up for Q4 earnings with AI and cloud momentum, but premium valuation and stiff competition weigh on the outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-q4-earnings-loom-buy-135500274.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] 4 Dividend ETFs Perfect For Retirees On Social Security</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-dividend-etfs-perfect-for-retirees-on-social-security/</link><description>When you are living on Social Security, it goes without saying that every dollar matters, and finding a way to supplement income can go a long way to not just covering basic expenses, but also helping out when emergency medical expenses happen. This is where dividend income becomes a central part of any investment portfolio, ... 4 Dividend ETFs Perfect For Retirees On Social Security</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-dividend-etfs-perfect-for-retirees-on-social-security/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Drops Ahead Of Trump Speech; Netflix Dives On Earnings (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-speech-netflix-stock-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Wednesday ahead of Trump's Davos speech. Netflix stock plunged on earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-speech-netflix-stock-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Alibaba, Applied Digital, ARM Holdings, FedEx, Flutter Entertainment, Ulta Beauty, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading lower again after a dreadful risk-off day across Wall Street, where all major indices finished the day solidly lower. The combination of President Trump’s pursuit of Greenland, multiple geopolitical hotspots, both foreign and domestic, and a market that remains very overbought led to the biggest selling day we ... Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Alibaba, Applied Digital, ARM Holdings, FedEx, Flutter Entertainment, Ult</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML) Losing Its Appeal After Strong Share Price Momentum?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-enxtam-asml-losing-131140478.html</link><description>With ASML Holding trading at around €1,140, this article examines what that price could mean for value-minded investors and whether it still represents a sensible entry or more of a stretch. The stock has recently shown strong momentum, with returns of 3.4% over 7 days, 26.4% over 30 days, 15.6% year to date, 57.2% over 1 year, 90.4% over 3 years and 160.1% over 5 years. Recent news coverage has centered on ASML Holding's role as a key supplier of advanced semiconductor manufacturing...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-enxtam-asml-losing-131140478.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wall Street's Wild Week</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/wall-streets-wild-week/</link><description>The biggest news was the U.S. government potentially spending $1.5 trillion on defense. Of course, there are strings attached, which investors don't like, but this could be an opportunity long-term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/wall-streets-wild-week/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Says AI Needs More Investment in Defiance of Bubble Fears</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-needs-more-investment-in-defiance-of-bubble-fears-9dabba63?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Speaking at Davos, Jensen Huang said AI’s application—how the technology is used in a specific industry—is the most critical element, and where economic benefits lie.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-needs-more-investment-in-defiance-of-bubble-fears-9dabba63?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>