<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:30:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:30:07 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[GOOG] Google, Shopify Lead Big 2025 Winners Near New Buy Points</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/google-shopify-buy-points/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>This week offered up an array of stocks to buy from across several different industries. These five stocks all showed promising action in their own right. They include major tech names like Alphabet and Shopify, retail stalwart TJX Cos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/google-shopify-buy-points/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Optimism Prevails for Zillow Group (ZG) Despite Fears of Third-Party Real Estate Advertisements</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/optimism-prevails-zillow-group-zg-124929715.html</link><description>Zillow Group (NASDAQ:ZG) is one of the best communication services stocks according to Hedge Funds. RBC Capital analyst Brad Erickson reiterated his bullish call on Zillow Group (NASDAQ:ZG). The analyst assigned a Buy rating on December 15, with a $95.00 price target. As per Erickson’s forecasts, investors should expect an upside of almost 41%. Erickson’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/optimism-prevails-zillow-group-zg-124929715.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] CoreWeave (CRWV) Emerges as an AI Infrastructure Stock to Watch After Truist Initiation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-emerges-ai-infrastructure-124539079.html</link><description>CoreWeave, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is one of the AI Stocks Gaining Attention on Wall Street. On January 6, Truist Securities analyst Arvind Ramnani initiated coverage on the stock with a Hold rating and an $84 price target. Despite the cloud service provider’s revenue gains and high-end clients, the firm believes that CRWV suffers from lofty leverage […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-emerges-ai-infrastructure-124539079.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Vs. Nvidia At CES 2026: Two Paths Into The $10 Trillion AI Era</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-nvidia-ces-2026-123108149.html</link><description>CES 2026 put a spotlight on how fractured the AI opportunity really is. On the same stage, Intel Corp (NASDAQ:INTC) and NVIDIA Corp (NASDAQ:NVDA) pitched radically different visions of how they plan to tap what investors broadly frame as a $10 trillion AI era. One focused on fixing what it lost. The other focused on expanding what it already owns. Intel's Pitch: AI Starts On Your Laptop Intel's CES narrative was all about execution. Panther Lake, part of the Core Ultra Series 3 lineup, marked th</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-nvidia-ces-2026-123108149.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Brad Gerstner Bets On This Stock To Benefit From Nvidia's Rubin Platform: 'A Really Interesting Opportunity'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brad-gerstner-bets-stock-benefit-120111790.html</link><description>Hedge funder Brad Gerstner, who is the CEO of Altimeter Capital, believes it is still the early innings of a super cycle for software and cloud companies benefiting from the growth of AI and data center spending. In a recent interview, he shared one of the beaten-down stocks that he's buying. Brad Gerstner's Cloud Pick In a recent appearance on CNBC's Halftime Report, Gerstner highlighted several stocks owned by Altimeter Capital, including NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA). While Nvidia is a top</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brad-gerstner-bets-stock-benefit-120111790.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: These 2 AI Stocks Will Be Worth More Than Palantir by the End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/prediction-these-2-ai-stocks-will-be-worth-more-th/</link><description>This is one of the easiest predictions ever.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/prediction-these-2-ai-stocks-will-be-worth-more-th/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Johnson Controls (JCI) Quietly Rewriting Its Core Story Around AI-Era Cooling and Smart Buildings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/johnson-controls-jci-quietly-rewriting-110852889.html</link><description>In recent days, Johnson Controls International has faced pressure after Nvidia’s CEO said future AI chips could sharply reduce traditional data-center cooling needs, while the company committed up to US$60.00 million over five years to expand its Singapore Innovation Centre for next-generation thermal management technologies. At the same time, Johnson Controls is highlighting growth initiatives such as AI-enabled retail loss-prevention tools and an expanded smart-building focus, underscoring...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/johnson-controls-jci-quietly-rewriting-110852889.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] The Smartest Growth Stock to Buy With $1,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor is a great choice for playing the AI race in a neutral way.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investing.com’s stocks of the week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-com-stocks-week-093005040.html</link><description>Investing.com – With the first week of full trading in 2026 in the bag, there has been much to assess, with various big-name stocks making strong moves.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-com-stocks-week-093005040.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva plc's (LON:AV.) Has Been On A Rise But Financial Prospects Look Weak: Is The Stock Overpriced?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-plcs-lon-av-rise-092601062.html</link><description>Aviva's (LON:AV.) stock is up by a considerable 5.1% over the past month. However, we decided to pay close attention to...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-plcs-lon-av-rise-092601062.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should You Be Worried About an AI Bubble in 2026? Here's What the Experts Have to Say.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/should-you-be-worried-about-an-ai-bubble-in-2026-h/</link><description>If more AI volatility is coming, here's how experts suggest you prepare.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/should-you-be-worried-about-an-ai-bubble-in-2026-h/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Says Rubin Architecture Is Now in Full Production. Here's Why That Matters.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-rubin-architecture-is/</link><description>These next-generation chips are available well ahead of expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-rubin-architecture-is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BofA Maintains Buy on Nvidia (NVDA) Following CES AI Updates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-maintains-buy-nvidia-nvda-082143740.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 6, Bank of America reiterated the stock as “Buy,” noting that the AI chipmaker is still a top AI pick following the company’s presentation at the Consumer Electronics Show on Monday. Analysts highlighted how CEO Jensen Huang highlighted robust demand […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-maintains-buy-nvidia-nvda-082143740.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Evercore Expects Tesla (TSLA) Shares to Trade Sideways in the Near Term</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-evercore-expects-tesla-tsla-081852605.html</link><description>Tesla, Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 6, Evercore ISI reiterated the stock as “In Line”. The firm believes that Tesla will likely “see-saw” for the foreseeable future. “For TSLA, who doesn’t guide, the stock is likely a short-term seesaw between lackluster legacy (~$100 of value; ~40c EPS […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-evercore-expects-tesla-tsla-081852605.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: 2 Ways To Capitalize on AI Stocks in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/prediction-3-ways-ai-stocks-will-change-in-2026/</link><description>The AI sector is set for some changes in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/prediction-3-ways-ai-stocks-will-change-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Could Investing $10,000 in ASML Make You a Millionaire?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/could-investing-10000-in-asml-make-you-a-millionai/</link><description>The company's backstory is exciting, but stories alone don't produce revenue or profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/could-investing-10000-in-asml-make-you-a-millionai/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mark Zuckerberg's Mom Predicted It, His Sister Bet On It: The Story Behind Meta CEO's Harvard Dropout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-zuckerbergs-mom-predicted-sister-023105826.html</link><description>Mark Zuckerberg's exit from Harvard University in 2004 has become one of the most famous college dropouts in tech history, but according to the Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) CEO, it was hardly a surprise at home. Friends And Family Expected Him To Leave Harvard During a 2013 appearance at Y Combinator's Startup School, Zuckerberg reflected on his early college days and the fallout from Facemash, a website he built that allowed students to rate classmates' photos. The project briefly overwhe</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-zuckerbergs-mom-predicted-sister-023105826.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Is It Too Late To Consider Analog Devices (ADI) After A 44% One Year Rally?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-analog-devices-adi-021203357.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Analog Devices at around US$300.93 is priced for perfection or still offers value, this article will walk through what the current market price might be telling you. The stock has posted returns of 9.9% over the last week, 6.9% over the last month, 9.9% year to date and 44.0% over the past year, with longer-term returns of 87.6% over three years and 108.2% over five years. Recent coverage of Analog Devices has focused on its role as a major analog and mixed...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-analog-devices-adi-021203357.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Walmart To Join Nasdaq 100 on Jan. 20 as AstraZeneca Exits</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-join-nasdaq-100-jan-020910743.html</link><description>Walmart’s addition follows its move last year to shift its stock listing from the New York Stock Exchange to Nasdaq, the largest exchange transfer on record.  Jefferies Financial Group Inc. analysts estimated in December that Walmart’s inclusion could prompt nearly $19 billion of inflows as index-tracking funds and exchange-traded products rebalance their holdings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-join-nasdaq-100-jan-020910743.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix Stock Has A January Superpower — And The Numbers Prove It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-stock-january-superpower-numbers-013135887.html</link><description>Netflix Inc. (NASDAQ:NFLX) has developed a striking seasonal pattern that traders have come to recognize: January has historically been its strongest month of the year, and by a wide margin. Over the past two decades, Netflix shares have posted an average January gain of 14.7%, finishing the month higher in 71% of years. That performance meaningfully outpaces both the broader S&amp;amp;P 500 and most large-cap technology peers over the same period, cementing January as a recurring sweet spot for the str</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-stock-january-superpower-numbers-013135887.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google moonshot spinout SandboxAQ claims an ex-exec is attempting ‘extortion’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-moonshot-spinout-sandboxaq-claims-003759454.html</link><description>A former SandboxAQ executive filed a wrongful termination lawsuit filled with shocking allegations. The company is fighting back, hard.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-moonshot-spinout-sandboxaq-claims-003759454.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Investor Michael Burry Reveals Options Bet Against Oracle</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investor-michael-burry-reveals-options-003350357.html</link><description>Burry owns put options on Oracle shares, he said in a Substack post after markets closed on Friday.  Burry, who revealed bearish bets against AI chipmaker Nvidia Corp. and Palantir Technologies Inc. in November, also directly shorted Oracle during the last six months, he said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investor-michael-burry-reveals-options-003350357.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Assessing Analog Devices (ADI) Valuation After AI-Fueled Semiconductor Rally And CES Optimism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-analog-devices-adi-valuation-001523775.html</link><description>Analog Devices (ADI) is back on traders’ radar after a sector wide semiconductor rally, linked to artificial intelligence enthusiasm at CES and shifting expectations for a more accommodative Federal Reserve policy. See our latest analysis for Analog Devices. The recent CES driven AI buzz and hopes for easier Federal Reserve policy have coincided with strong momentum for Analog Devices, with a 7 day share price return of 9.93% and a 90 day share price return of 33.56%. The 1 year total...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-analog-devices-adi-valuation-001523775.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank earnings, CPI inflation data, Fed comments: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-cpi-inflation-data-000021240.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come next week, including earnings results reported by the Big Banks, December's Consumer Price Index (CPI) inflation data, and a slew of commentary from Federal Reserve officials. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-cpi-inflation-data-000021240.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Dow Jones Futures: It's A Broad, Strong Rally, Do Your Stocks Reflect That? JPMorgan, Goldman, Delta, Taiwan Semi Loom</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market is at highs with JPMorgan, Goldman, Taiwan Semi and Delta earnings due. Two huge conferences, inflation data and perhaps a Trump tariffs ruling also are on tap.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why a $13 Million MercadoLibre Exit Means for Investors After a 25% Run</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/09/why-a-usd13-million-mercadolibre-exit-means-for-investors-after-a-25-run/</link><description>MercadoLibre runs a top e-commerce and fintech platform in Latin America, connecting marketplace, payments, and logistics in one ecosystem.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/09/why-a-usd13-million-mercadolibre-exit-means-for-investors-after-a-25-run/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) Outpaces Stock Market Gains: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-outpaces-225006810.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) closed at $327.31, indicating a +2.67% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-outpaces-225006810.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Senator Dumps Apple, Google, Microsoft To End 2025—But Refuses To Sell This Mag 7 Underperformer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senator-dumps-apple-google-microsoft-223108948.html</link><description>When it comes to members of Congress’s trading activity, there is a strong focus on what's being bought and when stocks are sold. One senator recently disclosed the sale of three Magnificent Seven stocks sold in December, but a Mag7 stock that wasn't sold could be more telling. Senator Ditches Magnificent Seven Stocks Sen. Shelley Moore Capito (R-W.Va.) recently disclosed selling multiple stocks, including several Magnificent Seven stocks, according to the Benzinga Government Trades page. Here w</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senator-dumps-apple-google-microsoft-223108948.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Stock Market Today, Jan. 9: S&amp;P 500 Sets New High and Intel Rallies</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/09/stock-market-today-jan-9-s-and-p-500-sets-new-high-and-intel-rallies/</link><description>Positive jobs data and high-profile political backing for Intel pushed major U.S. indexes toward new highs, today, Jan. 9, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/09/stock-market-today-jan-9-s-and-p-500-sets-new-high-and-intel-rallies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Is It Too Late To Consider KLA (KLAC) After Its Strong Multi Year Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-kla-klac-strong-221012364.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether KLA's share price still offers value after a strong run, this article will walk through what the numbers say and how to think about the current price tag. With the stock at US$1,324.60 and returns of 9.0% over 7 days, 8.1% over 30 days, 3.9% year to date and 94.7% over 1 year, KLA has clearly been on many investors' radar. This is further reflected in a 225.5% return over 3 years and 360.0% over 5 years. Recent share price interest has been supported by ongoing...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-kla-klac-strong-221012364.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Stock Back In Focus After Long Slumber</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/swing-trading/eli-lilly-stock-back-after-long-slumber/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Here's how we employ swing trading strategies of selling into strength, selling into weakness and cutting a loss quickly.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/swing-trading/eli-lilly-stock-back-after-long-slumber/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:07:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CES 2026 was dominated by these 3 tech themes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ces-2026-dominated-3-tech-214500142.html</link><description>CES 2026 took place this week, where a number of tech companies announced new projects and unveiled new products, such as Nvidia's (NVDA) Alpamayo open-source model to train and improve autonomous driving programs, Qualcomm's (QCOM) Snapdragon X Plus 2 artificial intelligence (AI) chip for PCs, and more. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley outlines the top three themes from the event. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Asking for a Trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ces-2026-dominated-3-tech-214500142.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank Earnings, Inflation Data: What to Watch Next Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-09-2026/card/bank-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-next-week-0OSTVh9i8cZCv4LVvaWQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Next week will be busy as 2026 launches into full swing. Key economic data are due, including the consumer-price index for December and producer-price index for November. Meanwhile, the nation’s largest banks are scheduled to report earnings, starting with JPMorgan Chase Tuesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-09-2026/card/bank-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-next-week-0OSTVh9i8cZCv4LVvaWQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Demand For Google, Palantir Is Mere Peanuts Next To These 3 Stocks</title><link>https://www.investors.com/etfs-and-funds/mutual-funds/best-mutual-funds-buy-google-broadcom-palantir-but-place-massive-bets-here/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>While AI stocks Google, Broadcom and Palantir remain in demand, the best mutual funds shoveled massive sums into 3 stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/etfs-and-funds/mutual-funds/best-mutual-funds-buy-google-broadcom-palantir-but-place-massive-bets-here/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Is It Too Late To Consider Buying IBM (IBM) After Its Strong Five Year Run?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-buying-ibm-ibm-201101276.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether International Business Machines is still fairly priced after its long run, this article will help you size up what you are actually paying for today. The stock closed at US$302.72, with returns of 2.2% over 7 days, a 2.5% decline over 30 days, 3.8% year to date, 39.1% over 1 year, 132.0% over 3 years and 202.3% over 5 years. This performance has many investors rechecking what is baked into the price. Recent attention on International Business Machines has...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-buying-ibm-ibm-201101276.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Chip Stocks Rise in Afternoon Trading</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite index was higher ahead of Friday's closing bell, with stocks of chip makers solidly in the green. U.S.-listed shares of Dutch chipmaking equipment manufacturer ASML Holding were up 7%, while those of Broadcom, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Texas Instruments were up 4%, 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-010926/card/chip-stocks-rise-in-afternoon-trading-pFxbCYYIwM9Od7AC05jH?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Jim Cramer Reveals When You Can Buy Vertiv (VRT)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-reveals-buy-vertiv-194716720.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Vertiv Holdings Co (NYSE:VRT) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Throughout 2025, Jim Cramer had been quite optimistic about data center infrastructure company Vertiv Holdings Co (NYSE:VRT). The shares are up by 33% over the past year and analysts have started 2026 on a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-reveals-buy-vertiv-194716720.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] JPMorgan (JPM)’s Multiple is an Insult to CEO Jamie Dimon, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</link><description>We recently published 11 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer radar. Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) crossed Jim Cramer’s radar after he discussed a Barclays note for Citigroup. Barclays bumped up Citi’s share price target, and its coverage came after a similar […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-jpm-multiple-insult-ceo-194635337.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $5,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</link><description>Investing in attractively valued AI stocks could be a smart move this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/have-5000-these-3-stocks-could-be-bargain-buys-for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Stock Broke Out Following Plan To Acquire Ventyx Biosciences</title><link>https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/ibd-big-cap-20/eli-lilly-stock-breaks-out-acquire-ventyx-biosciences/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Highly rated Eli Lilly stock is this week's Big Cap 20 pick to watch as it attempts to take out a flat-base buy point.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/ibd-big-cap-20/eli-lilly-stock-breaks-out-acquire-ventyx-biosciences/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly’s Taltz-Zepbound combo scores in late-stage PsA study</title><link>https://www.clinicaltrialsarena.com/news/eli-lilly-taltz-zepbound-combination-bests-taltz-psoriatic-arthritis-phase-iiib/</link><description>These results tout the potential of the combination as the new standard of care (SoC) for PsA patients with comorbid obesity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.clinicaltrialsarena.com/news/eli-lilly-taltz-zepbound-combination-bests-taltz-psoriatic-arthritis-phase-iiib/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Aktis Oncology Jumps 27% After $318 Million Upsized IPO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aktis-oncology-jumps-27-318-182459997.html</link><description>Shares traded at $22.91 after pricing at $18, valuing the clinical-stage biotech at about $1.2 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aktis-oncology-jumps-27-318-182459997.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Mizuho Picks Nvidia, Broadcom, Lumentum as Top AI Chip Stocks for 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mizuho-picks-nvidia-broadcom-lumentum-182013539.html</link><description>Mizuho Sees AI-Focused Semiconductors Outperforming Broader Market</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mizuho-picks-nvidia-broadcom-lumentum-182013539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 No-Brainer Tech Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These are all well-established giants that still have loads of opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/3-no-brainer-tech-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC's December Dip Isn't the Real Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</link><description>Full-year growth keeps AI demand narrative intact</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmcs-december-dip-isnt-real-173237086.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] SNOW's Robust Portfolio Fuels Revenue Growth: What's the Path Ahead?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snows-robust-portfolio-fuels-revenue-173200865.html</link><description>Snowflake's expanding AI portfolio and deepened cloud partnerships are driving strong revenue growth as it pushes to stay central in enterprise AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snows-robust-portfolio-fuels-revenue-173200865.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Stock Market Rallies Broadly To Highs; Nvidia, AMD, Bloom Energy In Focus: Weekly Review</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/stock-market-rallies-highs-nvidia-amd-bloom-energy/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones, S&amp;amp;P 500 and Russell 2000 all hit highs on the stock market this week. Nvidia and AMD fell despite unveiling new AI chips at CES.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/stock-market-rallies-highs-nvidia-amd-bloom-energy/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How Barclays' Downgrade and Trimmed Analyst Expectations Could Impact BJ's Wholesale Club (BJ) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</link><description>In recent months, Barclays downgraded BJ's Wholesale Club Holdings from an equal-weight to an underweight rating, signaling a more cautious view of the company’s outlook. This shift comes as a wider group of analysts has trimmed expectations for BJ's, highlighting growing uncertainty around its longer-term positioning. Next, we'll examine how Barclays' more cautious stance could influence BJ's existing investment narrative around membership growth and digital expansion. Explore 29 top...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-downgrade-trimmed-analyst-expectations-171228093.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Betting on a Boom: 3 Healthcare ETFs for 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/betting-boom-3-healthcare-etfs-164000679.html</link><description>After a late-2025 rebound eased policy fears, healthcare ETFs like IXJ are gaining attention as investors position for a sector comeback in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/betting-boom-3-healthcare-etfs-164000679.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] How Berkshire's Service Arm Drives Its Service and Retailing Business</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshires-arm-drives-retailing-business-163700724.html</link><description>BRK.B's service arm powers nearly half of its Service and Retailing earnings, fueling growth through steady cash flows and scale.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshires-arm-drives-retailing-business-163700724.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Could Nebius Group Stock Help You Become a Millionaire?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/could-nebius-group-stock-help-you-become-a-million/</link><description>The data center specialist's stock price has more than tripled over the past year, and it appears poised to soar even higher in the long run.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/could-nebius-group-stock-help-you-become-a-million/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Why Is Lam Research (LRCX) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) jumped 8% in the morning session after Goldman Sachs raised its price target on the stock amid broad strength in the semiconductor industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-stock-163132539.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Corporation (KLAC) Shares Skyrocket, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-klac-shares-skyrocket-163050196.html</link><description>Shares of semiconductor manufacturing equipment maker KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) jumped 5.1% in the morning session after Cantor Fitzgerald raised its price target on the stock to $1,750 from $1,500.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-klac-shares-skyrocket-163050196.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Healthcare dealmakers head to San Francisco hoping for megamergers in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/healthcare-dealmakers-head-san-francisco-161902747.html</link><description>NEW YORK, Jan 9 (Reuters) - Healthcare dealmakers are heading to San Francisco this weekend betting on a new wave of mega-mergers in 2026 that could eclipse the industry’s standout years of 2019 and 2021 when such tie-ups approached half a trillion dollars, according to more than a dozen ​top bankers and lawyers. Ahead of the week-long 43rd annual J.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/healthcare-dealmakers-head-san-francisco-161902747.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple stock slides in 2026 as AI strategy lags behind competitors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</link><description>Apple (AAPL) has slid by 5% year-to-date in 2026 as its AI products seemingly struggle to compete with Alphabet's new Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL). Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma and Innovator Capital Management chief investment strategist Tim Urbanowicz weigh in on recent executive departures and other headlines may be weighing on the iPhone maker's stock. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-stock-slides-2026-ai-161000341.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here’s What UBS Thinks About Eli Lilly and Company (LLY)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ubs-thinks-eli-lilly-company-155433063.html</link><description>Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) is one of the Best Unstoppable Growth Stocks to Buy Right Now. On January 7, Michael Yee from UBS initiated coverage of Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) with a Buy rating and raised the price target from $1,080 to $1,250. The analyst noted the company’s leadership in the obesity treatment […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ubs-thinks-eli-lilly-company-155433063.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] J&amp;J Strikes Drug Pricing Deal With Trump, Gets Tariff Reprieve</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/j-j-strikes-drug-pricing-155100851.html</link><description>JNJ cuts U.S. drug prices under a Trump deal, gains a tariff reprieve, and accelerates a $55 billion push to expand domestic manufacturing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/j-j-strikes-drug-pricing-155100851.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] 4 Stocks to Boost Your Portfolio on Steady Jump in Semiconductor Sales</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-stocks-boost-portfolio-steady-155100238.html</link><description>Rising global chip sales and AI-driven demand put ADI, NVDA, MTSI and ASYS in focus as semiconductor stocks gain momentum in a strong market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-stocks-boost-portfolio-steady-155100238.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] 2 Top-Ranked AI-Powered Tech Giants to Enhance Your Portfolio Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-top-ranked-ai-powered-154000349.html</link><description>APH and ADI stand out in the AI boom, supported by the massive growth of cloud computing and data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-top-ranked-ai-powered-154000349.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] TSMC Stock Rises After Bumper Sales. What That Says About a Potential AI Bubble.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-taiwan-semi-chip-sales-ai-bubble-5dc1377f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing stock has risen strongly on the AI boom and its latest sales figures should support the rally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-taiwan-semi-chip-sales-ai-bubble-5dc1377f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</link><description>The AI trade has grown quite volatile of late, but for investors who aren’t deterred by the AI bubble concerns of others, I think there’s a great opportunity to pursue a class of stocks that stand to gain from AI but aren’t yet priced with such AI-driven catalysts in mind. Of course, as Wedbush Securities’ ... 2 Stocks That Don’t Have Enough AI Priced in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/09/2-stocks-that-dont-have-enough-ai-priced-in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</link><description>Airbnb upgraded, Zillow downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-upgraded-zillow-downgraded-wall-144754327.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Mizuho names 3 core chip stocks and 2 outperformers for 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mizuho-names-3-core-chip-143801542.html</link><description>Investing.com -- In a note to clients on Friday, Mizuho analysts highlighted a mix of core semiconductor names and key outperformers for 2026, citing strong AI-driven demand and select memory and networking opportunities.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mizuho-names-3-core-chip-143801542.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Missed the AI Rally? Jefferies Says CrowdStrike and These 3 Other Cybersecurity Stocks Could Be Next</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</link><description>Cybersecurity stocks have trailed the tech rally, but Jefferies sees 2026 as the year market leaders begin to separate from the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36968544/missed-the-ai-rally-jefferies-says-crowdstrike-and-these-3-other-cybersecurity-stocks-could-be-next</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] ADI Climbs 35.7% in a Year: Should You Buy, Sell or Hold the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adi-climbs-35-7-buy-142400956.html</link><description>Analog Devices shares surge 35.7% in a year as AI-driven demand lifts industrial and communications growth, boosts data center sales and supports strong margins.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adi-climbs-35-7-buy-142400956.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why the stock market could easily get spooked</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-the-stock-market-could-easily-get-spooked-141851722.html</link><description>Can you say priced for perfection?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-the-stock-market-could-easily-get-spooked-141851722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence Design Systems, Inc. (CDNS) is Attracting Investor Attention: Here is What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-inc-cdns-140002774.html</link><description>Cadence (CDNS) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately. So, it is worth exploring what lies ahead for the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-inc-cdns-140002774.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>