<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:00:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang gives AI warning Wall Street can’t ignore</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/economy/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-gives-ai-warning-wall-street-cant-ignore</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang didn't deliver the same old "dog and pony show" at Davos. Everyone expected another long talk about chips; instead, he flipped the script. The charismatic leader of the world's biggest chipmaker took the opportunity to touch upon electricity, construction, bond issuance, and ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/economy/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-gives-ai-warning-wall-street-cant-ignore</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 2 Cybersecurity Stocks You Can Buy and Hold for the Next Decade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/2-cybersecurity-stocks-you-can-buy-and-hold-for/</link><description>Cybersecurity is more important than ever.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/2-cybersecurity-stocks-you-can-buy-and-hold-for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Top AI Stocks to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/2-top-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</link><description>These two companies have strong AI tailwinds, but they also have other businesses that provide stability and long-term value.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/2-top-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 "Magnificent Seven" Stocks That Are Virtually Unassailable Because of This Powerful Trait</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/2-magnificent-seven-stocks-powerful-trait/</link><description>Technology is moving faster than ever, but these companies are ahead of the pack.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/2-magnificent-seven-stocks-powerful-trait/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway Once Had a Big Silver Investment. Too Bad It Was Sold.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-silver-investment-1990s-sold-buffett-6f5b0d94?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The silver foray is one of several examples of former CEO Warren Buffett making a smart call, but then selling the investment too soon.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-silver-investment-1990s-sold-buffett-6f5b0d94?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Telecom Stock Could Be a Surprising Long-Term Winner as Artificial Intelligence Adoption Accelerates</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/this-telecom-stock-could-be-a-surprising-long-term/</link><description>After years of redefining itself as a telecom equipment provider, Nokia may finally be ready for a stock price breakout.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/this-telecom-stock-could-be-a-surprising-long-term/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] The Man Who Almost Replaced Warren Buffett</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/david-sokol-berkshire-hathaway-a2f92bf2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>David Sokol was seen as the next likely CEO of Berkshire Hathaway—until a controversy arose over his personal trades.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/david-sokol-berkshire-hathaway-a2f92bf2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Will Nvidia-Backed BioHive-2 and Big Pharma Alliances Redefine Recursion Pharmaceuticals' (RXRX) Narrative</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-backed-biohive-2-big-160703316.html</link><description>Earlier in January, Recursion Pharmaceuticals updated investors at the JP Morgan Healthcare Conference on its AI-powered drug discovery platform, clinical programs, and collaborations with partners such as Sanofi, Roche, and Genentech. The company also emphasized its Nvidia-backed BioHive-2 supercomputer and cash runway through 2027, underlining its ambitions as an AI-native drug developer. Next, we will examine how this AI-driven expansion, particularly the Nvidia partnership, shapes...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-backed-biohive-2-big-160703316.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Dow Jones Futures Loom: New Trump Tariff Threat, Government Shutdown, Earnings Wave In Focus</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-100-canada-tariff-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>President Donald Trump threatened a 100% tariff on Canada. Government shutdown risks soared. Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, Apple learnings loom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-100-canada-tariff-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 'We Would Likely See A Significant Contraction,' SoFi CEO Anthony Noto Says Of Trump's 10% Cap Plan — Consumers 'Will Still Need Access To Credit'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/likely-see-significant-contraction-sofi-153121058.html</link><description>A policy meant to make borrowing cheaper could end up changing who gets access to credit at all. That is the likely outcome of a proposed 10% cap on credit card interest rates, according to SoFi Technologies (NASDAQ:SOFI) CEO Anthony Noto. In a recent post on X, Noto responded to President Donald Trump's proposal, saying the immediate effect would likely be a contraction in credit card lending rather than a drop in consumer demand for borrowing. "If this is enacted—and that's a big if," Noto wro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/likely-see-significant-contraction-sofi-153121058.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investors Hedge China, Tech Risks Amid Trump TACO Trade Drama</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-hedge-china-tech-risks-150000906.html</link><description>For volatility markets, it’s an all-too familiar quick spike and reversal: The Cboe Volatility Index jumped Tuesday, then quickly retreated to below the level from the previous Friday, with the futures curve ending the week in an almost identical shape.  Meanwhile, away from the Trump-driven headlines that moved the broader indexes and the VIX, some investors were putting on hedges against geopolitical risks that could pressure shares of Chinese companies and against the potential for disappointing tech earnings.  Last week, investors bought about 400,000 lots of March-expiring puts in the iShares China Large-Cap ETF (FXI), along with 20,000 contracts in the KraneShares CSI China Internet ETF (KWEB) and 150,000 of Xtrackers Harvest CSI China A-Shares ETF (ASHR) puts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-hedge-china-tech-risks-150000906.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Opens Door to Nvidia H200 Chips But Questions Outnumber Answers</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/25/china-opens-door-to-nvidia-h200-chips-but-questions-outnumber-answers/</link><description>China has reportedly indicated willingness to approve NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA) H200 chips for import. The timing, conditions, and competitive dynamics present a complex situation for the company’s China market strategy. The Approval That Isn’t Really an Approval Jensen Huang is currently in Shanghai. China is “poised to approve” H200 imports. Questions remain about whether this represents ... China Opens Door to Nvidia H200 Chips But Questions Outnumber Answers</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/25/china-opens-door-to-nvidia-h200-chips-but-questions-outnumber-answers/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: These 2 Stocks Will Be the Biggest Winners From $500 Billion AI Spending in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/predict-stock-winner-billion-ai-spending-nvda/</link><description>Don't overthink the AI boom. This year's AI winners are sitting in plain sight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/predict-stock-winner-billion-ai-spending-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Analog Devices, Inc. (ADI) Stands to Benefit as BofA Highlights Sector Tailwinds</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-inc-adi-stands-135155174.html</link><description>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:ADI) is included among Dividend Contenders List: Top 20 Stocks. On January 21, BofA raised its price target on Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ:ADI) to $350 from $320, while maintaining a Buy rating on the stock. The move came alongside a broader update to the bank’s diversified analog semiconductor coverage, with higher targets […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-inc-adi-stands-135155174.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I am really confused about the consumer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/i-am-really-confused-about-the-consumer-133011221.html</link><description>This is a consumer head-scratcher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/i-am-really-confused-about-the-consumer-133011221.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How Americans are using AI at work, according to a new Gallup poll</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-using-ai-according-gallup-130123520.html</link><description>American workers adopted artificial intelligence into their work lives at a remarkable pace over the past few years, according to a new poll.  In addition, majorities of those working in professional services, at colleges or universities or in K-12 education, say they use AI at least a few times a year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-using-ai-according-gallup-130123520.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Big Tech earnings, Fed meeting feature as markets end January with busiest week of Q1: What to watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-fed-meeting-feature-as-markets-end-january-with-busiest-week-of-q1-what-to-watch-125211822.html</link><description>As geopolitical tensions simmer in the background, Big Tech earnings and the January Fed meeting take center stage this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-fed-meeting-feature-as-markets-end-january-with-busiest-week-of-q1-what-to-watch-125211822.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Every Stock in This Index Group Is Up Double-Digits in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/every-stock-in-this-index-group-is-up-double-digit/</link><description>Spending on chip fabrication equipment is soaring -- and sending these stocks higher.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/every-stock-in-this-index-group-is-up-double-digit/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The AI Computing Stock That Big Money Managers Are Quietly Buying</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/ai-computing-stock-big-money-managers-buying/</link><description>As competition heats up in AI chips, these billionaires continue to bet on the leader.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/ai-computing-stock-big-money-managers-buying/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Beyond the Hype: 3 Unexpected AI Stocks Hiding in Plain Sight</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/beyond-the-hype-3-unexpected-ai-stocks-hiding-in-p/</link><description>These companies see massive AI-driven growth potential.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/beyond-the-hype-3-unexpected-ai-stocks-hiding-in-p/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Can Trump and Big Pharma Get the World to Pay More for Drugs?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/pharma/can-trump-and-big-pharma-get-the-world-to-pay-more-for-drugs-bfe5e31d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Americans pay about three times what other wealthy nations do for branded prescription drugs.  For years, policymakers have tried to fix this by cutting U.S. drug prices directly.  President Trump has pushed a different idea: make foreign countries pay more so Americans can pay less.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/health/pharma/can-trump-and-big-pharma-get-the-world-to-pay-more-for-drugs-bfe5e31d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This Will Be the Next Artificial Intelligence (AI) Chip Stock to Join Nvidia, Taiwan Semiconductor, and Broadcom in the Trillion-Dollar Club (Hint: It's Not AMD)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/prediction-this-will-be-the-next-artificial-intell/</link><description>The trillion-dollar club features three artificial intelligence (AI) chip stocks, and another could soon join the ranks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/prediction-this-will-be-the-next-artificial-intell/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] What to Expect in Markets This Week: Fed Interest Rate Decision, Earnings From Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, Apple</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-fed-interest-rate-decision-earnings-from-microsoft-meta-tesla-apple-11890747</link><description>Coming up: A Federal Reserve interest rate decision, earnings from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, Apple, and other key firms, U.S. trade deficit data, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-fed-interest-rate-decision-earnings-from-microsoft-meta-tesla-apple-11890747</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Is Nebius Group Stock Going To $0?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/is-nebius-group-stock-going-to-0/</link><description>The stock has climbed in the triple digits in a year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/is-nebius-group-stock-going-to-0/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] OpenAI Stock vs. Anthropic Stock: Which Nvidia-Backed AI Start-up Would Be the Best IPO Stock to Buy in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/openai-anthropic-nvidia-backed-best-ipo-stock-buy/</link><description>Nvidia-backed AI start-ups OpenAI and Anthropic could hold IPOs in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/openai-anthropic-nvidia-backed-best-ipo-stock-buy/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Goldman Reaffirms Preference for Nvidia (NVDA) in AI Compute Ecosystem</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-reaffirms-preference-nvidia-nvda-091353958.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the Buzzing AI Stocks Analysts are Watching. On January 20, Goldman Sachs reaffirmed its preference for Broadcom and Nvidia, highlighting that it continues to prefer both names within the compute ecosystem. The firm developed an “investment cost curve” to compare the economies of different chipmakers’ AI solutions and their […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-reaffirms-preference-nvidia-nvda-091353958.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Why Bernstein Sees Structural Upside for ASML Through 2029</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-bernstein-sees-structural-upside-090221425.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the Buzzing AI Stocks Analysts are Watching. On January 16, Bernstein SocGen Group analyst David Dai reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $1,528.00 price target. The firm is strongly positive on ASML as it sees structural demand upside for the stock into 2026–2029. On January […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-bernstein-sees-structural-upside-090221425.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Chip Stock Will Outperform Nvidia Again in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/prediction-this-ai-chip-stock-will-outperform-nvid/</link><description>This semiconductor and networking specialist is increasingly the chip of choice for artificial intelligence (AI) processing in the data center space.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/prediction-this-ai-chip-stock-will-outperform-nvid/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Bloom Energy, Lumentum, and Other Hot Stocks Set up for Earnings Beats</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/bloom-energy-lumentum-stock-earnings-price-1d6b7709?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Which companies are most likely to beat Wall Street profit forecasts?  Investors can get a big clue by looking at recent changes to a key metric: the price-to-earnings ratios.  When it comes to picking stocks, conventional wisdom holds that low price-to-earnings ratios are an advantage.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/bloom-energy-lumentum-stock-earnings-price-1d6b7709?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Why Wall Street Is Wrong About Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/why-wall-street-is-wrong-about-taiwan-semiconducto/</link><description>Wall Street expects the company to gain about 25% this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/why-wall-street-is-wrong-about-taiwan-semiconducto/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Forget Tech Stocks: The Power Stock That AI Can't Live Without</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/forget-tech-stocks-the-power-stock-that-ai-cant-li/</link><description>Planned data center build-outs are working in its favor.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/25/forget-tech-stocks-the-power-stock-that-ai-cant-li/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Does Lloyds Banking Group (LSE:LLOY) Still Offer Value After Its Strong Five-Year Rally?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-lloyds-banking-group-lse-061331166.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Lloyds Banking Group shares still offer value after the recent run, this article will walk through what the current price might be implying. The stock last closed at £1.02, with returns of a 0.4% decline over 7 days, 4.8% over 30 days, 2.4% year to date and 72.7% over the past year, as well as 126.0% over 3 years and 288.1% over 5 years. Recent headlines around Lloyds Banking Group have focused on its position as a major UK retail and commercial bank and its...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-lloyds-banking-group-lse-061331166.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Is It Too Late To Consider Caterpillar (CAT) After Its Strong Share Price Rally?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-caterpillar-cat-strong-061312359.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Caterpillar shares still offer value after a strong run, this article will walk through what the current price might be implying. The stock last closed at US$626.62, with returns of 7.5% over 30 days, 4.7% year to date and 55.8% over 1 year, while the 7 day return was a 3.1% decline. Recent news coverage has focused on Caterpillar as a bellwether for construction and infrastructure activity. This often shapes how investors think about the stock's risk and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-caterpillar-cat-strong-061312359.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Inc. (GOOGL) Strengthens Its Position in AI and Cloud Innovation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-googl-strengthens-position-044216933.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the best stocks to buy, according to billionaire Bill Ackman. On January 12, Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL)’s market capitalization broke through the $4 trillion mark after Apple announced it would use Gemini models to power its artificial intelligence and next-generation Siri. The multiyear partnership will enable Apple to leverage Gemini […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-googl-strengthens-position-044216933.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Bernstein Names AT&amp;T (T) Top Telecom Pick for 2026, Barclays Stays Neutral</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-names-t-t-top-032913072.html</link><description>AT&amp;amp;T Inc. (NYSE:T) is one of the 12 Best 5G Stocks to Invest in According to Hedge Funds. On January 15, Bernstein named AT&amp;amp;T Inc. (NYSE:T) as its top pick in the US telecom market for 2026, even as competition in the industry is expected to grow. The research firm noted that the telecom sector […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-names-t-t-top-032913072.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The 5 Most Popular Stocks on Robinhood to Begin 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/the-5-most-popular-stocks-on-robinhood-to-begin-20/</link><description>The Robinhood Investor Index details which sectors and specific stocks investors are buying to start 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/the-5-most-popular-stocks-on-robinhood-to-begin-20/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Assessing Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) Valuation After Recent Flat Returns And Mixed Growth Expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-cadence-design-systems-cdns-031249990.html</link><description>Event context and recent stock performance Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) has been drawing investor attention after a period where the stock was roughly flat over the past month but showed a negative move over the past 3 months. Against that backdrop, the shares most recently closed at US$318.32, with year to date and 1 year total returns close to flat, while the 3 year and 5 year total returns sit at higher levels. See our latest analysis for Cadence Design Systems. At the current share price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-cadence-design-systems-cdns-031249990.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 03:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Stock Has Soared More Than 70% In 6 Months. Is It Too Late to Buy Shares?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/is-it-too-late-to-buy-alphabet-stock/</link><description>Does the search giant's cloud growth (and the spending required to support it) justify buying shares today?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/is-it-too-late-to-buy-alphabet-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Most Undervalued Chip Stock to Own in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/the-most-undervalued-chip-stock-to-own-in-2026/</link><description>The memory shortage could last into 2027, but this stock is priced like it won't.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/the-most-undervalued-chip-stock-to-own-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] FactSet Research Systems (FDS) Valuation After New Multiyear Barclays Agreement</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-research-systems-fds-valuation-001813159.html</link><description>Barclays has entered a multiyear arrangement with FactSet Research Systems (FDS), using the company’s analytics, data and technology to support its long term market data strategy and services for global clients. See our latest analysis for FactSet Research Systems. The Barclays agreement comes after a tough stretch for shareholders, with a 1 year total shareholder return decline of 37.91% and a relatively flat pattern in recent share price returns. This suggests momentum has been subdued even...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-research-systems-fds-valuation-001813159.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] GameStop Plugs 'Infinite Money Glitch,' Stock Starts Printing Cash</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gamestop-plugs-infinite-money-glitch-233112645.html</link><description>GameStop Corp. (NYSE:GME) was in the spotlight this week for two reasons: a literal infinite money glitch found within its own stores and massive insider buys from CEO Ryan Cohen. Infinite Money Glitch YouTuber RJCmedia exposed a trade-in loophole involving the newly released Nintendo Switch 2 that allowed customers to essentially print store credit. The exploit was remarkably simple: a customer would purchase a new Nintendo Switch 2 for $414.99. By immediately trading the console back in alongs</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gamestop-plugs-infinite-money-glitch-233112645.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Best Stocks to Invest $1,000 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/the-best-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</link><description>Alphabet, Micron, and Costco each have something unique to offer investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/the-best-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] My Top 3 Chip Stocks for 2025 Crushed the Market. Here's Why They Can Repeat Again in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/my-top-3-chip-stocks-for-2025-crushed-the-market/</link><description>AI spending is expected to stay elevated in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/my-top-3-chip-stocks-for-2025-crushed-the-market/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Ericsson Proposes Bigger Dividends After Strong Quarter</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ericsson-proposes-bigger-dividends-strong-230152531.html</link><description>Ericsson (NASDAQ:ERIC) stock rose Friday after the Swedish telecom giant reported stronger-than-expected fourth-quarter earnings. Ericsson, which generates the bulk of its revenue from network infrastructure, software solutions, and professional services, reported EPS of 27 cents, beating the analyst consensus estimate of 23 cents. The company’s reported sales for the quarter were 69.3 billion Swedish Krona ($7.37 billion). Although this represented a 5% year-over-year (Y/Y) decline, it topped t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ericsson-proposes-bigger-dividends-strong-230152531.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cathie Wood's Message on Quantum Computing Stocks: Wait Another 20 to 40 Years</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/cathie-wood-message-quantum-computing-stock/</link><description>Cathie Wood's firm, Ark Invest, is known for being a major investor in companies with disruptive technologies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/cathie-wood-message-quantum-computing-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] 2 Under-the-Radar Vanguard ETFs to Invest $1,000 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/2-under-the-radar-vanguard-etfs-to-invest-1000-in/</link><description>These ETFs can be good supplemental pieces in a portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/2-under-the-radar-vanguard-etfs-to-invest-1000-in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 22:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Broadcom’s (AVGO) Expanding AI Deal Pipeline Redefining Its Core Investment Story?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/broadcom-avgo-expanding-ai-deal-221000098.html</link><description>In recent weeks, Broadcom has deepened its role in the AI buildout, winning large custom accelerator and networking deals with hyperscalers such as Google, Meta, OpenAI and securing new VMware-related government and cloud agreements while institutional investors like Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest bought about US$50.74 million of its shares. Together with very strong AI semiconductor demand and an order backlog that includes tens of billions of AI-related contracts, these developments reinforce...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/broadcom-avgo-expanding-ai-deal-221000098.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI teams up with humans: How work will change</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/economy/ai-teams-up-with-humans-how-work-will-change</link><description>Savior or scourge. It's all in the AI of the beholder. Many people have called artificial intelligence the biggest technological innovation of all time, with some comparing it to the likes of fire, electricity, and the internet. Microsoft (MSFT) co-founder Bill Gates said the development of AI is ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/economy/ai-teams-up-with-humans-how-work-will-change</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 3 Reasons to Buy TSMC Stock Like There's No Tomorrow</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/reasons-to-buy-tsmc-stock-like-no-tomorrow/</link><description>The semiconductor manufacturer just reported stellar fourth-quarter results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/reasons-to-buy-tsmc-stock-like-no-tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Should You Dump Eli Lilly's Shares After This Setback?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/should-you-dump-eli-lillys-shares-after-this-setba/</link><description>The company got some bad news to start 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/should-you-dump-eli-lillys-shares-after-this-setba/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Tech CEOs boast and bicker about AI at Davos</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-ceos-boast-bicker-ai-200046915.html</link><description>There were times at this week’s meeting of the World Economic Forum when Davos seemed transformed into a high-powered tech conference.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-ceos-boast-bicker-ai-200046915.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>