<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:00:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[GOOG] Tech Weekly: Apple and Google do a deal, Glasses for the Blind</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-weekly-apple-google-deal-112701603.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: From Apple and Google doing a deal to Glasses for the Blind, this is Tech Weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: Tech Weekly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple and Google-owner Alphabet have done a deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The iPhone maker will use Google's Gemini models for its revamped Siri coming later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It deepens their alliance in the AI era and boosts Alphabet's position in the race against OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google's technology already drives much of Samsung's Galaxy AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the Siri deal unlocks a massive market with Apple's base of more than two billion active devices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there's no sign Apple's dominance of global smartphones has let up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm led the sector with a 20% share of the market last year - just ahead of Samsung.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading analyst Counterpoint Research said the firm saw solid demand in emerging and mid-sized markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And enjoyed strong sales of the iPhone 17 series.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest innovations in the tech sector were on show at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;.lumen showed off its so-called Glasses for the Blind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The device goes on a person's head and acts in a similar way to a guide dog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm said the glasses use haptics to help people with blindness go about daily life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And employs AI to distinguish between safe and unsafe surfaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new robotaxi design was unveiled in Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's the product of a partnership between EV-maker Lucid, Uber and autonomous vehicle tech firm Nuro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The car uses Nvidia's AI driving hardware, and can drive itself in certain conditions without a human using Nuro's autonomous tech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Salguero is Nuro's Head of Communications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We use an AI autonomy foundation model that basically learns as it goes along. So as we're driving, as we are testing, both on road and in simulations, it gets better and better at driving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group plans to launch robotaxi services in the San Francisco Bay Area later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And AI wearables were on show in Vegas, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the wearable tech included rings, jewelry, exoskeletons and glasses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI jewlery company Nirva showed products it claims can track your mood and record a journal of your day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While tech firm ible demonstrated noise-cancelling headphones which they said can detect pollution and purify the air in front of your face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tech-weekly-apple-google-deal-112701603.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Wall Street Could Be Underestimating in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-wall-street-nvda/</link><description>The market seems to have left this top artificial intelligence (AI) stock for dead. Don't be fooled.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-wall-street-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Stock Rises on $1 Billion AI Bet With Nvidia</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-stock-rises-1-112710258.html</link><description>Nvidia Pushes Deeper Into Health Care With Major Eli Lilly Partnership</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-stock-rises-1-112710258.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mike Novogratz Tells Scaramucci Crypto Treasuries Will Trade Below NAV Without Real Strategy: 'Not Going To Get Shareholder Value Just By...'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-novogratz-tells-scaramucci-crypto-110111715.html</link><description>Galaxy Digital Inc. (NASDAQ: GLXY) CEO Mike Novogratz expressed concern Wednesday about the current state of cryptocurrency treasury companies, emphasizing the importance of creating shareholder value beyond just owning the underlying asset. Novogratz Questions Current Landscape Speaking to SkyBridge Capital...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-novogratz-tells-scaramucci-crypto-110111715.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The trillion-dollar IPOs investors are watching for in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trillion-dollar-ipos-investors-watching-110019391.html</link><description>Listen and subscribe to Stocks In Translation on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you find your favorite podcast.Investors are buzzing over potential $1 trillion tech IPOs in 2026, but which giants will come out on top? In this episode of Stocks in Translation, The Futurum Group Daniel Newman joins host Jared Blikre and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma to discuss the potential $1 trillion IPOs of OpenAI and SpaceX. Newman breaks down investor hype, competitive moats, and market risks, while also exploring Google (GOOG) Gemini’s AI gains, Apple's (AAPL) innovation gap, and how Amazon (AMZN) and Meta (META) are positioned to dominate AI in 2026.Check out the full episode here. Twice a week, Stocks In Translation cuts through the market mayhem, noisy numbers and hyperbole to give you the information you need to make the right trade for your portfolio. You can find more episodes here, or watch on your favorite streaming service. This post was written by Lauren Pokedoff</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trillion-dollar-ipos-investors-watching-110019391.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] From Nvidia to Salesforce: Where money is made in Enterprise AI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-salesforce-where-money-made-110010284.html</link><description>Listen and subscribe to Stocks In Translation on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you find your favorite podcast. Forget chatbots, here's where AI is really going to make strides in 2026. In this episode of Stocks in Translation, The Futurum Group Daniel Newman joins host Jared Blikre and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma to break down where enterprise AI is really making money. Newman highlights top beneficiaries like Nvidia (NVDA), Salesforce (CRM), ServiceNow (NOW), Workday (WDAY), and IBM (IBM), and explains how AI is reshaping healthcare, defense, and SaaS, plus what investors should watch in 2026.Twice a week, Stocks In Translation cuts through the market mayhem, noisy numbers and hyperbole to give you the information you need to make the right trade for your portfolio. You can find more episodes here, or watch on your favorite streaming service. This post was written by Lauren Pokedoff</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-salesforce-where-money-made-110010284.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: JPMorgan, Delta, Alphabet, AMD, Intel, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-4b90f18a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Alphabet shares rise after the parent company of Google becomes the fourth U.S. company to top a $4 trillion valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-4b90f18a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] AbbVie Strikes a $100 Billion Deal With Trump. How the Drugmaker Will Dodge Tariffs.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/abbvie-stock-trump-tariffs-deal-4f08ec87?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AbbVie  has agreed to cut some drug prices and invest $100 billion in the U.S. in exchange for an exemption from some tariffs.  The pharma company said in a statement late Monday that it had struck a deal with the Trump administration to lower Medicaid prices and pour the money into U.S. research and development.  AbbVie will also expand its direct-to-patient offerings of certain drugs on the government portal TrumpRx.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/abbvie-stock-trump-tariffs-deal-4f08ec87?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Which Search Giant Is Poised for Explosive Growth in the Next 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/which-search-giant-is-poised-for-explosive-growth/</link><description>The tech company's powerful mix of a strong core search and advertising business, alongside other fast-growing businesses, sets it up for more strong growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/which-search-giant-is-poised-for-explosive-growth/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bull of the Day: Sandisk (SNDK)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-sandisk-sndk-102000551.html</link><description>Shares are up 680% since August because the NAND memory shortage nightmare is an SSD dream come true</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-sandisk-sndk-102000551.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bitwise CIO Blasts “Ridiculous” Bitcoin 401(k) Fears: “Less Volatile Than Nvidia”</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitwise-bitcoin-401k-ridiculous-nvidia-volatility/</link><description>Bitwise Chief Investment Officer Matt Hougan has pushed back sharply against renewed concerns that Bitcoin is too volatile to be considered for retirement accounts. He called efforts to block the asset from 401(k) plans “ridiculous” and out of step with how risk is treated elsewhere in financial markets.Hougan’s comments came ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cryptonews.com/news/bitwise-bitcoin-401k-ridiculous-nvidia-volatility/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trending tickers: Alphabet, UBS, Novo Nordisk, Persimmon and Whitbread</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-ubs-novo-nordisk-persimmon-whitbread-trending-tickers-100452578.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Tuesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-ubs-novo-nordisk-persimmon-whitbread-trending-tickers-100452578.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stocks to Watch Tuesday: JPMorgan, TSMC, Orsted</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-tuesday-jpmorgan-tsmc-orsted-IpQZNnCjVxXQtZhAIWJg?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>🔎 JPMorgan Chase (JPM) and Bank of New York Mellon (BK): The two Wall Street bastions will kick off bank earnings season early Tuesday. Delta Air Lines (DAL) is also due to report. ↗️ Orsted (DK:ORSTED): A U.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-tuesday-jpmorgan-tsmc-orsted-IpQZNnCjVxXQtZhAIWJg?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You'd Invested Just $1,000 in Nvidia 10 Years Ago, You'd Be Sitting on This Fortune Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/if-youd-invested-just-1000-in-nvidia-10-years-ago/</link><description>The chipmaker is one of the biggest success stories of the last decade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/if-youd-invested-just-1000-in-nvidia-10-years-ago/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google to develop, manufacture high-end smartphones in Vietnam, Nikkei Asia says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-develop-manufacture-smartphones-vietnam-091208535.html</link><description>Google will start developing and manufacturing high-end smartphones ​in Vietnam this year, Nikkei ‌Asia reported on Tuesday, citing sources familiar with ‌the matter.  Google already has a large network of suppliers in Vietnam that assemble its products, including Pixel smartphones.  Google ⁠will begin new ‌product introductions (NPI) for its Pixel, Pixel Pro, and Pixel Fold ‍phones in Vietnam, with development of the lower-end Pixel A series remaining in ​China for now, the report said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-develop-manufacture-smartphones-vietnam-091208535.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Move Over, AI Stocks: Wall Street Is Likely to Welcome a New Member to the Trillion-Dollar Club in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/move-over-ai-stocks-wall-st-trillion-dollar-club/</link><description>The industry leader with the clearest path to become the next trillion-dollar company is one of Wall Street's most prolific stock-split stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/move-over-ai-stocks-wall-st-trillion-dollar-club/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Is Barclays’ Renewed Overweight on DigitalOcean (DOCN) Reframing Its Role in AI Infrastructure?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-renewed-overweight-digitalocean-docn-091003704.html</link><description>Recently, Barclays reaffirmed its "Overweight" rating on cloud platform provider DigitalOcean Holdings and named the company one of its preferred software stocks for 2026, citing confidence in its market potential and sector backdrop. This endorsement highlights how DigitalOcean is being positioned by a major investment bank within the broader software and cloud landscape, particularly as investors reassess opportunities in smaller, AI-focused infrastructure providers. We’ll now examine how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-renewed-overweight-digitalocean-docn-091003704.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Fed Speakers, Bank Earnings, Inflation Data: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/fed-speakers-bank-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-this-week-KSH5EXvXkM9j9uQekJ73?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Key economic data are due this week, including two inflation readings. The U.S.'s largest banks are also scheduled to report earnings, starting with JPMorgan Chase. Later this week, results from Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing, known as TSMC, will pulse-check the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/fed-speakers-bank-earnings-inflation-data-what-to-watch-this-week-KSH5EXvXkM9j9uQekJ73?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang "Loves" This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Company. The Stock Could Soar 77% in 2026, According to 1 Wall Street Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-loves-this-artificial-inte/</link><description>This AI and robotics company is growing like wildfire, but still has a lot to prove.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-loves-this-artificial-inte/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Rallied 39% in 2025. This Year, It Could Go Much Higher</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/nvidia-stock-rallied-39-in-2025-this-year-it-could/</link><description>Despite challenges last year, Nvidia rewarded patient shareholders. It could be just the beginning.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/nvidia-stock-rallied-39-in-2025-this-year-it-could/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC to Expand $165 Billion U.S. Investment: Report. It’s Part of a Trump Tariffs Deal.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-price-trump-tariffs-chips-4cce647f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing could build as many as a dozen plants in Arizona, according to The Wall Street Journal.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-price-trump-tariffs-chips-4cce647f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Heard on the Street Monday Recap: Central Bank Shot</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-monday-recap-central-bank-shot-5eV1swOTbuxx96X1244m?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks shrug off latest Powell threat. U.S. indexes posted mild gains despite pressure following the news that the Trump administration has launched a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-monday-recap-central-bank-shot-5eV1swOTbuxx96X1244m?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Investors back energy providers over big tech for 2026 AI bets, says BlackRock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-back-energy-providers-over-080245347.html</link><description>BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, still believes in the investment case ​for artificial intelligence in the year ahead but ‌will be focusing on broader opportunities, it said on Tuesday.  Investors seeking ‌to play the AI theme into 2026 favour energy and infrastructure providers over Wall Street big tech, BlackRock said in its Investment Directions report, citing a recent investor ⁠survey it conducted.  AI and ‌big tech dominated markets and world equity returns in 2025, but as the multitrillion-dollar ‍race between the likes of Microsoft, Meta and Alphabet to build new data centres generates worries about uncertain returns on capital ​and higher borrowing, investors were looking for new ‌ideas, the BlackRock survey showed.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-back-energy-providers-over-080245347.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Earnings Season Is Still All About AI. That Won’t Last.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-ai-earnings-season-5cd39c11?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A wider range of companies are likely to contribute to 2026’s market gains as the economy holds steady and investors exit riskier artificial intelligence bets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-ai-earnings-season-5cd39c11?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Is HSBC Holdings (LSE:HSBA) Starting To Look Stretched After A 59% One Year Rally?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-holdings-lse-hsba-starting-070607813.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether HSBC Holdings is still good value after its strong run, this article walks through what the current share price might be telling you about the stock. The shares recently closed at £12.02, with a 7 day return of a 0.4% decline, a 30 day return of 8.1%, a year to date return of 0.9% and a 1 year return of 58.9%, while the 3 year return is very large and the 5 year return is roughly 3x. Recent coverage has focused on HSBC Holdings as a large global bank listed in...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-holdings-lse-hsba-starting-070607813.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Has Shopping in Its Sights. Amazon Is Pushing Back.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-shopping-chatgpt-google-amazon-comet-0b6d61f3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AI-based shopping remains a haphazard experience for now. But OpenAI, Google, and Microsoft are working hard to disrupt shopping once again.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-shopping-chatgpt-google-amazon-comet-0b6d61f3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] It's Official: Apple and Alphabet Are Teaming Up for an AI-Powered Siri. Why This Is a Win for Both Companies.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/its-official-apple-and-alphabet-are-teaming-up-for/</link><description>Apple gets a faster path to a smarter Siri, while Alphabet gets Gemini in front of one of the biggest consumer audiences in the world.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/its-official-apple-and-alphabet-are-teaming-up-for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix to Build $13 Billion Chip Packaging Plant in South Korea</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/sk-hynix-to-build-13-billion-chip-packaging-plant-in-south-korea-6583e853?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The supplier of high-bandwidth-memory products to Nvidia plans to build the chip packaging plant in Cheongju, south of Seoul amid surging demand for artificial-intelligence chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/sk-hynix-to-build-13-billion-chip-packaging-plant-in-south-korea-6583e853?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Want to Invest in AI Stocks in 2026? Here's Why This Popular Tech ETF Might Not Be a Good Choice</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/want-to-invest-in-ai-stocks-in-2026-heres-why-this/</link><description>Choosing this ETF could leave investors missing key companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/want-to-invest-in-ai-stocks-in-2026-heres-why-this/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Assessing HSBC (LSE:HSBA) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Performance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-hsbc-lse-hsba-valuation-031542800.html</link><description>How HSBC Holdings (LSE:HSBA) Has Been Performing HSBC Holdings (LSE:HSBA) has drawn attention after a period in which its share price total return sits at about 0.7% over the past day, 8.1% over the past month, and 20.7% over the past 3 months. See our latest analysis for HSBC Holdings. Looking beyond the recent move, HSBC Holdings’ share price return has been positive over the past quarter, while its 1 year and 5 year total shareholder returns of 58.9% and about 3x highlight strong...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-hsbc-lse-hsba-valuation-031542800.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] How Investors May Respond To Cisco (CSCO) Supreme Court Appeal On Alleged Human Rights Abuses</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-cisco-csco-031247728.html</link><description>Cisco Systems is facing renewed attention after asking the U.S. Supreme Court to dismiss a lawsuit alleging its technology enabled human rights abuses against Falun Gong practitioners in China under the Alien Tort Statute and Torture Victim Protection Act. At the same time, media focus on Cisco’s record operational cycle and legal exposure is prompting investors to reassess how flat sales, pressured free cash flow margins and potential reputational risks fit with the company’s longer-term...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-cisco-csco-031247728.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 Unstoppable Stocks to Buy With $5,000 for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/5-unstoppable-stocks-to-buy-with-5000-for-2026/</link><description>These five are great starting points for nearly surefire bets for 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/5-unstoppable-stocks-to-buy-with-5000-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia says no upfront payment needed for its H200 chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-says-no-upfront-payment-021209575.html</link><description>Nvidia does not require upfront payment for H200 chips, a ​spokesperson for the U.S. chipmaker said in ‌a statement to Reuters on Tuesday.  The company said it "would ‌never require customers to pay for products they do not receive", in a response to a Reuters story on January 8 about the company ⁠having imposed unusually ‌stringent terms requiring full upfront payment from Chinese customers seeking its artificial intelligence ‍chips.  One source told Reuters that Nvidia's standard terms for Chinese clients have previously included advance payment requirements, ​but they were sometimes allowed to place ‌a deposit rather than make a full payment upfront.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-says-no-upfront-payment-021209575.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix to Build $13 Billion AI Memory Chip Packaging Plant</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-plans-invest-13-002425361.html</link><description>SK Hynix is the world’s leading supplier of high-bandwidth memory for Nvidia Corp.’s AI accelerators.  Demand for HBM and other advanced memory chips has surged faster than anticipated as data center buildouts accelerate.  Memory — once treated as a commoditized component — has become a bottleneck that directly limits how quickly data centers can bring new AI accelerators online.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-plans-invest-13-002425361.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investors Are Panicking, But Is This Stock Actually a Screaming Buy?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/investors-are-panicking-but-is-this-stock-actually/</link><description>CoreWeave is risky but it trades at a surprisingly low valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/investors-are-panicking-but-is-this-stock-actually/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix to invest nearly $13 billion in chip packaging plant in South Korea</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-invest-nearly-13-005719060.html</link><description>South Korea's SK Hynix said on Tuesday it has ​decided to invest 19 trillion won ($12.90 billion) ‌to build an advanced chip packaging plant in South ‌Korea to meet rising memory chip demand related to artificial intelligence. The chipmaker said in a statement that the construction of the new factory ⁠will begin in ‌April, with completion targeted by the end of next year. SK Hynix said ‍accelerating global competition in AI is driving a sharp rise in demand for AI-focused memory, underscoring ​the need to respond proactively to growing ‌demand for high-bandwidth memory (HBM) chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-invest-nearly-13-005719060.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump Touts New Microsoft Data-Center Pledges After Local Backlash</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/trump-touts-new-microsoft-data-center-pledges-after-local-backlash-HiGA2DQvr3G9vty96P3X?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Microsoft has promised to pay higher utility bills for all of its U.S. data centers powering artificial-intelligence models, President Trump said Monday, accelerating plans by the tech industry and administration to respond to local fears that AI is pushing up electricity prices.  The software giant “will make major changes beginning this week to ensure that Americans don’t ‘pick up the tab’ for their power consumption,” Trump said on Truth Social.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/trump-touts-new-microsoft-data-center-pledges-after-local-backlash-HiGA2DQvr3G9vty96P3X?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Serve Robotics (SERV) Is Up 13.1% After NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang’s “Physical AI” Endorsement</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-serve-robotics-serv-13-001819622.html</link><description>At CES 2026, NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang publicly endorsed Serve Robotics as a leading example of “Physical AI,” highlighting its autonomous sidewalk delivery robots and partnerships with brands such as Uber Eats and Shake Shack. This high-profile backing places Serve Robotics at the center of discussions about how AI is moving into real-world, revenue-generating applications in last-mile delivery. We’ll now examine how this Physical AI spotlight from NVIDIA’s CEO shapes Serve Robotics’...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-serve-robotics-serv-13-001819622.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Did Toast’s New AI-Powered Retail Upgrades Just Shift Toast's (TOST) Investment Narrative?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-toast-ai-powered-retail-001740286.html</link><description>In early January 2026, Toast announced new retail-focused upgrades to its Toast IQ AI assistant and core platform, including real-time inventory actions, AI invoice scanning, cloud-enabled scales and labeling integrations, and an AI-supported digital advertising tool for Google and Meta. By embedding AI more deeply into catalog management, pricing, and marketing workflows, Toast is positioning its platform as an all-in-one operating system for complex retail operations rather than just a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-toast-ai-powered-retail-001740286.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Pfizer CEO plans for soaring consumer market for obesity drugs akin to Viagra</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pfizer-ceo-plans-soaring-consumer-234253473.html</link><description>SAN FRANCISCO, Jan 12 (Reuters) - Pfizer is preparing for a consumer market for obesity drugs on par with the booming business it saw after it launched erectile dysfunction drug ​Viagra in 1998, CEO Albert Bourla said on Monday. Bourla said that even when the drugmaker was ‌negotiating its purchase of weight-loss drugmaker Metsera, initially announced in September 2025, Pfizer did not expect the cash-pay market for obesity drugs ‌currently dominated by Eli Lilly and Co and Novo Nordisk to get s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pfizer-ceo-plans-soaring-consumer-234253473.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Heard on the Street Recap: Central Bank Shot</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-central-bank-shot-Q2K8LQAJeOeOivkpZH4U?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>What Happened in Markets Today Stocks shrug off latest Powell threat. Major U.S. stock indexes posted some mild gains Monday despite earlier pressure following news that the Trump administration has launched a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-central-bank-shot-Q2K8LQAJeOeOivkpZH4U?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Stock Market Today, Jan. 12: Markets Dip on DOJ Powell Probe, Rebound With Alphabet</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/12/stock-market-today-jan-12-markets-open-down-after-doj-opens-investigation-on-powell-but-rebounds-with-alphabet/</link><description>On Jan. 12, 2026, Alphabet’s $4 trillion milestone helped the market recover from volatility surrounding the DOJ's investigation into Fed chair Powell, and a potential interest rate "cap" for credit cards.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/12/stock-market-today-jan-12-markets-open-down-after-doj-opens-investigation-on-powell-but-rebounds-with-alphabet/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA (KLAC) Exceeds Market Returns: Some Facts to Consider</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-exceeds-market-returns-230006746.html</link><description>KLA (KLAC) closed at $1 in the latest trading session, marking a +2.01% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-exceeds-market-returns-230006746.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple Investors Are Still Waiting for an AI Siri. A New Deal With Google Could Help It Deliver</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/apple-investors-are-still-waiting-for-an-ai-siri-a-new-deal-with-google-could-help-it-deliver-11883948</link><description>Apple plans to use Google's Gemini to power future Apple Intelligence features, including an AI-enhanced Siri coming later this year, the companies said Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/apple-investors-are-still-waiting-for-an-ai-siri-a-new-deal-with-google-could-help-it-deliver-11883948</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Forget LLMs: Buy these 3 AI "Pick and Shovel" Plays Instead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/forget-llms-buy-3-ai-225000884.html</link><description>During the proverbial (and actual) gold rush, the most consistent fortunes are made by those selling the "picks and shovels." While the LLM wars between tech giants continue to dominate the headlines, the real staying power and predictability lie in the AI infrastructure stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/forget-llms-buy-3-ai-225000884.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM (IBM) Exceeds Market Returns: Some Facts to Consider</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-exceeds-market-returns-224507465.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw IBM (IBM) settling at $312.18, representing a +2.62% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-exceeds-market-returns-224507465.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar (CAT) Laps the Stock Market: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-cat-laps-stock-market-224506620.html</link><description>In the closing of the recent trading day, Caterpillar (CAT) stood at $629.77, denoting a +1.97% move from the preceding trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-cat-laps-stock-market-224506620.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Laps the Stock Market: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-laps-stock-224503924.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (LLY) concluded the recent trading session at $1, signifying a +1.64% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-laps-stock-224503924.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] 3 retail trends to watch in 2026, according to NRF 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/3-retail-trends-watch-2026-224500459.html</link><description>The National Retail Federation (NRF) is hosting its Retail's Big Show conference in New York City this week. Attending the event, Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma sat down with KPMG US consumer &amp;amp; retail sector leader Duleep Rodrigo and PwC partner and US consumer markets industry leader Alison Furman to hear how retailers will be employing AI applications and how companies are expected to adjust to the adoption of GLP-1 weight-loss drugs and more active lifestyles by consumers. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Asking for a Trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/3-retail-trends-watch-2026-224500459.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Google's co-founders and Peter Thiel are exiting California</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/why-googles-co-founders-peter-223000442.html</link><description>Big Tech elites, like Alphabet's (GOOG, GOOGL) Google co-founders Sergey Brin and Larry Page and Palantir's (PLTR) Peter Thiel, are hauling out of California to escape the state's billionaire tax act, which entails a one-time 5% tax on their wealth. If approved, the tax could affect individuals who were California residents at the year's start. Tusk Venture Partners founder and CEO Bradley Tusk outlines what the shift out of California signals about taxation and the sociopolitical dynamics at play. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/why-googles-co-founders-peter-223000442.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google's corporate parent joins $4 trillion club as investors continue to bet on AI breakthroughs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-corporate-parent-joins-4-214632364.html</link><description>Google parent Alphabet Inc. on Monday became the fourth Big Tech powerhouse to be valued at $4 trillion, a once seemingly unfathomable milestone that's become more like a rite of passage amid an artificial intelligence arms race.  Alphabet reached the threshold just four months after Google dodged the U.S. government's attempt to break up its internet empire following a ruling last year that branded its ubiquitous search engine an illegal monopoly.  In an effort to prevent further abuses, a federal judge overseeing the case ordered a shake-up that investors widely interpreted as a slap on the wrist, resulting in a 57% increase in Alphabet's stock price since then that has created an additional $1.4 trillion in shareholder wealth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-corporate-parent-joins-4-214632364.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mark Zuckerberg says Meta is launching its own AI infrastructure initiative</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-zuckerberg-says-meta-launching-214443279.html</link><description>Meta is ramping up its efforts to build out its AI capacity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-zuckerberg-says-meta-launching-214443279.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC Plans U.S. Expansion in Proposed Taiwan Tariff-Relief Deal</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/tsmc-plans-u-s-expansion-in-proposed-taiwan-tariff-relief-deal-280d8a08?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Trump administration has been negotiating for months to bring more high-tech chip manufacturing to the U.S.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/tsmc-plans-u-s-expansion-in-proposed-taiwan-tariff-relief-deal-280d8a08?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Futures: Nvidia, Tesla, Walmart Are Key Movers; CPI Inflation Report Next</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-nvidia-tesla-walmart-cpi-inflation-report/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Dow Jones Futures: Broadcom, Nvidia, Palantir, Tesla and Walmart were key movers Monday. The CPI inflation report is due Tuesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-nvidia-tesla-walmart-cpi-inflation-report/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alibaba stock surges amid probe, Citi to cut 1,000 jobs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/alibaba-stock-surges-amid-probe-213208899.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Brooke DiPalma tracks several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including Alibaba stock (BABA, 9988.HK) surging as Chinese regulators launch a probe into the food delivery space, Walmart (WMT) to join the Nasdaq 100 (^NDX) as it teams with Alphabet's Google Gemini AI (GOOG, GOOGL), and Bloomberg reporting that Citigroup (C) plans to lay off up to 1,000 workers this week. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/alibaba-stock-surges-amid-probe-213208899.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Can We Retire at 62 With $690K In A Roth IRA, $1,800 In Social Security, And No Mortgage — But $500 A Month In Out-of-Pocket Medical Costs?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/retire-62-690k-roth-ira-213111131.html</link><description>Retiring at 62 sounds doable when the house is paid off and there's a solid nest egg waiting. But for one Florida couple, even a well-prepped plan feels like it's riding a tightrope. Together, they've saved $690,000 in a Roth IRA and expect $1,800 a month in combined Social Security benefits. Their mortgage is gone, which lifts a major weight. But their biggest concern heading into retirement isn't housing — it's healthcare. They're budgeting $500 a month out-of-pocket for Medicare premiums, pre</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/retire-62-690k-roth-ira-213111131.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Nvidia Stock Closes Flat. The Chip Maker Is Launching an AI Lab with Eli Lilly.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-china-8bfa9df6?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  stock was languishing Monday despite news of a partnership with pharmaceutical company  Eli Lilly  The chip company’s investors remain focused progress on sales in China and the health of the wider artificial-intelligence sector.  The stock is down 1.8% over the past month, as a flurry of robotics and autonomous-driving related announcements at the CES trade show, formerly known as the Consumer Electronics Show, failed to provide a boost.  Nvidia said Monday that it was joining with  Eli Lilly  to fund an AI lab with an investment of up to $1 billion over five years to build models for biology and chemistry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-china-8bfa9df6?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Expect a Busy Year in Obesity Drugs as New Pills Hit the Market</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/obesity-drugs-pills-fda-ce526357?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Pill versions of the successful GLP1 drugs from Novo Nordisk and Eli Lilly will likely be on the market in 2026’s first half.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/obesity-drugs-pills-fda-ce526357?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta plans to cut around 10% of employees in Reality Labs division, NYT reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-plans-cut-around-10-211817584.html</link><description>Meta plans to cut around 10% of the employees in its Reality Labs division who ​work on products including the metaverse, the New York ‌Times reported on Monday, citing three people with knowledge of the discussions.  The cuts ‌to Reality Labs, which has roughly 15,000 employees, could be announced as soon as Tuesday and are set to disproportionately affect those in the metaverse unit who work on virtual reality ⁠headsets and virtual social ‌networks, the report said.  The metaverse had been a massive project spearheaded by CEO  Mark Zuckerberg, who prioritized and ‍spent heavily on the venture, only for the business to burn more than $60 billion since 2020.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-plans-cut-around-10-211817584.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Top Stock Reports for Microsoft, Eli Lilly &amp; Lam Research</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-stock-reports-microsoft-eli-211600623.html</link><description>Microsoft beat software peers as Azure's 25% cloud share and OpenAI-led AI lift cash flow, despite competition, regulation and rising AI capex.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-stock-reports-microsoft-eli-211600623.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Big Oil and More Surprising AI Winners for 2026</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-nvidia-exxon-chevron-2026-2577783b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AI growth pitted against power availability is a “perfect storm” for 2026, warns Jordi Visser, head of AI Macro Nexus Research for 22V Research.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-nvidia-exxon-chevron-2026-2577783b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia Will Be Worth $7 Trillion by the End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/prediction-nvidia-will-be-worth-7-trillion-by-the/</link><description>Nvidia's growth trajectory is unlike anything the market has seen.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/prediction-nvidia-will-be-worth-7-trillion-by-the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple teams up with Google Gemini for AI-powered Siri</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/12/tech/apple-google-gemini-siri</link><description>Apple plans to use Google’s Gemini artificial intelligence model to power its updated version of Siri, which is set to launch later this year, the two companies announced Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/12/tech/apple-google-gemini-siri</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Autonomous Trucking Stock Investors Overlook</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/the-autonomous-trucking-stock-investors-overlook/</link><description>A good portion of the next generation of trucks will be driverless.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/the-autonomous-trucking-stock-investors-overlook/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Fiscal Reauthorization Act Fuels 2026 Quantum Growth: 3 Stocks to Gain</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fiscal-reauthorization-act-fuels-2026-200000285.html</link><description>IONQ stands to benefit as the National Quantum Initiative Reauthorization Act pushes government funding from research into real-world quantum deployment in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fiscal-reauthorization-act-fuels-2026-200000285.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple's Siri will be powered by Google's Gemini AI in new partnership</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/california/2026/01/12/apple-google-deal-gemini-ai-siri-california-artificial-intelligence/88144909007/</link><description>Alphabet Inc. and Apple have announced a partnership to use Google's AI technology to power the foundation of Apple's Intelligence and Siri.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/california/2026/01/12/apple-google-deal-gemini-ai-siri-california-artificial-intelligence/88144909007/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple calls on Google to help smarten up Siri and bring other AI features to the iPhone</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-calls-google-help-smarten-190059968.html</link><description>Apple will rely on Google to help finish its efforts to smarten up its virtual assistant Siri and bring other artificial intelligence features to the iPhone as the trendsetting company plays catch up in technology's latest craze.  The deal allowing Apple to tap into Google's AI technology was disclosed Monday in a joint statement from the Silicon Valley powerhouses.  The partnership will draw upon Google's Gemini technology to customize a suite of AI features dubbed “Apple Intelligence” on the iPhone and other products.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-calls-google-help-smarten-190059968.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Sizing Up Whether The Global Select Equity ETF Is A Buy Right Now</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/sizing-up-whether-the-global-select-equity-etf-is-a-buy-right-now/</link><description>The JPMorgan (NYSE:JPM) Global Select Equity ETF (NASDAQ:JGLO) launched in September 2023 to actively select the best equity ideas globally. With $7.1 billion in assets and a 0.47% expense ratio, it holds roughly 40 companies. JGLO’s 15% gain over the past year stems from heavy concentration in mega-cap technology. The fund places over a quarter ... Sizing Up Whether The Global Select Equity ETF Is A Buy Right Now</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/sizing-up-whether-the-global-select-equity-etf-is-a-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple Taps Google's Gemini to Power AI Models After 'Apple Intelligence' Stumbles</title><link>https://decrypt.co/354283/apple-taps-googles-gemini-power-ai-models-apple-intelligence-stumbles</link><description>Apple says its next generation of AI models will be based on Google’s Gemini, marking a reset after its in-house effort failed to compete.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://decrypt.co/354283/apple-taps-googles-gemini-power-ai-models-apple-intelligence-stumbles</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple's Siri Will Get a Google Gemini Makeover. Here's What It Means for the Stock in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/apples-siri-will-get-a-google-gemini-makeover-here/</link><description>This could be a critical move to jump-start Apple's stock over the coming year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/apples-siri-will-get-a-google-gemini-makeover-here/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Tempus Shares Jump After Strong Preliminary 2025 Results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tempus-shares-jump-strong-preliminary-183532772.html</link><description>Investors Eye 2026 Guidance as Tempus AI Tops $1.1B in Contract Value</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tempus-shares-jump-strong-preliminary-183532772.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Walmart Stock Jumps on Google AI Partnership</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-stock-jumps-google-ai-182828254.html</link><description>Walmart Bets Big on AI With Gemini Integration</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-stock-jumps-google-ai-182828254.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] JPM26: Eli Lilly and NVIDIA deepen ties with $1bn AI partnership</title><link>https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/jpm26-eli-lilly-and-nvidia-deepen-ties-with-1bn-ai-partnership/</link><description>A new co-innovation lab in the San Francisco Bay area will see Lilly and NVIDIA scientists work alongside each other to fuel drug discovery improvements.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/jpm26-eli-lilly-and-nvidia-deepen-ties-with-1bn-ai-partnership/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Walmart a Tech Stock? Its Planned Move to the Nasdaq 100 Is a Vote for 'Yes'</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/is-walmart-a-tech-stock-its-planned-move-to-the-nasdaq-100-is-a-vote-for-yes-wmt-11883544</link><description>The Arkansas-based retailer, which has been touting its e-commerce capabilities, is slated to join the index on Jan. 20th.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/is-walmart-a-tech-stock-its-planned-move-to-the-nasdaq-100-is-a-vote-for-yes-wmt-11883544</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple and Google Stocks In Spotlight -- Teams Up in Multi-Year AI Deal</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-google-stocks-spotlight-teams-182118729.html</link><description>Wall Street Watches as Apple Taps Google AI to Boost Device Ecosystem</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-google-stocks-spotlight-teams-182118729.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Why CoreWeave Stock Popped Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/why-coreweave-stock-popped-today/</link><description>Management pushed back on concerns about GPU depreciation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/why-coreweave-stock-popped-today/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] TSMC rises on reported US–Taiwan deal, Nvidia &amp; Eli Lilly team up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-rises-reported-us-taiwan-181454197.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma tracks Monday's top moving stocks and biggest market stories in this Market Minute. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM) stock is moving higher on a New York Times report that the Trump administration is close to reaching a trade agreement with Taiwan. Nvidia (NVDA) and Eli Lilly (LLY) are partnering on drug discovery, jointly investing $1 billion to create a lab in San Francisco. Stay up to date on the latest market action, minute-by-minute, with Yahoo Finance's Market Minute.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-rises-reported-us-taiwan-181454197.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Tempus AI's Pharma Momentum Accelerates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tempus-ais-pharma-momentum-accelerates-180818076.html</link><description>Contract value passes $1.1 billion milestone</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tempus-ais-pharma-momentum-accelerates-180818076.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Nvidia Partners With Biotech Firms On AI Drug Discovery</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/nvidia-stock-ai-leader-partners-biotech-firms/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia announced AI partnerships with two biotech firms to transform the way lifesaving drugs are discovered and manufactured.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/nvidia-stock-ai-leader-partners-biotech-firms/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] BioAge Rockets As It Takes On Eli Lilly's Takeover Play, Ventyx Bio</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/bioage-labs-bioage-stock-eli-lilly-ventyx-biosciences-nlrp3/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>BioAge shares catapulted Monday on promising results for the company's cardiovascular diseases treatment, which could eventually rival Eli Lilly.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/bioage-labs-bioage-stock-eli-lilly-ventyx-biosciences-nlrp3/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly and Nvidia Make $1 Billion AI Bet to Revolutionize Pharma’s Future</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/eli-lilly-and-nvidia-make-1-billion-ai-bet-to-revolutionize-pharmas-future/</link><description>One of the major promises of artificial intelligence (AI) is its role in speeding up drug discovery. AI can process massive amounts of data far faster than humans, identifying potential drug candidates and predicting their effects. This could cut years off the traditional process, which often takes over a decade and costs billions. Eli Lilly ... Eli Lilly and Nvidia Make $1 Billion AI Bet to Revolutionize Pharma’s Future</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/eli-lilly-and-nvidia-make-1-billion-ai-bet-to-revolutionize-pharmas-future/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Jim Cramer Says International Business Machines “Is Still Very Inexpensive”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-international-business-174747686.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the stocks from different market sectors that Jim Cramer commented on. Cramer highlighted the “big runs” in companies like IBM, as he remarked: “Apart from that, retail favorites like Palantir and AppLovin stood out… And I also like to see some big runs in old tech that’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-international-business-174747686.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm Holdings (ARM) Expands in the Robotics Industry With Physical AI Unit</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-arm-expands-robotics-174728081.html</link><description>​Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the Best Stocks to Buy for High Returns in 2026. On January 7, Reuters reported that Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is reorganizing its business to expand its presence in the robotics industry by creating a new Physical AI unit. ​According to the report, this decision comes at a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-arm-expands-robotics-174728081.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Here’s What Wall Street Thinks About NVIDIA Corporation (NVDA)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-thinks-nvidia-corporation-174713448.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the Best Stocks to Buy for High Returns in 2026. On January 8, Harsh Kumar from Piper Sandler reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $225 price target. Earlier on January 6, Harlan Sur from J.P. Morgan also maintained a Buy rating on NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) without […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-thinks-nvidia-corporation-174713448.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alphabet Touches $4 Trillion Market Cap for the First Time</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/alphabet-stock-4-trillion-market-cap-b51c8c6b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>If the company closed above that level, it would join Nvidia, Apple, and Microsoft as the only stocks ever to do so.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/alphabet-stock-4-trillion-market-cap-b51c8c6b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple, Google Confirm Multiyear Deal for AI Technology, Siri</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-confirms-multiyear-ai-deal-162923372.html</link><description>“After careful evaluation, Apple determined that Google’s Al technology provides the most capable foundation for Apple Foundation Models and is excited about the innovative new experiences it will unlock for Apple users,” the two companies said Monday in a joint statement.  Bloomberg reported late last year that the two companies were finalizing such a deal, with Apple planning to pay about $1 billion a year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-confirms-multiyear-ai-deal-162923372.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Health Care Roundup: Market Talk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/health-care-roundup-market-talk-ba4bb526?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Find insight on U.S. pharmaceutical companies’ cash positions, the Thai health-care sector and more in the latest Market Talks covering the health care sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/health-care-roundup-market-talk-ba4bb526?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tech, Media &amp; Telecom Roundup: Market Talk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/tech-media-telecom-roundup-market-talk-940691c7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Find insight on Apple, Google Gemini, Shopify and more in the latest Market Talks covering technology, media and telecom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/tech-media-telecom-roundup-market-talk-940691c7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Financial Stocks Fall After Trump Calls for Credit-Card Rate Cap</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/capital-one-synchrony-stocks-fall-after-trump-calls-for-cap-on-credit-card-rates-xkGy1foivVYa4SaMagIG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks in a range of financial companies fell after President Trump called for credit-card interest rates to be capped at 10% for a year, in his latest attempt to address voters' affordability concerns.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/capital-one-synchrony-stocks-fall-after-trump-calls-for-cap-on-credit-card-rates-xkGy1foivVYa4SaMagIG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google parent Alphabet hits $4tn valuation after AI deal with Apple</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-parent-alphabet-hits-4tn-171452538.html</link><description>After Apple chose Gemini to power Siri, Alphabet surpassed Apple to become second-most valuable company in world</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-parent-alphabet-hits-4tn-171452538.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google’s Gemini to power Apple’s AI features like Siri</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-gemini-power-apple-ai-171241715.html</link><description>Apple and Google have embarked on a non-exclusive, multi-year partnership that will involve Apple using Gemini models and Google cloud technology for future foundational models.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-gemini-power-apple-ai-171241715.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Google’s Sergey Brin admits he’s hiring ‘tons’ of workers without degrees: ‘They just figure things out on their own in some weird corner’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-sergey-brin-admits-hiring-170658486.html</link><description>Google cofounder Sergey Brin studied graduate computer science at Stanford—but admits Gen Z no longer needs a degree to land a high-paying job at the tech giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-sergey-brin-admits-hiring-170658486.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Major bank issues striking new gold forecast</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/major-bank-issues-striking-new-gold-forecast</link><description>HSBC feels gold could trade as high as $5,000 an ounce in the first half of 2026.At the same time, the bank warns investors to expect anything but a smooth ride to get there. So long-term optimism aside, gold’s still flashing considerable short-term risk. In doing so, HSBC also lowered ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/major-bank-issues-striking-new-gold-forecast</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Push Into NAND Fuels Global Memory Crunch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-push-nand-fuels-global-170358597.html</link><description>AI chip surge from CES 2026 highlights growing strain on semiconductor supply.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-push-nand-fuels-global-170358597.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Parnassus Value Equity Fund Exits Ball Corp, Impacting Portfolio by -2.01%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/parnassus-value-equity-fund-exits-170104916.html</link><description>Insights into Parnassus Value Equity Fund (Trades, Portfolio)'s Strategic Moves in Q4 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/parnassus-value-equity-fund-exits-170104916.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Bond Sales Could Hit $300 Billion a Year, Bank of America Says</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/ai-bond-sales-could-hit-300-billion-a-year-bank-of-america-says-y0mW2Q3WpjK62vtcG65Q?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Large technology companies racing to develop artificial intelligence will likely issue between $140 billion and $300 billion of corporate bonds annually in the next three years, according to research by Bank of America.  Debt investors have already shown some signs of fatigue, demanding about one-third of a percentage point of extra yield compared to benchmark Treasuries to buy recent bonds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/ai-bond-sales-could-hit-300-billion-a-year-bank-of-america-says-y0mW2Q3WpjK62vtcG65Q?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Becomes Newest $4 Trillion Company, Joining Nvidia</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/google-4-trillion-valuation-0a022302?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Google parent  Alphabet  value topped $4 trillion in intraday trade, making it the latest tech company to cross that threshold as investors reward the internet-search leader for its artificial-intelligence gains.  Shares in  Alphabet  rose 1.66% to a record $334.04 on Monday morning, putting its market capitalization at $4.03 trillion for a time.  Four technology companies have traded at market capitalizations of $4 trillion, and only  Nvidia  is still above that mark.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/google-4-trillion-valuation-0a022302?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jefferies Sees Amazon (AMZN) Well-Positioned for AI Inference and Production Workloads</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-sees-amazon-amzn-well-165852356.html</link><description>Amazon Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) is among the best software infrastructure stocks to buy according to hedge funds. On January 5, Jefferies hiked the stock price target from $275 to $300 and reiterated its Buy rating. The firm acknowledged that Amazon’s shares have underperformed in 2025, partly due to negative investor sentiment stemming from a perceived lag in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-sees-amazon-amzn-well-165852356.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] How Berkshire's Retail Arm Drives Its Service and Retailing Business</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshires-retail-arm-drives-retailing-165600505.html</link><description>BRK.B's retail arm, led by auto and furniture sales, fuels stable earnings and cash flows in its Service and Retailing segment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshires-retail-arm-drives-retailing-165600505.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC’s Revenue Outlook ‘May Disappoint,’ Says Analyst. There’s a Silver Lining.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-revenue-outlook-6c4da913?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company, which dominates the market for manufacturing high-end chips, is scheduled to report its earnings on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-stock-revenue-outlook-6c4da913?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Meta Needs So Much Capital It Hired Its Own Banker</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/meta-facebook-dina-powell-mccormick-663d6dc0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Meta Platforms  announced on Monday that Dina Powell McCormick, who comes from the worlds of international finance and politics, has become the company’s president and vice chairman.  The move signals Meta won’t slow its enormous artificial-intelligence data center buildout soon.  As a child, McCormick came to America as an Egyptian immigrant who spoke no English.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/meta-facebook-dina-powell-mccormick-663d6dc0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM's Edge AI Expansion With Datavault AI: Will it Boost Profits?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-edge-ai-expansion-datavault-164700836.html</link><description>International Business Machines extended its collaboration with Datavault AI to deliver secure, ultra-low-latency enterprise AI at the edge with watsonx-powered zero-trust micro data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-edge-ai-expansion-datavault-164700836.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Smartest Way to Invest $2,000 If You Believe in AI's Next Wave</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/smart-way-invest-2000-if-believe-ai-next-wave/</link><description>The market appears to be split on what's next for artificial intelligence (AI).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/smart-way-invest-2000-if-believe-ai-next-wave/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] ‘Biotech Super Bowl’ Lands With a Thud. Stocks Slide on Lack of Deal News.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/biotech-stocks-chase-conference-b9cab762?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Monday is the first day of  J.P. Morgan’s  annual healthcare investor conference, which draws thousands of investors, analysts, and executives to San Francisco each year.  There is ample precedent: Last year,  Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson  announced a $14.6 billion deal to acquire Intra-Cellular Therapeutics on the first day of the gathering.  The Wall Street Journal reported last week that Merck was in talks to buy the biotech Revolution Medicines for roughly $30 billion, but as of late morning, no such agreement had been announced.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/biotech-stocks-chase-conference-b9cab762?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Nvidia, Eli Lilly announce $1 billion investment in AI drug discovery lab</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-eli-lilly-announce-1-billion-investment-in-ai-drug-discovery-lab-163446796.html</link><description>Nvidia and Eli Lilly are set to launch an AI lab in San Francisco.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-eli-lilly-announce-1-billion-investment-in-ai-drug-discovery-lab-163446796.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jefferies Sees Alphabet’s (GOOGL) Data Moat and Cloud Growth Driving Long-Term Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-sees-alphabet-googl-data-162709771.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is among the best software infrastructure stocks to buy according to hedge funds. On January 5, Jefferies reaffirmed its Buy rating but raised its price target on the stock from $320 to $365. As per the update, there were a number of factors that bolstered Jefferies’ positive case, and the first one among […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-sees-alphabet-googl-data-162709771.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alphabet Stock Hits $4 Trillion Market Cap</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/alphabet-stock-hits-4-trillion-market-cap-8Ru9gHTQ9QLDluc1Exv0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Google parent Alphabet’s value briefly topped $4 trillion Monday, making it the latest tech company to cross that threshold as investors reward the internet-search leader for its artificial- Alphabet stock rose 1.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-12-2026/card/alphabet-stock-hits-4-trillion-market-cap-8Ru9gHTQ9QLDluc1Exv0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google, Apple enter into multi-year AI deal for Gemini models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-apple-enter-multi-ai-162042367.html</link><description>Alphabet said on Monday it had entered ​into a multi-year deal ‌with Apple where the next generation of ‌the iPhone maker's AI models will be based on Google's Gemini models.  The tie-up signals a ⁠strong vote ‌of confidence in Google's AI technology, after its most ‍recent version of Gemini launched to strong reviews, intensifying pressure on ​rivals.  Google's models will power Apple's ‌future "Apple Intelligence" features, including the revamped Siri, set to launch this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-apple-enter-multi-ai-162042367.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google and Apple enter into multi-year AI deal for Gemini models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-apple-enter-multi-ai-162042206.html</link><description>Jan 12 (Reuters) - Alphabet has entered into a multi-year deal with Apple where the next generation of the iPhone maker's AI models will be based on Google's Gemini models, Alphabet said on Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-apple-enter-multi-ai-162042206.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] JPM26: Eli Lilly reportedly eyes €15bn takeover of Abivax</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/jpm26-eli-lilly-reportedly-eyes-e15bn-takeover-of-abivax/</link><description>Abivax’s lead asset is obefazimod, an anti-inflammatory drug that has produced positive Phase III results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/jpm26-eli-lilly-reportedly-eyes-e15bn-takeover-of-abivax/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Wall Street Gears up for Q4 Earnings Season</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-gears-q4-earnings-161700134.html</link><description>Wall Street Gears up for Q4 Earnings Season</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-gears-q4-earnings-161700134.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple Confirms Use Of Google Gemini For AI Upgrades</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/apple-stock-deal-google-gemini-siri-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Apple revealed Monday that it plans to use Google's Gemini AI models to power the next version of its Siri digital assistant. Apple stock was little changed.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/apple-stock-deal-google-gemini-siri-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple Picks Gemini to Run AI-Powered Siri: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-picks-gemini-run-ai-161400878.html</link><description>CNBC reported that Apple had picked Alphabet's Gemini to run an AI-powered version of its Siri digital assistant. Bloomberg Intelligence's Mandeep Singh has more on "Bloomberg Open Interest."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-picks-gemini-run-ai-161400878.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Memory Shortage Reshapes 2026 Outlook for Chipmakers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-memory-shortage-reshapes-2026-161237399.html</link><description>Wedbush flags tight DRAM and storage supply, rising prices, and shifting demand after CES announcements from major semiconductor players.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-memory-shortage-reshapes-2026-161237399.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] From Training AI to Designing Chips: Nvidia's Next Platform Play</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/from-training-ai-to-designing-chips-nvidias-next-p/</link><description>Nvidia will start delivering its promising Rubin platform to buyers in the second half of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/from-training-ai-to-designing-chips-nvidias-next-p/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Samsung looks to make AI unobtrusive as part 'ambient AI' push</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/samsung-looks-to-make-ai-unobtrusive-as-part-ambient-ai-push-160057839.html</link><description>According to Samsung, many users aren't aware of when they're using AI on their smartphones. Here's how the company plans to address that.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/samsung-looks-to-make-ai-unobtrusive-as-part-ambient-ai-push-160057839.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet briefly surpassed $4T on news of Apple AI partnership</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/alphabet-briefly-surpassed-4t-news-155838039.html</link><description>Alphabet's (GOOG, GOOGL) market cap briefly reached above $4 trillion after it was announced that Apple (AAPL) would reportedly utilize Google Gemini to power new AI features in Siri as part of a new partnership, according to CNBC. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/alphabet-briefly-surpassed-4t-news-155838039.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google's market cap hits $4 trillion, cementing its status as an AI trade champion</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-market-cap-hits-4-trillion-cementing-its-status-as-an-ai-trade-champion-155246459.html</link><description>Google's market cap surpassed the $4 trillion mark.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-market-cap-hits-4-trillion-cementing-its-status-as-an-ai-trade-champion-155246459.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Finally Entering Its Breakout Phase?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-txn-texas/</link><description>Its shares have lagged the market, but this under-the-radar AI stock is starting to take off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-txn-texas/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave stock surges after CEO rebuts GPU useful life concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-surges-ceo-rebuts-154939913.html</link><description>Investing.com -- CoreWeave (NASDAQ:CRWV) stock rose 10% Monday, outperforming the broader tech sector following CEO Michael Intrator’s recent podcast appearance where he addressed criticisms about the company’s business model.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-surges-ceo-rebuts-154939913.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why IREN Limited Skyrocketed 285% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/why-iren-limited-skyrocketed-285-in-2025/</link><description>Investors became aware of the hugely valuable asset IREN had been building for years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/why-iren-limited-skyrocketed-285-in-2025/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 5 U.S. chip stocks to buy in 2026: Bernstein</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-u-chip-stocks-buy-153442397.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Bernstein has reiterated its bullish stance on several major U.S. semiconductor names in 2026, arguing that the sector remains supported by strong AI spending trends and rising prospects for wafer-fab equipment demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-u-chip-stocks-buy-153442397.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet hits $4 trillion valuation as AI refocus lifts sentiment</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-hits-4-trillion-valuation-153054925.html</link><description>Alphabet hit a $4 trillion market valuation on Monday, as the Google parent's sharpened artificial intelligence focus allayed doubts about its strategy ​and thrust it back to the forefront of the high-stakes race.  The tech giant ‌on Wednesday surpassed Apple in market capitalization for the first time since 2019, becoming the second most ‌valuable company in the world.  The milestones mark a remarkable change in investor sentiment for Alphabet, with its stock surging about 65% in 2025, outperforming its peers on Wall Street's elite group of stocks, the so-called Magnificent Seven.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-hits-4-trillion-valuation-153054925.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018781.html</link><description>Nu Holdings Ltd. 3,225,985 17.42</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018781.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Meanders Ahead Of Taiwan Semiconductor's Results; Is Nvidia A Buy Or Sell Now?</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-ai-tsm/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock is flat Monday ahead of chip contract manufacturer Taiwan Semiconductor's fourth-quarter report due Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-ai-tsm/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Big Week for Data: Q4 Earnings, Inflation Rate</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-week-data-q4-earnings-152800196.html</link><description>Big banks reporting Q4 results and a fresh CPI Inflation Rate are expected to be two highlights to enhance market activity this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-week-data-q4-earnings-152800196.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Nvidia Partners With Eli Lilly on AI Drug Laboratory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-partners-eli-lilly-ai-152743875.html</link><description>Nvidia plans to invest $1 billion over five years in a new laboratory with&amp;amp;nbsp;Eli Lilly &amp;amp; Co., aiming to speed up the use of artificial intelligence in the pharmaceutical industry.&amp;amp;nbsp;Jessica Nix has more on "Bloomberg Open Interest."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-partners-eli-lilly-ai-152743875.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights NVIDIA, Alphabet, Amazon.com and CBL &amp; Associates Properties</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-nvidia-152600620.html</link><description>NVIDIA headlines Zacks' top research picks as AI-driven growth fuels strong performance across mega-cap tech leaders.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-nvidia-152600620.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] iShares ETF Has A ‘Set And Forget’ Investment For Retirees You Don’t Need To Overthink</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/ishares-etf-has-a-set-and-forget-investment-for-retirees-you-dont-need-to-overthink/</link><description>The hardest part of retirement investing isn’t picking stocks or timing the market – it’s resisting the urge to do either. iShares Core S&amp;amp;P Total U.S. Stock Market ETF (NYSEARCA:ITOT) solves this by offering exposure to the entire U.S. equity market in a single position, charging just 0.03% annually, and requiring no ongoing decisions beyond ... iShares ETF Has A ‘Set And Forget’ Investment For Retirees You Don’t Need To Overthink</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/ishares-etf-has-a-set-and-forget-investment-for-retirees-you-dont-need-to-overthink/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Zacks Industry Outlook Highlights Caterpillar, Terex and Astec Industries</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-industry-outlook-highlights-caterpillar-151100943.html</link><description>Caterpillar leads construction and mining equipment stocks to watch as infrastructure spending and energy transition demand offset manufacturing headwinds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-industry-outlook-highlights-caterpillar-151100943.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Wobbles Even as CEO Flags 'Very High' H200 Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-wobbles-even-ceo-151023750.html</link><description>Nvidia Stock Slows After Massive H200 Orders Hit Regulatory Snag</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-wobbles-even-ceo-151023750.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba Stock Jumps on Qwen Models Hit 700 Million Downloads</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-stock-jumps-qwen-models-150928656.html</link><description>BABA Stock Gains as AI Adoption Accelerates Across Alibaba Cloud</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-stock-jumps-qwen-models-150928656.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is TSMC Stock a 'Buy' or 'Sell' Ahead of Earnings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-stock-buy-sell-ahead-150736286.html</link><description>TSMC Earnings Are Coming This Week. AI Demand Will Be the Big Test</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-stock-buy-sell-ahead-150736286.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel Stock Gets a Higher Price Target. Why Wall Street Doesn’t Trust the Gains.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-target-7b07957c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The chip stock has rallied hard following President Donald Trump's praise for its CEO. Analysts still see issues for the company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-target-7b07957c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CRWD to Acquire SGNL: Is Identity Security the Next Growth Pillar?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-acquire-sgnl-identity-security-145900980.html</link><description>CrowdStrike agrees to acquire SGNL to boost identity security for AI-driven enterprises, adding real-time, risk-based access controls to the Falcon platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-acquire-sgnl-identity-security-145900980.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Stocks Retreat on Concerns Over Fed Independence</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36999567/stocks-retreat-on-concerns-over-fed-independence</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Index ($SPX ) (SPY ) today is down -0.23%, the Dow Jones Industrials Index ($DOWI ) (DIA ) is down -0.58%, and the Nasdaq 100 Index ($IUXX ) (QQQ ) is down -0.27%. March E-mini S&amp;amp;P futures (ESH26 ) are down -0.22%, and March E-mini Nasdaq futures...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36999567/stocks-retreat-on-concerns-over-fed-independence</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] This French Biotech Stock Surged 1,700% in 2025. Eli Lilly Is Taking an Interest.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/abivax-stock-price-eli-lilly-deal-d4360e1e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Eli Lilly’s  presence in France has spanned more than six decades, but rumors of an acquisition suggest the pharmaceutical giant could be looking to expand its footprint in the country.  French outlet La Lettre reported Monday that biotechnology company  Abivax  had become the subject of takeover interest by Lilly, which was prepared to offer 15 billion euros, or roughly $17.5 billion, to acquire it.  Eli Lilly  has yet to support a formal bid to Abivax’s board as it awaits clarity from French regulators on whether a bid would be subject to France’s foreign investment rules, the outlet reported.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/abivax-stock-price-eli-lilly-deal-d4360e1e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Netflix gets HSBC Buy rating as analyst highlights ’sturdy’ earnings outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-gets-hsbc-buy-rating-144944579.html</link><description>Investing.com -- HSBC has initiated coverage of Netflix with a Buy rating and a $107 target price, arguing that the recent pullback in the shares presents an opportunity for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-gets-hsbc-buy-rating-144944579.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Netflix initiated, Palantir upgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-initiated-palantir-upgraded-wall-144909530.html</link><description>Netflix initiated, Palantir upgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-initiated-palantir-upgraded-wall-144909530.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here's Why Eli Lilly (LLY) is a Strong Growth Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-eli-lilly-lly-144504168.html</link><description>The Zacks Style Scores offers investors a way to easily find top-rated stocks based on their investing style. Here's why you should take advantage.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-eli-lilly-lly-144504168.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Analysts turn more bullish on TSMC on stronger pricing power, earnings outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-turn-more-bullish-tsmc-142820383.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Analysts are growing more bullish on Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (TW:2330) (NYSE:TSM) as expectations around pricing power and medium-term earnings continue to build, supported by strong AI demand and advanced-node capacity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-turn-more-bullish-tsmc-142820383.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Walmart Partners With Alphabet Unit, Expands Drone Deliveries</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/walmart-alphabet-wing-drone-delivery-expansion-wmt-stock-dow-jones/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Walmart stock surges near buy zone. Dow retailer partners with Alphabet's Wing for drone deliveries, to join Nasdaq-100.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/walmart-alphabet-wing-drone-delivery-expansion-wmt-stock-dow-jones/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia Stock Could Drop 50% and Still Be Worth More Than Meta</title><link>https://247wallst.com/technology-3/2026/01/12/nvidia-stock-could-drop-50-and-still-be-worth-more-than-meta/</link><description>Nvidia's market cap is more than twice that of Meta Platforms. Nvidia has a huge advantage in that it almost single-handedly powers the AI revolution.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/technology-3/2026/01/12/nvidia-stock-could-drop-50-and-still-be-worth-more-than-meta/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Tech Stocks That Beat the Mag Seven By a Mile in 2025—Can They Repeat?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/2-tech-stocks-that-beat-the-mag-seven-by-a-mile-in-2025-can-they-repeat/</link><description>With the S&amp;amp;P 500 closing in on the 7,000 mark to start 2026 on the right footing, now seems like a good time to reflect on the big winners from 2025 and ponder whether there’s more gas left in the tank. Undoubtedly, 2026’s list of winners could have the potential to look vastly different than ... 2 Tech Stocks That Beat the Mag Seven By a Mile in 2025—Can They Repeat?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/2-tech-stocks-that-beat-the-mag-seven-by-a-mile-in-2025-can-they-repeat/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:02:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta Platforms is Shifting to Closed AI—Why That’s a Major Winning Move</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/meta-platforms-is-shifting-to-closed-ai-why-thats-a-major-winning-move/</link><description>Perhaps going down the open-source route wasn’t the way to go. With Meta Platforms (NASDAQ:META) now going down the proprietary AI model route after its LLaMa model fell short of expectations, questions linger as to whether the social-media and metaverse titan can really make up ground in the AI scene, one that’s been dominated by ... Meta Platforms is Shifting to Closed AI—Why That’s a Major Winning Move</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/meta-platforms-is-shifting-to-closed-ai-why-thats-a-major-winning-move/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Trending Stock Alphabet Inc. (GOOGL) a Buy Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trending-stock-alphabet-inc-googl-140007119.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately. So, it is worth exploring what lies ahead for the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trending-stock-alphabet-inc-googl-140007119.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Investors Heavily Search CrowdStrike (CRWD): Here is What You Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-heavily-search-crowdstrike-crwd-140006742.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately. So, it is worth exploring what lies ahead for the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-heavily-search-crowdstrike-crwd-140006742.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) is Attracting Investor Attention: Here is What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-attracting-investor-140006533.html</link><description>Snowflake (SNOW) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Therefore, it is wise to be aware of the facts that can impact the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-attracting-investor-140006533.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Trending Stock Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) a Buy Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trending-stock-alphabet-inc-goog-140003474.html</link><description>Recently, Zacks.com users have been paying close attention to Alphabet (GOOG). This makes it worthwhile to examine what the stock has in store.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trending-stock-alphabet-inc-goog-140003474.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] RVTY &amp; Eli Lilly Partner to Expand Access to AI Drug Discovery Models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rvty-eli-lilly-partner-expand-135700194.html</link><description>Revvity teams up with Eli Lilly to bring TuneLab AI models to Signals Xynthetica, aiming to unlock secure, federated drug discovery at scale.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rvty-eli-lilly-partner-expand-135700194.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Abercrombie &amp; Fitch Narrows Quarterly Guidance</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/retail/abercrombie-fitch-narrows-quarterly-guidance-d7b1444c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Abercrombie &amp;amp; Fitch narrowed its fiscal fourth-quarter guidance and said its Hollister and Abercrombie segments each saw strong holiday sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/retail/abercrombie-fitch-narrows-quarterly-guidance-d7b1444c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Upgrades: Analysts are Still Bullish on Nvidia (NVDA), Crowdstrike (CRWD) and Oracle (ORCL) Upside</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/upgrades-analysts-are-still-bullish-on-nvidia-nvda-crowdstrike-crwd-and-oracle-orcl-upside/</link><description>Analysts at Mizuho just reiterated an outperform rating on Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA), with a price target of $275 a share. The firm says Nvidia is its top pick in the semiconductor space. Not long ago, analysts at Barclays upgraded Nvidia to a buy rating thanks to strong AI spending. “We are OW [overweight] as the ... Upgrades: Analysts are Still Bullish on Nvidia (NVDA), Crowdstrike (CRWD) and Oracle (ORCL) Upside</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/upgrades-analysts-are-still-bullish-on-nvidia-nvda-crowdstrike-crwd-and-oracle-orcl-upside/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Buy Struggling Netflix Stock, Says Analyst. Why Warner Takeover Fears Are Overblown.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/netflix-stock-buy-warner-takeover-d4d1b633?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Savvy investors should see a recent selloff as a buying opportunity, HSBC analyst Mohammed Khallouf said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/netflix-stock-buy-warner-takeover-d4d1b633?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semiconductor to Report Q4 Earnings: How to Play the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-semiconductor-report-q4-earnings-134200108.html</link><description>TSM's Q4 revenues are likely to have benefited from AI-driven chip demand, while rising costs due to overseas expansions may have hurt profitability.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-semiconductor-report-q4-earnings-134200108.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Quantum Computing Stocks: 'Winner-Take-All Scenario' Possible, Says JPMorgan</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-winner-take-all-scenario-jpmorgan/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A "winner-take-all scenario" is possible, said JPMorgan in a report on quantum computing stocks that looked at IBM, Google and other players.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-winner-take-all-scenario-jpmorgan/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 Things to Know Before the Stock Market Opens</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-january-12-2026-11883331</link><description>News of the day for Jan. 12, 2026</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-january-12-2026-11883331</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] What's Next for Seagate Stock After a 241.8% Stellar Run in a Year?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/whats-next-seagate-stock-241-133200802.html</link><description>STX has surged nearly 242% in a year as AI-driven data growth, tight HDD supply and rising HAMR adoption fuel demand for high-capacity drives.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/whats-next-seagate-stock-241-133200802.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Capture Rolls-Royce's Record '26 Rally Through These Diversified ETFs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/capture-rolls-royces-record-26-132200729.html</link><description>RYCEY is up 12.9% YTD, hitting record highs in 2026; diversified ETFs like EUAD offer exposure to the rally while reducing risk from a potential pullback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/capture-rolls-royces-record-26-132200729.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Shake Shack’s Quarterly Sales Hurt by Inclement Weather</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/shake-shacks-quarterly-sales-hurt-by-inclement-weather-87838d8c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shake Shack said inclement weather in some of its most heavily penetrated markets hurt sales during the recent quarter, resulting in lower than expected revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/shake-shacks-quarterly-sales-hurt-by-inclement-weather-87838d8c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here Are Monday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Airbnb, Akamai, Applied Materials, CoreWeave, CrowdStrike, Datadog, NetFlix, Snowflake, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/here-are-mondays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-airbnb-akamai-applied-materials-coreweave-crowdstrike-datadog-netflix-snowflake-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading lower on Monday morning after a strong finish to the week on Friday, completing a winning week for investors as all three of the major indices closed at all-time highs. The news that Jay Powell, the Chairman of the Federal Reserve, is under criminal investigation by the Department ... Here Are Monday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Airbnb, Akamai, Applied Materials, CoreWeave, CrowdStrike, Datadog, NetFlix, Snowflake, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/12/here-are-mondays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-airbnb-akamai-applied-materials-coreweave-crowdstrike-datadog-netflix-snowflake-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:07:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: The Best Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-the-best/</link><description>Nvidia has been the star of the artificial intelligence show for three years, and its stellar performance doesn't appear to be coming to an end.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-the-best/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Delivered Solid Performance in the Quarter</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-delivered-solid-performance-130136376.html</link><description>Bristlemoon Capital, a global equities firm, released its “Bristlemoon Global Fund” fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The fund returned -6.2% in the December quarter and a 0.3% return in December. Since its inception, the fund has produced a cumulative return of 11.9%, net of fees. In 2025, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-delivered-solid-performance-130136376.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Bristlemoon Global Fund’s Thesis on ASML (ASML) is Paying Off</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bristlemoon-global-fund-thesis-asml-125940820.html</link><description>Bristlemoon Capital, a global equities firm, released its “Bristlemoon Global Fund” fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The fund returned -6.2% in the December quarter and a 0.3% return in December. Since its inception, the fund has produced a cumulative return of 11.9%, net of fees. In 2025, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bristlemoon-global-fund-thesis-asml-125940820.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls 350 Points On Powell Investigation; Nvidia, Tesla Slide (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-powell-nvidia-nvda-tesla-tsla/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped 350 points on the investigation into Fed Chair Powell. Nvidia and Tesla declined.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-powell-nvidia-nvda-tesla-tsla/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Quietly Outperformed Nvidia in 2025. It Can Continue Soaring in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/this-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-quietly-outp/</link><description>Investors looking for attractive AI stock picks should take a closer look at Seagate Technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/this-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-quietly-outp/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Is One of the Best Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks to Hold for the Next 10 Years</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/best-ai-stocks-hold-for-next-10-years/</link><description>This dominant AI stock is trading at a very attractive valuation at the start of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/12/best-ai-stocks-hold-for-next-10-years/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Walmart Stock Is Rising. It’s Not Just a Google AI Deal Giving It a Boost.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/walmart-stock-price-google-ai-deal-4cfd3593?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Two developments over the weekend underlined the retailer’s transformation from big-box store chain to e-commerce giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/walmart-stock-price-google-ai-deal-4cfd3593?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Kroger Expands Google Cloud AI Partnership Nationwide</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kroger-expands-google-cloud-ai-120056365.html</link><description>Kroger rolls out Gemini Enterprise nationwide to power AI-driven shopping and meal assistants, aiming to enhance digital personalization and customer engagement.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kroger-expands-google-cloud-ai-120056365.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>