<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[TSM] The Chip Technology That Finally Gives Intel an Edge Over TSMC</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-chip-technology-that-finally-gives-intel-an-ed/</link><description>Intel was first to market with backside power delivery.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-chip-technology-that-finally-gives-intel-an-ed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Week In AI Chips - Innovative Cooling Solutions Fuel Next-Gen AI Data Centers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-innovative-cooling-113745338.html</link><description>Motivair by Schneider Electric has unveiled the MCDU-70, a cutting-edge 2.5MW Coolant Distribution Unit (CDU), designed to address the cooling needs of next-generation AI data centers. This new CDU model supports scalability up to 10MW and is engineered to handle the intense heat generated by advanced GPUs, which power AI Factories. By integrating with Schneider Electric’s EcoStruxure software, the unit promises reliable and efficient cooling solutions for high-density data centers at a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-innovative-cooling-113745338.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang pushes back against AI bubble worries</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-pushes-113729636.html</link><description>Speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang defended the billions of dollars being spent on AI and pushed back on worries that there may be an AI bubble forming. Watch the full conversation with Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-pushes-113729636.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 1 Magnificent Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock to Buy in 2026 and Hold Forever (Hint: It's Not Nvidia)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-magnif/</link><description>Alphabet is beginning to emerge as Wall Street's new favorite artificial intelligence (AI) growth stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-magnif/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Nvidia and Broadcom Look Attractive Again. Citi Names Top Chip Picks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-look-attractive-again-111909812.html</link><description>Semiconductor Stocks Are in Focus. Citi Sees Upside in Nvidia and Broadcom</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-look-attractive-again-111909812.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Alphabet (GOOGL) Fairly Priced After Recent Share Price Pullback?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-fairly-priced-recent-110908107.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Alphabet's current share price lines up with its underlying worth, you are not alone. That is exactly what this article will unpack. Alphabet closed at US$322.00 recently, after a 4.2% decline over the last 7 days, a 4.8% gain over 30 days, a 2.2% return year to date and a 63.2% return over the past year, with a 232.1% return over 3 years and 240.1% over 5 years. These moves have kept Alphabet in the spotlight, as investors weigh how its core businesses and long...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-fairly-priced-recent-110908107.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 7 Stocks Rallied More Than 200% Since Trump's Inauguration Day</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/7-stocks-rallied-more-200-110112579.html</link><description>A year after President Donald Trump returned to the White House, seven stocks in the Russell 1000 ETF have delivered staggering returns, each topping 200% gains. The performance table reads like a mood board for the market narrative of the past year: space, defense, AI supply constraints, precious metals and a national-security scramble for critical minerals. 7) MP Materials: Rare Earths Become A National Security Matter MP Materials Corp. (NYSE:MP) has rallied 225.84% since Jan. 20, 2025, as Wa</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/7-stocks-rallied-more-200-110112579.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Zinnia collaborates with Snowflake on real-time insurance analytics and AI</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/zinnia-collaborates-snowflake-insurance-analytics/</link><description>As part of the arrangement, Zinnia has deployed Snowflake’s data platform across its operations to underpin ML and AI-driven applications.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/zinnia-collaborates-snowflake-insurance-analytics/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2 No-Brainer AI Stocks to Buy Hand Over Fist for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/2-no-brainer-ai-stocks-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</link><description>These chip companies are well positioned for the growing investment in AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/2-no-brainer-ai-stocks-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Investors Bet on AWS to Pull the Stock Out of Its Malaise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-investors-bet-aws-pull-103914610.html</link><description>The optimism starts with demand for the Amazon Web Services cloud-computing business, which is positioned to benefit from the explosion of artificial intelligence technology.  “An improvement in AWS should help materially in terms of the perception of the stock as being the relative loser in cloud,” said Pat Burton, a portfolio manager at Winslow Capital Management, who counts Amazon as one of his biggest overweights among the Magnificent Seven tech giants.  Amazon shares were the worst performers among the Mag Seven in 2025, their seventh straight year trailing the group.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-investors-bet-aws-pull-103914610.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] CGI adopts Google’s Gemini Enterprise for enterprise AI integration</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/cgi-adopts-google-gemini-enterprise/</link><description>The agreement will enable CGI consultants to use Gemini Enterprise AI tools and support client digital transformation projects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/cgi-adopts-google-gemini-enterprise/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix defends Warner Bros bid as shares drop on tepid results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-101203336.html</link><description>Jan 21 (Reuters) - "YouTube is not just user-generated content and cat videos anymore," Netflix CEO Ted Sarandos said on Tuesday.  Making a compelling case for why the streaming giant wanted Warner Bros Discovery's studio and streaming assets, Sarandos noted how tech giants such ​as Alphabet's YouTube had changed what television viewing meant and forced Netflix to change tack to keep up.  Sarandos and his co-CEO Greg Peters spent a large portion of the post-earnings call talking effusively about how strong and complementary Warner Bros' services were, a sharp change from the long-held company credo: build, don't buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-101203336.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Best Momentum Stock to Buy for January 21st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-momentum-stock-buy-january-100500196.html</link><description>LRCX, BNPQY and LRLCY made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) momentum stocks list on January 21, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-momentum-stock-buy-january-100500196.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] US insurtech company Ethos begins IPO roadshow, seeks up to $1.3bn valuation</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/ethos-ipo-roadshow-valuation/</link><description>The US-based insurer and its shareholders intend to raise up to $210.5m by offering approximately 10.5 million shares.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/ethos-ipo-roadshow-valuation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Down 40%, Is CoreWeave a Buy on the Dip?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/down-40-is-coreweave-a-buy-on-the-dip/</link><description>CoreWeave launched its IPO last March.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/down-40-is-coreweave-a-buy-on-the-dip/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Chainlink Enables 24/5 On-Chain Trading for Stocks, Gold, and Silver as Crypto Volatility Fades</title><link>https://www.ccn.com/news/crypto/chainlink-on-chain-trading-gold-silver-crypto/</link><description>Chainlink launches 24/5 U.S. equities data streams, enabling continuous on-chain trading of stocks and ETFs. The feeds provide real-time prices for assets such as Nvidia, ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ccn.com/news/crypto/chainlink-on-chain-trading-gold-silver-crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights Sandisk, Amphenol, ASML Holding and Corning</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-sandisk-092800762.html</link><description>Sandisk, Amphenol, ASML Holding and Corning are tech names positioned to beat Q4 earnings as AI-driven demand lifts chips and data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-sandisk-092800762.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] How Arm’s AI-Focused Reorganization Amid Valuation Questions At Arm Holdings (ARM) Has Changed Its Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-ai-focused-reorganization-amid-091149667.html</link><description>In recent weeks, Arm Holdings has faced analyst downgrades, questions about valuation, and concern over SoftBank’s margin loan tied to Arm shares, even as it reorganized around new Cloud and AI, Edge, and Physical AI divisions targeting robotics and autonomous vehicles. This restructuring marks a shift in Arm’s story from its traditional smartphone base toward longer-horizon opportunities in data centers, intelligent machines, and “physical AI” applications. Next, we’ll examine how Arm’s...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-ai-focused-reorganization-amid-091149667.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump at Davos, Intel Earnings, Supreme Court: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/trump-at-davos-intel-earnings-supreme-court-what-to-watch-this-week-5msZk5NpuZWckBchQvar?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season kicked up a gear this week, with results still due from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and Intel, among other companies. Plus, President Trump is at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, where he is due to speak on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/trump-at-davos-intel-earnings-supreme-court-what-to-watch-this-week-5msZk5NpuZWckBchQvar?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 3 Quantum Computing Stocks to Buy and Hold</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-3-quantu/</link><description>A few years from now, many investors could look back and wish they had bought these stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-3-quantu/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Invests in AI Start-up Baseten. It Shows a Shift in the Market.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-baseten-dff85821?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  has backed a funding round in artificial-intelligence start-up Baseten.  Baseten helps companies deploy and run large AI models.  The deal comes hot on the heels of Nvidia’s big licensing agreement with Groq, a privately held chip start-up focusing on hardware for AI inference.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-baseten-dff85821?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Assessing Arm Holdings (NasdaqGS:ARM) Valuation After Recent Share Price Weakness</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-arm-holdings-nasdaqgs-arm-080818609.html</link><description>Why Arm Holdings (ARM) is Back in Focus Arm Holdings (NasdaqGS:ARM) is back on many watchlists after recent trading, where the stock has seen a 6% decline over the past month and roughly 35% decline over the past 3 months. See our latest analysis for Arm Holdings. At the latest share price of US$107.17, Arm’s recent moves reflect fading momentum, with a 30 day share price return of 6.02% and a 90 day share price return of 35.33%. The 1 year total shareholder return of 30.95% highlights how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-arm-holdings-nasdaqgs-arm-080818609.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Group (NBIS) Falls Below $100 on Trade Worries</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-falls-below-073928842.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Investors Are Dumping. Nebius Group NV (NASDAQ:NBIS) was one of the worst performers on Tuesday. Nebius fell below the $100 territory on Tuesday, shedding 8.68 percent to close at $99.29 apiece and mirroring an overall market pessimism after President Donald Trump triggered another round of geopolitical tensions with the European […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-falls-below-073928842.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] What Rigetti Computing (RGTI)'s Quantum Roadmap Delay and India Deployment Deal Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-computing-rgti-quantum-roadmap-071220431.html</link><description>In early January 2026, Rigetti Computing revised its roadmap for the Cepheus-1-108Q system, pushing general availability of the 108-qubit, twelve-chiplet modular quantum computer to around the end of the first quarter of 2026 while reaffirming its broader scaling plans. An on-premises 108-qubit system order from India’s Centre for Development of Advanced Computing adds real-world deployment momentum to Rigetti’s modular architecture ambitions. With the Cepheus-1-108Q launch delay and fresh...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-computing-rgti-quantum-roadmap-071220431.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Is Arm Holdings (ARM) Pricing Reflect Future Growth After Recent Share Price Weakness</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-arm-pricing-reflect-071211611.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Arm Holdings' current share price lines up with its underlying value, you are not alone. This article will walk through what the numbers actually say. Over the last year the stock has seen a 30.9% decline, with returns of 0.6% over 7 days, 6.0% over 30 days and 6.6% year to date. These figures can change how investors think about both risk and potential opportunity. Recent coverage has focused on Arm Holdings as a key semiconductor licensing business...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-arm-pricing-reflect-071211611.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft clicks on Formula One grid with new Mercedes deal</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-clicks-formula-one-grid-064000998.html</link><description>Microsoft, the $3.4trn computing behemoth, will this week unveil a partnership with the Mercedes Formula One team that will underline the sport's resurgent appeal among the world's biggest technology companies.  Sky News understands that Microsoft will be announced as a major sponsor of the Brackley-based outfit when it unveils its 2026 car livery and design at an event on Thursday.  The deal will make Microsoft the latest tech company to sign a big commercial agreement in F1, with rivals such as Google already having a presence through a partnership with McLaren Racing, the reigning world champions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-clicks-formula-one-grid-064000998.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] The Ultimate Growth Stock to Buy With $1,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-ultimate-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</link><description>This company's stock is up 200% over the last year -- and is still rising.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-ultimate-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What Berkshire’s Greg Abel Should Do With All That Cash</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-greg-abel-buffett-cash-ffcbba65?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The new CEO could enhance the company’s returns on its massive cash position with a simple options strategy: cash-secured put sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-greg-abel-buffett-cash-ffcbba65?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is FICO’s (FICO) GPU-Powered Xpress Upgrade Quietly Rewiring Its Long-Term Moat In Analytics?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fico-fico-gpu-powered-xpress-052109531.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, FICO released version 9.8 of its FICO Xpress Optimization suite, integrating NVIDIA CUDA-X libraries to accelerate its hybrid gradient algorithm and delivering much faster solutions for extremely large, dense optimization problems on supported NVIDIA GPUs. This move pushes FICO Xpress further into high-performance computing, widening its appeal for organizations tackling massive, complex optimization workloads across data-intensive operations. Next, we’ll examine how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fico-fico-gpu-powered-xpress-052109531.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 05:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] US futures edge higher and gold hits another record as markets swoon over Greenland dispute</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-edge-higher-gold-045146410.html</link><description>Asian shares mostly extended their losses on Wednesday and gold prices hit a record high as concerns over U.S. President Donald Trump’s tariff threats on Greenland fueled unease among investors.  U.S. futures rose after steep losses Tuesday on Wall Street.  Gold prices crossed the $4,800 mark for the first time, gaining 1.7% as money flowed into assets considered to be safe havens at times of uncertainty.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-edge-higher-gold-045146410.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Tesla a Good AI Growth Stock to Buy and Hold For the Next 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-tesla-a-good-ai-growth-stock-to-buy-and-hold-fo/</link><description>Tesla CEO Elon Musk believes its AI-powered Robotaxi service will fundamentally change the nature of transport.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-tesla-a-good-ai-growth-stock-to-buy-and-hold-fo/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 2 Undervalued AI Stocks to Buy in 2026 and Hold for Decades</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-undervalued-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-hold/</link><description>These stocks have incredible long-term opportunities.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-undervalued-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-hold/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Huang plans to visit China as he seeks to reopen market, Bloomberg reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-huang-plans-visit-030251592.html</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang plans to travel to China in ​late January as he seeks to ‌reopen a critical market for the company's artificial intelligence ‌chips, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.  Huang is expected to attend company events ahead of ⁠the Lunar New ‌Year holidays in February, and may also visit Beijing, according to ‍the report.  Nvidia declined to comment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-huang-plans-visit-030251592.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What growth?: Taiwan's traditional manufacturers miss out on export boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/growth-taiwans-traditional-manufacturers-miss-024145018.html</link><description>Taiwan's economy soared last year on skyrocketing exports of AI hardware and semiconductors, but companies in more traditional manufacturing sectors could only look on with envy as they were clobbered by US tariffs and a strong local currency.Taiwan's information and communication technology (ICT) sector, which includes semiconductor chips, has become by far the biggest driver of the island's export-dependent economy. </description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/growth-taiwans-traditional-manufacturers-miss-024145018.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AMD Stock Soared Past Nvidia Last Year. Will That Trend Continue in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/amd-stock-soared-past-nvidia-last-year-will-that-t/</link><description>This past year was the first time AMD's stock outperformed Nvidia's since 2019.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/amd-stock-soared-past-nvidia-last-year-will-that-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Warren Buffett Sent a Clear Multibillion-Dollar Message About Artificial Intelligence That Investors Shouldn't Ignore</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/warren-buffett-sent-a-clear-multibillion-dollar/</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway finally invested in a company with some AI chops.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/warren-buffett-sent-a-clear-multibillion-dollar/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia’s Huang Plans to Visit China as He Works to Reopen Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-plans-visit-china-021000843.html</link><description>Huang will be in the country to attend company parties ahead of the Lunar New Year holidays, according to a person familiar with the matter.  The executive is also expected to visit Beijing, though it’s unclear whether he will meet with senior Chinese officials, said the person, who asked not to be identified because the plans are private.  Huang’s itinerary could still change, depending on whether prospective meetings come through.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-plans-visit-china-021000843.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Oklo Stock a Buy in 2026 After Its Nuclear Deal With Meta?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oklo-stock-a-buy-after-its-nuclear-deal-with-me/</link><description>Oklo and Meta announced a partnership to support 1.2 gigawatts of power in Ohio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oklo-stock-a-buy-after-its-nuclear-deal-with-me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 1 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Semiconductor Stock to Buy Hand Over Fist Before It Soars Up to 32%, According to a Wall Street Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-artifi/</link><description>Wall Street is calling for massive upside in Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-artifi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Anthropic’s CEO stuns Davos with Nvidia criticism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-ceo-stuns-davos-nvidia-013958947.html</link><description>Anthropic CEO Dario Amodei unloaded on both the administration and U.S. chip companies over plans to sell to China. The criticism was particularly notable because one of those chipmakers, Nvidia, is a major partner and investor in Anthropic.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-ceo-stuns-davos-nvidia-013958947.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Says He Hasn't Sold Tesla Stock For Over Three Years: 'Bought A Billion Dollars...'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-hasnt-sold-013105702.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared that he has not sold any of the EV giant's stock in the past three years. Bought A Billion Dollars Worth Of Stock Responding to a now-deleted post by influencer Mario Nawfal on the social media platform X on Sunday, the billionaire shared that he hadn't "sold stock for about 3 years." Musk also added that instead, he has invested in acquiring more Tesla shares. "bought a billion dollars of Tesla stock last year," he said in the post. I have not s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-hasnt-sold-013105702.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Predicted Nvidia Would Be a $5 Trillion Company in 2025. Here's Why I Was Right (and Wrong).</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-said-nvidia-would-be-a-5-trillion-company-2025/</link><description>Nvidia breifly crossed the $5 trillion mark in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-said-nvidia-would-be-a-5-trillion-company-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Will Intel Stock Keep Soaring as Q4 Earnings Approach?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-keep-soaring-q4-010400690.html</link><description>Analyst upgrades and bullish commentary have piled up ahead of Intel's Q4 results on Thursday, January 22, pushing its stock to a two-year high of $50 a share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-keep-soaring-q4-010400690.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What Nvidia didn’t show at CES, and whether AMD should care</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/what-nvidia-didnt-show-at-ces-and-whether-amd-should-care</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) stock is trading about 3.39% lower near $180, at the time of writing, Tuesday afternoon, Jan. 20, according to Yahoo Finance. And as if the worries about the AI bubble weren’t enough, other big tech stocks, including Apple, Meta, Microsoft, Tesla, and Google, are also down, as ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/what-nvidia-didnt-show-at-ces-and-whether-amd-should-care</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway May Sell Stock in Kraft Heinz, Filing States</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-sell-kraft-heinz-087ba49f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway  may sell shares from its $7.8 billion equity stake in  Kraft Heinz  according to a prospectus filed late Tuesday with the Securities and Exchange Commission.  The front page of the prospectus says that Berkshire, which received the Kraft Heinz equity as part of a merger of Kraft and Heinz in 2015, may “offer to sell from time to time” shares from that stake.  Berkshire now holds a 27.5% stake in the food company—or 325.4 million shares.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-sell-kraft-heinz-087ba49f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Rivian Automotive Stock While It's Below $17?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/should-you-buy-rivian-automotive-stock-while-its-b/</link><description>The upstart electric vehicle maker is failing to generate a profit, but has large ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/should-you-buy-rivian-automotive-stock-while-its-b/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] One-time hot insurance tech Ethos poised to be first tech IPO of the year</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-time-hot-insurance-tech-233632607.html</link><description>Ethos was backed by a who's who of VCs and celebs through 2021. It is currently profitable, it says.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-time-hot-insurance-tech-233632607.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks slide after Trump threatens European allies with tariffs</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stock-market-down-january-20-trump-greenland/?ftag=YHF4eb9d17</link><description>U.S. stocks sank on Tuesday following President Trump's weekend threats to impose tariffs on some NATO trading partners.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stock-market-down-january-20-trump-greenland/?ftag=YHF4eb9d17</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] With Gemini Powering Apple's Siri, Alphabet Could Soon Be the Undisputed AI Leader</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/with-gemini-powering-apples-siri-alphabet-could-so/</link><description>The new collaboration gives Alphabet the AI momentum it needs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/with-gemini-powering-apples-siri-alphabet-could-so/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] What International Business Machines (IBM)'s New Enterprise AI Platform Push Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/international-business-machines-ibm-enterprise-231130146.html</link><description>IBM recently announced several AI initiatives, including IBM Enterprise Advantage for building internal AI platforms, an enterprise-grade agentic AI collaboration with e&amp;amp;, and GRAMMY IQ built with watsonx to power interactive fan experiences using historical Recording Academy data. Together, these moves highlight IBM's push to embed governed, agentic AI across both mission-critical enterprise workflows and high-visibility consumer-facing experiences, underscoring its ambition to be an...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/international-business-machines-ibm-enterprise-231130146.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 20: Intel Rises on Analyst Upgrades Highlighting AI Server CPU Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-intel-rises-on-analyst-upgrades-highlighting-ai-server-cpu-growth/</link><description>On Jan. 20, 2026, Wall Street's AI server growth upgrades put this legacy chipmaker's turnaround narrative under a brighter spotlight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-intel-rises-on-analyst-upgrades-highlighting-ai-server-cpu-growth/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Why CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Dipped More Than Broader Market Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-dipped-225504568.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) closed at $442.73 in the latest trading session, marking a -2.46% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-dipped-225504568.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Sees a More Significant Dip Than Broader Market: Some Facts to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-sees-more-significant-225504162.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) reached $322 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a -2.42% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-sees-more-significant-225504162.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here's Why Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) Fell More Than Broader Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-alphabet-inc-goog-225504674.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) concluded the recent trading session at $322.16, signifying a -2.48% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-alphabet-inc-goog-225504674.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) Stock Moves -1.98%: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-stock-moves-225503787.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) settling at $206.21, representing a -1.98% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-stock-moves-225503787.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Falls More Steeply Than Broader Market: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-falls-more-steeply-225502967.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, Nvidia (NVDA) closed at $178.18, indicating a -4.32% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-falls-more-steeply-225502967.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM (IBM) Suffers a Larger Drop Than the General Market: Key Insights</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-suffers-larger-drop-225501587.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, IBM (IBM) closed at $291.35, indicating a -4.68% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-suffers-larger-drop-225501587.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] YouTube TV faces growing backlash as users demand key upgrade</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/entertainment/youtube-tv-faces-growing-backlash-as-users-demand-live-button-upgrade</link><description>No streaming platform can satisfy every subscriber's needs. That’s why many households subscribe to multiple services simultaneously, while others switch between platforms seasonally. Each one has something slightly different, but enough to make users want to have it as well. For ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/entertainment/youtube-tv-faces-growing-backlash-as-users-demand-live-button-upgrade</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Tumbles As Trump's Greenland Threats Spur Sell The U.S. Trade; Tesla, Nvidia Skid</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-greenland-davos-speech-nvidia-tesla-netflix-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq broke key support on Trump's Greenland push with his Davos speech on tap. Nvidia, Tesla and other megacaps slumped. Netflix fell late.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-greenland-davos-speech-nvidia-tesla-netflix-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 20: Markets Slide After Trump Tariff Threats Spark Selloff</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-markets-slide-after-trump-tariff-threats-spark-selloff/</link><description>On Jan. 20, 2026, Trump's Greenland-linked tariff threats rattled megacap tech as geopolitics, not earnings, drove Wall Street's pullback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-markets-slide-after-trump-tariff-threats-spark-selloff/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Serve Robotics Buying Fellow Nvidia-Powered Bot Maker</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/serve-robotics-buying-diligent-robotics/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Serve Robotics has agreed to acquire Diligent Robotics, a maker of robot assistants for the health care industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/serve-robotics-buying-diligent-robotics/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA ascends to Aa1 status at Moody’s on AI infrastructure dominance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ascends-aa1-status-moody-223046310.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Moody’s Ratings has elevated NVIDIA Corporation’s (NASDAQ:NVDA) senior unsecured rating to Aa1, marking a significant milestone in the chipmaker’s financial evolution. The credit agency simultaneously maintained a positive outlook, suggesting further upward mobility is possible as the firm solidifies its grip on the artificial intelligence sector. The upgrade is underpinned by NVIDIA’s formidable presence within the rapidly expanding data center ecosystem and its robust liquidit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ascends-aa1-status-moody-223046310.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Bold Predictions to Start 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/3-bold-predictions-to-start-2026/</link><description>It's the most wonderful time of the year. No, not the holdiays. We're talking about making stock investing predictions for 2026. This week, the Fools each give their 2026 hot takes on specific parts of the stock market along with three stocks on their radar</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/3-bold-predictions-to-start-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Valuation Check After Cooling Momentum And Conflicting Fair Value Signals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-valuation-check-cooling-220835113.html</link><description>Recent performance snapshot NVIDIA (NVDA) has seen mixed share performance recently, with a 0.4% decline over the past day, a small gain over the past week, and low single digit positive returns over the past month and past 3 months. Over longer periods, NVIDIA shows a 1.4% negative return year to date but a 32.3% total return over the past year and a very large multi year total return over 3 and 5 years. This helps frame how current moves sit against its longer run record. See our latest...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-valuation-check-cooling-220835113.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] xAI Just Raised $20 Billion. Can Grok Keep Up With Google Gemini?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/xai-just-raised-20-billion-can-grok-keep-up-with-google-gemini/</link><description>Elon Musk’s xAI rang in the new year by raising $20 billion in its latest funding round. Undoubtedly, as the AI race intensifies and the use cases of the technology become more apparent (Claude Code and its Cowork agent seem to have sparked a panic in software), perhaps we’ll begin to hear a bit less ... xAI Just Raised $20 Billion. Can Grok Keep Up With Google Gemini?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/xai-just-raised-20-billion-can-grok-keep-up-with-google-gemini/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Wall Street sees worst day since October after Trump tariff threats</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-sees-worst-day-215357399.html</link><description>Sell-off hits US stocks in first trading day since president threatened tariffs against eight countries</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-sees-worst-day-215357399.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Big Tech Stocks Hit Hard in Selloff</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/big-tech-stocks-hit-hard-in-selloff-AwsGv5yl8bMI2P5nHa2x?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>All seven of the giant tech stocks known as the Magnificent Seven fell at least 1% Tuesday. That was the first time that has happened since October.    Microsoft was down the least, about 1.2%, with Tesla and Nvidia down 4% or more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/big-tech-stocks-hit-hard-in-selloff-AwsGv5yl8bMI2P5nHa2x?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Serve Robotics is acquiring a hospital assistant robot company</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-serve-robotics-acquiring-hospital-213000945.html</link><description>Serve Robotics is expanding beyond its sidewalk delivery roots by acquiring Diligent Robotics, which makes a hospital assistant bot named Moxi.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-serve-robotics-acquiring-hospital-213000945.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] FTC Appeals Loss in Antitrust Case Against Meta</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/ftc-appeals-loss-in-antitrust-case-against-meta-BcOxWhUDjwnqKQUqiGBG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Federal Trade Commission said Tuesday it would appeal a court's decision last year dismissing its claims that Facebook-owner Meta Platforms built an illegal monopoly through the acquisitions of Instagram and WhatsApp.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/ftc-appeals-loss-in-antitrust-case-against-meta-BcOxWhUDjwnqKQUqiGBG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Does Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A) Still Offer Value After Its Strong Multi‑Year Run?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-berkshire-hathaway-brk-still-210816051.html</link><description>This article examines what Berkshire Hathaway's current share price may be implying about the business for investors wondering if the shares still offer value after years of strong compounding. The stock recently closed at US$740,750, with returns of 5.4% over 1 year and 57.3% and 112.1% across the last 3 and 5 years. Shorter term moves have been quieter, with a 0.2% decline over 7 days, 0.7% over 30 days, and 0.5% year to date. Recent attention has focused on Berkshire Hathaway as a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-berkshire-hathaway-brk-still-210816051.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] RBC Initiates Astera Labs (ALAB) at Outperform, Sees Retimer Growth and Scorpio Ramp Driving Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-astera-labs-alab-210610190.html</link><description>Astera Labs, Inc. (NASDAQ:ALAB) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage of the stock with an Outperform rating and a price target of $225. The analyst sees robust retimer growth and Scorpio-P switch ramp for ALAB, which they believe should support […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-astera-labs-alab-210610190.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel Stock Is Already Up 19% in 2026. Can Q4 Earnings Propel It Higher in 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37135682/intel-stock-is-already-up-19-in-2026-can-q4-earnings-propel-it-higher-in-2026</link><description>Intel’s Q4 earnings could determine the stock’s next move. Here's what to watch when the company reports on Jan. 22.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37135682/intel-stock-is-already-up-19-in-2026-can-q4-earnings-propel-it-higher-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Morgan Stanley Initiates Nebius (NBIS) at Equalweight, Flags Long-Term AI Infrastructure Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-initiates-nebius-nbis-210437033.html</link><description>Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 15, Morgan Stanley analyst Josh Baer initiated coverage on the stock with an “Equalweight” rating and a price target of $126. The analyst highlights AI infrastructure scale-up potential for NBS, urging investors to focus on long-term metrics for […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-initiates-nebius-nbis-210437033.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow plummets 800 points, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq sink over 2% as Trump's Greenland threats clobber stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-plummets-800-points-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-over-2-as-trumps-greenland-threats-clobber-stocks-210046255.html</link><description>The market is on edge over Trump's threatened tariffs over Greenland and a Japan-led global bond sell-off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-plummets-800-points-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-over-2-as-trumps-greenland-threats-clobber-stocks-210046255.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] RBC Sees Multiple Secular and Cyclical Drivers Supporting ASML Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-sees-multiple-secular-cyclical-205413330.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage on the stock with an Outperform rating and a price target of $1,550. The analyst sees multiple secular and cyclical growth drivers across ASML’s memory and logic businesses. According to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-sees-multiple-secular-cyclical-205413330.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] RBC Initiates Intel (INTC) at Sector Perform, Awaits Proof on Margins and Foundry Execution</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-intel-intc-sector-205239771.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage of the stock with a “Sector Perform” rating and a price target of $50. Firm analysts see strategic progress for Intel, but are awaiting proof of execution on gross margins and […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-intel-intc-sector-205239771.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Could Buying Tesla Stock Today Set You Up for Life?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/could-buying-tesla-stock-today-set-you-up-for-life/</link><description>Tesla has delivered 30x gains over the last 10 years. Can it do even better in the next decade?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/could-buying-tesla-stock-today-set-you-up-for-life/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Wall Street Analyst Just Revealed Her Top Artificial Intelligence (AI) Chip Stock for 2026 -- and It's Not Nvidia. Here's Why I Think She Could Be Right.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-wall-street-analyst-just-revealed-her-top-artifi/</link><description>Beth Kindig of the I/O Fund is calling for Micron to have a big year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-wall-street-analyst-just-revealed-her-top-artifi/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia's place in AI, Apple downgrade, JPMorgan cautious on oil</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidias-place-ai-apple-downgrade-204706772.html</link><description>Market Domination Host Josh Lipton and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma track several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including Nvidia's (NVDA) position in the AI ecosystem, Citi analysts cutting their price target on Apple (AAPL), and JPMorgan's cautious outlook on the oil industry (CL=F, BZ=F). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidias-place-ai-apple-downgrade-204706772.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Himax, Broadcom, KLA Corporation, Impinj, and Qualcomm Stocks Trade Down, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/himax-broadcom-kla-corporation-impinj-204554608.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Europe over control of Greenland sparked a broad, risk-off mood in asset markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/himax-broadcom-kla-corporation-impinj-204554608.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Nvidia (NVDA) Stock Is Down Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-nvda-stock-down-204542603.html</link><description>Shares of leading designer of graphics chips Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) fell 3.8% in the afternoon session after rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Europe over control of Greenland sparked a broad, risk-off mood in asset markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-nvda-stock-down-204542603.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] RBC Initiates Nvidia (NVDA) at Outperform, Cites $500B+ AI Backlog and Ecosystem Dominance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-nvidia-nvda-outperform-203907038.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage on the stock with an “Outperform” rating and a price target of $240. He sees robust AI demand for Nvidia, a backlog exceeding $500 billion, and ecosystem dominance. The analyst said […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-nvidia-nvda-outperform-203907038.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon (AMZN) Seen as One of the Strongest AI Bull Cases Heading Into 2026, Bernstein Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-amzn-seen-one-strongest-203638058.html</link><description>Amazon.com, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 15, Bernstein SocGen Group analyst Nikhil Devnani reiterated an “Outperform” rating on the stock with a $300.00 price target. The analyst sees 2026 as the strongest bull case story ever since the pandemic, citing a palatable entry point for […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-amzn-seen-one-strongest-203638058.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 2 Clear AI Winners Investors Should Buy for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-clear-ai-winners-investors-should-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor and Micron Technology are at the core of AI investing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-clear-ai-winners-investors-should-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bill Gates Recalls Warren Buffett Treating Him to McDonald's — Then Paying With Coupons</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bill-gates-recalls-warren-buffett-203108944.html</link><description>Being rich doesn't always mean acting rich. Just ask the two men who've taken turns wearing the crown of richest person alive. Bill Gates and Warren Buffett could afford just about any lunch they wanted—but when they grabbed McDonald's in Hong Kong, one of them reached into his pocket and pulled out coupons. Spoiler: it wasn't Bill Gates. Gates told the story himself in a letter he wrote to Buffett in 2017. "Remember the laugh we had when we traveled together to Hong Kong and decided to get lunc</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bill-gates-recalls-warren-buffett-203108944.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] What Happened to Viking Therapeutics in 2025, And Is it a Buy for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/what-happened-to-viking-therapeutics-in-2025-and-i/</link><description>Despite a challenging year, the company has a lot to look forward to in the coming years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/what-happened-to-viking-therapeutics-in-2025-and-i/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Navitas Semiconductor (NVTS) Deepens AI Data Center Ties With Nvidia 800V Platform Is The Story Shifting?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/navitas-semiconductor-nvts-deepens-ai-200951299.html</link><description>In mid-January 2026, Navitas Semiconductor’s CEO Chris Allexandre presented at the 28th Annual Needham Growth Conference in New York, outlining the company’s latest power semiconductor initiatives. This appearance comes as Navitas pivots toward higher‑power gallium nitride and silicon carbide chips for AI data centers, including work aligned with Nvidia’s next‑generation 800V architecture. We’ll now examine how this renewed emphasis on AI data center partnerships, particularly around...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/navitas-semiconductor-nvts-deepens-ai-200951299.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is Oral Wegovy a Game Changer for Novo Nordisk?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oral-wegovy-a-game-changer-for-novo-nordisk/</link><description>The past couple of years have been challenging for the company. But this could be the beginning of a new chapter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oral-wegovy-a-game-changer-for-novo-nordisk/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cantor Fitzgerald Assumes Coverage of Reddit (RDDT), Highlights the Company’s 120M Daily Users</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cantor-fitzgerald-assumes-coverage-reddit-195631010.html</link><description>Reddit Inc. (NYSE:RDDT) ranks among the 10 best new stocks to buy in Ray Dalio’s portfolio. On January 8, Cantor Fitzgerald began coverage of Reddit Inc. (NYSE:RDDT) with a Neutral rating and a $240 price target. The firm emphasized Reddit’s solid standing as a prominent digital media platform, with around 120 million daily active users, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cantor-fitzgerald-assumes-coverage-reddit-195631010.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google-backed AI drug discovery startup Isomorphic Labs delays clinical trial timeline</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-backed-ai-drug-discovery-195423147.html</link><description>Isomorphic Labs, which uses artificial ​intelligence for drug discovery, ‌expects to have its first ‌clinical trials by the end of 2026, founder and CEO Demis Hassabis ⁠said on ‌Tuesday.  Hassabis had said last year the company would have AI-designed drugs in clinical trials by ⁠the end of ​2025.  Isomorphic was ​founded in 2021 as a spin-off from Alphabet's ‍AI ⁠research subsidiary, Google DeepMind, which is headed by ⁠Hassabis.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-backed-ai-drug-discovery-195423147.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BofA Analysts Highlight Uber’s (UBER) Autonomous Vehicle Potential</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-analysts-highlight-uber-uber-195232615.html</link><description>Uber Technologies, Inc. (NYSE:UBER) ranks among the most active blue chip stocks to buy now. On January 6, BofA Securities reaffirmed its Buy rating on Uber Technologies, Inc. (NYSE:UBER) with a $119 price target, noting the company’s key position in the autonomous vehicle (AV) sector. The firm sees NVIDIA’s autonomous vehicle activities as crucial to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-analysts-highlight-uber-uber-195232615.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] I Predicted Alphabet Would Be the Best-Performing "Magnificent 7" Stock in 2025. Here Are the Main Reasons Why It Actually Happened.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-predicted-alphabet-would-be-the-best-performing/</link><description>Alphabet's stock was up more than 65% in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-predicted-alphabet-would-be-the-best-performing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] ‘I’m Also Very Nervous’ TSMC CEO C.C. Wei says on AI Demand. Here’s the $56 Billion ‘Disaster’ Taiwan Semi Wants to Avoid in 2026.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37134548/im-also-very-nervous-tsmc-ceo-c-c-wei-says-on-ai-demand-heres-the-56-billion-disaster-taiwan-semi-wants-to-avoid-in-2026</link><description>As TSMC ramps up spending, this article explores why CEO C.C. Wei is closely monitoring AI demand and the $56 billion ‘disaster’ the company is determined to avoid in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37134548/im-also-very-nervous-tsmc-ceo-c-c-wei-says-on-ai-demand-heres-the-56-billion-disaster-taiwan-semi-wants-to-avoid-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave (CRWV) Partners With NVIDIA for AI Cloud Growth, Truist Initiates Coverage</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-partners-nvidia-ai-193926991.html</link><description>CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) ranks among the 10 best new stocks to buy in Ray Dalio’s portfolio. On January 6, Truist Securities initiated coverage of CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) with a Hold rating and a $84 price target. According to the firm, the company continues to maintain a solid partnership with NVIDIA, which Truist considers critical to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-partners-nvidia-ai-193926991.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google DeepMind’s Partnership With Boston Dynamics Might Have Kicked Off the Humanoid Robot Race</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/google-deepminds-partnership-with-boston-dynamics-might-have-kicked-off-the-humanoid-robot-race/</link><description>CES 2026 has come and gone, and while there was certainly a slew of fantastic showcases, I’d argue that one of the biggest developments came from Boston Dynamics as it unveiled its partnership with Google DeepMind (whose parent company is Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOGL)). Undoubtedly, 2026 might be the year when physical AI and robotics finally start ... Google DeepMind’s Partnership With Boston Dynamics Might Have Kicked Off the Humanoid Robot Race</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/google-deepminds-partnership-with-boston-dynamics-might-have-kicked-off-the-humanoid-robot-race/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Goldman Sachs Raising Price Targets 10%+ on Tech and Financial Blue Chip Giants</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/goldman-sachs-raising-price-targets-10-on-tech-and-financial-blue-chip-giants/</link><description>Goldman Sachs has raised price targets on these three blue-chip giants, including a top-performing Magnificent 7 stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/goldman-sachs-raising-price-targets-10-on-tech-and-financial-blue-chip-giants/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Stock Is Getting Cheaper. When Will the Company Resume Buybacks?</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-buybacks-greg-abel-valuation-6560a5ce?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Greg Abel faces pressure to signal confidence with buybacks as Berkshire trades at a lower multiple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-buybacks-greg-abel-valuation-6560a5ce?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] HSBC starts SAP at Hold, says stock valuation already reflects cloud growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-starts-sap-hold-says-191520359.html</link><description>Investing.com -- HSBC started coverage of SAP at Hold, saying the software group’s strong fundamentals and cloud-driven growth are already reflected in the share price, hence leaving limited upside and some downside to consensus expectations. U.S. listed shares are down 3%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-starts-sap-hold-says-191520359.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Streaming captures nearly half of U.S. TV viewing in December</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/streaming-captures-nearly-half-u-190038441.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Streaming services captured nearly half of all U.S. television viewership in December, powered by Christmas Day NFL games on Netflix and its highly anticipated final season of "Stranger Things."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to a report Tuesday by audience measurement firm Nielsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its monthly report, The Gauge, Nielsen said&amp;amp;nbsp;streaming cemented its dominance over broadcast and cable with a record 47.5% of total TV viewing in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Christmas Day alone, streaming commanded 54% of all TV viewership, the largest single-day share ever recorded by the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google's YouTube accounted for more than 12.5% of all TV viewing last month, representing the largest audience share for a streaming service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix viewership was up 10% from November, with "Stranger Things" December's most-watched streaming title.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nielsen said broadcast accounted for roughly 21% of TV viewership in December, while cable had a 20% share.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data reflects the ongoing transformation of the television industry, as viewers increasingly gravitate toward on-demand content and live sports migrate to digital platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift is driving consolidation in the sector, with Netflix bidding nearly $83 billion to acquire Warner Bros. Discovery's studio and streaming assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/streaming-captures-nearly-half-u-190038441.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq sink as Trump tariff threats and bond sell-off shake Wall Street</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-as-trump-tariff-threats-and-bond-sell-off-shake-wall-street-184742836.html</link><description>The market is on edge over Trump's threatened tariffs over Greenland and a Japan-led global bond sell-off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-as-trump-tariff-threats-and-bond-sell-off-shake-wall-street-184742836.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Are These 2 Dividend Stocks Bargains Yet?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/are-these-2-dividend-stocks-bargains-yet/</link><description>With increased volatility could come an opportunity to pick up a steady dividend stock at a slightly lower price and perhaps a few more basis points of yield. In any case, this piece will concentrate on two dividend-paying blue chips that are starting to look cheap. Though it might be too soon to label them ... Are These 2 Dividend Stocks Bargains Yet?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/are-these-2-dividend-stocks-bargains-yet/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Chinese AI companies are six months behind the West, says DeepMind CEO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinese-ai-companies-six-months-183944584.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Google DeepMind CEO Demis Hassabis stated that Chinese artificial intelligence companies remain approximately six months behind leading Western laboratories in terms of frontier AI technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinese-ai-companies-six-months-183944584.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Hidden Tradeoffs Between Dividend Income and Total Return</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/the-hidden-tradeoffs-between-dividend-income-and-total-return/</link><description>Dividend investing and total return investing are often presented as competing philosophies, each with its own set of loyal advocates who dismiss the other as missing the point. Dividend investors are going to argue that cash flow matters more than any kind of paper gains. Separately, total return investors will counter that focusing on yield ... The Hidden Tradeoffs Between Dividend Income and Total Return</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/the-hidden-tradeoffs-between-dividend-income-and-total-return/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Expands Regional Cloud Footprint</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-expands-regional-cloud-footprint-182239959.html</link><description>CrowdStrike launches local cloud infrastructure in Saudi Arabia, India, and the UAE to meet residency rules.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-expands-regional-cloud-footprint-182239959.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia, Tesla, and Amazon Lead Tech Stocks Fall on Tuesday</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-tesla-amazon-lead-tech-182103985.html</link><description>AI Stocks Retreat With the Market. What Tariffs and Earnings Mean Next</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-tesla-amazon-lead-tech-182103985.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Intel Stock Is Climbing Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-stock-climbing-today-182057570.html</link><description>INTC Climbs After HSBC and Seaport Upgrades; Foundry Business Gains Attention</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-stock-climbing-today-182057570.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Richtech Robotics Stock Popped Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/why-richtech-robotics-stock-popped-today/</link><description>Richtech is growing revenue on its humanoid robot business. Will it ever earn a profit?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/why-richtech-robotics-stock-popped-today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Anthropic CEO warns as Nvidia gains US approval to sell H200s to China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-ceo-warns-nvidia-gains-182020189.html</link><description>Dario Amodei says allowing H200 chip exports to China carries national security risks as the Trump administration eases restrictions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-ceo-warns-nvidia-gains-182020189.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Advanced Micro Devices Shares Are Climbing Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-advanced-micro-devices-shares-181941723.html</link><description>Meta Platforms Chooses AMD Over Google for AI Deployment</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-advanced-micro-devices-shares-181941723.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Macquarie Capital Completes Rare $1 Billion Risk Transfer Deal</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/macquarie-capital-completes-rare-1-181938805.html</link><description>Non-bank lender executes significant risk transfer tied to high-yield loans, with Alvarez &amp;amp; Marsal advising, sources say.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/macquarie-capital-completes-rare-1-181938805.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Rise of AI Factories | VRT Stock, NVT Stock, MOD Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</link><description>Summary: To ring in 2026, our 24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are counting down 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. The second trend the two have discussed is the rise of AI factories – a new generation of massive data centers designed to manufacture intelligence at industrial scale. ... 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Rise of AI Factories | VRT Stock, NVT Stock, MOD Stock</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Why CrowdStrike (CRWD) Stock Is Down Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-crwd-stock-down-180039096.html</link><description>Shares of cybersecurity platform provider CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) fell 1.9% in the afternoon session after geopolitical tensions between the United States and the European Union escalated, sparking fears of a renewed trade war.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-crwd-stock-down-180039096.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Pegasystems and Cadence Design Systems Shares Are Falling, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pegasystems-cadence-design-systems-shares-175059783.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after geopolitical tensions between the United States and the European Union escalated, sparking fears of a renewed trade war.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pegasystems-cadence-design-systems-shares-175059783.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] WEBTOON, Pitney Bowes, IBM, DXC, and First Advantage Shares Plummet, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/webtoon-pitney-bowes-ibm-dxc-173545341.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after geopolitical tensions between the United States and the European Union escalated, sparking fears of a renewed trade war.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/webtoon-pitney-bowes-ibm-dxc-173545341.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Tesla Stock Dips as Market Worries Mount -- Musk Highlights AI Chip Plans</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-stock-dips-market-worries-173253922.html</link><description>Tesla AI5 Chip Nears Completion; Shares Drift Lower</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-stock-dips-market-worries-173253922.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Gavin Newsom Built His Political Career With Billionaire Backing — Now California Is Preparing To Hit That Same Wealth Class With A Massive New Tax</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gavin-newsom-built-political-career-173108041.html</link><description>Gavin Newsom's (D-Calif.) rise from a Getty-backed entrepreneur to California governor now collides with a proposed billionaire wealth tax he calls "bad economics" and has vowed to defeat. A Governor Shaped By Wealth — And By Struggle Newsom's first major business success came in the early 1990s with PlumpJack, a San Francisco wine shop launched with financial backing from Gordon Getty, an oil heir and longtime family friend. Getty and his family later invested in Newsom's expanding portfolio of</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gavin-newsom-built-political-career-173108041.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Upgraded by HSBC and Seaport Ahead of Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-upgraded-hsbc-seaport-ahead-173019996.html</link><description>Analysts cite stronger server demand and improving foundry outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-upgraded-hsbc-seaport-ahead-173019996.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Teradyne vs. KLAC: Which AI Infrastructure Stock Is the Better Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teradyne-vs-klac-ai-infrastructure-171100485.html</link><description>Teradyne rides on AI test demand, but KLAC's process control and advanced packaging momentum point to stronger upside in the AI infrastructure race.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teradyne-vs-klac-ai-infrastructure-171100485.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia and 19 Other Tech Stocks to Buy on the Dip</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tech-stocks-buy-dip-nvidia-20-eb7da4c6?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tariff fears are hitting tech shares, but analysts say profits and AI trends make this pullback a buying opportunity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tech-stocks-buy-dip-nvidia-20-eb7da4c6?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Why Nebius Stock Is Tumbling Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nebius-stock-tumbling-today-164822302.html</link><description>NBIS Stock Reacts to Global Tariff News Ahead of Earnings</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nebius-stock-tumbling-today-164822302.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft Stock at $600 or $400? Here’s What You Should Bet On</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/microsoft-stock-at-600-or-400-heres-what-you-should-bet-on/</link><description>Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) has been sliding since October despite the company posting strong results. It is down over 16% since the start of November, and the slide looks to be getting worse, even though there isn’t a scare of any kind. This is rather puzzling, as Microsoft is a key part of the AI buildout and ... Microsoft Stock at $600 or $400? Here’s What You Should Bet On</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/microsoft-stock-at-600-or-400-heres-what-you-should-bet-on/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What Is One of the Best Tech Stocks to Hold for the Next 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/one-best-tech-stocks-hold-next-10-years/</link><description>This tech juggernaut is building multiple revenue streams to monetize its AI technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/one-best-tech-stocks-hold-next-10-years/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Gemini Usage Doubles in Five Months</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-gemini-usage-doubles-five-163703262.html</link><description>Rising demand highlights growing momentum in Google's AI business.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-gemini-usage-doubles-five-163703262.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia, Tesla lead tech stocks lower as Trump trade war threats rattle market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-tesla-lead-tech-stocks-lower-as-trump-trade-war-threats-rattle-market-162928073.html</link><description>Tech stocks led broader market declines as investors grew skittish over geopolitical tensions and fears of an AI bubble continued.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-tesla-lead-tech-stocks-lower-as-trump-trade-war-threats-rattle-market-162928073.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer States “Given How Competitive That World Is, Intel’s Actual Earnings May Not Be Big Enough”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-states-given-competitive-160247848.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s game plan for this week. Cramer highlighted that the stock has been performing quite well after the CEO change, as he remarked: “After close, Intel reports. This stock’s been flying ever since Lip-Bu Tan came in as CEO. Under his leadership, Intel’s started to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-states-given-competitive-160247848.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] MDB vs. SNOW: Which Data Platform Stock is the Better Buy Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mdb-vs-snow-data-platform-155500859.html</link><description>MongoDB holds an edge over Snowflake through architectural advantages for AI deployment. Strong Atlas contribution and partner ecosystem support growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mdb-vs-snow-data-platform-155500859.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] UBER Stock Price Decreases 9% in 3 Months: Should You Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-stock-price-decreases-9-155500017.html</link><description>UBER shares decline 8.8% in three months on robotaxi fears, but strong bookings and strategic growth may signal a buying opportunity for long-term investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-stock-price-decreases-9-155500017.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Stock Jumps On Robust AI Chip Demand. Is It Time to Sell or Double Up on the Stock?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-stock-jumps-on/</link><description>TSMC continues to turn in strong results, driven by demand for AI chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-stock-jumps-on/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Falls. ‘The Honeymoon Is Over for AI.’</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-346dc649?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  stock was dropping early on Tuesday, hit both by wider market jitters over President Donald Trump’s drive to acquire Greenland and doubts about where the artificial-intelligence boom goes from here.  Nvidia shares were down 2.9% at $180.84 in early trading Tuesday, while the  has fallen 1.1%, and the  has declined 1%.  The move was broadly line with the wider market: Technology stocks are out of favor as investors flee to haven assets such as gold.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-346dc649?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple will ship millions of $2,000 foldable iPhones this year: Citi</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-will-ship-millions-of-2000-foldable-iphones-this-year-citi-153849468.html</link><description>Citi thinks Apple will be all in on a foldable iPhone — and soon.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-will-ship-millions-of-2000-foldable-iphones-this-year-citi-153849468.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Can IBM's Agentic AI Collaboration With e&amp; Boost Its Global Lead?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-agentic-ai-collaboration-e-153600941.html</link><description>International Business Machines teams up with e&amp;amp; to launch enterprise-grade agentic AI for compliance, policy, and risk, powered by watsonx Orchestrate.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-agentic-ai-collaboration-e-153600941.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] 4 Top-Ranked Technology Stocks Set to Beat Q4 Earnings Expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-top-ranked-technology-stocks-153500407.html</link><description>Here, we have picked four technology stocks, SNDK, APH, ASML and GLW, which are likely to pull off earnings surprises this earnings season.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/4-top-ranked-technology-stocks-153500407.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Overlooked AI Chip Stock That Could Outperform Nvidia in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/overlooked-ai-chip-stock-outperform-nvidia/</link><description>Micron looks poised to outperform in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/overlooked-ai-chip-stock-outperform-nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm Holdings Stock is Down 43%. It’s an Underrated Play on Physical AI</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/arm-holdings-stock-is-down-43-its-an-underrated-play-on-physical-ai/</link><description>The tech and AI trade has grown a bit chppier in recent years, in some places more than others. Of course, the semiconductor stocks have been blasting off in recent weeks (led by the memory chip makers and the semiconductor equipment plays), with the momentum showing few signs of slowing down. But not every AI ... Arm Holdings Stock is Down 43%. It’s an Underrated Play on Physical AI</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/arm-holdings-stock-is-down-43-its-an-underrated-play-on-physical-ai/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017333.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017333.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] America’s Biggest Tech Stocks Lead Tuesday’s Sell-Off as Trump's Greenland Rhetoric Rattles Markets</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/america-biggest-tech-stocks-lead-tuesday-selloff-as-trump-greenland-rhetoric-rattles-markets-11888430</link><description>Big tech stocks led markets lower Tuesday amid a broad market sell-off after Trump over the weekend threatened new tariffs on a number of European countries unless the U.S. is allowed to acquire Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/america-biggest-tech-stocks-lead-tuesday-selloff-as-trump-greenland-rhetoric-rattles-markets-11888430</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dropbox, Inc. (DBX): A Bear Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dropbox-inc-dbx-bear-case-152313254.html</link><description>We came across a bearish thesis on Dropbox, Inc. on Inwood’s Substack’s Substack by Inwood Capital. In this article, we will summarize the bears’ thesis on DBX. Dropbox, Inc.’s share was trading at $26.75 as of January 13th. DBX’s trailing and forward P/E were 15.20 and 8.89 respectively according to Yahoo Finance. Dropbox, Inc. provides a content collaboration platform […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dropbox-inc-dbx-bear-case-152313254.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] AMAT vs. ASML: Which Semiconductor Equipment Stock is a Better Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amat-vs-asml-semiconductor-equipment-152100758.html</link><description>Applied Materials' expanding HBM, NAND and advanced packaging tools contrast with ASML Holding's EUV-led shift in semiconductor patterning.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amat-vs-asml-semiconductor-equipment-152100758.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI startup Humans&amp; raises $480 million at $4.5 billion valuation in seed round</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-startup-humans-raises-480-151839506.html</link><description>AI startup Humans&amp;amp;, founded by former OpenAI, Alphabet and xAI researchers, has raised $480 million ​in a seed financing round, which values the company ‌at $4.48 billion, it said on Tuesday.  The outsized seed round highlights intense investor interest ‌in next-generation AI labs founded by veteran researchers as companies race to build systems that go beyond chatbots and agentic tools.  The round was led by Ron Conway's SV Angel and co-founder Georges Harik, ⁠while Nvidia, Jeff Bezos, ‌Alphabet's VC arm, GV, among other venture capital investors, also participated.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-startup-humans-raises-480-151839506.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Recursion Pharmaceuticals, Inc. (RXRX): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recursion-pharmaceuticals-inc-rxrx-bull-151420534.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on Recursion Pharmaceuticals, Inc. on r/stocks by Antique-Reference585. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on RXRX. Recursion Pharmaceuticals, Inc.’s share was trading at $4.67 as of January 16th. Recursion Pharmaceuticals, Inc. operates as a clinical-stage biotechnology company, engages in the decoding biology and chemistry by integrating technological innovations across biology, chemistry, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recursion-pharmaceuticals-inc-rxrx-bull-151420534.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] World stocks sink, gold hits high on escalating trade war fears</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asian-markets-sink-silver-hits-030106953.html</link><description>World stock markets lost ground on Tuesday, while precious metals hit fresh peaks on fears of a US-EU trade war fuelled by Donald Trump's tariff threat over opposition to his ambitions to grab Greenland, which has stoked volatility."Overall, this is a manmade crisis, and the continued sell off on Tuesday suggests that US threats to Greenland and their effects on financial markets could have further to go if the situation does not deescalate soon," Brooks opined. </description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asian-markets-sink-silver-hits-030106953.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Streaming captures nearly half of US TV viewing in December on 'Stranger Things' boost</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/tv/articles/streaming-captures-nearly-half-us-150828740.html</link><description>Jan 20 (Reuters) - Streaming services captured nearly half of all television viewership in the U.S. in December, powered by Netflix's Christmas Day NFL games and the highly anticipated final season of</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/tv/articles/streaming-captures-nearly-half-us-150828740.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia Will Overtake Alphabet, Apple, and Microsoft to Become the World's Most Profitable Company by the End of 2027. Here's Why the "Magnificent Seven" Stock Is a Buy in January.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/nvidia-stock-overtake-alphabet-apple-microsoft/</link><description>Nvidia is already the most valuable company in the world, but it could soon become the most profitable, too.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/nvidia-stock-overtake-alphabet-apple-microsoft/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump's battle for Greenland: Why the stock market hates it all</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-battle-for-greenland-why-the-stock-market-hates-it-all-145802180.html</link><description>The market hates surprises, usually.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-battle-for-greenland-why-the-stock-market-hates-it-all-145802180.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] CRWD vs. CSCO: Which Cybersecurity Stock Has an Edge Right Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-vs-csco-cybersecurity-stock-145300801.html</link><description>Cisco Systems is gaining ground in cybersecurity with steadier growth and a cheaper valuation, while CrowdStrike faces slowing sales momentum.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwd-vs-csco-cybersecurity-stock-145300801.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Buy the pullback in this chip stock: Mizuho</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-pullback-chip-stock-mizuho-144951091.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Mizuho said in a note Tuesday that investors should take advantage of the recent slide in one chip stock, arguing that the market has become overly pessimistic about handset demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-pullback-chip-stock-mizuho-144951091.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stock Market News for Jan 20, 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-news-jan-20-143800331.html</link><description>U.S. stocks ended flat on Friday as investors weighed comments on geopolitics and the Fed from President Trump, as well as digested quarterly reports from some major companies, marking the start of the fourth-quarter earnings season.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-news-jan-20-143800331.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq sink as Trump tariff threats and bond sell-off rattle nerves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-as-trump-tariff-threats-and-bond-sell-off-rattle-nerves-235748444.html</link><description>The market is on edge over Trump's threatened tariffs over Greenland and a Japan-led global bond sell-off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-as-trump-tariff-threats-and-bond-sell-off-rattle-nerves-235748444.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Inventec Says Nvidia H200 Chip Approval Stalled in China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inventec-says-nvidia-h200-chip-142416640.html</link><description>Delay underscores ongoing U.S.-China technology tensions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inventec-says-nvidia-h200-chip-142416640.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Wedbush Calls Tech Selloff a Buying Chance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wedbush-calls-tech-selloff-buying-142320260.html</link><description>Tariff noise seen as short-term market pressure</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wedbush-calls-tech-selloff-buying-142320260.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Morgan Stanley upgrades EU chip sector to overweight and highlights top-rated stocks</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-overweight-eu-chip-stocks-141641185.html</link><description>Morgan Stanley has upgraded its view on the European semiconductor sector to "overweight" and highlighted three top-rated stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-overweight-eu-chip-stocks-141641185.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Investors’ Confidence Boosted Alphabet (GOOG) in Q4</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-confidence-boosted-alphabet-goog-141331638.html</link><description>Fred Alger Management, an investment management company, released its “Alger Spectra Fund” fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The US equity market ended the fourth quarter on a strong note, with the S&amp;amp;P surging 2.7%, maintaining its steady upward momentum. Investors’ optimism was supported by better-than-expected corporate earnings, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-confidence-boosted-alphabet-goog-141331638.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Is It Too Late To Consider Lam Research (LRCX) After A 176% One Year Surge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-lam-research-lrcx-141136631.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Lam Research is still reasonably priced after its run, this article will walk through what the current share price might be implying about value. The stock most recently closed at US$222.96, with returns of 4.0% over 7 days, 29.4% over 30 days, 20.5% year to date, 176.1% over 1 year and 371.9% over 3 years, which naturally raises questions about growth potential and changing risk perceptions. Recent coverage has highlighted Lam Research in the context of strong...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-lam-research-lrcx-141136631.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Assessing ASML (ENXTAM:ASML) Valuation After Recent Share Price Volatility</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-asml-enxtam-asml-valuation-141031857.html</link><description>What ASML’s Recent Performance Tells Current Shareholders ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML) has drawn attention after a recent daily decline of about 4%, even as the stock shows positive returns over the past week, month and past 3 months. That mix of short term volatility and stronger recent performance is prompting investors to reassess what they are paying for the business today. See our latest analysis for ASML Holding. Zooming out, ASML’s recent 4% daily share price decline sits against a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-asml-enxtam-asml-valuation-141031857.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Group N.V. (NBIS) Slid Along with Broader Selloff of AI Infrastructure-Related Equities</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-n-v-nbis-135831985.html</link><description>Fred Alger Management, an investment management company, released its “Alger Small Cap Focus Fund” fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. The US equity market ended the fourth quarter on a strong note, with the S&amp;amp;P surging 2.7%, maintaining its steady upward momentum. Investors’ optimism was supported by better-than-expected corporate […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-n-v-nbis-135831985.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] The 'Sell America' Trade Is Real, Cohn Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/sell-america-trade-real-cohn-135236732.html</link><description>IBM Vice Chairman Gary Cohn says he is still optimistic about the US economy despite geopolitical tensions, citing high GDP growth as a major tailwind. But he does say the "Sell America" trade is real. He speaks on "Bloomberg Surveillance" at the 2026 World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/sell-america-trade-real-cohn-135236732.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Dives 700 Points On Trump Greenland Tariffs; Nvidia And Tesla Slide (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-greeland-tariffs-netflix-earnings-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dived 700 points Tuesday on Trump's Greenland tariff threats. Nvidia and Tesla sold off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-greeland-tariffs-netflix-earnings-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Beyond the Hype: Top ETFs to Buy as AI Shifts Into a Long-Term Growth Phase</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beyond-hype-top-etfs-buy-134900535.html</link><description>AI is entering a long-term growth phase in 2026, with $527B in capex driving a broadening bull market in AI ETFs like AIQ.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beyond-hype-top-etfs-buy-134900535.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is This Stock The Hidden AI Opportunity You’re Missing?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-this-stock-the-hidden-ai-opportunity-youre-missing/</link><description>The AI revolution has created obvious investment opportunities in semiconductor stocks like Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) and even those supplying the chipmakers like ASML (NASDAQ:ASML). But with the data center boom underway and hyperscalers like Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) and Amazon (NASDAQ:AMZN) committed to spending hundreds of billions on new facilities, investors may be overlooking a hidden investment opportunity ... Is This Stock The Hidden AI Opportunity You’re Missing?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-this-stock-the-hidden-ai-opportunity-youre-missing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Leads Declines Across the ‘Mag 7’. What’s Hitting Big Tech Stocks.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-meta-google-microsoft-stock-price-tariffs-39329a15?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Amazon.com  was the steepest decliner among the so-called Magnificent Seven stocks early on Tuesday.  The group of large technology companies were all falling as investors fled perceived riskier assets after President Donald Trump ramped up tariff threats against a number of European countries in his push for U.S. ownership of Greenland.  Amazon was down 3.1% in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-meta-google-microsoft-stock-price-tariffs-39329a15?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Predicted AI Stocks Would Power Stock Market Gains in 2025, and They Did. Here's What May Happen Next in 2026. (And It May Surprise You.)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-predicted-ai-stocks-would-power-stock-market-gai/</link><description>Could AI stocks continue to climb?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-predicted-ai-stocks-would-power-stock-market-gai/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] AI-Driven Demand Fuels TSM's Growth: Will It Meet 2026 Revenue Target?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-driven-demand-fuels-tsms-131800757.html</link><description>TSM's AI chip demand drove 35.9% revenue growth in 2025 and a 30% outlook for 2026 as 3nm and 5nm orders surge and global fabs expand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-driven-demand-fuels-tsms-131800757.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Which Pharma Stock Stands Taller Right Now: LLY or PFE?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pharma-stock-stands-taller-now-130800136.html</link><description>Eli Lilly's Mounjaro and Zepbound fuel rapid growth as new launches and an oral GLP-1 near approval shape its investment case against peers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pharma-stock-stands-taller-now-130800136.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] OpenAI Accuses Elon Musk Of 'Cherry-Picking' Evidence In Lawsuit, Says He Backed For-Profit Shift And Quit After Failing To Secure Control</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openai-accuses-elon-musk-cherry-130115381.html</link><description>On Friday, OpenAI stated that Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) and xAI CEO Elon Musk initially supported a for-profit structure but exited the company after negotiations broke down over control, rather than mission. OpenAI Says Musk Misrepresented Internal Records OpenAI pushed back against Musk's lawsuit, accusing the billionaire of selectively using internal documents to misrepresent the company's origins and its shift to a for-profit structure. In a detailed blog post, OpenAI said Musk agreed as earl</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openai-accuses-elon-musk-cherry-130115381.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cloud AI Update - Intuitive.ai and Matilda Cloud Join Forces to Transform Life Sciences</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cloud-ai-intuitive-ai-matilda-123755905.html</link><description>A recent strategic partnership between Intuitive.ai and Matilda Cloud has been formed to enhance AI and cloud modernization efforts within the Life Sciences sector. This collaboration aims to address challenges such as rising infrastructure costs and limited visibility into risk by providing actionable intelligence for rapid execution. Through this partnership, Life Sciences organizations gain compliance-ready insights into AI costs, security, and modernization pathways, enabling them to make...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cloud-ai-intuitive-ai-matilda-123755905.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This $2 Trillion Opportunity Could Send These Top Stocks Soaring</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-trillion-opportunity-send-these-stocks-soaring/</link><description>These companies could benefit enormously from the deeper integration of AI into consumer products.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-trillion-opportunity-send-these-stocks-soaring/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Steve Jobs' 1976 Paper Trail: Guess How Much the First-Ever Apple Check and His Boyhood Desk Are Fetching at 50 Years</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/steve-jobs-1976-paper-trail-123111451.html</link><description>Some of the rarest memorabilia from the early days of Apple Inc (NASDAQ:AAPL) and personal items belonging to co-founder and former CEO Steve Jobs are up for auction to celebrate the company's 50th anniversary. Just like other past Apple and Jobs memorabilia that has come up for sale, these rare pieces are generating strong interest and bids. Apple 50th Anniversary Auction RR Auctions is hosting an auction with top Apple memorabilia items and like past auctions in recent years, early checks in t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/steve-jobs-1976-paper-trail-123111451.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Netflix Results to Shine Light on Fundamentals Amid Warner Fight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-results-shine-light-fundamentals-111003588.html</link><description>Investors have been concerned about Netflix’s slowing flow of subscribers and the sustainability of its growth.  The issue sparked the worst selloff in the stock in more than three years after the company’s previous earnings report on Oct. 21.  At the time, Netflix was seen as a possible suitor for Warner Bros. Now that the deal is on the table at $82.7 billion, some investors are on edge and all the risks are amplified.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-results-shine-light-fundamentals-111003588.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML stock target lifted at UBS on ’too strong’ momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-stock-target-lifted-ubs-122027996.html</link><description>Investing.com -- ASML shares have further room to run, UBS analysts say, hiking the price target to €1,400 from €1,030 as they raise earnings estimates and argue that momentum across logic, memory, and China remains “too strong” to ignore.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-stock-target-lifted-ubs-122027996.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Could IonQ Become the Nvidia of Quantum Computing?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/could-ionq-become-the-nvidia-of-quantum-computing/</link><description>Nvidia's dominance in the accelerated computing realm is unheard of.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/could-ionq-become-the-nvidia-of-quantum-computing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Sequoia, Accel-backed Ethos Technologies eyes $1.3 billion valuation in US IPO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sequoia-accel-backed-ethos-technologies-121313998.html</link><description>Ethos Technologies, backed by venture capital firms Accel and Sequoia, said on Tuesday it was targeting ​a valuation of up to $1.26 billion in its U.S. ‌initial public offering, as the insurance IPO momentum extends into 2026.  The life insurance technology ‌company and some of its existing shareholders are seeking up to $210.5 million by selling 10.5 million shares priced between $18 and $20 apiece.  First-time share sales from insurance companies hit a 20-year high on Wall Street in ⁠2025 as investors flocked ‌to firms insulated from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sequoia-accel-backed-ethos-technologies-121313998.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Rigetti Computing Stock Soared 45.2% Last Year and Has Kept Gaining in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/why-rigetti-computing-stock-soared-452-last-year-a/</link><description>The quantum-computing stock continues to be highly volatile, but it has posted huge gains over the last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/why-rigetti-computing-stock-soared-452-last-year-a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 'Nobody Will Remember Tesla Ever Made A Car:' Tech Investor Says Optimus Could Become Elon Musk's Biggest Legacy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nobody-remember-tesla-ever-made-120107159.html</link><description>Jason Calacanis, tech investor and podcaster, said Tesla Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:TSLA) humanoid robot Optimus could overshadow the company's automotive legacy after a visit to its robotics facility. Visit To Tesla Optimus Lab On Thursday's episode of the All-In Podcast, Calacanis said he visited Tesla's Optimus lab with CEO Elon Musk two Sundays earlier at 10 a.m., where he saw Optimus 3 and watched teams of engineers at work. He made the remarks while speaking with Bob Sternfels, global managing partner</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nobody-remember-tesla-ever-made-120107159.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>