<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Stays Constructive on Cognex (CGNX) as Industrial Tech Demand Holds Up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-stays-constructive-cognex-cgnx-114958829.html</link><description>Cognex Corporation (NASDAQ:CGNX) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 12, Barclays trimmed its price target on Cognex Corporation (NASDAQ:CGNX) to $54 from $56, while keeping an Overweight rating on the stock. The move came as part of the firm’s broader 2026 outlook for industrial technology and distribution […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-stays-constructive-cognex-cgnx-114958829.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates First American Financial (FAF) in Broader Coverage Reset</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-first-american-financial-114754482.html</link><description>First American Financial Corporation (NYSE:FAF) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 6, Barclays slightly lowered its price target on First American Financial Corporation (NYSE:FAF) to $68 from $71, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The firm’s broader 2026 outlook suggests it still sees opportunity […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-first-american-financial-114754482.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] What Are the 3 Top Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks to Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/what-are-the-3-top-artificial-intelligence-stock/</link><description>AI chip stocks still have a lot of upside from here.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/what-are-the-3-top-artificial-intelligence-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 No-Brainer AI Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/3-no-brainer-ai-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>The AI race is still heating up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/3-no-brainer-ai-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Initiates Badger Meter (BMI) Coverage, Citing Valuation and Growth Concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-initiates-badger-meter-bmi-112352633.html</link><description>Badger Meter, Inc. (NYSE:BMI) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 7, Barclays analyst William Grippin launched coverage of Badger Meter, Inc. (NYSE:BMI) with an Underweight rating and a $157 price target. In his view, Badger is a “solid company with a difficult setup.” He argued that the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-initiates-badger-meter-bmi-112352633.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Oracle's Cash Is Vanishing — But Larry Ellison's Dividend Check Still Clears Tomorrow</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oracles-cash-vanishing-larry-ellisons-110121309.html</link><description>Oracle Corp (NYSE:ORCL) is torching cash to build its AI cloud—but it's still sending billions back to shareholders. That tension is becoming one of the most underappreciated capital allocation stories in Big Tech. On Friday, Oracle will pay out roughly $1.4 billion in dividends, even as analysts expect nearly $23 billion in cash burn this fiscal year. On paper, cutting the dividend looks logical. In reality, it's complicated. Larry Ellison’s Stake Raises The Bar For A Cut Co-founder and executi</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oracles-cash-vanishing-larry-ellisons-110121309.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Is Cadence Design Systems (NASDAQ:CDNS) A Risky Investment?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-nasdaq-cdns-110010098.html</link><description>Warren Buffett famously said, 'Volatility is far from synonymous with risk.' So it seems the smart money knows that...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-nasdaq-cdns-110010098.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] TD Cowen Trims Coty Inc. (COTY) Target Ahead of Q4, Keeps Hold Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/td-cowen-trims-coty-inc-104835503.html</link><description>Coty Inc. (NYSE:COTY) is among the overlooked penny stocks to invest in. On January 21, TD Cowen cut the price target on Coty Inc. (NYSE:COTY) to $3.40 from $3.50, and maintained a Hold rating, according to TheFly. This revision, suggesting upside potential of nearly 4%, was part of the firm’s Q4 preview, during which it […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/td-cowen-trims-coty-inc-104835503.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Alphabet Stock Before Feb. 4?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/should-you-buy-alphabet-stock-before-feb-4/</link><description>Alphabet has rocketed to the top of the artificial intelligence (AI) industry over the last few months.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/should-you-buy-alphabet-stock-before-feb-4/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Stock Is Quietly Becoming a Cornerstone of the Artificial Intelligence Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/stock-quietly-becoming-cornerstone-ai-micron/</link><description>Micron Technology's advanced memory chips are proving essential in the AI race.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/stock-quietly-becoming-cornerstone-ai-micron/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The 4 Best AI Stocks to Buy as Trillion-Dollar Tech Shapes a Once-in-a-Lifetime Investment Opportunity</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/4-best-ai-stocks-buy-once-in-lifetime-investment/</link><description>Robotaxis could revolutionize the transportation industry unlike any technology since the automobile was invented.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/4-best-ai-stocks-buy-once-in-lifetime-investment/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Is There An Opportunity With AstraZeneca PLC's (LON:AZN) 46% Undervaluation?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/opportunity-astrazeneca-plcs-lon-azn-092618452.html</link><description>Key Insights Using the 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity, AstraZeneca fair value estimate is UK£250 AstraZeneca's UK£136...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/opportunity-astrazeneca-plcs-lon-azn-092618452.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Poised to Approve Nvidia's H200 Chips for Import. Here's What It Means for Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/china-poised-to-approve-nvidias-h200-chips-for-imp/</link><description>This could be a major catalyst for the AI chipmaker.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/china-poised-to-approve-nvidias-h200-chips-for-imp/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Stock Could Outperform the "Magnificent Seven" by 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/prediction-this-ai-stock-could-outperform-the-magn/</link><description>IREN might be one of the biggest winners as gigawatts become a crucial AI bottleneck.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/prediction-this-ai-stock-could-outperform-the-magn/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2 AI Stocks to Buy Before They Soar to $20 Trillion, According to Wall Street Experts</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/2-ai-stocks-buy-before-soar-20-trillion-wall-stree/</link><description>Nvidia and Tesla could deliver monster returns for shareholders as the AI revolution continues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/2-ai-stocks-buy-before-soar-20-trillion-wall-stree/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Infrastructure Could Triple to $1.4 Trillion by 2030: Here's the Best Stock to Buy for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/ai-infrastructure-could-triple-to-14-trillion-by-2/</link><description>The data center boom continues to gain steam. There's one clear winner.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/ai-infrastructure-could-triple-to-14-trillion-by-2/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How Google’s TPU Assembly Shift Could Reshape Celestica’s Hyperscaler Exposure (TSX:CLS) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-tpu-assembly-shift-could-080829186.html</link><description>In recent days, reports that Google is shifting some tensor processing unit (TPU) server assembly work from Celestica to additional suppliers have raised questions about the company’s role in future AI infrastructure programs. Amid this customer-sourcing uncertainty, Celestica’s strong positioning in AI data center hardware and networking keeps attention firmly on how much hyperscaler demand it can retain and win. We’ll now examine how Google’s reported TPU server assembly shift shapes...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-tpu-assembly-shift-could-080829186.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 08:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang in Shanghai amid China regulatory headwinds</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-shanghai-054808546.html</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang is in Shanghai, a person briefed on the matter said ​on Saturday, as the U.S. chip giant faces fierce ‌competition from local rivals and scrutiny from Chinese authorities.  The timing of Huang's trip, ‌to kick off annual celebrations with Nvidia's China employees, is routine.  He is expected to attend an Nvidia party in Shanghai on Saturday before travelling to Beijing, Shenzhen and then Taiwan, another person with ⁠knowledge of the plans ‌said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-shanghai-054808546.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Legal AI giant Harvey acquires Hexus as competition heats up in legal tech</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-ai-giant-harvey-acquires-052722699.html</link><description>Hexus founder and CEO Sakshi Pratap, who previously held engineering roles at Walmart, Oracle, and Google, tells TechCrunch that her San Francisco-based team has already joined Harvey, while the startup's India-based engineers will come onboard once Harvey establishes a Bangalore office.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-ai-giant-harvey-acquires-052722699.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Assessing Whether Lam Research (LRCX) Still Offers Value After Strong Recent Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-whether-lam-research-lrcx-042146140.html</link><description>Lam Research stock performance snapshot Lam Research (LRCX) has seen mixed short term moves, with a 1 day return of about a 1.3% decline and a 7 day return of roughly a 2.3% decline, while longer horizons look very different. See our latest analysis for Lam Research. Despite the recent 1 day and 7 day share price pullback, Lam Research’s latest share price of $217.94 sits against a strong backdrop, with a 1 month share price return of 22.90% and a very large 1 year total shareholder return...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-whether-lam-research-lrcx-042146140.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] What Catalysts Are Shifting The Story For ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML)?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/catalysts-shifting-story-asml-holding-042024954.html</link><description>The latest update to ASML Holding has centered on a revised price target, reflecting a shift in how the market is framing the stock’s potential and risks. Without a specific prior or new target disclosed, the key story here is the reasoning behind this adjustment and what it suggests about expectations for the company. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of future changes in the ASML narrative as new targets and commentary emerge. Analyst Price Targets don't always capture the full...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/catalysts-shifting-story-asml-holding-042024954.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How To Earn $500 A Month From SLB Stock Ahead Of Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earn-500-month-slb-stock-033110187.html</link><description>SLB N.V. (NYSE:SLB) will release earnings for the fourth quarter before the opening bell on Friday, Jan. 23. Analysts expect the company to report fourth-quarter earnings of 74 cents per share. That's down from 92 cents per share in the year-ago period. The consensus estimate for SLB's quarterly revenue is $9.55 billion (it reported $9.28 billion last year), according to Benzinga Pro. On Wednesday, Stifel analyst Stephen Gengaro maintained SLB with a Buy rating and raised the price target from $</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earn-500-month-slb-stock-033110187.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] GE Aerospace Backlog Nears $190 Billion As Airlines Spend Big On Engine Upkeep</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ge-aerospace-backlog-nears-190-013133464.html</link><description>GE Aerospace (NYSE:GE) on Thursday reported strong fourth-quarter 2025 results, reflecting continued momentum across its businesses. It posted total revenue (GAAP) of $12.717 billion, up 18% year over year. Sales of $12.717 billion beat the $11.177 billion estimate, and adjusted EPS of $1.57 beat the $1.43 estimate. Continuing EPS (GAAP) was $2.31, up 32%, and adjusted EPS was $1.57, up 19%. Cash from operating activities was $2.096 billion, up 59%, and free cash flow was $1.760 billion, up 15%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ge-aerospace-backlog-nears-190-013133464.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Is It Time To Reassess IBM (IBM) After Its Recent Share Price Pullback?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-ibm-ibm-recent-011244357.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether International Business Machines (IBM) is still reasonably priced after its long run in tech, this article walks through what the current share price may be implying about value. IBM closed at US$292.44, with a 4.3% decline over the last 7 days and a 4.0% decline over the last 30 days, while its returns stand at 0.3% year to date, 33.5% over 1 year, 142.8% over 3 years and 216.2% over 5 years. These moves have come alongside continued attention on IBM's position...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-ibm-ibm-recent-011244357.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] A Winter Storm Is on Track to Hit Insurers. Why the Damage Could Be Huge.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/winter-storm-us-news-auto-insurance-progressive-eb23a9f0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A major winter storm advancing across the southern and eastern United States this weekend won’t just test municipal snow crews and utility companies’ gridlines.  With freezing temperatures, snow, sleet, and ice expected to sweep through millions of households, policyholders will likely file loss reports in the weeks and months ahead, ranging from auto accidents and property damage to burst pipes and roof collapses.  Although winter storms are often viewed as less severe weather events than hurricanes or earthquakes, they can lead to meaningful losses for residential and commercial property owners and impact automobiles and infrastructure across a broad swath of the country.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/winter-storm-us-news-auto-insurance-progressive-eb23a9f0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Overlooked Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Could Be a Long-Term Compounder</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/overlooked-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-asml/</link><description>This high-quality business, unfortunately, trades at a lofty valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/overlooked-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-asml/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Is Daiichi Sankyo (TSE:4568) Turning ENHERTU’s China Approval Into a Durable Oncology Moat?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/daiichi-sankyo-tse-4568-turning-002002430.html</link><description>Earlier this week, Daiichi Sankyo and AstraZeneca received approval in China for ENHERTU as the first HER2-directed antibody-drug conjugate for second-line treatment of HER2 positive metastatic gastric cancer, based on the DESTINY-Gastric04 phase 3 trial showing a survival benefit over ramucirumab plus paclitaxel. This decision opens access to ENHERTU in a country that accounts for more than one third of global gastric cancer cases, highlighting the importance of Daiichi Sankyo’s oncology...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/daiichi-sankyo-tse-4568-turning-002002430.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What Ultra Clean Holdings (UCTT)'s Rising AI Chip Supply-Chain Profile Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-rising-001840733.html</link><description>In the past week, Ultra Clean Holdings drew attention as enthusiasm around the AI chip supply chain lifted suppliers tied to advanced semiconductor manufacturing, following TSMC’s plans to ramp up spending on AI and high-performance chips. Because Ultra Clean provides specialized subsystems and ultra-high purity manufacturing services essential for leading-edge fabs, many investors now view it as a critical enabler of AI-related semiconductor production rather than just a traditional...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-rising-001840733.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Mag 7 earnings, Fed's rate decision: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mag-7-earnings-feds-rate-000012663.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come throughout next week, including a wide array of earnings results due out from major companies like Microsoft (MSFT), Meta Platforms (META), Apple (AAPL), Tesla (TSLA), and many more; and the Federal Reserve's latest interest rate decision followed by a press conference with chairman Jerome Powell. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mag-7-earnings-feds-rate-000012663.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Bubble or Sustainable Growth? Here Are 2 Healthcare Companies Harnessing AI for the Long Term.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/ai-bubble-growth-healthcare-stocks-bmy-isrg/</link><description>Artificial intelligence may be all the rage in the technology sector, but it's also having a huge impact on healthcare.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/ai-bubble-growth-healthcare-stocks-bmy-isrg/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Surprising Reason Nvidia Looks Recession-Proof in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/the-surprising-reason-nvidia-looks-recession-proof/</link><description>The AI leader is insulated from the machinations of the consumer-level economy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/the-surprising-reason-nvidia-looks-recession-proof/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 catalysts that could drive Nvidia stock higher in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/3-catalysts-could-drive-nvidia-230000225.html</link><description>The Chinese government tells tech companies to prep their Nvidia (NVDA) H200 chip orders, according to Bloomberg. Bernstein managing director and senior analyst Stacy Rasgon — who has a Buy rating on Nvidia — reacts to the headline and compares the supply-demand dynamic for chips in China. Catch Stacy Rasgon also weigh in on the leadership of Intel (INTC) CEO Lip-Bu Tan. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/3-catalysts-could-drive-nvidia-230000225.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway B (BRK.B) Stock Dips While Market Gains: Key Facts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-b-brk-b-224505646.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, Berkshire Hathaway B (BRK.B) closed at $478.97, indicating a -1.14% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-b-brk-b-224505646.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Stock Sinks As Market Gains: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-stock-sinks-224503485.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (LLY) closed at $1 in the latest trading session, marking a -2.12% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-stock-sinks-224503485.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Waymo Probed by US Safety Agency Over Austin School Bus Mishaps</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-probed-us-safety-agency-224442046.html</link><description>The National Transportation Safety Board will “examine the interaction between Waymo vehicles and school buses stopped for loading and unloading students,” the agency said in a social media post.  The issue had occurred about two dozen times as of earlier this month, according to the Austin Independent School District.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-probed-us-safety-agency-224442046.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 23: Intel's Weak Outlook Weighs on Dow While Nasdaq Edges Higher</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-s-weak-outlook-weighs-on-dow-while-nasdaq-edges-higher/</link><description>Intel's downbeat outlook knocked the Dow while strength in mega-cap and AI names kept the Nasdaq in the green, today, Jan. 23, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-s-weak-outlook-weighs-on-dow-while-nasdaq-edges-higher/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 23: Intel Plunges After Weak Outlook Highlights Supply Constraints and Foundry Losses</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-plunges-after-weak-outlook-highlights-supply-constraints-and-foundry-losses/</link><description>Today, Jan. 23, 2026, investors are weighing whether Intel’s supply snags and foundry losses threaten its AI data-center ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-plunges-after-weak-outlook-highlights-supply-constraints-and-foundry-losses/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Dethrones Apple As Taiwan Semiconductor's Largest Customer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dethrones-apple-taiwan-semiconductors-223132958.html</link><description>Nvidia Corp's (NASDAQ:NVDA) surge in artificial intelligence demand is reshaping the global semiconductor supply chain. Nvidia has overtaken Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd's (NYSE:TSM) largest customer. Nvidia chief Jensen Huang confirmed the change publicly for the first time during a recent podcast. Nvidia now ranks as Taiwan Semiconductor's biggest client—an outcome he suggested would please Taiwan Semiconductor founder Morris Chang. Don't Miss: Missed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dethrones-apple-taiwan-semiconductors-223132958.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 AI Infrastructure Stocks to Buy as the Market Heads Toward $1.4 Trillion by 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/3-ai-infrastructure-stocks-to-buy-as-the-market-he/</link><description>Nvidia, Equinix, and Digital Realty will profit from the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/3-ai-infrastructure-stocks-to-buy-as-the-market-he/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investing $13,000 in These 3 Stocks in 2020 Would Have Made You a Millionaire Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/investing-13000-in-these-3-stocks-in-2020-would-ha/</link><description>All three stocks have soared more than 1,400% since the start of the decade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/investing-13000-in-these-3-stocks-in-2020-would-ha/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Dow Jones Futures: Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, Apple Lead Earnings Wave After Whipsaw Trump Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings-wave-trump-week/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tesla, Microsoft, Meta and Apple lead an earnings wave after the stock market weathered whipsaw action from President Trump's moves</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings-wave-trump-week/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Earnings live: Intel stock plunges, with more Big Tech earnings from Apple, Microsoft, and Tesla ahead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-intel-stock-plunges-with-more-big-tech-earnings-from-apple-microsoft-and-tesla-ahead-213536730.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear in the week ahead, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-intel-stock-plunges-with-more-big-tech-earnings-from-apple-microsoft-and-tesla-ahead-213536730.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Cathie Wood Thinks AMD Will Challenge Nvidia This Year</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-cathie-wood-thinks-amd-will-challenge-nvidia/</link><description>Should investors be wary of AMD's cheaper data center GPUs?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-cathie-wood-thinks-amd-will-challenge-nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Energy Firms Backed by Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates Look to Go Public</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/energy-ai-gates-bezos-ipo-98cd8911?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Two novel energy companies just filed papers to go public, giving investors a chance to buy into trends that could reshape electricity generation in the coming decade—if they work.  Fervo, a geothermal energy company that generates electricity from underground heat, filed confidentially with the SEC to go public, according to Axios.  Fervo is one of the most talked-about clean energy companies in private markets, and just raised $462 million in a Series E fund-raising in December.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/energy-ai-gates-bezos-ipo-98cd8911?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500 cap volatile week with back-to-back weekly losses</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-cap-volatile-week-with-back-to-back-weekly-losses-210233078.html</link><description>Wall Street is faltering as it heads into the end of holiday shortened but rollercoaster week defined by Trump's moves on Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-cap-volatile-week-with-back-to-back-weekly-losses-210233078.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Baillie Gifford's Strategic Moves: Cloudflare Inc. Reduction by 23%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/baillie-giffords-strategic-moves-cloudflare-210021123.html</link><description>Exploring Baillie Gifford (Trades, Portfolio)'s Fourth Quarter 2025 Investment Adjustments</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/baillie-giffords-strategic-moves-cloudflare-210021123.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Terex, Caterpillar, Titan International, Ryder, and Littelfuse Shares Are Falling, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/terex-caterpillar-titan-international-ryder-205044687.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell as much as 0.7%, reflecting lingering uncertainty, and capping off a volatile week which saw stocks enjoy some relief as President Donald Trump reduced tensions with European allies by backing off his threat of imposing new tariffs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/terex-caterpillar-titan-international-ryder-205044687.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Top Stocks to Double Up on Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/top-stocks-to-double-up-on-right-now/</link><description>These stocks look like market-beaters over the next five years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/top-stocks-to-double-up-on-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Intel stock plunges as hopes for a 'clean' turnaround story meet reality</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-plunges-as-hopes-for-a-clean-turnaround-story-meet-reality-202949131.html</link><description>Intel stock plunged on Friday following the chipmaker's disappointing first quarter outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-plunges-as-hopes-for-a-clean-turnaround-story-meet-reality-202949131.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] These Two Charts Sum Up the AI Stock Rally in 2026</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/these-two-charts-sum-up-the-ai-stock-rally-in-2026-11891429</link><description>Artificial intelligence is once again fueling a scorching tech stock rally, but the rising tide is notably not lifting all boats.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/these-two-charts-sum-up-the-ai-stock-rally-in-2026-11891429</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel vs. TSMC: Can Intel Close the Gap?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-tsmc-intel-close-195400413.html</link><description>Intel stock is selling off following its earnings report, but is there more to this story?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-tsmc-intel-close-195400413.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Stock Plunges: Time To Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-stock-plunges-time-to-buy-the-dip/</link><description>Intel's guidance disappointed the market. Is the turnaround story still alive?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-stock-plunges-time-to-buy-the-dip/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 6 of My Top 10 Stocks for 2025 Increased by More Than 25%. Are They Still Buys Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/6-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-increased-by-more-t/</link><description>The market delivered a strong gain in 2025, but it was no match for these stock picks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/6-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-increased-by-more-t/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Ripple CEO Weighs In On Crypto Bill: 'We're So Close We Can't Give Up Now'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ripple-ceo-weighs-crypto-bill-193110821.html</link><description>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse on Thursday commented on the CLARITY Act, saying ” “we’re so close we can’t give up now” with regards to delayed crypto bill after Coinbase Global Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) withdrew support. Garlinghouse Defends The Bill Garlinghouse called...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ripple-ceo-weighs-crypto-bill-193110821.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 AI Stocks Make Excellent Long-Term Plays to Buy in January</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-ai-stocks-make-excellent-long-term-plays-to-buy/</link><description>The best AI stocks aren't always the hidden gems.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-ai-stocks-make-excellent-long-term-plays-to-buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tesla is a 'believe or not' religion, not a stock based on fundamentals: Robinhood exec</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-a-believe-or-not-religion-not-a-stock-based-on-fundamentals-robinhood-exec-192320023.html</link><description>As the EV giant prepares to report fourth quarter earnings on Jan. 28, retail sentiment remains detached from traditional valuation metrics.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-a-believe-or-not-religion-not-a-stock-based-on-fundamentals-robinhood-exec-192320023.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Investor Bets $100k On David v Goliath Matchup With Altimmune and Eli Lilly</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investor-bets-100k-on-david-v-goliath-matchup-with-altimmune-and-eli-lilly/</link><description>Shares of Altimmune (NASDAQ:ALT) surged 35.4% over the past week, coinciding with a dramatic shift in retail investor sentiment on Reddit. The clinical-stage biotech develops treatments for metabolic diseases and became one of the highest-rated stocks in social sentiment tracking after the FDA granted Breakthrough Therapy Designation for its lead drug pemvidutide on January 16. ... Investor Bets $100k On David v Goliath Matchup With Altimmune and Eli Lilly</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investor-bets-100k-on-david-v-goliath-matchup-with-altimmune-and-eli-lilly/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Could Define the Next Chapter of the Tech Market</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-next-tech-uipath/</link><description>UiPath could be set to define the AI agent market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-next-tech-uipath/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Stocks: Nvidia, Amgen Are Near Buy Points But This Longtime Loser Is Winning The Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stocks-nvidia-amgen-buy-points-procter-gamble/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan upgraded long-ailing consumer goods giant Procter &amp;amp; Gamble. Nvidia and Amgen are among several Dow Jones stocks near buy points.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stocks-nvidia-amgen-buy-points-procter-gamble/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Forget Quantum Computing Stock: Buy This Dividend‑Paying Quantum Pioneer, And Never Sell</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-quantum-computing-stock-buy-this-dividendpa/</link><description>IBM is a more balanced play on this secular trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-quantum-computing-stock-buy-this-dividendpa/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] TSLA: Tesla Stock Slides as Robotaxi Autonomy Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsla-tesla-stock-slides-robotaxi-181400328.html</link><description>Musk's No-Monitor Claim Faces Scrutiny; TSLA Investors Cautious</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsla-tesla-stock-slides-robotaxi-181400328.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Fei-Fei Li's World Labs Discusses Funding at $5 Billion Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fei-fei-lis-world-labs-181347025.html</link><description>AI startup World Labs is in talks to raise hundreds of millions, potentially adding about $500 million to its balance sheet.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fei-fei-lis-world-labs-181347025.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Applied Materials Stock Rises On Deutsche Bank Upgrade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-stock-rises-deutsche-181343411.html</link><description>Applied Materials Gains Analyst Support Amid Rising Memory Capex</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-stock-rises-deutsche-181343411.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Morgan Stanley Names ASML and ASMI as Top Pick Ahead of Q4 Results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-names-asml-asmi-181200829.html</link><description>ASML and ASMI Set to Surge as Morgan Stanley Calls Breakthrough Quarter Ahead</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-names-asml-asmi-181200829.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China--Nvidia Ties Appear Back On</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-nvidia-ties-appear-back-180834649.html</link><description>Officials move to restart H200 order preparations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-nvidia-ties-appear-back-180834649.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Should You Forget Eli Lilly and Buy These Unstoppable Stocks Instead?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-eli-lilly-buy-these-unstoppable-stock/</link><description>Eli Lilly's valuation has been driven higher by investor excitement around GLP-1 drugs, leaving other drugmakers languishing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-eli-lilly-buy-these-unstoppable-stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia, IBD Stock Of The Day, Looks To Finally Score China Sales</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/nvidia-stock-nvda-looks-to-score-china-sales/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia is the IBD Stock Of The Day as signs point to the AI chipmaker finally regaining access to the China market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/nvidia-stock-nvda-looks-to-score-china-sales/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] LRCX Likely to Beat Q2 Earnings Estimates: Should You Buy the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcx-likely-beat-q2-earnings-174700059.html</link><description>Lam Research's Q2 results are likely to reflect benefits from strong demand for AI chips and rising DRAM spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcx-likely-beat-q2-earnings-174700059.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investors Are Acting As if QQQ Is the Perfect Investment Right Now (And Maybe It Actually Is)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investors-are-acting-as-if-qqq-is-the-perfect-investment-right-now-and-maybe-it-actually-is/</link><description>Shares of the Invesco QQQ Trust (NASDAQ:QQQ) are having a good week, coinciding with a surge in retail investor sentiment on Reddit and X. The fund now carries a social sentiment score of 90, one of the highest readings tracked across all ETFs and stocks. This optimism centers on aggressive options positioning, particularly in the ... Investors Are Acting As if QQQ Is the Perfect Investment Right Now (And Maybe It Actually Is)</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investors-are-acting-as-if-qqq-is-the-perfect-investment-right-now-and-maybe-it-actually-is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Is Arm Holdings' High Valuation Testing Market Patience?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-high-valuation-testing-174400152.html</link><description>ARM faces pressure as a premium valuation demands near-term proof, with delayed licensing revenues and thin patience testing today's expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-high-valuation-testing-174400152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] NVIDIA (NVDA) Invests $150 million in Baseten</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-invests-150-million-173323306.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the Best Quantum Computing Stocks to Buy for 2026. On January 20, WSJ reported that the company is investing $150 million in Baseten, a startup that specializes in AI inference. Baseten has raised $300 million at a $5 billion valuation. This deal demonstrates NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA)’s aggressive push into […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-invests-150-million-173323306.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] At 22, He's Making $120K And Asks If He Should Buy A Duplex And Continue Living With His Parents. 'I Wanna Make My Money Work For Me'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/22-hes-making-120k-asks-173109029.html</link><description>A 22-year-old with a $120,000 annual salary turned to Reddit for advice on whether to buy a duplex while continuing to live rent-free with his parents. The poster has already maxed out his 401(k), saved $32,000 in cash, and built up $6,000 in an investment account. “I wanna make my money work for me and make more money,” he wrote on r/personalfinance recently. Redditors Say He’s Crushing It Financially Commenters were quick to praise his financial habits, with many encouraging him to stay with h</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/22-hes-making-120k-asks-173109029.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Signals H200 Purchase Preparations for Alibaba, Tencent, ByteDance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-signals-h200-purchase-preparations-172248794.html</link><description>Regulators gave in-principle approval for talks on Nvidia's H200 orders, with domestic chip buying encouraged as a condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-signals-h200-purchase-preparations-172248794.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel’s High-Flying Stock Wasn’t Priced for Reality</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-s-high-flying-stock-wasn-t-priced-for-reality-3Yfq0Pade7OOtd1bIAN2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel is on pace for its worst selloff in nearly 18 months.  Intel was down nearly 17% Friday.  The selloff came after the company’s fourth-quarter report made clear that Intel’s turnaround is still a work in progress.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-s-high-flying-stock-wasn-t-priced-for-reality-3Yfq0Pade7OOtd1bIAN2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Invests in Japan's Sakana AI to Boost Gemini</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-invests-japans-sakana-ai-170657856.html</link><description>Partnership aims to speed AI adoption in secure sectors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-invests-japans-sakana-ai-170657856.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:06:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Stock Rebounds As Weight-Loss Drug Battle Continues</title><link>https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/sector-leaders/eli-lilly-stock-lly-orforglipron-weight-loss-drugs/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Eli Lilly stock has been climbing back from a recent pullback and nearing a buy point. The drugmaker teamed up with Nvidia on a new project.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/sector-leaders/eli-lilly-stock-lly-orforglipron-weight-loss-drugs/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] This Semiconductor Stock Could Be at the Center of the Artificial Intelligence Spending Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/semiconductor-stock-center-ai-spending-micron/</link><description>Micron is in a prime position to benefit from the increasing demand for high-bandwidth memory.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/semiconductor-stock-center-ai-spending-micron/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Are You Looking for a Top Momentum Pick? Why Lloyds (LYG) is a Great Choice</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-top-momentum-pick-why-170002198.html</link><description>Does Lloyds (LYG) have what it takes to be a top stock pick for momentum investors? Let's find out.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-top-momentum-pick-why-170002198.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO to Visit China as AI Chip Sales Face Hurdles</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-visit-china-ai-164836352.html</link><description>Trip comes amid tighter U.S. export rules and slower China demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-visit-china-ai-164836352.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Could Owe $8B Under California's 5% Billionaire Tax — But Says 'I Haven't Thought About It Even Once'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-could-164619172.html</link><description>A proposed wealth tax in California has renewed questions about whether billionaires might reconsider where they live and companies choose to build. In a recent Bloomberg interview, Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang said he has not given the proposal any thought, even though the tax could cost him nearly $8 billion if it becomes law. "I haven't thought about it even once," Huang said. "We work in Silicon Valley because that's where the talent pool is." Don't Miss: Missed Nvidia and Tesla? RA</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-could-164619172.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Elon Musk kills Tesla Autopilot to push Full Self-Driving subscriptions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-kills-tesla-autopilot-to-push-full-self-driving-subscriptions-164159266.html</link><description>Tesla removed its Autopilot basic self-driving software as a standard feature in the US on new Model Y and Model 3 purchases as the company pushes its more advanced FSD (full-self driving) subscriptions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-kills-tesla-autopilot-to-push-full-self-driving-subscriptions-164159266.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Rises With China Set To Allow H200 Chip Orders; Is Nvidia A Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-ai-january-2026/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock rises, firming its footing at the 50-day moving average amid news that Chinese companies may order the H200 chip soon.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-ai-january-2026/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Should Board Shake-Up and Shareholder Rights Debate Require Action From Analog Devices (ADI) Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/board-shake-shareholder-rights-debate-161252579.html</link><description>Analog Devices has announced that long-serving director Susie Wee will retire from its board after the March 11, 2026 annual meeting, while appointing AI and robotics expert Yoky Matsuoka as an independent director and Corporate Development Committee member effective January 20, 2026. At the same time, the company faces a shareholder proposal from John Chevedden seeking easier rights to call special meetings, highlighting an active debate over how Analog Devices balances innovation-focused...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/board-shake-shareholder-rights-debate-161252579.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Judge Questions Google--Epic Antitrust Settlement Terms</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/judge-questions-google-epic-antitrust-161043395.html</link><description>Federal judge signals skepticism over proposed Google Play settlement, raising concerns about competition, remedies, and public interest impact.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/judge-questions-google-epic-antitrust-161043395.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The US Has Lost $2.4 Billion on Its Intel Stake Today</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-us-stake-loss-8b399820?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>One of Intel’s largest shareholders is the U.S. government, stemming from an August deal that converted some of Intel’s CHIPS Act subsidies into newly issued shares overseen by the Commerce Department.  With the stock down 15.2% in midday Friday trading, the government has taken a $2.4 billion loss on the day—but has still notched a 121% return overall since August.  Over two tranches, the Commerce Department bought 278 million shares of  Intel  through the end of last year, at a weighted average price of $20.73.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-us-stake-loss-8b399820?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Planet Labs Stock Fell This Week</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-planet-labs-stock-fell-this-week/</link><description>An insider sale and valuation concerns likely pushed Planet Labs stock down this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-planet-labs-stock-fell-this-week/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why a 15% Dividend Wasn’t Enough to Keep This $3.3 Million Position</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/23/why-a-15-dividend-wasn-t-enough-to-keep-this-usd3-3-million-position/</link><description>Trinity Capital provides venture debt and equipment financing to growth-stage tech companies seeking non-dilutive capital solutions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/23/why-a-15-dividend-wasn-t-enough-to-keep-this-usd3-3-million-position/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar, e.l.f. Beauty, Starbucks: Top Analyst Calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/caterpillar-e-l-f-beauty-154527369.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma keeps track of several Wall Street analyst calls on top trending stocks, including calls around shares of Caterpillar (CAT), e.l.f. Beauty (ELF), and Starbucks (SBUX). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/caterpillar-e-l-f-beauty-154527369.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] One Climate ETF Holds 10.2% in NVIDIA but Zero Energy Stocks – How?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/one-climate-etf-holds-10-2-in-nvidia-but-zero-energy-stocks-how/</link><description>Most climate-focused ETFs require investors to choose between their values and their returns. iShares Paris-Aligned Climate Optimized MSCI USA ETF (NASDAQ:PABU) takes a different approach by keeping one foot in the growth trade while screening for climate alignment. The question is whether this middle ground delivers on either promise. What PABU Actually Does PABU tracks ... One Climate ETF Holds 10.2% in NVIDIA but Zero Energy Stocks – How?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/one-climate-etf-holds-10-2-in-nvidia-but-zero-energy-stocks-how/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Stocks to watch next week: Tesla, Meta, Microsoft, Apple and Lloyds</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-meta-microsoft-apple-lloyds-stocks-to-watch-153735797.html</link><description>Earnings preview of key companies reporting this week and what to look out for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-meta-microsoft-apple-lloyds-stocks-to-watch-153735797.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] VanEck Pharmaceutical Fund Bets Big on Weight-Loss Drug Market Approaching $150 Billion</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/vaneck-pharmaceutical-fund-bets-big-on-weight-loss-drug-market-approaching-150-billion/</link><description>The VanEck Pharmaceutical ETF (NYSEARCA:PPH) has surged 26% over the past year, driven almost entirely by the weight-loss drug revolution. The fund’s concentrated bet on GLP-1 manufacturers makes this a call option on the market’s continued growth. Eli Lilly (NYSE:LLY) and Novo Nordisk (NYSE:NVO) combined represented nearly one-third of the ETF. If you believe the ... VanEck Pharmaceutical Fund Bets Big on Weight-Loss Drug Market Approaching $150 Billion</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/vaneck-pharmaceutical-fund-bets-big-on-weight-loss-drug-market-approaching-150-billion/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017784.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017784.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2 Monster Stocks to Hold for the Next 5 Years</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-monster-stocks-to-hold-for-the-next-5-years/</link><description>Nvidia and Broadcom are two top picks in the AI computing space.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-monster-stocks-to-hold-for-the-next-5-years/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] As Apple Builds Its New Campos Chatbot, Should You Buy, Sell, or Hold AAPL Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37197885/as-apple-builds-its-new-campos-chatbot-should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-aapl-stock</link><description>Apple is building a new chatbot that it plans to integrate into its operating system by the end of the year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37197885/as-apple-builds-its-new-campos-chatbot-should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-aapl-stock</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Boeing Stock Rips Higher Ahead Of Q4 Results; 3 Data Storage Stocks In Earnings Spotlight</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/boeing-stock-rips-higher-q4-earnings-data-storage-western-digital-seagate-sandisk-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Boeing stock has been on a tear ahead of its Q4 report as Wall Street bets on clearer skies ahead for the aerospace giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/earnings-preview/boeing-stock-rips-higher-q4-earnings-data-storage-western-digital-seagate-sandisk-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Outfront Media Surges 40% in One Year, Then Gets Cut Loose Despite 'Exceptional Performance'</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/23/outfront-media-surges-40-in-one-year-then-gets-cut-loose-despite-usd0-30-dividend/</link><description>This out-of-home advertising REIT connects brands with urban audiences through a broad network of billboard and transit assets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/23/outfront-media-surges-40-in-one-year-then-gets-cut-loose-despite-usd0-30-dividend/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Enabler Sparkles And Shines. Now Comes The Main Event.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-analysis/corning-stock-near-breakout-ai-infrastructure-collaboration-with-nvidia-broadcom-microsoft-drives-demand/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Collaboration on AI infrastructure with Nvidia, Broadcom and Microsoft has Corning stock set to light up a breakout.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-analysis/corning-stock-near-breakout-ai-infrastructure-collaboration-with-nvidia-broadcom-microsoft-drives-demand/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] WealthStack Roundup: NVIDIA AI Survey Results Indicate Growth, Challenges and Steady AI Budgets</title><link>https://www.wealthmanagement.com/artificial-intelligence/wealthstack-roundup-nvidia-ai-survey-results-indicate-growth-challenges-and-steady-ai-budgets</link><description>Financial services firms maintain AI spending while advisor prospecting platforms introduce enhanced capabilities and flexible pricing models.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wealthmanagement.com/artificial-intelligence/wealthstack-roundup-nvidia-ai-survey-results-indicate-growth-challenges-and-steady-ai-budgets</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] 'Jobs, jobs, jobs' the AI mantra as fears take back seat in Davos</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jobs-jobs-jobs-ai-mantra-150415222.html</link><description>Biting cold, political tensions and doubts about artificial intelligence did nothing to curb the enthusiasm of business leaders in Davos over technology's ability to create jobs.  Top executives at the World Economic Forum's annual meeting said that while jobs would disappear, new ones would spring up, with ​two telling Reuters that AI would be used as an excuse by companies which were planning layoffs anyway.  Flag bearers of AI's trillion-dollar expansion, including chip titan Jensen Huang, ‌said the technology heralded higher pay and more jobs for plumbers, electricians and steelworkers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jobs-jobs-jobs-ai-mantra-150415222.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:04:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Best Momentum Stock to Buy for January 23rd</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-momentum-stock-buy-january-150000740.html</link><description>BWMX, LRCX and APH made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) momentum stocks list on January 23, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-momentum-stock-buy-january-150000740.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] Lloyds set to see annual profits rise despite motor finance hit</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-set-see-annual-profits-144621947.html</link><description>Most analysts expect the lender to deliver a 7% rise in pre-tax profits for the year, with the City pencilling in £6.38 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/lloyds-set-see-annual-profits-144621947.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls In Wake Of Greenland Deal Rally; Intel Plunges After Earnings (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Friday following two days of gains from the Greenland deal rally. Intel plunged on earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet upgraded, Micron initiated: Wall Street’s top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-upgraded-micron-initiated-wall-144146903.html</link><description>The most talked about and market moving research calls around Wall Street are now in one place. Here are today’s research calls that investors need to know, as compiled by The Fly.Top 5 Upgrades: Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper decisions Stay ahead of the market with the latest news and analysis and maximize your portfolio's potential Raymond James upgraded Alphabet (GOOGL) to Strong Buy from Outperform with a price tar</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-upgraded-micron-initiated-wall-144146903.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia stock pops on H200 China reports, Capital One buys Brex</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-stock-pops-h200-china-144013159.html</link><description>Morning Brief host Julie Hyman and Yahoo Finance Markets and Data Editor Jared Blikre track several of Friday's top trending stock tickers, including Nvidia (NVDA); Capital One (COF); Brex (BREX.PVT); and airline stocks, such as Delta (DAL), American (AAL), United (UAL), JetBlue (JBLU), Alaska (ALK), and Southwest (LUV). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-stock-pops-h200-china-144013159.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix price target lowered to $110 from $141 at Argus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-price-target-lowered-110-143626289.html</link><description>Argus lowered the firm’s price target on Netflix (NFLX) to $110 from $141 but keeps a Buy rating on the shares. The company’s agreement to acquire Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD) is undoubtedly a bold move although shares have been punished in the aftermath as the market sees risk in Netflix getting involved in a bidding war with Paramount Skydance (PSKY) as well as around regulatory antitrust concerns, not to mention the potential for political interference, the analyst tells investors in a resear</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-price-target-lowered-110-143626289.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel stock sinks as company's Q1 outlook falls short of Wall Street expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-sinks-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143343615.html</link><description>Intel reported fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-sinks-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143343615.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Mizuho Says You Should Buy the Dip in Arm Stock. Why?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37196642/mizuho-says-you-should-buy-the-dip-in-arm-stock-why</link><description>Arm’s recent slump may look worrying, but Mizuho says the dip could be a compelling entry point for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37196642/mizuho-says-you-should-buy-the-dip-in-arm-stock-why</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Can Intel Live up to the Hype This Year and Shoot Through $100?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/can-intel-live-up-to-the-hype-this-year-and-shoot-through-100/</link><description>Investors rewarded Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) prematurely heading into earnings on January 22, but it ended up being a disappointment. Revenue and EPS both beat consensus, but it wasn’t enough to lift the mood. Revenue came in at $13.67 billion vs. the $13.39 consensus. Non-GAAP EPS came in at $0.15 vs. the $0.08 consensus. What disappointed the ... Can Intel Live up to the Hype This Year and Shoot Through $100?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/can-intel-live-up-to-the-hype-this-year-and-shoot-through-100/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Upper-Middle-Class Americans Share The Smartest Money Moves They Made Last Year.  'The Material Purchases Provide Us Less And Less Joy'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/upper-middle-class-americans-share-141612909.html</link><description>Reddit’s r/UpperMiddleFinance has become a surprisingly practical look at how people are managing their money in a high-cost, high-volatility world. From paying off mortgages and skipping luxury upgrades to doubling down on long-term investments, upper-middle-class Americans say these were their best financial decisions in the last year. Prioritizing Intentional Spending Over Flash One of the most recurring themes was a shift away from materialism and toward intentional living. One person summed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/upper-middle-class-americans-share-141612909.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Unlocking Q4 Potential of IBM (IBM): Exploring Wall Street Estimates for Key Metrics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unlocking-q4-potential-ibm-ibm-141509233.html</link><description>Evaluate the expected performance of IBM (IBM) for the quarter ended December 2025, looking beyond the conventional Wall Street top-and-bottom-line estimates and examining some of its key metrics for better insight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unlocking-q4-potential-ibm-ibm-141509233.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Stay Ahead of the Game With Lam Research (LRCX) Q2 Earnings: Wall Street's Insights on Key Metrics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stay-ahead-game-lam-research-141506142.html</link><description>Evaluate the expected performance of Lam Research (LRCX) for the quarter ended December 2025, looking beyond the conventional Wall Street top-and-bottom-line estimates and examining some of its key metrics for better insight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stay-ahead-game-lam-research-141506142.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google’s Making a Splash in AI Shopping. Why It’s a Massive Deal</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/googles-making-a-splash-in-ai-shopping-why-its-a-massive-deal/</link><description>Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOGL) has been the best of the Magnificent Seven for a reason. Whether we’re talking about the strength of its latest Gemini launch or all the new ways where Google could put its AI to work, it’s hard to be bearish about the firm, especially as investors look far beyond just search to the ... Google’s Making a Splash in AI Shopping. Why It’s a Massive Deal</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/googles-making-a-splash-in-ai-shopping-why-its-a-massive-deal/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Bruised Tech Stocks on the Fast Track to AGI</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-bruised-tech-stocks-on-the-fast-track-to-agi/</link><description>The race to achieve artificial general intelligence (AGI) is on, and the race might be closer than investors realize. Of course, it’s up for debate as to how long it’ll take for true AGI to be achieved. Some of the bigger bulls think it could happen in as little as a few years, while others ... 2 Bruised Tech Stocks on the Fast Track to AGI</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-bruised-tech-stocks-on-the-fast-track-to-agi/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Novo's Wegovy pill hits 18,410 US prescriptions in encouraging debut week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/novos-wegovy-pill-tracks-18-123235063.html</link><description>By Sriparna Roy Jan 23 (Reuters) - Novo Nordisk's Wegovy pill was prescribed 18,410 times in the U.S. in the first full week after its launch in an encouraging start to the oral weight-loss drug race,</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/novos-wegovy-pill-tracks-18-123235063.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Is Most-Watched Stock Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) Worth Betting on Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-snowflake-inc-140005638.html</link><description>Snowflake (SNOW) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately. So, it is worth exploring what lies ahead for the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-snowflake-inc-140005638.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike (CRWD) Is a Trending Stock: Facts to Know Before Betting on It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-trending-stock-facts-140005624.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Therefore, it is wise to be aware of the facts that can impact the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-trending-stock-facts-140005624.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here is What to Know Beyond Why Alphabet Inc. (GOOGL) is a Trending Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/know-beyond-why-alphabet-inc-140005960.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Therefore, it is wise to be aware of the facts that can impact the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/know-beyond-why-alphabet-inc-140005960.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel shares tumble as supply chain snarls hamper turnaround</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-shares-tumble-supply-chain-135036641.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Intel shares plunged 12% on Friday (January 23).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors sold off after the company struggled to meet strong AI demand for data center chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It blamed that on supply constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm had also forecast quarterly revenue and profit below market estimates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market watchers were disappointed as many had bet on Intel's turnaround.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm is a latecomer to the AI boom and has finally enjoyed a demand surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers want its traditional server chips which are used alongside AI processors in data centers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investor interest also grew due to investments in the firm from the U.S. government, Softbank and Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intel's stock outpaced most semiconductor firms last year with an 84% gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It extended its rally into this year - and was up close to half this month so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the company couldn't keep up with the demand surge even as it runs factories at capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also warned a spike in memory chip prices could hurt sales in the PC market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its new "Panther Lake" PC chips were expected to spark a comeback after years of market share losses to AMD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The memory chip surge is driven by growing AI demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Intel said it expects available memory supply to improve in the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That after hitting its lowest levels in the first quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/intel-shares-tumble-supply-chain-135036641.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should Investors Buy Nvidia Stock Before Feb. 25?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/should-investors-buy-nvidia-stock-before-feb-25/</link><description>Nvidia is coming off a strong year in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/should-investors-buy-nvidia-stock-before-feb-25/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here's How Eli Lilly's Oncology Drugs Are Poised Ahead of Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-eli-lillys-oncology-drugs-133600753.html</link><description>LLY's oncology drugs, led by Verzenio and new launches, are set to support upcoming Q4 results as investor focus broadens beyond GLP-1s.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-eli-lillys-oncology-drugs-133600753.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mike Novogratz Tells Anthony Scaramucci Crypto Industry Will Lose Stablecoin Rewards Battle To Banking Lobby: 'There'll Be A Compromise'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-novogratz-tells-anthony-scaramucci-133111201.html</link><description>Galaxy Digital Inc. (NASDAQ: GLXY) CEO Mike Novogratz said Wednesday that the cryptocurrency industry will have to eventually compromise on the controversial stablecoin rewards clause in the market structure bill. Will Crypto Lobby Lose Against Banking Lobby? In a discussion...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-novogratz-tells-anthony-scaramucci-133111201.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] If You Invested $1000 in Analog Devices 10 Years Ago, This Is How Much You'd Have Now</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invested-1000-analog-devices-10-133002008.html</link><description>Why investing for the long run, especially if you buy certain popular stocks, could reap huge rewards.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invested-1000-analog-devices-10-133002008.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Navitas (NVTS) Climbs 15.7% on Tech Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/navitas-nvts-climbs-15-7-131205107.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Delivering Double-Digit Gains Effortlessly; 4 Hit Highs. Navitas Semiconductor Corp. (NASDAQ:NVTS) was one of the best performers on Thursday. Navitas snapped a two-day losing streak on Thursday, jumping 15.68 percent to close at $11.29 apiece, as investor funds poured back into US markets after President Donald Trump withdrew a plan […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/navitas-nvts-climbs-15-7-131205107.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Is Artificial Intelligence (AI) Still in a Bubble? This Stock Suggests Otherwise.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/is-artificial-intelligence-ai-still-in-a-bubble-th/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing, also known as TSMC, is a reason to believe there is no AI bubble.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/is-artificial-intelligence-ai-still-in-a-bubble-th/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] He Spent Decades In Corporate Marketing, Now He's Delivering For Uber Eats. 'The Idea Of Starting Gig Work Came From My Therapist'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spent-decades-corporate-marketing-now-130117980.html</link><description>Jay Mandel spent years climbing the corporate ladder. He led global social media at MasterCard (NYSE:MA), worked at IBM (NYSE:IBM), taught college courses, and built a respectable career as a marketing consultant. But these days, you might spot him dropping off your Uber Eats order in New York City. Gig Work, Humility And A Reality Check “The idea of starting gig work came from my therapist,” Mandel told Business Insider recently. At first, he resisted. “I went to Columbia University. I have a m</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spent-decades-corporate-marketing-now-130117980.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jensen Huang Says His Parents Have The 'Most Expensive Car' In The World, But He Regrets Buying It For Them — Mom, Dad Aren't Thrilled Either</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jensen-huang-says-parents-most-130116722.html</link><description>On Wednesday, Nvidia Corp (NASDAQ:NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang revealed that selling shares after the company's 1999 IPO to buy his parents a Mercedes is his "only regret"—and that his parents aren't exactly thrilled about it either. Nvidia's Historic Returns Spotlighted The revelation came during a conversation with BlackRock (NASDAQ:BLK) CEO Larry Fink at the 56th Annual Meeting of the World Economic Forum. Fink praised Nvidia's long-term performance, noting that shareholders have seen annualized re</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jensen-huang-says-parents-most-130116722.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Made-For-The-AI-Moment Energy Play Outperforms Nvidia And Other Big Tech Names</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/the-new-america/bloom-energy-outperforming-nvidia-as-the-fuel-behind-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Renewable energy and power supplier Bloom Energy is up more than 70% in the young 2026 stock market and has galloped more than 480% in the last 12 months, outperforming Nvidia, Oracle and other Big Tech artificial intelligence plays.  Bloom's cells operate independently of traditional power grids.  In its earlier iterations Bloom Energy was viewed as a green energy company, with promising tech, but it struggled with the same skepticism from investors as other climate stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/the-new-america/bloom-energy-outperforming-nvidia-as-the-fuel-behind-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>