<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:00:12 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NVDA] Did NVIDIA’s US$2 Billion AI “Factory” Bet Just Shift CoreWeave’s (CRWV) Investment Narrative?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-nvidia-us-2-billion-070716049.html</link><description>NVIDIA and CoreWeave previously announced an expanded collaboration under which NVIDIA invested US$2 billion for new CoreWeave Class A shares at US$87.20 each, aiming to help CoreWeave build more than 5 gigawatts of AI “factories” by 2030 using NVIDIA’s accelerated computing platform. A distinctive aspect of the deal is NVIDIA’s plan to use its own balance sheet strength to support CoreWeave’s access to land, power and infrastructure, deepening the integration of CoreWeave’s AI-native...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/did-nvidia-us-2-billion-070716049.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Sees Defensive Appeal in PepsiCo (PEP) but Flags 2026 Risks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-sees-defensive-appeal-pepsico-065916369.html</link><description>PepsiCo, Inc. (NASDAQ:PEP) is included among the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Dividend Stocks to Buy in 2026. On January 16, Barclays raised PepsiCo, Inc. (NASDAQ:PEP) price target to $148 from $144 and kept an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The firm updated price targets across the consumer staples group as part of its Q4 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-sees-defensive-appeal-pepsico-065916369.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Year After the DeepSeek Crash, Markets Face a New Chinese AI Threat</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/deepseek-ai-gemini-chatgpt-stocks-ccde892c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company took down the artificial-intelligence market in early 2025. A year on, there is still reason to pay attention to Chinese AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/deepseek-ai-gemini-chatgpt-stocks-ccde892c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML rides Nvidia's coattails with lasers and huge chip 'printers'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145690.html</link><description>By Toby Sterling and Nathan Vifflin AMSTERDAM, Jan 27 (Reuters) - As artificial intelligence firms jostle for the Nvidia chips needed to power the AI boom, Dutch firm ASML has carved out a key niche</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145690.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ASML rides Nvidia's coattails with lasers and huge chip 'printers'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145161.html</link><description>As artificial intelligence firms jostle for the Nvidia chips needed to power the AI boom, Dutch firm ASML has carved out a key niche in the supply chain: building the laser-using machines needed ​to print them.  ASML, which counts Taiwan's TSMC and Intel amongst its clients, makes the huge precision machines needed to print the minuscule ‌circuitry onto silicon chips, dominating the market for the high-end microprocessors needed for AI.  The Veldhoven, Netherlands-based company has seen its shares double in value since last April and rise 25% ‌this month alone amid signs that its chipmaker clients are ramping up investment as a supply crunch pushes up chip prices.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-rides-nvidias-coattails-lasers-060145161.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Taxing tech: How do digital services levies differ across Europe?</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/business/2026/01/27/taxing-tech-how-do-digital-services-levies-differ-across-europe?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</link><description>Several European countries have introduced digital services taxes in recent years, while others are planning to do so. Given that the US hosts many global digital giants, these taxes have become a flashpoint for tariff threats.View on euronews</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.euronews.com/business/2026/01/27/taxing-tech-how-do-digital-services-levies-differ-across-europe?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Palantir and 5 More Stocks to Play Trump’s Plan to Invest in America</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-investments-government-palantir-apple-98f5e987?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>There is a change in the way the federal government operates that investors need to incorporate into their thinking.  If they do it right, they can get some gains by holding stocks that President Donald Trump might covet.  The White House often points out that Trump is a businessman and his second administration has demonstrated a willingness to do business directly with American companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-investments-government-palantir-apple-98f5e987?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Gold, silver pull off shock move big tech never saw coming</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/gold-silver-pull-off-shock-move-big-tech-never-saw-coming</link><description>Gold’s total market cap has “officially hit a record $35 trillion and silver’s market cap has hit a record $6 trillion,” according to The Kobeissi Letter's X post. That same post said “gold and silver are now worth 9 TIMES the market cap of Nvidia.” Everyone talks about Nvidia as the face of this ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/gold-silver-pull-off-shock-move-big-tech-never-saw-coming</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] India To Slash Tariffs On EU Car Imports To 40%: How This Move Could Affect Elon Musk's Tesla, Stellantis</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-slash-tariffs-eu-car-043124713.html</link><description>The Indian government has reportedly reached an agreement with the EU to lower tariffs on cars imported into India from the bloc from 110% to 40%. Tariffs Could Go Lower The two governments are expected to announce the deal this week, with the tariffs on imported cars further going down to 10% over time, Reuters reported on Sunday. The agreement would see an immediate reduction in tariffs by the Indian government on cars with an import price of around 15,000 Euros (approximately $17,700), anonym</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-slash-tariffs-eu-car-043124713.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] China’s Moonshot Unveils New AI Model Ahead of DeepSeek Release</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-moonshot-unveils-ai-model-042306788.html</link><description>The latest iteration of Moonshot’s Kimi can process text, images, and videos simultaneously from a single prompt, the company said in a statement on Tuesday, aligning with a trend toward so-called omni models pioneered by industry leaders like OpenAI and Alphabet Inc.’s Google.  Seeking to capitalize on reignited investor appetite for the country’s top-tier model makers, Moonshot last month raised $500 million from investors including Alibaba and IDG Capital at a post-money valuation of $4.3 billion, according to people familiar with the matter.  To satisfy pent-up investor demand, the company has kicked off new rounds of financing seeking a valuation of as much as $5 billion, one of the people said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-moonshot-unveils-ai-model-042306788.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Supply Deal In Crosshairs, Samsung Set To Start HBM4 Chip Production Next Month As Korean Giant Takes On SK Hynix: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-supply-deal-crosshairs-samsung-033108443.html</link><description>Samsung Electronics Co. (OTC:SSNLF) is reportedly preparing to begin production of its next-generation high-bandwidth memory chips as it seeks to supply Nvidia Corp (NASDAQ:NVDA) and narrow the gap with SK Hynix. Samsung Pushes Into Next-Gen AI Memory Samsung plans to start manufacturing HBM4 as early as next month and is expected to supply it to Nvidia, reported Reuters, citing a person familiar with the matter. The move marks a key step in Samsung's efforts to regain momentum in the high-bandw</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-supply-deal-crosshairs-samsung-033108443.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research Earnings: What To Look For From LRCX</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-earnings-look-lrcx-030612787.html</link><description>Semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) will be reporting results this Wednesday after market close. Here’s what you need to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-earnings-look-lrcx-030612787.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM (IBM) To Report Earnings Tomorrow: Here Is What To Expect</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-report-earnings-tomorrow-030237610.html</link><description>Technology and consulting giant IBM (NYSE:IBM) will be reporting earnings this Wednesday after the bell. Here’s what to look for.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-report-earnings-tomorrow-030237610.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Jim Cramer on Caterpillar: “In the Old Days, CAT Usually Went Down on Earnings, That’s Over”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-caterpillar-old-days-023320584.html</link><description>Caterpillar Inc. (NYSE:CAT) is one of the stocks in focus as Jim Cramer shared his weekly game plan. Cramer was bullish on the company stock as he remarked: We talk a lot about ancillary data center plays, which means Caterpillar, which has backup generators that are needed to keep these server farms running. In the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-caterpillar-old-days-023320584.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Jim Cramer Says Traders Don’t Understand International Business Machines’ Value</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-traders-don-023315320.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the stocks in focus as Jim Cramer shared his weekly game plan. Cramer said that the stock is going to receive the same market reaction as the previous quarter, as he commented: Last quarter, IBM reported a number that left the Street rankled, but the stock quickly […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-traders-don-023315320.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Does This New Chip Threaten Nvidia?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/does-this-new-chip-threaten-nvidia/</link><description>Microsoft's new Maia accelerator captures the growing competitive pressure on Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/does-this-new-chip-threaten-nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] What Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A)'s Potential Kraft Heinz Exit Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-potential-kraft-020923930.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, Kraft Heinz disclosed in an SEC filing that Berkshire Hathaway, now led by CEO Greg Abel, may sell up to its entire 325,442,152-share stake, potentially ending a decade-long investment Warren Buffett helped create through the 2015 Kraft–Heinz merger. This possible full exit marks a rare reversal of a high-profile Buffett-era deal and offers an early signal of how Abel may reshape Berkshire’s portfolio and capital allocation priorities. We’ll now examine how this...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-potential-kraft-020923930.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Is It Too Late To Consider KLA (KLAC) After Its 121% One Year Surge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-kla-klac-121-020804184.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether KLA's share price still makes sense after its huge run, this article will walk through what the current valuation might be telling you. KLA closed at US$1,543.03, with a 1.6% decline over the last 7 days, a 20.6% gain over the last 30 days, a 21.1% gain year to date, a 121.5% return over the past year, and a very large gain over 5 years. This article was prompted as part of ongoing coverage, and recent attention around KLA has focused on its role in the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-kla-klac-121-020804184.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) Pricing In Its Rapid 1 Year Share Price Surge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-nasdaqgs-asml-pricing-010924516.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether ASML Holding's current share price lines up with its underlying value, you are not alone. This article is designed to walk you through what the numbers suggest. With the stock at US$1,413.35 and returns of 4.0% over 7 days, 31.8% over 30 days, 21.4% year to date and 106.5% over 1 year, many investors are asking what is already priced in and what might still be on the table. Recent news coverage has focused on ASML Holding's central role in supplying advanced...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-nasdaqgs-asml-pricing-010924516.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Can This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Justify Its Valuation?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/can-this-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-justify/</link><description>Revenue growth rates may determine whether Palantir can sustain its current valuations in the long term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/can-this-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-justify/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google pays $68 million to settle claims its voice assistant spied on users</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-pays-68-million-settle-004335410.html</link><description>The tech giant did not admit wrongdoing in the case.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-pays-68-million-settle-004335410.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why CoreWeave Stock Climbed Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/why-coreweave-stock-is-up-today/</link><description>A partnership with an artificial intelligence (AI) titan should help to accelerate the cloud infrastructure specialist's growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/why-coreweave-stock-is-up-today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why CleanSpark Plunged Nearly 10% Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/why-cleanspark-plunged-nearly-10-today/</link><description>The transition from cryptocurrency mining to becoming full-fledged AI infrastructure companies hasn't been as smooth as many thought.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/why-cleanspark-plunged-nearly-10-today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI chip startup Ricursive hits $4B valuation two months after launch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-ricursive-hits-001315716.html</link><description>Ricursive joins Recursive and Unconventional AI in raising massive funds at multi-billion valuations out of the gate.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-ricursive-hits-001315716.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia's Stock Price Will Reach This Level By the End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/prediction-nvidia-will-reach-this-price/</link><description>Nvidia may have some catalysts ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/prediction-nvidia-will-reach-this-price/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Why Astrazeneca (AZN) Outpaced the Stock Market Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-astrazeneca-azn-outpaced-stock-231502251.html</link><description>Astrazeneca (AZN) closed at $94.23 in the latest trading session, marking a +1.38% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-astrazeneca-azn-outpaced-stock-231502251.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Bull Case For Tencent Holdings (SEHK:700) Could Change Following Fresh Access To Nvidia H200 Chips - Learn Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-tencent-holdings-sehk-231424182.html</link><description>In recent days, Chinese regulators granted in-principle approval for major tech firms including Tencent Holdings to prepare purchase orders for Nvidia’s H200 artificial intelligence chips, marking a shift from earlier uncertainty around access to advanced US-approved semiconductors. The move not only supports Tencent’s ability to build out high-performance AI infrastructure, but also underscores Beijing’s effort to balance foreign chip imports with encouragement of domestic alternatives in...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-tencent-holdings-sehk-231424182.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) Exceeds Market Returns: Some Facts to Consider</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-exceeds-225003193.html</link><description>In the closing of the recent trading day, Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) stood at $322, denoting a +1.15% move from the preceding trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-exceeds-225003193.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Things Alphabet Needs to Prove in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-things-alphabet-needs-to-prove-in-2026/</link><description>Alphabet had an excellent year in 2025, but 2026 is not yet a given.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-things-alphabet-needs-to-prove-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 26: CoreWeave Jumps After Nvidia Invests $2 Billion in AI Infrastructure Partnership</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/26/stock-market-today-jan-26-coreweave-jumps-after-nvidia-invests-usd2-billion-in-ai-infrastructure-partnership/</link><description>Today, Jan. 26, 2026, investors weigh a deepening AI infrastructure pact against bubble talk for this fast-growing cloud player.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/26/stock-market-today-jan-26-coreweave-jumps-after-nvidia-invests-usd2-billion-in-ai-infrastructure-partnership/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) Outperforms Broader Market: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-goog-outperforms-broader-224504019.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) reached $333.59 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.57% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-goog-outperforms-broader-224504019.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Rises Higher Than Market: Key Facts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-rises-higher-market-224504045.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) closed the most recent trading day at $333.25, moving +1.62% from the previous trading session.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-rises-higher-market-224504045.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dan Niles: Not All AI-Associated Stocks Will Win</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/dan-niles-not-ai-associated-223310065.html</link><description>Dan Niles, founder of Niles Investment Management, says not all AI-related companies will secure funding this year. He tells Romaine Bostick and Katie Greifeld on "The Close" that Google-linked stocks have risen about 20% since late October, while parts of the open-AI ecosystem have fallen roughly 20%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/dan-niles-not-ai-associated-223310065.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] GameStop’s Original Bull Is Back. CEO Ryan Cohen Has Berkshire-Like Ambitions.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/gamestop-stock-michael-burry-ryan-cohen-meme-trade-0a0c4a4f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>In buying shares of GameStop, Michael Burry compared Ryan Cohen to Warren Buffett. Here’s what Cohen told Barron’s about his next plans for GameStop.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/gamestop-stock-michael-burry-ryan-cohen-meme-trade-0a0c4a4f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] YouTubers sue Snap for alleged copyright infringement in training its AI models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtubers-sue-snap-alleged-copyright-214314911.html</link><description>The YouTubers claim Snap, like others, used AI datasets meant for research and academic use to train its AI models.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtubers-sue-snap-alleged-copyright-214314911.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Samsung Wins Memory Chip Deal With Nvidia, Report Says. Why Micron Stock Is Dropping.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/micron-stock-price-samsung-memory-chip-deal-nvidia-3a857e7c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Micron stock has surged on excitement around high-bandwidth memory chips but it doesn't have the market to itself.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/micron-stock-price-samsung-memory-chip-deal-nvidia-3a857e7c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 AI Chip Stocks to Buy in January: Nvidia, AMD, and Broadcom Battle for Market Share</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-ai-chip-stocks-to-buy-in-january-nvidia-amd-and/</link><description>These three chipmakers will profit from the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-ai-chip-stocks-to-buy-in-january-nvidia-amd-and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Why Cisco (CSCO) Stock Is Trading Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cisco-csco-stock-trading-205558166.html</link><description>Shares of networking technology giant Cisco (NASDAQ:CSCO) jumped 3.7% in the afternoon session after Evercore ISI upgraded the stock to Outperform from In Line and raised its price target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cisco-csco-stock-trading-205558166.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Why CrowdStrike (CRWD) Stock Is Trading Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-crwd-stock-trading-205553841.html</link><description>Shares of cybersecurity platform provider CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) jumped 3.4% in the afternoon session after the stock's positive momentum continued following recent analyst upgrades.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-crwd-stock-trading-205553841.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple (AAPL) Stock Trades Up, Here Is Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-stock-trades-why-205543182.html</link><description>Shares of iPhone and iPad maker Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) jumped 3.3% in the afternoon session after investor optimism grew ahead of its earnings report, fueled by positive analyst commentary citing strong iPhone 17 sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-stock-trades-why-205543182.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft debuts its next-gen AI chip</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/microsoft-debuts-its-next-gen-ai-chip-204529930.html</link><description>Microsoft (MSFT) is debuting its next-generation custom AI chip that will allow it to take on rivals like Google (GOOGL, GOOG), Amazon (AMZN), and Nvidia (NVDA). Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley reports on the latest chip. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/microsoft-debuts-its-next-gen-ai-chip-204529930.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Ex-crypto stock surges after $2B Nvidia investment</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/crypto/markets/ex-bitcoin-miner-jumps-after-2b-nvidia-backing</link><description>Another former crypto miner is quietly making the case that pivoting to AI may be the smartest survival move in today’s market. This time, the proof point is CoreWeave (NASDAQ: CRWV), a firm that began life as a Bitcoin mining operation and is now pulling in billions from Big Tech. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/crypto/markets/ex-bitcoin-miner-jumps-after-2b-nvidia-backing</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] BofA says the chip reshuffle makes Nvidia a 'compelling' value play</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-says-the-chip-reshuffle-makes-nvidia-a-compelling-value-play-203403961.html</link><description>As equipment makers hit pricey peaks, BofA urges investors to reshuffle toward "dependable customers" like Nvidia and AMD to navigate the next leg of the AI trade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-says-the-chip-reshuffle-makes-nvidia-a-compelling-value-play-203403961.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Is Trading at a Massive Discount Despite Red-Hot Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/this-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-is-trading-a/</link><description>It looks like a deal for long-term investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/this-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-is-trading-a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should Wells Fargo’s AI Hire and Emberpoint Bet Prompt a Rethink by WFC Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wells-fargo-ai-hire-emberpoint-201020702.html</link><description>In recent weeks, Wells Fargo has joined Lockheed Martin, PG&amp;amp;E and Salesforce to launch Emberpoint, a wildfire-technology venture backed by more than US$100 million of committed partner funding, reported full-year 2025 earnings with net income of US$21,338 million, and continued issuing a range of senior unsecured notes across multiple maturities. Wells Fargo also named former Amazon Web Services and Google executive Faraz Shafiq as its new Head of AI Products and Solutions, underscoring how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wells-fargo-ai-hire-emberpoint-201020702.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Figma’s IPO Is a Cautionary Tale. How AI Busted the Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/figmas-ipo-is-a-cautionary-tale-how-ai-busted-the-stock-ea777690?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The software design firm soared early on, then sank. Investors bought the hype. And worries about artificial intelligence pulled it down.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/figmas-ipo-is-a-cautionary-tale-how-ai-busted-the-stock-ea777690?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave Stock Soars. Why Nvidia Is Investing $2 Billion in the AI Cloud Company.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/coreweave-stock-price-nvidia-ai-investment-78d0b985?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence cloud company  CoreWeave  surged early Monday on news of an expanded partnership with  Nvidia  which includes a $2 billion investment from the chip maker.  Nvidia invested in CoreWeave Class A common stock at a purchase price of $87.20 per share.  CoreWeave shares were up 6.6% to $99.06 in afternoon trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/coreweave-stock-price-nvidia-ai-investment-78d0b985?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia unveils AI models for faster, cheaper weather forecasts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-unveils-ai-models-faster-194409918.html</link><description>Nvidia on Monday released three open-source artificial intelligence models aimed at helping create better weather forecasts, ​faster.  The models, which the AI chip firm announced at the American Meteorological ‌Society’s annual meeting in Houston, are part of a broader push by the company to provide open-source ‌software, powered by its chips, for everything from chatbots to self-driving vehicles.  In the case of weather forecasting, Nvidia is aiming to replace expensive and time-consuming conventional weather simulations with AI-driven versions that the company said can rival or exceed the accuracy of ⁠older methods.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-unveils-ai-models-faster-194409918.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron Shares Fall as Samsung Nears Nvidia HBM4 Certification</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-shares-fall-samsung-nears-193539509.html</link><description>Competition in high-bandwidth memory tightens amid rising AI demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-shares-fall-samsung-nears-193539509.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Tariffs linger over earnings, even as companies get used to them</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tariffs-linger-over-earnings-even-193425906.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: Many U.S. companies have sought to reassure investors that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs are "manageable."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But corporate America so far this earnings season is signaling that profit margins could be squeezed as consumers push back on higher prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bellwethers including Procter &amp;amp; Gamble and 3M have flagged these challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Andy Jassy, CEO of Amazon, told CNBC on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum in Davos that the retail giant was seeing prices tick up on its e-commerce platform as sellers have sold the inventory they built up before tariffs went into effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous companies with global footprints report results in the coming week, including General Motors and Caterpillar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While broader consumer spending has held up, buyers have been more judicious, often looking for value items, particularly lower- and middle-income earners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One economic strategist told Reuters quote, “Most consumers are still mad about the level of current prices and won't take kindly to further hikes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Levi Strauss reports holiday-quarter results on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company said in October that tariffs would cut its margins more than it had anticipated. &amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Levis has raised some prices while trying to diversify its supply chain, and the company also warned of a softer consumer environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three Harvard University professors have been tracking the price of roughly 360,000 goods, from carpets to coffee, at major online and brick-and-mortar retailers in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They estimate that as of year-end, domestic goods cost about 4.3 percentage points more than would have been expected based on the pre-tariff regime, while imported goods are about 5.8 percentage points more expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Yale Budget Lab, the effective tariff rate on U.S. consumers as of mid-November was 14.4%, the highest in 85 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current tariff regime could be interrupted if the U.S. Supreme Court rules against President Donald Trump's use of emergency economic powers to implement them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That could lead to massive refunds for companies that had to pay&amp;amp;nbsp;duties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the process could play out over years, and the White House plans to use other means to keep the tariffs in place.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tariffs-linger-over-earnings-even-193425906.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] The Intel Business Growing 50% That Nobody's Talking About</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-intel-business-growing-50-that-nobodys-talking/</link><description>Intel's custom chip business is taking off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-intel-business-growing-50-that-nobodys-talking/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Commits $2 Billion to CoreWeave in Expanded AI Infrastructure Push</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-commits-2-billion-coreweave-192942098.html</link><description>The investment deepens collaboration as the companies target over 5 gigawatts of AI factory capacity by 2030.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-commits-2-billion-coreweave-192942098.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Microsoft Launches Maia 200 AI Chip for Faster Model Inference</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-launches-maia-200-ai-192556018.html</link><description>New accelerator aims to boost efficiency across Azure and OpenAI workloads.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-launches-maia-200-ai-192556018.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft Takes Aim at Amazon, Google AI Chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-takes-aim-amazon-google-192107308.html</link><description>Maia 200 rolls into Azure data center</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-takes-aim-amazon-google-192107308.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AppLovin Stock Is Climbing. The Ad Platform Won Some Big Clients, Analyst Says.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/applovin-stock-price-5471de64?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Needham &amp;amp; Company upgraded AppLovin stock to Buy from Hold and set a $700 price target in a research note Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/applovin-stock-price-5471de64?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nancy Pelosi Files New Trades Across Big Tech and Asset Management</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/nancy-pelosi-files-trades-across-191750511.html</link><description>Disclosure shows option exercises, share sales, new call purchases, and a fresh AllianceBernstein position across multiple holdings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/nancy-pelosi-files-trades-across-191750511.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Why Cisco Systems (CSCO) Price Target Revision Is Rewriting The Story Around The Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cisco-systems-csco-price-191009142.html</link><description>The latest update on Cisco Systems focuses squarely on a revised price target, highlighting how fresh information and shifting expectations are reshaping the story around the stock. While the exact figures behind this new target are not detailed here, the change itself signals that analysts are reassessing what they think the shares are worth under current assumptions. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of these price target moves and the evolving narrative around Cisco from...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cisco-systems-csco-price-191009142.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] The Only Index Fund I Would Buy and Never Sell Is the Vanguard Total Stock Market ETF (VTI)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-only-index-fund-id-buy-and-never-sell-is-vti/</link><description>This fund is a perfect example of buying the haystack instead of seeking the needle.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-only-index-fund-id-buy-and-never-sell-is-vti/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The AI Application Boom: Why Microsoft and Nvidia Will Win Big This Year</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-ai-application-boom-why-microsoft-and-nvidia-w/</link><description>The two tech giants remain the most balanced plays in the booming AI market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-ai-application-boom-why-microsoft-and-nvidia-w/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Invests $2 Billion in CoreWeave to Expand U.S. Data Centers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-invests-2-billion-coreweave-183403683.html</link><description>Move strengthens Nvidia's position in AI infrastructure and cloud capacity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-invests-2-billion-coreweave-183403683.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVDA: CoreWeave Stock Pops on Nvidia's $2 Billion AI Deal</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvda-coreweave-stock-pops-nvidias-183259025.html</link><description>CoreWeave Stock Jumps. Nvidia Makes a $2 Billion Bet on AI Infrastructure</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvda-coreweave-stock-pops-nvidias-183259025.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Bets $2 billion on CoreWeave AI Buildout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-bets-2-billion-coreweave-183110675.html</link><description>Strategic collaboration targets large-scale AI factory buildout.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-bets-2-billion-coreweave-183110675.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron Slips on Samsung HBM4 Nvidia Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-slips-samsung-hbm4-nvidia-182506389.html</link><description>Samsung HBM4 plans pressure AI memory outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-slips-samsung-hbm4-nvidia-182506389.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Stock Has Trailed Tech Peers. Why It’s This Analyst’s Top Pick.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-stock-tech-analyst-top-pick-beb09f6c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Amazon.com  stock could be poised for a much-needed boost, according to one Roth Capital analyst, who expects margins to improve, AWS to grow, and retail performance to strengthen with artificial intelligence.  Rohit Kulkarni raised his price target on  Amazon  stock to $295 from $270, which implies a 23% increase from the stock’s previous closing price of $239.16.  Kulkarni also maintained a Buy rating on the stock and wrote in a research note on Monday that Amazon is his top mega cap pick for 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-stock-tech-analyst-top-pick-beb09f6c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] If You'd Invested $10,000 in Taiwan Semiconductor Stock a Year Ago, This Is How Much You'd Have Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/if-youd-invested-10000-in-taiwan-semiconductor-sto/</link><description>The chip company is enjoying AI tailwinds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/if-youd-invested-10000-in-taiwan-semiconductor-sto/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet, Nvidia Back Synthesia in $200 Million Funding at $4 Billion Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-nvidia-back-synthesia-200-175405598.html</link><description>Funding highlights growing investor appetite for AI video technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-nvidia-back-synthesia-200-175405598.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Stock Market Today: Dow Rises Despite Schumer Shutdown Call; CoreWeave Pops On Nvidia Move (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-tariff-threats-tesla-earnings-tsla-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stock Market Today: The Dow Jones index rises Monday even as Trump threatens new tariffs on Canada. Tesla stock slides but CoreWeave jumps.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-tariff-threats-tesla-earnings-tsla-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These Are The 5 Best Stocks To Buy Now Or Watch</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/best-stocks-to-buy-now/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Buying a stock is easy, but buying the right stock without a good strategy is incredibly hard. Here are five top-performing stocks to buy now or put on a watchlist.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/best-stocks-to-buy-now/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The ‘Magnificent 7’ Are Off to a Mixed Start in 2026. Here’s What to Watch as Their Earnings Start</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/the-magnificent-7-are-off-to-a-mixed-start-in-2026-here-is-what-to-watch-as-their-earnings-start-11891595</link><description>America’s heavy-hitting “Magnificent 7” stocks have driven years of market gains. That may not continue to be the case.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/the-magnificent-7-are-off-to-a-mixed-start-in-2026-here-is-what-to-watch-as-their-earnings-start-11891595</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 No-Brainer AI Stocks to Buy Hand Over Fist for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/2-no-brainer-ai-stocks-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</link><description>These top tech stocks could benefit from higher AI spending this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/2-no-brainer-ai-stocks-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jeff Bezos Said He Made $80K A Year At Amazon And Turned Down More Because It Would Feel 'Icky' —'How Could I Possibly Need More Incentive?'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jeff-bezos-said-made-80k-170111599.html</link><description>While other CEOs chased performance bonuses and stock grants, Amazon founder Jeff Bezos said he took a different route—and made it official. At the 2024 New York Times DealBook Summit, Jeff Bezos said that for his entire tenure as the company's CEO, he asked the company's compensation committee to cap his salary at $80,000 a year. "I asked the comp committee of the board not to give me any comp," he said. "I just didn't feel good about taking more." Don't Miss: The AI Marketing Platform Backed b</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jeff-bezos-said-made-80k-170111599.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Landmark Trial Tests Claims That Social Media Harms Teens</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/us-news/law/landmark-trial-tests-claims-that-social-media-harms-teens-74409b2f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A California case follows a similar script to lawsuits against big tobacco and pharmaceutical companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/us-news/law/landmark-trial-tests-claims-that-social-media-harms-teens-74409b2f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave Bonds Pop on Nvidia Investment</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-26-2026/card/coreweave-bonds-pop-on-nvidia-investment-7zW0pNawHgm322Y8lVpf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>CoreWeave bond prices jumped 2-3% Monday after chip-maker Nvidia announced a new $2 billion equity injection into the data-center operator.  About $240 million of CoreWeave bonds due in 2030 and 2031 changed hands before noon, making them among the most traded U.S. corporate bonds, according to data from MarketAxess.  Unlike companies like Meta Platforms and Nvidia, which generate significant cash flow, “neo-cloud” operators like CoreWeave depend heavily on borrowed money to build data centers and purchase the costly micro-chips that power them.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-26-2026/card/coreweave-bonds-pop-on-nvidia-investment-7zW0pNawHgm322Y8lVpf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] As Nvidia Sets Up, This AI Stock Tickles New Buy Zone While Top Funds Gobble Up Shares</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/how-to-find-the-best-stocks-to-buy/google-stock-teases-buy-zone-while-nvidia-finds-support/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>As top funds scoop up shares, AI bellwether Google stock finds support for a new run and climbs back into buy range.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/how-to-find-the-best-stocks-to-buy/google-stock-teases-buy-zone-while-nvidia-finds-support/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Could Micron Technology Stock Make You a Millionaire in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/could-micron-technology-make-you-a-millionaire/</link><description>Shares in this computer memory giant are trading for a rock-bottom valuation despite solid growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/could-micron-technology-make-you-a-millionaire/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly or Viking Therapeutics: Which Stock Is More Likely to be a Millionaire-Maker?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/eli-lilly-or-viking-therapeutics-millionaire-maker/</link><description>Both companies may succeed in this industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/eli-lilly-or-viking-therapeutics-millionaire-maker/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Crypto Investors Cry 'Rug' As Token Tied To Pokémon Card Trading Project Crashes Near Zero</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-investors-cry-rug-token-163252217.html</link><description>Cryptocurrency investors have accused proposed Pokémon cards perpetual exchange Trove Markets of a rug pull after its token crashed over 95% within minutes of its launch on Jan. 19. The token, which launched at a market cap of nearly $19...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-investors-cry-rug-token-163252217.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Lululemon Founder Outraged Over See-Through Leggings: 'A New Low'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lululemon-founder-outraged-over-see-163133398.html</link><description>Lululemon Athletica, Inc. (NASDAQ:LULU) founder Chip Wilson has launched an attack on the company's board of directors, labeling recent quality control issues with the brand's product lines as a “new low” for the yoga-wear giant. In a viral LinkedIn post, Wilson — who stepped down from the company years ago but remains its largest individual shareholder — did not hold back. He pointed directly to the board's management as the root cause of what he describes as see-through leggings and declining</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lululemon-founder-outraged-over-see-163133398.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 OpenAI-Adjacent Stocks To Buy Now</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/2-openai-adjacent-stocks-to-buy-now/</link><description>It seems like any stock sitting adjacent to OpenAI has been punished severely in the past couple of months. Undoubtedly, it did not take long for sentiment to shift in the weeks and months that followed the launch of Gemini 3.0. Though OpenAI’s “code red” response was decent, with GPT-5.2 launching surprisingly earlier than expected, ... 2 OpenAI-Adjacent Stocks To Buy Now</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/2-openai-adjacent-stocks-to-buy-now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BofA flags attractive compute valuations, highlights 4 key stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-flags-attractive-compute-valuations-160342927.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Bank of America said compute-focused chipmakers look increasingly attractive as valuations remain well below historical levels, even as artificial intelligence investment accelerates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-flags-attractive-compute-valuations-160342927.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Microsoft rolls out next generation of its AI chips, takes aim at Nvidia's software</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-rolls-next-generation-ai-160312249.html</link><description>SAN FRANCISCO, Jan 26 (Reuters) - Microsoft on Monday unveiled the second generation of its in-house artificial intelligence chip, along with software tools that take aim at one of Nvidia's biggest</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-rolls-next-generation-ai-160312249.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Chart of the Day: Tech stock domination gets a reality check</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chart-of-the-day-tech-stock-domination-gets-a-reality-check-160308604.html</link><description>The largest tech stocks in the market get served a reality check.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chart-of-the-day-tech-stock-domination-gets-a-reality-check-160308604.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Microsoft takes aim at Google, Amazon, and Nvidia with new AI chip</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-takes-aim-at-google-amazon-and-nvidia-with-new-ai-chip-160027494.html</link><description>Microsoft announced its new Maia 200 AI chip, taking aim at Amazon, Google, and Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-takes-aim-at-google-amazon-and-nvidia-with-new-ai-chip-160027494.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] NVIDIA Just Made a Bigger Push Into AI Drug Discovery</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/nvidia-just-made-a-bigger-push-into-ai-drug-discovery/</link><description>Shares of GPU titan Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) may have been stuck in a sideways channel for the past six months, but a lot has been going on behind the scenes amid the intense sideways action. Of course, Nvidia isn’t solely to blame for the recent consolidation. In fact, the Magnificent Seven players have really run out ... NVIDIA Just Made a Bigger Push Into AI Drug Discovery</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/nvidia-just-made-a-bigger-push-into-ai-drug-discovery/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] Buy These 3 ETFs and Hold For Decades</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/buy-these-3-etfs-and-hold-for-decades/</link><description>Each one of us works hard to make money, and it is always a delight to have your money work for you. Investing in the right assets and holding them for the long term can be one way of making money. Exchange-traded funds have gained immense popularity over the past year. It is a passive ... Buy These 3 ETFs and Hold For Decades</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/buy-these-3-etfs-and-hold-for-decades/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Upgraded On Above Consensus Profit, Revenue Outlook</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/cisco-stock-evercore-upgrade-outperform-jan2026/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Cisco stock rose amid Evercore ISI upgrade to outperform on views the company can deliver above consensus profit and revenue growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/cisco-stock-evercore-upgrade-outperform-jan2026/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017549.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;Hycroft Mining Holding Corp.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017549.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Magnificent 7 in 2026: What Should Investors Expect?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-2026-investors-expect-151805984.html</link><description>Of the Magnificent 7, only Nvidia and Alphabet beat the S&amp;amp;P 500 index in 2025. Here’s what investors could expect from the Magnificent 7 stocks in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-2026-investors-expect-151805984.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Celestica Hit by Fears Over Google TPU Orders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/celestica-hit-fears-over-google-151748354.html</link><description>TPU assembly work may move elsewhere</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/celestica-hit-fears-over-google-151748354.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Will Check Point's Recent AI Advancements Help Steer the Competition?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/check-points-recent-ai-advancements-151400683.html</link><description>CHKP rolls out an AI-driven exposure management strategy to close the remediation gap, automate responses and speed fixes as cyber threats intensify.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/check-points-recent-ai-advancements-151400683.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Ultimate Growth Stock to Buy With $1,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-ultimate-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right/</link><description>This business is being left for dead despite its huge potential.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/the-ultimate-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Teradyne (TER) Earnings Expected to Grow: What to Know Ahead of Next Week's Release</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teradyne-ter-earnings-expected-grow-150002482.html</link><description>Teradyne (TER) doesn't possess the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teradyne-ter-earnings-expected-grow-150002482.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google settles Google Assistant privacy lawsuit for $68 million</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-settles-google-assistant-privacy-145644415.html</link><description>Smartphone users accused Google, a unit ⁠of Alphabet, of ‌illegally recording and disseminating private conversations after Google Assistant was triggered, in order ‍to send them targeted advertising.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-settles-google-assistant-privacy-145644415.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia, Amazon and TikTok Shape Tech Headlines</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-amazon-tiktok-shape-tech-145535837.html</link><description>China access, job cuts and politics collide</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-amazon-tiktok-shape-tech-145535837.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta Has the World’s Best ‘Demand Machine.’ Buy the Stock, Analysts Say.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/meta-ai-demand-machine-analysts-price-target-upgrade-8673a5c3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Rothschild &amp;amp; Co Redburn upgraded Meta to Buy and lifted its price target to $900, arguing the company can keep gaining share in non-search digital ads.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/meta-ai-demand-machine-analysts-price-target-upgrade-8673a5c3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway Stock Trades at a Premium to Industry: How to Play</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-stock-trades-premium-145200961.html</link><description>BRK.B trades at a premium to peers with soft ROE and near-term earnings pressure despite strong diversification.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-stock-trades-premium-145200961.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Netflix, Meta upgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-meta-upgraded-wall-streets-145018203.html</link><description>Netflix, Meta upgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-meta-upgraded-wall-streets-145018203.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Millennial Found Their First Apartment Lease From 2013 And Couldn't Believe How Cheap It Was. The Price Felt Unreal By Today's Standards</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/millennial-found-first-apartment-lease-144612655.html</link><description>While cleaning out their parents’ garage, one millennial stumbled across a document that stopped them in their tracks: their first apartment lease from 2013. The price? Just $675 a month for a one-bedroom in Phoenix, with an in-unit washer and dryer. Rent Was Once Reasonable “I remember at the time thinking it was kinda expensive and being super careful with my budget,” the original poster wrote in a recent Reddit post. “Now that same complex is going for like $1,850 for the exact same floorplan</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/millennial-found-first-apartment-lease-144612655.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks to Watch Monday: CoreWeave, American Airlines, IonQ, Enphase</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-26-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-monday-american-airlines-usa-rare-earth-revmed-HSxB2cwZrQSqN8JS06UK?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️ CoreWeave (CRWV): Chip maker Nvidia (NVDA) is investing an extra $2 billion in the data-center company to build new AI factories. CoreWeave shares gained 15%. ↘️ American Airlines (AAL): Flight cancellations and delays mounted after a winter storm snarled the central and eastern U.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-26-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-monday-american-airlines-usa-rare-earth-revmed-HSxB2cwZrQSqN8JS06UK?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia’s Unspoken Problem: 40% of Revenue Comes From Companies Developing Their Own AI Chips</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/nvidias-unspoken-problem-40-of-revenue-comes-from-companies-developing-their-own-ai-chips/</link><description>Jensen Huang has built a $4.6 trillion empire selling the picks and shovels of the AI revolution. But while he preaches accelerated computing, three existential threats aren’t discussed in earnings calls. They’re happening now. Threat #1: Your Best Customers Are Building Your Replacement Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT), Meta (NASDAQ:META), Amazon (NASDAQ:AMZN), and Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOGL) represent 40-50% of ... Nvidia’s Unspoken Problem: 40% of Revenue Comes From Companies Developing Their Own AI Chips</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/nvidias-unspoken-problem-40-of-revenue-comes-from-companies-developing-their-own-ai-chips/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] CoreWeave stock surges amid fresh $2 billion investment from Nvidia</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-surges-amid-fresh-2-billion-investment-from-nvidia-143717366.html</link><description>Nvidia said Monday that its latest investment in CoreWeave will help the company build AI data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-surges-amid-fresh-2-billion-investment-from-nvidia-143717366.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Invests $2 Billion in CoreWeave in AI-Factory Collaboration</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-invests-2-billion-in-coreweave-in-ai-factory-collaboration-68088ca0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  is pouring an additional $2 billion into  CoreWeave  in a vote of confidence in the artificial-intelligence data-center company that uses Nvidia’s chips.  The companies said Monday that they would build new AI factories on Nvidia’s computing-platform technology, operated by CoreWeave, with a goal of 5 gigawatts of capacity by 2030.  Nvidia also said it would leverage its financial strength to help procure land and power for the projects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-invests-2-billion-in-coreweave-in-ai-factory-collaboration-68088ca0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Prediction: This Healthcare Stock Could Soar by 40% in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/prediction-healthcare-stock-soar-40-nvo/</link><description>This pharmaceutical giant has recently caught fire, and the stock's run is likely just beginning.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/prediction-healthcare-stock-soar-40-nvo/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tech stocks are confronting a challenge they haven't had to worry about in a while</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-stocks-are-confronting-a-challenge-they-havent-had-to-worry-about-in-a-while-141856177.html</link><description>Tech stocks face several important headwinds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-stocks-are-confronting-a-challenge-they-havent-had-to-worry-about-in-a-while-141856177.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Countdown to KLA (KLAC) Q2 Earnings: A Look at Estimates Beyond Revenue and EPS</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/countdown-kla-klac-q2-earnings-141508236.html</link><description>Beyond analysts' top-and-bottom-line estimates for KLA (KLAC), evaluate projections for some of its key metrics to gain a better insight into how the business might have performed for the quarter ended December 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/countdown-kla-klac-q2-earnings-141508236.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Ahead of Caterpillar (CAT) Q4 Earnings: Get Ready With Wall Street Estimates for Key Metrics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ahead-caterpillar-cat-q4-earnings-141508837.html</link><description>Beyond analysts' top-and-bottom-line estimates for Caterpillar (CAT), evaluate projections for some of its key metrics to gain a better insight into how the business might have performed for the quarter ended December 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ahead-caterpillar-cat-q4-earnings-141508837.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] How Will Ozempic and Wegovy Sales Aid NVO's Upcoming Q4 Results?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ozempic-wegovy-sales-aid-nvos-141500549.html</link><description>Novo Nordisk's Q4 results hinge on Ozempic and Wegovy sales as demand growth slows amid guidance cuts due to intense rivalry and compounded drug headwinds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ozempic-wegovy-sales-aid-nvos-141500549.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave Pops On New Nvidia Investment Amid Data Center Build-Out</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/coreweave-stock-pops-new-nvidia-investment-data-center-expansion/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>CoreWeave stock popped after AI chip maker Nvidia said it has invested another $2 billion in the cloud computing services provider.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/coreweave-stock-pops-new-nvidia-investment-data-center-expansion/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why venture capitalist Bill Gurley said a 'correction' is inevitable for AI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-venture-capitalist-bill-gurley-said-a-correction-is-inevitable-for-ai-134459662.html</link><description>Gurley has seen and done it all in tech.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-venture-capitalist-bill-gurley-said-a-correction-is-inevitable-for-ai-134459662.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave stock rises 10% after NVIDIA invests $2 billion to expand AI partnership</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-rises-10-nvidia-133811130.html</link><description>Investing.com -- CoreWeave (NASDAQ:CRWV) stock rose 10% Monday morning after NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA) announced a $2 billion investment in the company to expand their AI infrastructure partnership.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-rises-10-nvidia-133811130.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Earnings live: Nucor stock falls, Baker Hughes rises as Big Tech earnings loom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-nucor-stock-falls-baker-hughes-rises-as-big-tech-earnings-loom-133500372.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-nucor-stock-falls-baker-hughes-rises-as-big-tech-earnings-loom-133500372.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Earnings live: Baker Hughes stock rises as Big Tech earnings come into view</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-baker-hughes-stock-rises-as-big-tech-earnings-come-into-view-133500361.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-baker-hughes-stock-rises-as-big-tech-earnings-come-into-view-133500361.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] AI-Driven Foundry Demand Likely to Boost LRCX's Systems Revenues in Q2</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-driven-foundry-demand-likely-132000828.html</link><description>Lam Research's AI-driven foundry demand is set to lift Systems revenues in Q2, with advanced etch and deposition tools gaining traction at chipmakers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-driven-foundry-demand-likely-132000828.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Here Are Monday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Amazon.com, AppLovin, Cisco Systems, Cognizant Technology, Dutch Bros., Meta Platforms, Netflix, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/here-are-mondays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-amazon-com-applovin-cisco-systems-cognizant-technology-dutch-bros-meta-platforms-netflix-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: Futures are trading flat as we get ready to start the new trading week, and despite a strong rebound last Wednesday through Friday, we still ended with our second straight losing week. As the smoke cleared from the Greenland turmoil and no new tariffs were imposed on Europe, investors renewed scrutiny of ... Here Are Monday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Amazon.com, AppLovin, Cisco Systems, Cognizant Technology, Dutch Bros., Meta Platforms, Netflix, and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/here-are-mondays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-amazon-com-applovin-cisco-systems-cognizant-technology-dutch-bros-meta-platforms-netflix-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Stock Rises on Upgrade. It’s a Big-Cap Bargain, Analyst Says.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/cisco-stock-upgrade-ai-fe8acf7d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Evercore upgrades Cisco stock to Outperform from In Line and lifts its price target to $100 from $80.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/cisco-stock-upgrade-ai-fe8acf7d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia invests $2 billion in CoreWeave, expands partnership</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-invests-2-billion-coreweave-130850099.html</link><description>Nvidia has invested $2 billion in CoreWeave at a purchase price ​of $87.20 per share, the companies said ‌on Monday, as they expand their partnership to boost ‌CoreWeave's data center build out ambitions.  Shares of CoreWeave jumped nearly 10% in premarket trading.  CoreWeave is targeting to build more than 5 gigawatts ⁠in AI data ‌center capacity by 2030.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-invests-2-billion-coreweave-130850099.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Retail Investors Dump Apple Stock While Nvidia, Tesla See Massive Inflows</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/retail-investors-dump-apple-stock-130114493.html</link><description>Retail investors have been divesting Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) shares while flocking to Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA) and Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) stocks. Retail investors have bought $15 billion of Nvidia stock since July 2025, outpacing all other Magnificent 7 companies combined, according to The Kobeissi Letter, which cited data from J.P. Morgan Equity Strategy &amp;amp; Quantitative Research. Tesla followed with $6 billion in net retail purchases. Retail investors are dumping Apple stock while piling in</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/retail-investors-dump-apple-stock-130114493.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 Reasons to Buy Vertiv Stock Like There's No Tomorrow​</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-reasons-to-buy-vertiv-stock-like-theres-no-tomor/</link><description>Vertiv has crushed the stock market over the past five years, and the expanded AI buildout suggests that more gains are on the way.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-reasons-to-buy-vertiv-stock-like-theres-no-tomor/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Holding Before Q4 Earnings: How Should Investors Play the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-q4-earnings-investors-124600373.html</link><description>ASML heads into Q4 earnings with AI-driven chip demand, strong EUV momentum and revenues projected to be EURO 9.8B - should investors buy now or wait?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-q4-earnings-investors-124600373.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Slips. What It Needs From Big Tech Earnings.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-earnings-tech-676426ea?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock could rise if technology companies like Microsoft raise their capital expenditure guidance for the year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-earnings-tech-676426ea?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Evercore ISI upgrades Cisco, sees ’plenty of tailwinds’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-upgrades-cisco-sees-123737903.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Cisco shares received a boost, trading around 1.6% higher premarket after Evercore ISI upgraded the stock to Outperform, arguing that the company is positioned for “high single-digit sales and low-teens EPS growth on a multi-year basis.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-upgrades-cisco-sees-123737903.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here's How Google Parent Alphabet Could Boost Revenue From Artificial Intelligence (AI)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/google-alphabet-stock-boost-revenue-ai/</link><description>No company has expertise in digital advertising like this one does.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/google-alphabet-stock-boost-revenue-ai/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] My Top AI Healthcare Stock to Buy and Hold for 20 Years</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/my-top-ai-healthcare-stock-to-buy-and-hold-for-20/</link><description>This drugmaker continues to strengthen its investment thesis.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/my-top-ai-healthcare-stock-to-buy-and-hold-for-20/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLOY.L] UK bank fined for breaking Russia sanctions</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-bank-fined-breaking-russia-121500210.html</link><description>Bank of Scotland (BoS) has been fined by a regulator for breaking sanctions related to Russia's war in Ukraine.  The Office of Financial Sanctions Implementation (OFSI) said ‌a penalty of £160,000 had been imposed over financial transactions dating back to 2023.  OFSI, which oversees compliance with all sanctions levied against Russia on behalf of the UK government, said it had concluded that the ​bank breached prohibitions on dealing with, and making funds available to, a sanctioned person.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-bank-fined-breaking-russia-121500210.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Shares Stall as Job Cuts Loom Against $35B AI Spending | AMZN Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/amazon-shares-stall-as-job-cuts-loom-against-35b-ai-spending-amzn-stock/</link><description>Shares of Amazon (NASDAQ:AMZN) are up 0.5% this week, but retail investor sentiment tells a darker story. The company’s social sentiment score dropped to negative 0.15 on Reddit and X over the past week, a sharp reversal from its neutral-bullish 0.12 average over the prior quarter. Among select tech peers, Amazon stands alone in sustained ... Amazon Shares Stall as Job Cuts Loom Against $35B AI Spending | AMZN Stock</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/26/amazon-shares-stall-as-job-cuts-loom-against-35b-ai-spending-amzn-stock/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Clearway Energy (CWEN.A) Valuation Check After New Long Term Google PPAs For 1.17 GW Of Clean Energy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearway-energy-cwen-valuation-check-120646401.html</link><description>Clearway Energy (CWEN.A) has drawn fresh attention after Clearway Energy Group agreed to three new long term power purchase agreements with Google, totaling 1.17 GW of carbon free projects across Missouri, Texas, and West Virginia. See our latest analysis for Clearway Energy. While the Google PPAs have put Clearway Energy back in the headlines, the shares are trading at US$33.60 after a 30 day share price return of 6.87% and a 90 day share price return of 12.15%. The 1 year total shareholder...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearway-energy-cwen-valuation-check-120646401.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Option Volatility And Earnings Report For January 26 - 30</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37225536/option-volatility-and-earnings-report-for-january-26-30</link><description>It’s the biggest week of the quarter for earnings this week with plenty of big names set to report. This week we have Tesla, Microsoft, Apple, Meta Platforms, UnitedHealth Group, Exxon Mobil, Visa, Mastercard, Chevron and Caterpillar all reporting in what shapes as a busy and pivotal week for stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37225536/option-volatility-and-earnings-report-for-january-26-30</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tech, Media &amp; Telecom Roundup: Market Talk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/tech-media-telecom-roundup-market-talk-54a73a86?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Find insight on TSMC, Baidu, the smart-glasses market and more in the latest Market Talks covering Technology, Media and Telecom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/tech-media-telecom-roundup-market-talk-54a73a86?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Samsung Enters Final Nvidia Certification Phase for HBM4 AI Memory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/samsung-enters-final-nvidia-certification-115716834.html</link><description>Samsung has moved into Nvidia's final qualification stage for its HBM4 chip ahead of planned mass production preparations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/samsung-enters-final-nvidia-certification-115716834.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Zurich targets Beazley to lead global speciality market</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/analyst-comment/zurich-targets-beazley/</link><description>Zurich is looking to strike a deal to acquire Beazley and cement its place as one of the leading commercial insurers globally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/analyst-comment/zurich-targets-beazley/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Calls Anthropic's Claude 'Incredible,' Says Every Software Company Needs To Use It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-calls-114616796.html</link><description>Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang endorsed Anthropic's Claude AI platform during his first appearance at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, calling the technology a breakthrough in coding and reasoning capabilities. Huang Says ‘We Use It All Over’ On Wednesday, during a conversation with BlackRock Inc. (NYSE:BLK) CEO Larry Fink, Huang said, "Claude is incredible. Anthropic made a huge leap in coding and reasoning." Don't Miss: Missed Nvidia and Tesla? RAD Intel Could Be th</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-calls-114616796.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Chips Today - Europe Advances AI Sovereignty With EU AI GRID Launch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chips-today-europe-advances-113715408.html</link><description>A significant advancement in AI infrastructure has been introduced with the launch of the EU AI GRID in Vilnius, Lithuania, resulting from a collaboration between Telecentras and Singapore-based technology firm Embedded LLM. This project aims to establish a network that complies with GDPR and the EU AI Act, fostering digital sovereignty and providing enhanced data protection for AI users across Europe. Highlighted at the iconic Vilnius TV Tower, the initiative underscores Europe's commitment...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chips-today-europe-advances-113715408.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Stocks Set for Muted Open After Trump’s Tariff Threats, Big Tech Earnings and Fed Meeting in Focus</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37224979/stocks-set-to-open-lower-after-trumps-tariff-threats-big-tech-earnings-and-fed-meeting-in-focus</link><description>March S&amp;amp;P 500 E-Mini futures (ESH26) are down -0.05%, and March Nasdaq 100 E-Mini futures (NQH26) are down -0.14% this morning, pointing to a muted open on Wall Street as President Trump’s tariff threats against Canada and the looming risk of a partial U.S. government shutdown curbed risk appetite at the start of a busy week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37224979/stocks-set-to-open-lower-after-trumps-tariff-threats-big-tech-earnings-and-fed-meeting-in-focus</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Tariffs linger over earnings, even as companies get used to them</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tariffs-linger-over-earnings-even-110845013.html</link><description>By Juveria Tabassum Jan 26 (Reuters) - Many U.S. companies have sought to reassure investors that tariffs are "manageable," but early earnings-season comments suggest profit margins are at risk with</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tariffs-linger-over-earnings-even-110845013.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Assessing ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) Valuation After A Strong Multi‑Month Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-asml-110709890.html</link><description>Recent performance snapshot for ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) has recently attracted attention after a strong month and past 3 months, with the stock showing a 29.48% monthly return and a 31.98% total return over the past 3 months. See our latest analysis for ASML Holding. At a latest share price of US$1,389.04, ASML Holding’s recent 30 day share price return of 29.48% and 90 day return of 31.98% sit alongside a 1 year total shareholder return of 102.90%. This...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-asml-110709890.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Drugmakers turn to AI to speed trials, regulatory submissions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/drugmakers-turn-ai-speed-trials-110213746.html</link><description>By Maggie Fick and Michael Erman SAN FRANCISCO, Jan 26 (Reuters) - Artificial intelligence has yet to deliver on the most challenging aspect of drug development -- finding new molecules that lead to</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/drugmakers-turn-ai-speed-trials-110213746.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:04:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar stock is an 'overlooked' AI play. Here's how.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/caterpillar-stock-overlooked-ai-play-110054816.html</link><description>Caterpillar (CAT) is an unexpected winner of the artificial intelligence (AI) era, Gabelli Funds portfolio manager Brian Sponheimer tells Yahoo Finance. Watch the video above to hear more about how the industrial name is set up for success in terms of AI infrastructure build-outs and beyond. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/caterpillar-stock-overlooked-ai-play-110054816.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: USA Rare Earth, Micron, Intel, AMD, Newmont, RevMed, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-e7656fb8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stock futures were falling Monday after President Donald Trump threatened to impose further tariffs on Canada, fueling fears that the “sell America” trade could gather pace, and as the chances of a partial U.S. government shutdown appeared more likely.  USA Rare Earth  surged 37% to $33.90 ahead of the opening bell.  The Trump administration is planning to inject $1.6 billion into the miner and will receive a 10% stake, the Financial Times reported on Saturday, citing people familiar with the matter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-e7656fb8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple's Action Tells Me That Another "Magnificent Seven" Stock Is the Best AI Investment Opportunity in 2026 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/apple-magnificent-seven-best-ai-stock/</link><description>Apple is figuring out how to participate in the AI race by leaning on its fellow California-based tech peer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/apple-magnificent-seven-best-ai-stock/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] NVIDIA (NVDA)’s Stock “Can’t Get Out of its Way,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-stock-t-way-103351180.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) continues to be on Jim Cramer’s radar. The CNBC TV host has continued to defend the stock even though gains have stalled lately. Since early November, the shares are down by […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-stock-t-way-103351180.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] British AI Start-up Synthesia Doubles Valuation to $4bn In a Year</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/british-ai-start-synthesia-doubles-100847577.html</link><description>The Nvidia-Backed Startup, creates digital humans for businesses and plans to offer interactive audio-visual "agents" that can carry on conversations in specific topics. Victor Riparbelli, Synthesia's chief executive speaks with Bloomberg's anchor Guy Johnson, Anna Edwards and Tom MacKenzie on 'The Opening Trade' about the new product as a way to meet the demand from companies to "upskill" employees using automation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/british-ai-start-synthesia-doubles-100847577.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 AI Stocks That Will Trounce Palantir in 2026, According to Wall Street</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-ai-stocks-that-will-trounce-palantir-in-2026-acc/</link><description>Analysts are much more bullish about these AI stocks than they are about Palantir.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/3-ai-stocks-that-will-trounce-palantir-in-2026-acc/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia-Backed AI Startup Synthesia Raises Funding at $4 Billion Valuation</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/entrepreneurship/nvidia-backed-ai-startup-synthesia-raises-funding-at-4-billion-valuation-7941abae?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence company Synthesia raised $200 million, adding fresh capital to develop software that businesses can use to train employees through interactive videos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/entrepreneurship/nvidia-backed-ai-startup-synthesia-raises-funding-at-4-billion-valuation-7941abae?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Micron Stock Is Up Over 260%. Here's Why It Could Go Even Higher</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/micron-stock-is-up-over-260-heres-why-it-could-go/</link><description>The market dynamics are ideal for Micron's momentum to continue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/26/micron-stock-is-up-over-260-heres-why-it-could-go/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] London tech staff set for windfall after $4bn deal</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2026/01/26/london-tech-staff-set-for-windfall-after-4bn-deal/</link><description>Staff at a British tech startup are in line for a major windfall after an investment deal valued their company at $4bn (£2.9bn).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2026/01/26/london-tech-staff-set-for-windfall-after-4bn-deal/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bull of the Day: Nvidia (NVDA)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-nvidia-nvda-090000071.html</link><description>Nvidia's transformation from a gaming pioneer to the bedrock of the global AI revolution has solidified its future growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-nvidia-nvda-090000071.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Synthesia hits $4B valuation, lets employees cash out</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/synthesia-hits-4b-valuation-lets-090000792.html</link><description>British startup Synthesia, whose AI platform helps companies create interactive training videos, has raised a $200 million Series E round of funding that brings its valuation to $4 billion — up from $2.1 billion just a year ago.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/synthesia-hits-4b-valuation-lets-090000792.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Meta Earnings, Fed Decision, Venezuela Testimony: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-26-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-what-to-watch-this-week-1Jv5cZpyfIzUkTKxZyVz?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full throttle, with results expected from big-name companies including UnitedHealth, Chevron and Boeing. A quartet of tech giants—Apple, Meta Platforms, Microsoft and Tesla—will also report results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-26-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-what-to-watch-this-week-1Jv5cZpyfIzUkTKxZyVz?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Samsung to Win Memory-Chip Deal with Nvidia, Report Says. What It Means for Micron.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/samsung-nvida-chips-micron-stock-3a857e7c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Micron stock has surged on excitement around high-bandwidth memory chips but it doesn't have the market to itself.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/samsung-nvida-chips-micron-stock-3a857e7c?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>