<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NBIS] This Genius AI Stock Has Far More Potential Than Nvidia in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/this-genius-ai-stock-has-far-more-potential-than-n/</link><description>Nebius expects huge growth in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/this-genius-ai-stock-has-far-more-potential-than-n/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bitdeer (BTDR) Soars 15.6% on Nvidia GB200 Adoption</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitdeer-btdr-soars-15-6-101036390.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names Delivering Outsized Gains. Bitdeer Technologies Group (NASDAQ:BTDR) was one of the top performers on Wednesday. Bitdeer Technologies extended its winning streak to a third consecutive day on Wednesday, jumping 15.58 percent to finish at $14.76 apiece, as investors gobbled up shares following the launch of its NVIDIA GB200 NVL72 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitdeer-btdr-soars-15-6-101036390.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] European chip stocks rally after TSMC blowout earnings; ASML hits record high</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/european-chip-stocks-rally-tsmc-100600820.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Shares in ASML climbed to a fresh record on Thursday, lifting the Dutch semiconductor equipment group’s market value above $500 billion and reinforcing its position as Europe’s most valuable listed company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/european-chip-stocks-rally-tsmc-100600820.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC smashes forecasts with record profit, flags more U.S. factories</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-smashes-forecasts-record-profit-100501507.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: TSMC smashed profit forecasts in the fourth-quarter as the AI boom continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world's main producer of advanced AI chips said Thursday (January 15) profits jumped 35% to $16 billion during the October-December period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It further predicted strong growth this year and said it was working on building more U.S. manufacturing capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taiwanese firm - which counts Nvidia and Apple as major customers - announced plans last year to invest $100 billion in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was on top of $65 billion pledged for three plants in the state of Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TSMC said more land had been bought in the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York Times has also reported the Trump administration is close to a trade deal with Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It aims to reduce its tariff rate to 15% and Washington wants TSMC to commit to building at least five more facilities in Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, TSMC believes first-quarter revenue could surge as much as 40% from a year earlier to $35.8 billion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AI boom has helped TSMC outshine its rivals and its&amp;amp;nbsp;Taipei-listed shares jumped 44% last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm's stock is up around 9% so far this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-smashes-forecasts-record-profit-100501507.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why I Won't Touch the Sell Button on Alphabet Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/why-i-wont-touch-the-sell-button-on-alphabet-stock/</link><description>This company is clearly different than almost any other.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/why-i-wont-touch-the-sell-button-on-alphabet-stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Soars Above $500 Billion Value on TSMC’s Upbeat Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-soars-above-500-billion-093955329.html</link><description>ASML is only the third European company to reach the $500 billion milestone after luxury conglomerate LVMH and Danish drugmaker Novo Nordisk A/S.  ASML surged over the symbolic level after TSMC on Thursday forecast capital spending to rise to as much as $56 billion in 2026, more than expected, showing how the chipmaker is benefiting from the artificial intelligence boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-soars-above-500-billion-093955329.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Global Markets Mixed as Concerns Over Potential U.S. Strikes on Iran Ease</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/global-markets-mixed-as-concerns-over-potential-u-s-strikes-on-iran-ease-6cef77c1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>U.S. stock futures were mixed, while oil benchmarks fell along with precious metals, after Trump said Iran had stopped killing protesters.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/global-markets-mixed-as-concerns-over-potential-u-s-strikes-on-iran-ease-6cef77c1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Artificial Intelligence (AI) Still the Best Growth Theme for Long Term Investors?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/is-ai-still-the-best-growth-theme/</link><description>It's important to look ahead to what's next.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/is-ai-still-the-best-growth-theme/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trending tickers: TSMC, Google, Airbnb, Schroders, BP</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-google-airbnb-schroders-bp-trending-tickers-092715889.html</link><description>AI chips and tools moved markets on Thursday as earnings season continues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-google-airbnb-schroders-bp-trending-tickers-092715889.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML tops $500 billion market cap as TSMC results ignite semis rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-tops-500-billion-market-090946358.html</link><description>Jan 15 - Shares in ASML surged to ​a new all-time ‌high on Thursday, pushing its ‌market capitalisation past the $500 billion milestone and cementing its lead as ⁠Europe's ‌most valuable company. The surge in the Dutch ‍chipmaking equipment manufacturer was fuelled by TSMC's blockbuster ​results, which sparked a ‌broad rally across European semiconductor stocks. ASML shares were up around 5%, hitting a record 1,167 ⁠euros earlier ​in the session.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-tops-500-billion-market-090946358.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wikipedia owner signs on Microsoft, Meta in AI content training deals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wikipedia-owner-signs-microsoft-meta-083412169.html</link><description>Wikipedia on Thursday unveiled partnerships with several Big Tech companies including Microsoft, Meta and Amazon, marking a major step up in the ​non-profit's ability to monetize tech firms' reliance on its content.  Wikimedia Foundation, the operator ‌of the online encyclopedia, said it also signed on AI startup Perplexity and France's Mistral AI, among other firms, ‌over the past year, having enlisted Meta and Amazon as partners previously.  Wikipedia content is crucial to training AI models — its 65 million articles across over 300 languages are a key part of training data ⁠for generative AI chatbots and assistants ‌developed by tech majors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wikipedia-owner-signs-microsoft-meta-083412169.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank Earnings, Fed Speakers, Jobless Claims: Still to Come This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-15-2026/card/goldman-sachs-tsmc-earnings-fed-speakers-still-to-come-this-week-rFEQavMGnxfZXgVYWK7k?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>More big banks are scheduled to report earnings on Thursday. Investors will also check for any fallout from the criminal probe into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, plus any news on who may be the central bank's next chair.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-15-2026/card/goldman-sachs-tsmc-earnings-fed-speakers-still-to-come-this-week-rFEQavMGnxfZXgVYWK7k?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Heard on the Street Wednesday Recap: AI Selloff Resumes</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-15-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-wednesday-recap-ai-selloff-resumes-uRDRFbOcniXRKpvagebr?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>U.S. stock indexes fell, with the Nasdaq Composite dopping 1% for the first time in a month.  The S&amp;amp;P 500 declined 0.5% while the Dow industrials slipped 42 points.  The artificial-intelligence semiconductor leader must meet new security requirements to send H200 chips to China, the Trump administration said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-15-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-wednesday-recap-ai-selloff-resumes-uRDRFbOcniXRKpvagebr?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Lenovo’s Hybrid AI Platform Push Might Change The Case For Investing In Lenovo Group (SEHK:992)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lenovo-hybrid-ai-platform-push-080954428.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, Lenovo unveiled an extensive wave of Hybrid AI innovations at Tech World @ CES, spanning AI PCs and smartphones, new ThinkSystem and ThinkEdge inferencing servers, the Lenovo and Motorola Qira cross-device AI “super agent,” and expanded Hybrid AI Advantage offerings for enterprises and cloud providers. The breadth of these launches – from classroom Chromebooks and AI retail tools to NVIDIA-backed AI cloud “gigafactories” – underscores how Lenovo is positioning its...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lenovo-hybrid-ai-platform-push-080954428.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Taiwan computer chip maker TSMC's to expand investment as profit jumps 35%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-computer-chip-maker-tsmcs-080725424.html</link><description>Taiwan-based TSMC, the world’s largest computer chip maker, plans to increase its capital spending by about 40% this year after it reported a 35% jump in its net profit for the latest quarter thanks to the boom in artificial intelligence, the company said Thursday.  Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corp., a major supplier to companies including Nvidia and Apple, reported a net profit of 506 billion new Taiwan dollars ($16 billion) for the October-December quarter, a 35% surge from a year earlier, better than analysts’ estimates.  TSMC said Thursday that its revenue in the last quarter increased 21% from a year earlier to more than 1.046 trillion new Taiwan dollars ($33 billion).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-computer-chip-maker-tsmcs-080725424.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-15/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (NYSE:TSM) reported fourth-quarter 2025 results that management said were supported by strong demand for leading-edge process technologies, while outlining a stepped-up investment plan and a long-term growth framework driven largely by AI-related demand. Fourth-qu</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-15/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:03:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Boosts UNM Price Target, Sees Life Insurers Supported by Consolidation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-boosts-unm-price-target-075048654.html</link><description>Unum Group (NYSE:UNM) is included among the 14 Best Mid Cap Dividend Aristocrat Stocks to Buy Now. On January 8, Barclays raised its price target on Unum Group (NYSE:UNM) to $96 from $94 and maintained an Overweight rating. The firm said it remains “cautiously optimistic” on life insurers as the industry heads into 2026. Barclays […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-boosts-unm-price-target-075048654.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC: Q4 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-earnings-snapshot-074852663.html</link><description>HSINCHU, Taiwan (AP) — Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSM) on Thursday reported fourth-quarter net income of $16.31 billion. The Hsinchu, Taiwan-based company said it had profit of $3.14 per share. The results topped Wall Street expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-earnings-snapshot-074852663.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates 2026 View on Life Insurers, Lowers RGA Price Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-2026-view-life-074149491.html</link><description>Reinsurance Group of America, Incorporated (NYSE:RGA) is included among the 14 Best Mid Cap Dividend Aristocrat Stocks to Buy Now. On January 8, Barclays reduced its price target on Reinsurance Group of America, Incorporated (NYSE:RGA) to $237 from $251, while still maintaining an Overweight rating. The firm said it is heading into 2026 feeling “cautiously […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-2026-view-life-074149491.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] RenaissanceRe (RNR) Target Lifted by TD Cowen and Barclays as Market Pricing Softens</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/renaissancere-rnr-target-lifted-td-073724479.html</link><description>RenaissanceRe Holdings Ltd. (NYSE:RNR) is included among the 14 Best Mid Cap Dividend Aristocrat Stocks to Buy Now. On January 8, TD Cowen nudged up its price target on RenaissanceRe Holdings Ltd. (NYSE:RNR) to $280 from $278 and maintained a Hold rating. The firm said the move came after updating its model ahead of the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/renaissancere-rnr-target-lifted-td-073724479.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump imposes 25% tariff on imports of some AI chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-072910627.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: :: File&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday imposed a 25% tariff on certain AI chips under a new national security order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Affected products include Nvidia's H200 and a rival semiconductor from AMD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proclamation says “the United States currently fully manufactures only approximately 10 percent of the chips it requires, making it heavily reliant on foreign supply chains."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It says such reliance is a "significant economic and national security risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move follows a nine-month investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It targets a number of high-end semiconductors meeting certain performance benchmarks and devices containing them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it exempts chips bound for new data centers.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Nvidia, AMD and Qualcomm edged lower in after-hours trading following the news.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration this week required that China-bound Nvidia H200 chips make a detour to the U.S. from Taiwan, where they are made, for testing by a third-party lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: Nvidia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the chips enter the U.S., they are subject to the new 25% levy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, Taiwan signaled it was close to a deal with the U.S. on tariffs on its goods.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taiwan has been in talks with the U.S. to get the levies on its exports cut from 20% to 15%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Reuters sources said an announcement on a&amp;amp;nbsp;deal could come by the end of the month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-072910627.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Got $3,000? 4 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks to Buy and Hold for the Long Term</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/got-3000-4-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-to-bu/</link><description>The effects of AI investments will benefit investors for years to come.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/15/got-3000-4-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-to-bu/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] TSMC’s Strong Outlook Shores Up Hopes of Sustained AI Boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-strong-outlook-shores-hopes-072434087.html</link><description>It also foresees revenue growth of close to 30% in 2026, faster than the average analyst estimate.  Shares in key supplier ASML Holding NV rose 5% on Tradegate in Europe.  The outlook from TSMC — a bellwether for the artificial intelligence boom — reflects a development frenzy by the likes of Meta Platforms Inc. and Amazon.com Inc. that’s spurred demand for Nvidia Corp. accelerators.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-strong-outlook-shores-hopes-072434087.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC Says Spending to Surge in Strong Signal for AI Boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-says-spending-surge-strong-065646551.html</link><description>TSMC surpassed $100 billion in annual revenue for the first time in 2025 and expects capital spending to surge to as much as $56 billion in 2026. The stronger-than-anticipated projection signals its confidence in the longevity of the global AI boom. Bloomberg Intelligence's Robert Lea breaks down the numbers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tsmc-says-spending-surge-strong-065646551.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Bonds Could Devour Credit Markets. Let Stock Investors Take the Risk.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-bonds-credit-markets-stocks-7a1dc0b1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Amazon, Meta, and other large tech companies are issuing more debt than ever. Why you should steer clear.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-bonds-credit-markets-stocks-7a1dc0b1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Taiwan's TSMC logs net profit jump on AI boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwans-tsmc-logs-net-profit-061920911.html</link><description>Taiwanese chipmaking titan TSMC announced Thursday a forecast-busting net profit for the fourth quarter in a sign of sustained global demand for AI technology.Net revenue for the fourth quarter rose 20.5 percent from a year ago to NT$1.05 trillion, TSMC said, also beating expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwans-tsmc-logs-net-profit-061920911.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How The Evolving Story On NMI Holdings (NMIH) Is Shaping Fresh Views On Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evolving-story-nmi-holdings-nmih-060918826.html</link><description>NMI Holdings has just seen a small lift in its fair value estimate, rising from US$44.14 to US$45.14, alongside a slightly lower discount rate assumption of 7.64% instead of 7.72%. These tweaks reflect recent Street research that balances confidence in a stable credit backdrop and potential support from a stronger mortgage origination market in 2026 with ongoing caution around sector regulation and volatility. Stay tuned to see how you can keep track of these kinds of narrative shifts as they...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evolving-story-nmi-holdings-nmih-060918826.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC Ends 2025 With a Bang as AI Keeps Boosting Profits</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/tsmc-ends-2025-with-a-bang-as-ai-keeps-boosting-profits-9f775b1e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The world’s largest contract chip maker ended 2025 with another quarter of record earnings amid supply challenges and mounting pressure to bring production to American soil.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/tsmc-ends-2025-with-a-bang-as-ai-keeps-boosting-profits-9f775b1e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] NatWest, Barclays, Nationwide and Halifax cut mortgage costs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-barclays-halifax-bank-of-england-interest-rates-060030835.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-barclays-halifax-bank-of-england-interest-rates-060030835.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC Q4 profit jumps 35% to record, beats expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-profit-jumps-35-053601365.html</link><description>TSMC, the world's largest ​contract chipmaker, posted ‌a 35% jump in fourth-quarter ‌net profit on Thursday, beating market forecasts and hitting a record as ⁠it benefited ‌from surging demand for semiconductors used ‍in artificial intelligence applications. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co, whose customers include ​Nvidia and Apple, ‌saw October-December net profit rise to T$505.7 billion ($16.01 billion). The profit handily beat a T$478.4 billion LSEG ⁠SmartEstimate, which is ​weighted toward ​forecasts from analysts who are more consistently accurate.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-q4-profit-jumps-35-053601365.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 Reasons to Buy Alphabet (Google) Stock Like There's No Tomorrow</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/5-reasons-to-buy-alphabet-google-stock-like-theres/</link><description>Google's parent was the biggest winner among the "Magnificent Seven" stocks over the last 12 months. Its momentum could continue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/5-reasons-to-buy-alphabet-google-stock-like-theres/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] JPM26: Novo Nordisk reshapes its strategy under new CEO</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/analyst-comment/jpm26-novo-nordisk-reshapes-its-strategy-under-new-ceo/</link><description>Novo is positioning itself as a long‑term leader across multiple obesity segments.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/analyst-comment/jpm26-novo-nordisk-reshapes-its-strategy-under-new-ceo/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] JPM26: Eli Lilly enters 2026 with strong momentum given pipeline innovation</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/analyst-comment/jpm26-eli-lilly-enters-2026-with-strong-momentum-given-pipeline-innovation/</link><description>Lilly has launched six early-stage clinical programs, and 34 discovery programs with a focus on incretins, amylins, and novel targets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/analyst-comment/jpm26-eli-lilly-enters-2026-with-strong-momentum-given-pipeline-innovation/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China drafting purchase rules for Nvidia H200 chips, Nikkei Asia reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-drafting-purchase-rules-nvidia-032124261.html</link><description>China is working to set rules on how many advanced artificial ​intelligence chip companies can buy from foreign ‌makers such as Nvidia, Nikkei Asia reported on Thursday, citing ‌two people familiar with the matter.  The Chinese central government is working on rules that will likely regulate the total volume of cutting-edge AI chips ⁠local companies can ‌purchase, effectively allowing some sales by Nvidia instead of banning them outright, the ‍report added.  Nvidia declined to comment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-drafting-purchase-rules-nvidia-032124261.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO delivers biblical-scale reality check on AI</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-delivers-biblical-scale-reality-check-on-ai</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang said, before bluntly saying that we’re nowhere close to that day. The statement took me, and probably everyone covering AI, aback, as it breaks sharply from what we’ve come to expect from Huang and others like him. In contrast to the flamboyance Huang typically ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-delivers-biblical-scale-reality-check-on-ai</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia vs. Alphabet: Which Is the Better AI Growth Stock for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidia-vs-alphabet-which-is-the-better-ai-growth-s/</link><description>Both companies are riding the AI wave, but one stock offers a better mix of growth momentum and valuation today.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidia-vs-alphabet-which-is-the-better-ai-growth-s/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] A Look At monday.com (MNDY) Valuation After Barclays Target Cut And Revenue Guidance Concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/look-monday-com-mndy-valuation-021624640.html</link><description>monday.com (MNDY) has drawn fresh attention after Barclays cut its price target, citing softer revenue guidance that fell short of expectations and coincided with a single-day drop of about 5%. See our latest analysis for monday.com. The recent 6.39% one day share price decline and 13.72% 30 day share price return extend a weaker trend, with a 26.34% 90 day share price pullback and a 44.34% 1 year total shareholder return loss suggesting fading momentum despite a modestly positive 3 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/look-monday-com-mndy-valuation-021624640.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Condo Owner Says HOA Fining $500 A Month Over 'Loud' Floors Installed Before He Bought Unit—Claims 'Board Tyrant' Tried To Personally Rip Them Up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/condo-owner-says-hoa-fining-020108538.html</link><description>Before buying the condo, it looked like the hard part had already been done. The previous unit burned, the interior was fully rebuilt, and the new buyer figured that anything installed post-fire—especially by the restoration company—had to be compliant. But...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/condo-owner-says-hoa-fining-020108538.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 AI ETFs Poised for 100% Surge as Tech Revolution Accelerates</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/3-ai-etfs-poised-for-100-surge-as-tech-revolution/</link><description>Investors have been able to enjoy huge gains from artificial intelligence (AI) stocks. We're still in the early innings, though, and that means opportunities are still available.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/3-ai-etfs-poised-for-100-surge-as-tech-revolution/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump Says Microsoft, Big Tech Must Bear Data Center Power Bills, So Americans Don't 'Pick Up The Tab'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-microsoft-big-tech-013109981.html</link><description>President Donald Trump announced on Monday that his administration is working with major U.S. tech companies, particularly Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT), to prevent Americans from bearing the brunt of data center power consumption. Through a Truth Social post, Trump said: “I never want Americans to pay higher electricity bills because of data centers.” He highlighted that the U.S is “Number One” in AI and that data centers are key to the AI boom, but emphasized that the tech companies must</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-microsoft-big-tech-013109981.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] JGB Yield Curve Likely to Steepen Further</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/investing/jgbs-rise-tracking-gains-in-u-s-treasurys-8ff30fc5?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The JGB yield curve could steepen further, said HSBC Global Investment Research, which maintains a mildly bearish stance on Japanese bonds.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/investing/jgbs-rise-tracking-gains-in-u-s-treasurys-8ff30fc5?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should You Forget Nvidia and Buy These 2 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks Instead?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/forget-nvidia-buy-artificial-intelligence-ai/</link><description>Broadcom and Taiwan Semiconductor have the potential to outperform Nvidia in the coming years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/forget-nvidia-buy-artificial-intelligence-ai/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Review &amp; Preview: Not So Magnificent</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-today-rotation-mag-7-selloff-318554f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>FEATURE S&amp;amp;P 493. A wave of selling in technology stocks overshadowed an otherwise decent day on Wall Street. The Nasdaq Composite dropped 1%. The S&amp;amp;P 500 fell 0.5%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 42 points, or 0.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-today-rotation-mag-7-selloff-318554f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Where Will Nvidia Stock Be in 5 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/where-will-nvidia-stock-be-in-5-years/</link><description>Nvidia has made investors significantly richer in the past five years, but can it continue to deliver more upside in the long run?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/where-will-nvidia-stock-be-in-5-years/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix Bets $13 Billion To Lock In AI Memory Dominance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-bets-13-billion-003113661.html</link><description>SK Hynix, Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd. (OTC:SSNLF), and global rivals, including Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Ltd. (NYSE:TSM) and Micron Technology Inc. (NASDAQ:MU), are accelerating investments as competition intensifies to supply high-bandwidth memory and advanced chips for the artificial intelligence boom. SK Hynix Commits $13 Billion To Expand AI Memory Capacity SK Hynix is ramping up investment to strengthen its position in the global AI chip supply chain as demand for high-ba</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-bets-13-billion-003113661.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM tackles cloud, AI sovereignty with new platform</title><link>https://www.ciodive.com/news/ibm-unveils-sovereignty-platform-cloud-ai/809667/</link><description>Built on Red Hat's open source foundation, Sovereign Core aims to inherently provide control over the environment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ciodive.com/news/ibm-unveils-sovereignty-platform-cloud-ai/809667/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank earnings, Fed comments, jobless claims: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-fed-comments-jobless-000000630.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come tomorrow, Thursday, January 15, including earnings results from Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM), Morgan Stanley (MS), Goldman Sachs (GS), and BlackRock (BLK); commentary from Federal Reserve officials; and the latest reading on initial jobless claims. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-fed-comments-jobless-000000630.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump imposes 25% tariff on imports of some AI chips</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-214026683.html</link><description>Jan 14 (Reuters) - U.S.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-214026683.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures rise as chipmaker TSMC's strong outlook buoys optimism for AI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-as-chipmaker-tsmcs-strong-outlook-buoys-optimism-for-ai-235521259.html</link><description>Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-as-chipmaker-tsmcs-strong-outlook-buoys-optimism-for-ai-235521259.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures stall after Wall Street's first back-to-back losses this year</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-stall-after-wall-streets-first-back-to-back-losses-this-year-235521412.html</link><description>Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-stall-after-wall-streets-first-back-to-back-losses-this-year-235521412.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures slip after Wall Street's first back-to-back losses in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-after-wall-streets-first-back-to-back-losses-in-2026-235521867.html</link><description>Stock futures fell following consecutive days of losses. Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slip-after-wall-streets-first-back-to-back-losses-in-2026-235521867.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures slide after Wall Street's first back-to-back losses in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slide-after-wall-streets-first-back-to-back-losses-in-2026-235521066.html</link><description>Stock futures fell following consecutive days of losses. Investors have been buffeted by industry losses and geopolitical issues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-slide-after-wall-streets-first-back-to-back-losses-in-2026-235521066.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet and Amazon Just Said Something That May Eliminate Nvidia's Biggest Risk</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/something-that-may-eliminate-nvidia-biggest-risk/</link><description>Investors have wondered how long Nvidia may hold onto its AI leadership.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/something-that-may-eliminate-nvidia-biggest-risk/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Astrazeneca (AZN) Ascends While Market Falls: Some Facts to Note</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/astrazeneca-azn-ascends-while-market-231506316.html</link><description>Astrazeneca (AZN) closed the most recent trading day at $96.34, moving +1.94% from the previous trading session.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/astrazeneca-azn-ascends-while-market-231506316.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 14: Intel Jumps on Sold Out 2026 Server CPU Capacity</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/14/stock-market-today-jan-14-intel-jumps-on-sold-out-2026-server-cpu-capacity/</link><description>On Jan. 14, 2026, investors weighed fresh AI server demand signals and foundry wins that sharpen the stakes of Intel’s turnaround.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/14/stock-market-today-jan-14-intel-jumps-on-sold-out-2026-server-cpu-capacity/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump enacts 25% tariff on chips — with a caveat</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/14/tech/chip-tariff-trump</link><description>President Donald Trump enacted a new 25% tariff on “certain advanced computing chips” on Wednesday, according to a White House fact sheet. That includes Nvidia’s H200 chip and AMD’s MI325X. However, chips imported to support building up the US technological supply chain would be exempt.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/14/tech/chip-tariff-trump</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy the "Magnificent Seven" Laggards in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-you-buy-magnificent-seven-laggards-2026/</link><description>Investors often look at stocks that struggled in a previous year and are currently out of favor to see if there is an investment case to be made.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-you-buy-magnificent-seven-laggards-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Futures: Market Split With Tesla, Broadcom, AppLovin, Wells Fargo Key Losers; Nvidia Chipmaker Due</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-broadcom-applovin-wells-fargo-losers-nvidia-chipmaker-taiwan-semi/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Small caps hit a new high but Tesla, Broadcom, AppLovin and Wells Fargo weighed on the major indexes. Nvidia chipmaker Taiwan Semi looms.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-broadcom-applovin-wells-fargo-losers-nvidia-chipmaker-taiwan-semi/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Tech Investors Worry About High Prices, Regulation</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/tech-investors-worry-about-high-prices-regulation-lcZSxX44ZOML6TnS0Ncx?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tech stocks stumbled Wednesday with investors voicing concerns about high valuations and burdensome new rules.  Nvidia fell 1.4%, dragging down the Nasdaq composite, which ended the day 1% lower.  The Russell 2000 index of smaller companies jumped 0.7% to its fourth record high of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/tech-investors-worry-about-high-prices-regulation-lcZSxX44ZOML6TnS0Ncx?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) Falls More Steeply Than Broader Market: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-falls-more-224506360.html</link><description>In the latest trading session, Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) closed at $206.1, marking a -1.57% move from the previous day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-falls-more-224506360.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Systems (CSCO) Registers a Bigger Fall Than the Market: Important Facts to Note</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-registers-bigger-224504543.html</link><description>Cisco Systems (CSCO) reached $74.4 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a -1.41% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-registers-bigger-224504543.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Here's Why CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Fell More Than Broader Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-224503871.html</link><description>In the closing of the recent trading day, CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) stood at $460.63, denoting a -1.58% move from the preceding trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-224503871.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Undervalued Artificial Intelligence (AI) Semiconductor Stock Looks Like a Better Buy Than Nvidia or Broadcom in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/artificial-intelligence-ai-semiconductor-stock-tsm/</link><description>This chip giant is flexing its pricing power and is on a path to strong profit growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/artificial-intelligence-ai-semiconductor-stock-tsm/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 14: Nvidia Leads Tech Losses as Investors Cool on AI</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/14/stock-market-today-jan-14-nvidia-leads-tech-losses-as-investors-cool-on-ai/</link><description>Tech and bank stocks weighed on markets as a risk-off sentiment took hold today, Jan. 14, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/14/stock-market-today-jan-14-nvidia-leads-tech-losses-as-investors-cool-on-ai/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Tech Spending Is Still Strong. There’s 1 Big Winner and Plenty of Losers.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-stocks-microsoft-amazon-oracle-a633e1b4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>This year’s growth in IT spending could reach its fastest pace since the pandemic. Why Microsoft is the big winner.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ai-stocks-microsoft-amazon-oracle-a633e1b4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC likely to post fourth-quarter profit leap driven by AI boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-221545201.html</link><description>TAIPEI, Jan 15 () - TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 28% jump in fourth-quarter net profit to a ​record high on Thursday driven by ongoing strong demand for AI infrastructure. Taiwan Semiconductor ‌Manufacturing Co, the world's top contract chipmaker and a key supplier to Nvidia and Apple, is forecast to report a ‌net profit of T$479.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-221545201.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Xi Welcomes Stream of Leaders Shaken by Trump’s New World Order</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xi-welcomes-stream-leaders-shaken-103000921.html</link><description>Now, President Xi Jinping is welcoming a procession of leaders looking to mend fences with the world’s other major economy.  Canada’s Mark Carney followed suit when he arrived late Wednesday, closing a near-decade gap in leader-to-leader diplomacy between Ottawa and Beijing in the Asian nation.  Days later, Prime Minister Keir Starmer is set to travel to the Chinese capital to buoy British business, marking a first since 2018.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xi-welcomes-stream-leaders-shaken-103000921.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC smashes forecasts with record profit as it rides AI boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-221107479.html</link><description>TSMC, the world's main producer of advanced AI chips and a major supplier ​to Nvidia, on Thursday posted a 35% jump in fourth-quarter profit to record ‌levels that blew past market forecasts and predicted more robust growth this year.  Riding high on the global ‌boom in artificial intelligence, it said first-quarter revenue could surge as much as 40% from a year earlier to $35.8 billion, adding that it expected to increase capital spending in 2026 to as much as 37% to $56 billion.  Customers were "providing strong signals" and reaching out directly ⁠to request capacity, said TSMC, Asia's ‌most valuable listed company with a market capitalisation of around $1.4 trillion - more than twice that of South Korean rival Samsung Electronics.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-likely-post-fourth-quarter-221107479.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Tech Slide Drags Nasdaq Composite to Worst Day in a Month</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/global-stocks-markets-dow-news-01-14-2026-3cccf726?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tech stocks retreated Wednesday, with declines in  Nvidia  and other chip companies dragging the Nasdaq composite to its worst day in almost a month.  On Tuesday, the Trump administration said Nvidia must meet new security requirements before sending H200 artificial-intelligence chips to China.  Meanwhile, Florida Gov.  Ron DeSantis  reiterated plans for consumer protection rules on artificial intelligence.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/stocks/global-stocks-markets-dow-news-01-14-2026-3cccf726?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Apple's AI partnership with Google a major loss for OpenAI?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-ai-partnership-google-major-214700767.html</link><description>OpenAI (OPAI.PVT) is reportedly taking early steps to go public, according to the New York Times, setting up 2026 to be the "Year of the Mega IPO." While co-founder and CEO Sam Altman is "zero percent" interested in leading a public company, he stated that OpenAI needed to continue raising more funds. Yahoo Finance Tech and Markets Reporter Laura Bratton comes on Market Domination Overtime to discuss OpenAI's spending forecasts, going into detail how Apple's (AAPL) partnership with Alphabet's Google Gemini 3 (GOOG, GOOGL) is a major loss for OpenAI. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apples-ai-partnership-google-major-214700767.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump imposes 25% tariff on imports of some advanced computing chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-214026806.html</link><description>U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday imposed a ​25% tariff on certain advanced computing ‌chips, such as the Nvidia H200 AI ‌processor and a similar semiconductor from AMD called the MI325X, according to a fact sheet released by the White ⁠House.  The proclamation cited ‌national security concerns for the tariffs, and is part of ‍a broader effort to create incentives for chipmakers to produce more semiconductors in the ​U.S. and decrease reliance on ‌chip manufacturers in places like Taiwan.  The tariff will not apply to chips imported for U.S. data centers, startups, non-data center consumer applications, non-data center civil ⁠industrial applications and U.S. ​public sector applications.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-imposes-25-tariff-imports-214026806.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet vs. OpenAI: Which AI Giant Will Drive 100% Gains?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-vs-openai-which-ai-giant-will-drive-x-gai/</link><description>AI is big business, but can the start-up that made it mainstream stand up to an industry giant throwing its weight around?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-vs-openai-which-ai-giant-will-drive-x-gai/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Elon Musk Slams Google, Apple Deal: 'Unreasonable Concentration Of Power'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-slams-google-apple-213106434.html</link><description>Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla, Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) and xAI, voiced criticism of the AI partnership between Apple, Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) and Alphabet, Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) announced on Monday. In a post on X replying to the News from Google account, Musk questioned the partnership as possibly allowing Google too much "power," considering it owns the Android operating system and Chrome browser. "This seems like an unreasonable concentration of power for Google, given that the[y] also have Andro</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-slams-google-apple-213106434.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] How major US stock indexes fared Wednesday, 1/14/2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/major-us-stock-indexes-fared-211913514.html</link><description>Losses for several banks and Big Tech stocks pulled U.S. indexes lower, even though most stocks on Wall Street rose. The S&amp;amp;P 500 sank 0.5% Wednesday for its second straight loss after setting its all-time high. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dipped 0.1%, and the Nasdaq composite lost 1%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/major-us-stock-indexes-fared-211913514.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google vs. Apple: Which Magnificent 7 Stock is a Better Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37047986/google-vs-apple-which-magnificent-7-stock-is-a-better-buy-right-now</link><description>After these two Mag 7 rivals finally partnered on AI, which stock is worth the investment?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37047986/google-vs-apple-which-magnificent-7-stock-is-a-better-buy-right-now</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nasdaq Drops 1%. Small Stocks Take Lead From Big Tech.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/nasdaq-drops-1-small-stocks-take-lead-from-big-tech--4SP73wyThk4PhB7mspng?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A rotation away from large technology stocks dragged down the major indexes on Wednesday. The Nasdaq Composite fell 1%. The S&amp;amp;P 500 dropped 0.6%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 66 points, or 0.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/nasdaq-drops-1-small-stocks-take-lead-from-big-tech--4SP73wyThk4PhB7mspng?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why the Nasdaq Composite Is Lagging the S&amp;P 500 and Dow</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/why-the-nasdaq-composite-is-lagging-the-s-p-500-and-dow-J9b196YXOLfheNb7RmC4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A rotation away from Big Tech and into smaller stocks was a big drag on the Nasdaq Composite on Wednesday.  The tech-heavy index fell 1.2%, while the S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.7%.  The Dow was down just 100 points, or 0.2%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011426/card/why-the-nasdaq-composite-is-lagging-the-s-p-500-and-dow-J9b196YXOLfheNb7RmC4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump Shares Post Accusing Netflix Of Being 'Woke' — Is President Signaling He Won't Support Warner Bros. Merger?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-shares-post-accusing-netflix-203116774.html</link><description>The merger between Netflix Inc (NASDAQ:NFLX) and Warner Bros. Discovery (NASDAQ:WBD), which has seen Paramount Skydance (NASDAQ:PSKY) try to play spoiler, could have a new wrinkle with President Donald Trump sharing a piece on social media in opposition to the tie-up. Trump's Social Media Post Could Worry Netflix Netflix is the current winning bidder for Warner Bros. Discovery, with the streaming giant acquiring the film and television studio and streaming assets from the media giant. That deal</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-shares-post-accusing-netflix-203116774.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is This the Smartest Growth Stock to Buy Heading Into 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/is-this-the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-heading-i/</link><description>The biggest tech stock is still one of the smartest picks of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/is-this-the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-heading-i/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft Stock Ready to Rebound After Recent Slide</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-stock-ready-rebound-recent-201023104.html</link><description>The security is trading near a historically bullish trendline</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-stock-ready-rebound-recent-201023104.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Tech Selloff Weighs on Nasdaq; Precious Metals Scale New Peaks</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/u-s-futures-fall-precious-metals-gain-on-iranian-unrest-d8a82a84</link><description>Stocks retreated, with the Nasdaq composite leading declines as Nvidia and other chip stocks such as Broadcom and Arm Holdings traded lower.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/finance/u-s-futures-fall-precious-metals-gain-on-iranian-unrest-d8a82a84</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] MongoDB, DigitalOcean, Cadence Design Systems, HubSpot, and Workday Shares Are Falling, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mongodb-digitalocean-cadence-design-systems-200619096.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after markets pulled back as reports surfaced that Chinese customs authorities blocked Nvidia's H200 AI chips, effectively halting their entry despite recent U.S. export approvals.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mongodb-digitalocean-cadence-design-systems-200619096.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Autodesk and Nutanix Shares Are Falling, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/autodesk-nutanix-shares-falling-know-200617640.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after tech stocks pulled back as reports surfaced that Chinese customs authorities blocked Nvidia's H200 AI chips, effectively halting their entry despite recent U.S. export approvals.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/autodesk-nutanix-shares-falling-know-200617640.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why these 5 tech stocks could dominate the market in 2026</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/video/why-these-5-tech-stocks-could-dominate-the-market-in-2026</link><description>Transcript: Caroline Woods Here with his top tech picks for 2026 is Daniel Newman, the CEO of the Futurum Group. Daniel, great to have you. Good to be with you. So let's get right into it. Not in any particular order, but Micron top pick up 20% in 2026 already and still undervalued. Daniel Newman ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/video/why-these-5-tech-stocks-could-dominate-the-market-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Why Japanese Stocks Are Hitting Record Highs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-japanese-stocks-hitting-record-194400200.html</link><description>We examine the key drivers behind record gains in Japan ETFs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-japanese-stocks-hitting-record-194400200.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly's Most Promising Weight Loss Drug May Come With a Surprising Benefit: Pain Relief</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/eli-lilly-most-promising-weight-loss-drug-may-come/</link><description>Retatrutide is an exciting GLP-1 drug that has explosive potential.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/eli-lilly-most-promising-weight-loss-drug-may-come/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta Hires Former Trump Adviser, Senator's Wife: President Says Zuckerberg Made 'A Great Choice'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-hires-former-trump-adviser-193114816.html</link><description>Meta Platforms (NASDAQ:META) could look more like an AI stock in the coming years than a social media company thanks to new investments. The company recently partnered with the nuclear sector to help power future growth. On Monday, while there were multiple headlines about the social media company, one caught the attention of President Donald Trump. Meta Adds Former Trump Adviser Dina Powell McCormick was named as the president and vice chairman for Meta Platforms on Monday, which brings the for</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-hires-former-trump-adviser-193114816.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Amid the AI boom, Intel is focusing on the basics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amid-the-ai-boom-intel-is-focusing-on-the-basics-192933560.html</link><description>Intel's Core Ultra Series 3 could be the key to the company's turnaround effort.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amid-the-ai-boom-intel-is-focusing-on-the-basics-192933560.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] After Apple Deal, Is Google — Not OpenAI — Now the Premier AI Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37046543/after-apple-deal-is-google-not-openai-now-the-premier-ai-stock</link><description>Alphabet's strategic AI advancements, highlighted by the transformative Apple partnership and strong 2025 performance, position it as a leading contender in the evolving technology landscape.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37046543/after-apple-deal-is-google-not-openai-now-the-premier-ai-stock</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump's greenlight for Nvidia AI chips to China draws fire from lawmakers, former officials</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-greenlight-nvidia-ai-chips-185729502.html</link><description>By Alexandra Alper WASHINGTON, Jan 14 (Reuters) - U.S. lawmakers and former officials on Wednesday questioned President Donald Trump's decision to allow Nvidia to sell its second most powerful AI</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-greenlight-nvidia-ai-chips-185729502.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: Self-Driving Cars | TSLA Stock, GOOGL Stock, UBER Stock, NVDA Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-self-driving-cars-tsla-stock-googl-stock-uber-stock-nvda-stock/</link><description>24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are kicking the New Year off in style with 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. Over the course of 12 videos, the two will share their thoughts on everything from the memory explosion to software stocks to robotics. In this video, Eric and Austin focus on recent developments in self-driving cars. Specifically, NVIDIA just launched its new Alpamayo suite of self-driving models. That move serves as a level of validation to Tesla's vision-only strategy, but also could create more competition for Tesla as well. Eric and Austin also look at the growth rate of Waymo's ridership in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-self-driving-cars-tsla-stock-googl-stock-uber-stock-nvda-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] JPMorgan's Q4 Results To Reveal If Dealmaking Will Replace Rate-Driven Profits For Big Banks In 2026— SpaceX's $1.5 Trillion IPO In Focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgans-q4-results-reveal-dealmaking-190108783.html</link><description>JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. (NYSE:JPM) is set to report its fourth-quarter results before markets open on Tuesday, kickstarting the bank earnings season. Leading analysts expect the company to set the tone for the entire industry in 2026, with several key catalysts lining up. Dealmaking Set To Replace Rate-Driven Profits? “The story for 2026 is really going to be about deal-making,” said Alexis Garcia, Senior Editor at Investor’s Business Daily, noting that investment banking and trading revenue will b</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgans-q4-results-reveal-dealmaking-190108783.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Return of CPUs | INTC Stock, AMD Stock, NVDA Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-return-of-cpus-intc-stock-amd-stock-nvda-stock/</link><description>24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are kicking the New Year off in style with 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. Over the course of 12 videos, the two will share their thoughts on everything from the memory explosion to software stocks to robotics. In this video, Eric focuses on the unexpected return of CPUs in 2026. The rise of AI agents and Reinforcement Learning Environments is creating enormous demand for CPUs. That could lead to significant pricing power for leading CPU companies like Intel (Nasdaq: INTC) and AMD (Nasdaq: AMD).</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-return-of-cpus-intc-stock-amd-stock-nvda-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Rise of AI Factories | VRT Stock, NVT Stock, MOD Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</link><description>24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are kicking the New Year off in style with 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. Over the course of 12 videos, the two will share their thoughts on everything from the memory explosion to software stocks to robotics. In this video, Eric takes a deeper look at the rise of AI factories, massive data centers with a capacity of more than 1 gigawatt. As Eric notes, it's not just Oracle's Stargate getting into the race. There are also new super factories from Microsoft, Amazon, Meta, and many others. Companies with data center cooling portfolios like Vertiv (NYSE: VRT), nVent Electric (NYSE: NVT), Modine Manufacturing (NYSE: MOD) could be winners as the construction of this new generation of data centers takes off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Why Arm Holdings Stock Lost 11% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-arm-holdings-stock-lost-11-in-2025/</link><description>The chip stock was trading up for most of the year but fell late in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-arm-holdings-stock-lost-11-in-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Navitas Semiconductors Doubled in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-navitas-semiconductors-doubled-in-2025/</link><description>When a small-cap stock announces a possible partnership with Nvidia, that's a recipe for big gains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-navitas-semiconductors-doubled-in-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Why Eli Lilly Stock Gained 39.2% In 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-eli-lilly-stock-gained-392-in-2025/</link><description>The company is benefiting mightily from its portfolio of weight-loss drugs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-eli-lilly-stock-gained-392-in-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] JPM26: AstraZeneca bids to accelerate oncology R&amp;D with Modella AI acquisition</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/jpm26-astrazeneca-bids-to-accelerate-oncology-rd-with-modella-ai-acquisition/</link><description>The company is embracing AI integration throughout drug development, aiming to improve efficiency and drive portfolio expansion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/jpm26-astrazeneca-bids-to-accelerate-oncology-rd-with-modella-ai-acquisition/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia &amp; Broadcom stocks dragged by China's tech bans: Reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-broadcom-stocks-dragged-chinas-181524268.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance anchor Josh Lipton tracks Wednesday's top moving stocks and biggest market stories in this Market Minute. Nvidia (NVDA) stock is under pressure after Reuters reported that China is not allowing the sale of its H200 chips. There are also reports that China is banning Chinese companies from using US cybersecurity software, sending Broadcom (AVGO) stock lower. Meanwhile, AppLovin (APP) is the worst performer in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (^GSPC) so far in Wednesday's trading session. Stay up to date on the latest market action, minute-by-minute, with Yahoo Finance's Market Minute.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-broadcom-stocks-dragged-chinas-181524268.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Vertiv Sets Up After 43% Gain; Nvidia's Rubin To Boost AI Infrastructure Demand</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/vertiv-vrt-stock-nvidia-nvda-ai-data-center/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Ai data center infrastructure play Vertiv stock is setting up in an early-stage double-bottom base that has a buy point of 189.66.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/vertiv-vrt-stock-nvidia-nvda-ai-data-center/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AMD stock bets shift after analyst drops $15 billon message</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/amd-stock-shifts-after-analyst-drops-comments-before-earnings</link><description>AMD(Advanced Micro Devices) is set to announce its Q4 and full fiscal year 2025 report on February 3, 2026, after the market close. Ahead of this, the semiconductor company's shares are reacting to new research from analysts at KeyBanc. The company, under the leadership of CEO Lisa Su, has grown ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/amd-stock-shifts-after-analyst-drops-comments-before-earnings</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Wolfe Research Raises Citigroup (C) PT Citing Constructive Outlook for Preferred Subsectors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wolfe-research-raises-citigroup-c-175330335.html</link><description>Citigroup Inc. (NYSE:C) is one of the cheap S&amp;amp;P 500 stocks to invest in now. On January 7, Wolfe Research raised the firm’s price target on Citi to $141 from $121 and maintained an Outperform rating on the shares. As part of the firm’s Top 10 Themes for 2026 report, Wolfe Research highlighted Retail Brokers […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wolfe-research-raises-citigroup-c-175330335.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Mizuho Raises PT on NVIDIA (NVDA) Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mizuho-raises-pt-nvidia-nvda-175302588.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the Best Fundamental Stocks to Buy According to Analysts. On January 9, Mizuho analyst Vijay Rakesh lifted the price objective on NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA)’s stock to $275 from $245, while keeping an “Outperform” rating, as reported by The Fly. Notably, the firm adjusted targets in the broader semiconductors and semiconductor capital equipment group with respect […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mizuho-raises-pt-nvidia-nvda-175302588.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Super Micro Computer (SMCI) Announces Collaboration with Technology Partners</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/super-micro-computer-smci-announces-175301207.html</link><description>Super Micro Computer, Inc. (NASDAQ:SMCI) is one of the Best Fundamental Stocks to Buy According to Analysts. On January 11, the company announced collaboration with technology partners for AI-powered intelligent in-store retail solutions, which have been designed to meet increasing customer expectations with scalability, improved productivity, and higher profitability. Through combining Super Micro Computer, Inc. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/super-micro-computer-smci-announces-175301207.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Oracle Deemed Undervalued After Sell Off</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oracle-deemed-undervalued-sell-off-173310672.html</link><description>Analyst maintains Overweight rating with $300 price target, citing strong fundamentals.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oracle-deemed-undervalued-sell-off-173310672.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] India’s security plan could create a new headache for iPhone and Android users</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/indias-security-plan-could-create-a-new-headache-for-iphone-and-android-users</link><description>India is talking about a set of 83 smartphone security rules that Reuters said would oblige big phone makers to update their software and, in certain cases, let government-approved labs look into the source code. The ideas are part of the Indian Telecom Security Assurance Requirements framework and ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/indias-security-plan-could-create-a-new-headache-for-iphone-and-android-users</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] SNOW Expands Portfolio on Acquisitions: What's Ahead for the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snow-expands-portfolio-acquisitions-whats-172800066.html</link><description>Snowflake boosts its data and AI platform with Datometry and Observe deals as AI adoption accelerates and supports revenue growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snow-expands-portfolio-acquisitions-whats-172800066.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here's an AI Stock Nobody's Talking About -- But Should Be</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/heres-an-ai-stock-nobodys-talking-about-but-should/</link><description>Being in the business of innovation is a lucrative model for this company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/heres-an-ai-stock-nobodys-talking-about-but-should/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ‘Sickening and greedy’: California millionaire slams Larry Page and Sergey Brin for cutting ties with the state to avoid wealth tax</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sickening-greedy-california-millionaire-slams-171608346.html</link><description>As billionaires flee the state to avoid the proposed wealth tax, other high earners support the one-time tax.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sickening-greedy-california-millionaire-slams-171608346.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] The Bull Case For Revvity (RVTY) Could Change Following Upbeat 2025 Guidance And New Lilly AI Alliance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-revvity-rvty-could-171608034.html</link><description>In recent days, Revvity, Inc. updated its outlook for the fourth quarter and full year 2025, guiding to approximately US$772,000,000 in Q4 revenue and about US$2.86 billion for the year, while indicating adjusted earnings per share should exceed its prior guidance range. A separate announcement revealed that Revvity and Eli Lilly are jointly expanding access to Lilly’s TuneLab AI models through Revvity’s Signals platform, underscoring Revvity’s push to embed advanced AI and federated...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-case-revvity-rvty-could-171608034.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft Spending on Anthropic AI Nears $500 Million Annually</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-spending-anthropic-ai-nears-171421507.html</link><description>Partnership expands Microsoft's use of Anthropic technology across products.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-spending-anthropic-ai-nears-171421507.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike CEO says AI agents are unpredictable as company snaps up more cybersecurity startups</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-ceo-says-ai-agents-are-unpredictable-as-company-snaps-up-more-cybersecurity-startups-165836482.html</link><description>CrowdStrike has come out swinging in 2026 with some key deals. Here's why.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-ceo-says-ai-agents-are-unpredictable-as-company-snaps-up-more-cybersecurity-startups-165836482.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Keeps an Overweight Rating on Shake Shack Inc. (SHAK)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-keeps-overweight-rating-shake-165221562.html</link><description>Shake Shack Inc. (NYSE:SHAK) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. The Fly reported on January 7, 2026, that Barclays kept its Overweight rating on Shake Shack Inc. (NYSE:SHAK) and lowered the price goal to $110 from $115. The change reflects outlooks for the restaurant industry in 2026, where sales difficulties […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-keeps-overweight-rating-shake-165221562.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Prediction: These Could Be the Best-Performing Healthcare Stocks Through 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-best-performing-healthcare-stocks-2030/</link><description>Plenty of growth lies ahead for these top healthcare companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-best-performing-healthcare-stocks-2030/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The AI Boom Gets Its First Earnings Test of the Year. Watch TSMC Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-taiwan-semi-earnings-stock-price-8ccafaeb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>When  Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing  reports fourth-quarter earnings on Thursday, investors will be watching for the company’s comments on revenue and capital expenditure for clarity on where the boom in artificial-intelligence processors goes from here.  TSMC is expected to report a net profit of 469.13 billion New Taiwan dollars ($14.86 billion), according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates, up 25% from the same period a year ago.  The Taiwanese chip manufacturer releases monthly revenue figures, which makes it easier for investors to calculate fourth-quarter revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-taiwan-semi-earnings-stock-price-8ccafaeb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 2 "Magnificent Seven" Stocks May Announce Stock Splits in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/these-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-may-announce-stoc/</link><description>Stock splits can cause a stock to rally in the short term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/these-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-may-announce-stoc/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] As Wayfair Launches New AI Shopping Features, Should You Buy, Sell, or Hold W Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37043364/as-wayfair-launches-new-ai-shopping-features-should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-w-stock</link><description>Wayfair stock has almost tripled in the last year as the company continues to improve profit margins, driven by investments in AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37043364/as-wayfair-launches-new-ai-shopping-features-should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-w-stock</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Citi Retains a Neutral Rating on Sysco Corporation (SYY)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-retains-neutral-rating-sysco-161618895.html</link><description>Sysco Corporation (NYSE:SYY) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. According to TheFly, on January 7, 2026, Citi reduced its price target for Sysco Corporation (NYSE:SYY) from $82 to $81. It kept a neutral rating on the stock. The revision was part of Citi’s overall 2026 projection upgrade for the food […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-retains-neutral-rating-sysco-161618895.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Deutsche Bank is Bullish on The Kroger Co. (KR)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/deutsche-bank-bullish-kroger-co-161552290.html</link><description>The Kroger Co. (NYSE:KR) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. The Fly reported on January 8, 2026, that Deutsche Bank has resumed coverage of The Kroger Co. (NYSE: KR), with a $75 price target and a Buy rating. The firm anticipates 2026 to be a mixed year and has restored […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/deutsche-bank-bullish-kroger-co-161552290.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Robotics software maker Skild AI hits $14B valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/robotics-software-maker-skild-ai-161333284.html</link><description>Skild AI, which is building general-purpose robotic software, just raised a $1.4 billion funding round led by SoftBank.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/robotics-software-maker-skild-ai-161333284.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bank of America delivers sharp take on Apple stock after major shift</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-delivers-sharp-take-on-apple-stock-after-major-shift</link><description>Bank of America is leaning bullish on Apple (AAPL) stock ahead of a critical earnings test on Jan. 29. The sharper take comes right after a major shift in Apple’s AI future, following a breakthrough deal for Siri with Google, a unit of Alphabet (GOOGL). The bank sees multiple potent near-term ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-delivers-sharp-take-on-apple-stock-after-major-shift</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Chip Startup Etched Raises $500 Million in New Funding Round</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-etched-raises-160625909.html</link><description>Stripes-led financing values Etched at $5 billion as it develops AI processors to compete with Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-etched-raises-160625909.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:06:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Greenland Technologies Stock Soars. There Are Better Ways to Play the Geopolitical Tug-of-War.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/greenland-technologies-stock-price-trump-de794d1a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Greenland, the thinly populated island and territory of NATO member Denmark, has become the unexpected apple of President Trump’s eye.  Whatever happens, investors should remember that there is potential for heartache, too, when using stocks to bet on the outcome of an event.  Coming into Wednesday trading, shares of tiny  Greenland Technologies  Holding were up 31% over the past week despite having nothing to do with Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/greenland-technologies-stock-price-trump-de794d1a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Jim Cramer on Arm Holdings: “I Think I’m a Buyer, Not a Seller”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-155750173.html</link><description>Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. A caller mentioned that they have held the stock for about a year but had a 23% loss. Here’s what Cramer had to say: “Oh, Arm Holdings, that’s Rene Haas. I think he’s doing a real good job. I don’t know […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-155750173.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia stock falls as China reportedly restricts imports of H200 chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-falls-as-china-reportedly-restricts-imports-of-h200-chips-155203605.html</link><description>Chinese authorities have instructed customs agents to ban the entrance of Nvidia's H200 AI chips into the country, according to Reuters.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-falls-as-china-reportedly-restricts-imports-of-h200-chips-155203605.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike defeats shareholder lawsuit over huge software outage</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-155130284.html</link><description>A federal judge dismissed a lawsuit by CrowdStrike shareholders who said the cybersecurity company defrauded them by concealing its inadequate ​software testing and quality assurance procedures, before a July 2024 outage crashed more ‌than 8 million Microsoft Windows-based computers worldwide.  In a decision made public on Tuesday, U.S. District Judge Robert Pitman ‌in Austin, Texas said shareholders failed to plausibly allege that a large number of statements by CrowdStrike and top executives in regulatory filings, on earnings calls and on the company's website were materially false and misleading, or motivated by an intent to defraud.  Led by New York State ⁠Comptroller Thomas DiNapoli, the shareholders ‌alleged that CrowdStrike had "no test plans and no quality assurance team," citing former employees, and that executives at the Austin-based company prioritized "speed over ‍everything else" to maximize profit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-155130284.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike CEO on M&amp;A: Identity security is the 'new perimeter'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/crowdstrike-ceo-m-identity-security-155100218.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has closed a deal valued at $420 million to acquire Seraphic Security; this comes after acquiring identity security platform SGNL last week for $740 million. CrowdStrike also bought Pangea and Onum in 2025. CrowdStrike Co-Founder and CEO George Kurtz joins Yahoo Finance Executive Editor Brian Sozzi on Opening Bid to talk about the cybersecurity operator's goals to expand its identity security portfolio and the value these companies add to CrowdStrike. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/crowdstrike-ceo-m-identity-security-155100218.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Skyrockets 30% in a Month: Should Investors Buy or Hold Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-skyrockets-30-month-investors-154800017.html</link><description>NBIS surges nearly 30% in a month as AI cloud demand, big tech deals and rapid data center expansion fuel a 97% six-month rally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-skyrockets-30-month-investors-154800017.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bitdeer deploys NVIDIA GB200s for AI workloads in Malaysian data center</title><link>https://blockspace.media/insight/bitdeer-deploys-nvidia-gb200s-for-ai-workloads-in-malaysian-data-center/</link><description>Bitdeer is now operating NVIDIA GB200 NVL72 GPUs at a datacenter in Malaysia as the bitcoin miner dives into AI services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blockspace.media/insight/bitdeer-deploys-nvidia-gb200s-for-ai-workloads-in-malaysian-data-center/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA's Next Chip Isn't Just Faster -- It Could Make AI 10 Times Cheaper to Run</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidias-next-chip-ai-ten-times-cheaper/</link><description>The Rubin platform can significantly reduce token costs, opening up new use cases for AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidias-next-chip-ai-ten-times-cheaper/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple and Qualcomm Stocks Falls -- Report Says Companies Facing Potential Supply Issues</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-stocks-falls-report-153353729.html</link><description>The AI Supply Chain Has a New Choke Point. Apple and Qualcomm Are Exposed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-stocks-falls-report-153353729.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017534.html</link><description>Nu Holdings Ltd. 3,024,710 16.62</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017534.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Hope for first time buyers as Nationwide and HSBC push through mortgage rate cuts</title><link>https://www.standard.co.uk/business/mortgage-first-time-buyers-nationwide-hsbc-rate-cuts-b1266488.html</link><description>New mortgage price war follows a period of falling gilt yields at the start of the year</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.standard.co.uk/business/mortgage-first-time-buyers-nationwide-hsbc-rate-cuts-b1266488.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML's Installed Base Management Business Picks Up: What's Driving it?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asmls-installed-management-business-picks-151000608.html</link><description>ASML Holding's IBM business is gaining momentum in 2025, driven by system upgrades, expanding EUV adoption, and rising service revenues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asmls-installed-management-business-picks-151000608.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights NVIDIA, Lockheed Martin, IBM, Microsoft and Palantir</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-nvidia-150900563.html</link><description>NVIDIA anchors a 2026 investment thesis built on AI infrastructure, defense spending and quantum priorities reshaping global tech markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-nvidia-150900563.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Nvidia Stock Could Jump During the Period From Jan. 15 to Feb. 4</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-nvidia-stock-could-jump-jan-15-feb-4/</link><description>A series of events may shed light on Nvidia's future.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-nvidia-stock-could-jump-jan-15-feb-4/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] JPM26: Paying cash for obesity drugs, renewed IPO optimism and pharma’s cell therapy view</title><link>https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/jpm26-biotech-ipos-novo-wegovy-gsk-cell-therapy/809600/</link><description>Drugmaker CEOs see sales online channels as a budding opportunity, while some biotech investors told BioPharma Dive to expect a rebound in new stock offerings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/jpm26-biotech-ipos-novo-wegovy-gsk-cell-therapy/809600/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sales of a powerful Nvidia AI chip to China gets the greenlight, with conditions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sales-powerful-nvidia-ai-chip-145354822.html</link><description>The Trump administration placed new security requirements on Nividia's semiconductor sales to China, but essentially greenlighted the export of its powerful H200 artificial intelligence chips to Chinese buyers.  Nvidia must ensure that there is an adequate supply in the U.S., and the H200 chips must undergo a third-party review before being exported to China, according to new rules set by the Commerce Department's Bureau of Industry and Security.  China won't be allowed to use the chips for military purposes and is not allowed to import more than 50% of the chips sold to U.S. customers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sales-powerful-nvidia-ai-chip-145354822.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here's Why Eli Lilly (LLY) is a Strong Momentum Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-eli-lilly-lly-145004555.html</link><description>The Zacks Style Scores offers investors a way to easily find top-rated stocks based on their investing style. Here's why you should take advantage.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-eli-lilly-lly-145004555.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Micron Before 2027?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-you-buy-stock-before-year/</link><description>Demand for high-bandwidth memory is increasing exponentially, and Micron's investors will reap the reward.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-you-buy-stock-before-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] ARM's Self-Reinforcing Ecosystem Cements Its Industry Leadership</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arms-self-reinforcing-ecosystem-cements-144800087.html</link><description>Arm Holdings' self-reinforcing network ties developers and chipmakers, turning vast software compatibility into a mobile CPU moat rivals struggle to breach.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arms-self-reinforcing-ecosystem-cements-144800087.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls On Surprise Inflation Data; Nvidia Slides (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-inflation-data-wells-fargo-wfc-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Wednesday on surprise inflation data. Nvidia tumbled in morning trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-inflation-data-wells-fargo-wfc-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM vs. MSFT: Which Cloud &amp; AI Tech Giant is a Better Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-vs-msft-cloud-ai-143600677.html</link><description>Microsoft's AI edge and stronger growth outlook give it an edge over IBM, despite the latter's stronger valuation and stock gains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-vs-msft-cloud-ai-143600677.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Hardware Stock Could Become One of the Next $1 Trillion Companies</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-this-ai-hardware-stock-could-become-one/</link><description>AMD could regain some AI market share from Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-this-ai-hardware-stock-could-become-one/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why AMD's Least Hyped CES Announcement Could Be Its Most Important</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-amds-least-hyped-ces-announcement-could-be-its/</link><description>As AI inference shifts to local devices, AMD is ready.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-amds-least-hyped-ces-announcement-could-be-its/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Google stock is on fire in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-google-stock-is-on-fire-in-2026-142253886.html</link><description>Google's stock has picked up where it left off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-google-stock-is-on-fire-in-2026-142253886.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to acquire Seraphic Security, terms undisclosed</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-acquire-seraphic-security-terms-141633279.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) announced it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire Seraphic Security. The purchase price is contemplated to be paid predominantly in cash and includes a portion to be delivered in the form of stock subject to vesting conditions. The proposed acquisition is expected to close during CrowdStrike’s first quarter of FY’27, subject to customary closing conditions. Claim 70% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper deci</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-acquire-seraphic-security-terms-141633279.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Looking for Stocks with Positive Earnings Momentum? Check Out These 2 Computer and Technology Names</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-stocks-positive-earnings-momentum-140004237.html</link><description>Why investors should use the Zacks Earnings ESP tool to help find stocks that are poised to top quarterly earnings estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-stocks-positive-earnings-momentum-140004237.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Just Hit a $4T Market Cap. This Bull Sees More Gains Ahead</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-just-hit-a-4t-market-cap-this-bull-sees-more-gains-ahead/</link><description>Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOGL) surpassed the $4 trillion market cap mark and could be headed to a $5 trillion valuation at some point in 2026, especially if the latest parabolic move has gas in the tank. With shares of Alphabet hitting new highs on Tuesday’s session, effectively leaving many of its Magnificent Seven peers behind, questions linger ... Alphabet Just Hit a $4T Market Cap. This Bull Sees More Gains Ahead</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-just-hit-a-4t-market-cap-this-bull-sees-more-gains-ahead/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence &amp; Microsoft Redefine Data Center Memory With Advanced Solutions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-microsoft-redefine-data-center-135600886.html</link><description>CDNS unveils the first LPDDR5X 9600Mbps enterprise memory IP with Microsoft, bringing DDR5-class reliability to low-power data center AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-microsoft-redefine-data-center-135600886.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is It Time to Dump Your Shares of Eli Lilly?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/is-it-time-to-dump-your-shares-of-eli-lilly/</link><description>What happens with Eli Lilly's GLP-1 shot now that Novo Nordisk has come out with a GLP-1 pill?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/is-it-time-to-dump-your-shares-of-eli-lilly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] CRWV Stock Beats Industry Returns in a Year: Buy, Hold or Fold in 2026?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwv-stock-beats-industry-returns-134600854.html</link><description>CoreWeave surges 119% in a year on booming AI cloud demand, but heavy CapEx, rising debt and valuation concerns raise questions about upside in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwv-stock-beats-industry-returns-134600854.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Quantum Computing Stocks: Honeywell's Quantinuum Plans IPO</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-honeywell-quantinuum-plans-ipo/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Honeywell said its‌ quantum computing unit Quantinuum will filing for an IPO, adding to the growing number of quantum computing stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-honeywell-quantinuum-plans-ipo/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Slides -- China Approval for AI Chips Remains Uncertain</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-slides-china-approval-133723410.html</link><description>Nvidia Navigates Export Rules as AI Chip Sales to China Hang in Balance</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-slides-china-approval-133723410.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Blocks Nvidia H200 AI Chips From Entering Country, Sources Say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-blocks-nvidia-h200-ai-133609358.html</link><description>Move clouds Nvidia's China outlook just days after U.S. approved limited exports.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-blocks-nvidia-h200-ai-133609358.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Zillow Group, Inc. (ZG): A Bear Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zillow-group-inc-zg-bear-133522890.html</link><description>We came across a bearish thesis on Zillow Group, Inc. on investing subreddit by Guy_PCS. In this article, we will summarize the bears’ thesis on ZG. Zillow Group, Inc.’s share was trading at $67.80 as of January 13th. ZG’s forward P/E was 32.89 according to Yahoo Finance. Zillow Group, Inc. operates real estate brands in mobile applications and Websites in the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zillow-group-inc-zg-bear-133522890.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Tops $4 Trillion With Apple AI Deal -- Is GOOGL Stock Still a Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-apple-133509931.html</link><description>Google's AI Push Expands Through Apple Partnership</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-apple-133509931.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar Inc. (CAT): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-inc-cat-bull-case-133454104.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on Caterpillar Inc. on Chip Stock Investor’s YouTube channel. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on CAT. Caterpillar Inc.’s share was trading at $636.53 as of January 13th. CAT’s trailing and forward P/E were 32.35 and 28.49, respectively according to Yahoo Finance. Caterpillar, widely recognized for its construction […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-inc-cat-bull-case-133454104.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] CoreWeave's 2026 CapEx Spend to Double: High Risk or High Reward?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweaves-2026-capex-spend-double-133200147.html</link><description>CRWV expects significantly high 2026 capex as AI demand drives rapid scaling, but rising interest costs and margin pressure test execution.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweaves-2026-capex-spend-double-133200147.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Will LRCX's China Revenue Drop Below 30% Hurt 2026 Growth Outlook?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcxs-china-revenue-drop-below-132200026.html</link><description>Lam Research sees revenues from China falling below 30% in 2026 as export curbs ail, but AI-led demand outside China could help sustain growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcxs-china-revenue-drop-below-132200026.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Factors Led Mar Vista’s U.S. Quality Strategy’s New Addition: Taiwan Semiconductor (TSM)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factors-led-mar-vista-u-131539272.html</link><description>Mar Vista Investment Partners, LLC, an investment management company, released its “Mar Vista U.S. Quality Strategy” fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. US equities experienced a strong momentum in 2025 and marked their second consecutive year of double-digit gains. The market witnessed one of the fastest recoveries following its […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factors-led-mar-vista-u-131539272.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) Stock Price Prediction for 2026: Where Will It Be in 1 Year (Jan 14)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</link><description>Nvidia remains the dominant AI chipmaker in the market, but where is the stock headed for the rest of this year and into the next?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Boom Hits Energy Reality Check</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-boom-hits-energy-reality-130453342.html</link><description>Electricity rules may reshape data center buildouts</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-boom-hits-energy-reality-130453342.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM's 2026 Outlook Could Turn Brighter</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-2026-outlook-could-turn-130448250.html</link><description>2026 guidance may reflect steadier enterprise demand</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-2026-outlook-could-turn-130448250.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: AppLovin, Blackrock, Citigroup, DoorDash, Fabrinet, KLA Corp, Okta, Rivian, Uber and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-applovin-blackrock-citigroup-doordash-fabrinet-kla-corp-okta-rivian-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: Futures are trading lower after the January rally hit a wall on Wednesday, with all major indices falling, and the selling looks set to continue today. The main culprit yesterday was JPMorgan (NYSE: JPM) shares, which took a hit after missing analyst estimates for the quarter. The banking giant posted $4.63 per ... Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: AppLovin, Blackrock, Citigroup, DoorDash, Fabrinet, KLA Corp, Okta, Rivian, Uber and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-applovin-blackrock-citigroup-doordash-fabrinet-kla-corp-okta-rivian-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Nvidia Eyes First Breakout Of 2026. These Clues — And An Innovative Deal With Eli Lilly — Bode Well.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/nvidia-stock-eyes-first-breakout-of-2026-with-eli-lilly-ai-collaboration/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Now set to collaborate with Eli Lilly to develop drugs in the AI era, Nvidia looks to trigger a new climb.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/nvidia-stock-eyes-first-breakout-of-2026-with-eli-lilly-ai-collaboration/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] BRK.B vs. CB: Which Insurer is a Safer Option for a Solid Portfolio?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brk-b-vs-cb-insurer-125100827.html</link><description>CB edges out BRK.B as the safer bet, with stronger ROE, dividend yield, and earnings momentum heading into 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brk-b-vs-cb-insurer-125100827.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What to Expect From Alphabet’s Next Quarterly Earnings Report</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37037320/what-to-expect-from-alphabets-next-quarterly-earnings-report</link><description>Here’s what analysts are expecting prior to Alphabet’s Q4 earnings, after the stock topped the $4 trillion market cap recently.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37037320/what-to-expect-from-alphabets-next-quarterly-earnings-report</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] PFE Market Cap Falls More Than $7B in a Month: How to Play the Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pfe-market-cap-falls-more-124500360.html</link><description>Pfizer shares fall nearly 5% in a month after weak 2026 guidance, sparking debate over buying the dip or staying cautious.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pfe-market-cap-falls-more-124500360.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should Nvidia Worry About the Rise of China’s New Optical AI Chips?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-nvidia-worry-about-the-rise-of-chinas-new-optical-ai-chips/</link><description>It’s been over a year since DeepSeek caused a bit of a panic across the AI stocks, as its distillation techniques caused many to question whether the frontier innovators needed all that hardware firepower. As it turned out, DeepSeek R1 wasn’t the disruptor that was meant to derail the AI trade for good. Fast forward ... Should Nvidia Worry About the Rise of China’s New Optical AI Chips?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-nvidia-worry-about-the-rise-of-chinas-new-optical-ai-chips/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Warren Buffett compares AI risks to those posed by nuclear weapons: 'The genie is out of the bottle'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-compares-ai-risks-to-those-posed-by-nuclear-weapons-the-genie-is-out-of-the-bottle-122210523.html</link><description>In comments during a two-hour CNBC special on his life and legacy, Warren Buffett compared the potential of AI technology to the threat of nuclear weapons.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-compares-ai-risks-to-those-posed-by-nuclear-weapons-the-genie-is-out-of-the-bottle-122210523.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Stock Surges Further Toward 2-Year High. What the Excitement’s About.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-chips-4ce48217?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday.  The chip company’s shares are on the brink of levels not seen for several years as investors bet President Donald Trump’s support for the company will boost its chip-manufacturing ambitions.  Intel was up 1.6% at $48.06 in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-chips-4ce48217?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] US Moves Toward Allowing Nvidia AI Chip Sales to China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-moves-toward-allowing-nvidia-121655363.html</link><description>Revised Commerce Department rules shift AI chip export reviews to case-by-case approvals, easing prior presumptions of denial.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-moves-toward-allowing-nvidia-121655363.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Honeywell announces Quantinuum's plan to file for IPO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/honeywell-announces-quantinuums-plan-file-121011580.html</link><description>Honeywell said on Wednesday ​it plans for ‌its majority-owned quantum computing unit ‌Quantinuum to confidentially file draft IPO papers with the U.S. ⁠securities ‌regulator. The number of shares to be ‍offered and the price range for the proposed ​offering have not yet ‌been determined, the company said. Following the news, Honeywell's shares were up about 1% during ⁠premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/honeywell-announces-quantinuums-plan-file-121011580.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Warby Parker (WRBY) Soars 9.4% on Strong AI Glasses Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warby-parker-wrby-soars-9-120943721.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Leaving Wall Street in the Dust; 4 Hit Fresh Records. Warby Parker Inc. (NYSE:WRBY) was one of the top performers on Tuesday. Warby Parker bounced back by 9.44 percent on Tuesday to close at $29.09 apiece, as news of strong demand for artificial intelligence glasses spilled over to its stock. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warby-parker-wrby-soars-9-120943721.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meet the Quantum Computing Stock That Billionaires Can't Get Enough Of (Hint: It's Not IonQ, Rigetti Computing, or D-Wave Quantum)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/meet-the-quantum-computing-stock-that-billionaires/</link><description>Several notable billionaire investors are buying the same quantum computing stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/meet-the-quantum-computing-stock-that-billionaires/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] See How Bullish Inflows Boost Lam Research</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/see-bullish-inflows-boost-lam-120306682.html</link><description>Lam Research Ltd. (LRCX) is up 188% in the last year thanks to six outlier inflows since September.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/see-bullish-inflows-boost-lam-120306682.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Braze Highlights ChatGPT SDK, Agent Console and AI Personalization Push at Needham Conference</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/braze-highlights-chatgpt-sdk-agent-console-and-ai-personalization-push-at-needham-conference-2026-01-14/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Braze (NASDAQ:BRZE) positions itself as a “reference architecture for the modern customer engagement stack,” emphasizing real-time, cross-channel messaging built on stream processing technology, Chief Financial Officer Isabelle Winkles said during a Needham conference discussion with analyst Scott B</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/braze-highlights-chatgpt-sdk-agent-console-and-ai-personalization-push-at-needham-conference-2026-01-14/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AMD Teams Up with Tata Consultancy Services to Boost Enterprise AI Adoption</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-teams-tata-consultancy-services-115409291.html</link><description>Collaboration targets faster, more secure deployment of AI solutions for global businesses.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-teams-tata-consultancy-services-115409291.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Lilly, chasing Novo, expects second-quarter FDA decision on obesity pill</title><link>https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/lilly-obesity-pill-orforglipron-fda-decision-dtc-sales/809598/</link><description>Speaking at the J.P. Morgan conference, CEO David Ricks said he anticipates a “rapid review” for orforglipron that's currently speeding along “at pace.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/lilly-obesity-pill-orforglipron-fda-decision-dtc-sales/809598/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dow Jones Futures Fall As Wells Fargo, Bank Of America Report; Tesla To Stop Selling FSD</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp-500-citigroup-wells-fargo-bac-tesla-fsd-stop-selling/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Futures fell as Wells Fargo and BofA reported with Citigroup due. Tesla will stop selling Full Self-Driving, offering it only as a subscription.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp-500-citigroup-wells-fargo-bac-tesla-fsd-stop-selling/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The ‘Magnificent 7’ stocks are dying, and Wall Street is pretty happy about it</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stocks-dying-wall-113857386.html</link><description>But the dominance of the Mag 7 is likely to come to an end this year, many on Wall Street believe—if only because their valuations can’t exponentially go up forever.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stocks-dying-wall-113857386.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Week In AI Chips - TCS and AMD Unite to Boost AI Solutions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-tcs-amd-113759755.html</link><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) have announced a strategic collaboration aimed at enhancing AI accessibility and adoption across enterprises. This partnership focuses on co-developing industry-specific AI and GenAI solutions, leveraging TCS's systems integration capabilities and AMD’s high-performance computing technologies. The collaboration aims to modernize hybrid cloud and edge environments, deploy AI-powered solutions, and enhance AI performance for...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-tcs-amd-113759755.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks to Watch Wednesday: Netflix, Bank of America, Citi</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-netflix-bank-of-america-citi-4vjsTACY6ZhwFCTPHOuZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>🔎 Bank of America (BAC): The lender is due to post quarterly earnings, as are Wells Fargo (WFC) and Citigroup (C). ↗️ Netflix (NFLX): The streaming company is preparing an all-cash bid for Warner Bros.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-netflix-bank-of-america-citi-4vjsTACY6ZhwFCTPHOuZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Most popular stocks and funds investors bought in 2025</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-popular-stocks-funds-investing-2025-113311183.html</link><description>Despite ongoing volatility and geopolitical events, 2025 delivered strong returns for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-popular-stocks-funds-investing-2025-113311183.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Women's, advocacy groups call on Apple, Google to drop X and Grok from app stores</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/womens-advocacy-groups-call-apple-110255271.html</link><description>By Raphael Satter WASHINGTON, Jan 14 (Reuters) - A coalition of women's groups, tech watchdogs, and progressive activists is calling on Alphabet owner Google and Apple to remove the social media site</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/womens-advocacy-groups-call-apple-110255271.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Next Phase of the AI Boom May Not Come From Chipmakers</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/next-phase-ai-boom-not-come-chipmaker-ceg/</link><description>Chipmakers and data centers dominate the headlines for AI infrastructure, but another sector is set to profit big from the next phase of the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/next-phase-ai-boom-not-come-chipmaker-ceg/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] ‘The rejections are piling up’: why computer science graduates can’t get a job</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/rejections-piling-why-computer-science-110800679.html</link><description>Towards the end of last year, Rashik Parmar began getting calls from anxious students who had just graduated with degrees in computer science.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/rejections-piling-why-computer-science-110800679.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>