<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[LLY0.F] Jim Cramer Says “Chatter” About NVIDIA (NVDA)’s Circular Deals is “Nonsense”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-chatter-nvidia-145448319.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is a regular stock on Jim Cramer’s radar. The CNBC TV host is one of the stock’s biggest proponents. As January kicked off, Citi reiterated a Buy rating on the shares […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-chatter-nvidia-145448319.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research (LRCX) Has a Shortage That Can’t Be Met, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-shortage-t-145424180.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Lam Research Corporation (NASDAQ:LRCX) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Lam Research Corporation (NASDAQ:LRCX) is an American semiconductor manufacturing equipment provider. Its shares are up by 194% over the past year and by 20% year-to-date. Goldman Sachs started the year on a strong […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-shortage-t-145424180.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Corp (KLAC) Has a Shortage That Can’t Be Met, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corp-klac-shortage-t-145320779.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) makes and sells equipment used in the chip manufacturing process. Its shares are up by 119% over the past year and by 21% year-to-date. Morgan Stanley increased the stock’s rating to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corp-klac-shortage-t-145320779.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] “Alphabet (GOOGL)’s Extraordinary,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-extraordinary-says-jim-145114032.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is a stock that Jim Cramer has consistently discussed over the past couple of months. During this time period, his opinion about the firm has shifted from being wary due to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-extraordinary-says-jim-145114032.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Is Cheapest in Years -- Should You Buy NVDA Stock Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-cheapest-years-buy-nvda-145042256.html</link><description>What Analysts See After the Recent Pullback</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-cheapest-years-buy-nvda-145042256.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Rises After China Approves First H200 AI Chip Imports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-rises-china-approves-144922818.html</link><description>Nvidia Edge Strengthens as China Clears First Batch of H200 Chips</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-rises-china-approves-144922818.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Some of Pharma's Biggest Brands Face a New Reality</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pharmas-biggest-brands-face-reality-144809825.html</link><description>A government process quietly moves forward</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pharmas-biggest-brands-face-reality-144809825.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Confirms AI-Driven Strength With Record Orders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-confirms-ai-driven-strength-144805528.html</link><description>Q4 bookings surge as EUV demand signals sustained chip capex</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-confirms-ai-driven-strength-144805528.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SoftBank Weighs $30 Billion Investment in OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-weighs-30-billion-investment-144431004.html</link><description>Talks could value the AI developer at roughly $830 billion</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-weighs-30-billion-investment-144431004.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 🎧What Does a Weaker Dollar Mean for Businesses and the World?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/-what-does-a-weaker-dollar-mean-for-businesses-and-the-world--QjIdEIhnaU1rwOrPEaQV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The dollar is steadying following its biggest one-day decline since April’s tariff turmoil. That’s after President Trump said he wouldn't mind a weaker currency. WSJ editor Alex Frangos explains why that statement caused such a selloff.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/-what-does-a-weaker-dollar-mean-for-businesses-and-the-world--QjIdEIhnaU1rwOrPEaQV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] CEO hot takes: Elevator manufacturer on robots, AI data centers, and an economic boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ceo-hot-takes-elevator-manufacturer-on-robots-ai-data-centers-and-an-economic-boom-143927670.html</link><description>One of the world's largest makers of elevators is a great proxy on a lot of things happening in the US economy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ceo-hot-takes-elevator-manufacturer-on-robots-ai-data-centers-and-an-economic-boom-143927670.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500 breaches 7,000 mark Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-breaches-7000-mark-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-143835732.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-breaches-7000-mark-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-143835732.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Artificial Intelligence Stock Is a Must-Own for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-artificial-intelligence-stock-is-a-must-own-f/</link><description>The rise of artificial intelligence (AI) has only strengthened this tech powerhouse.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-artificial-intelligence-stock-is-a-must-own-f/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You Had Gone All-In on Nvidia in 2016, Here’s How Much Richer You Would’ve Been</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/had-gone-nvidia-2016-much-142204443.html</link><description>Nvidia stock has soared over 23,000% since 2016. See how much an investment made then would be worth now and whether the AI giant is still a smart buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/had-gone-nvidia-2016-much-142204443.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML’s €12b Buyback Links AI Equipment Demand To Capital Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-12b-buyback-links-ai-141245271.html</link><description>ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML) has launched a new €12b share buyback program alongside record demand for its semiconductor equipment. The latest quarterly order intake was far ahead of expectations, with management pointing to sustained demand tied to AI-related chip production. Company leaders describe an AI-driven growth outlook that they view as durable, aligning capital returns with strong current business conditions. ASML Holding, trading at €1,217.6, sits at the center of the high end...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-12b-buyback-links-ai-141245271.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Expands Beyond GLP 1s With Gene Editing And Oncology Bets</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-expands-beyond-glp-141147815.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (NYSE: LLY) announced a global research collaboration with Seamless Therapeutics to develop programmable gene editing therapies for hearing loss. The company also received FDA Breakthrough Therapy designation for an antibody drug conjugate in ovarian cancer. Both developments expand Lilly’s pipeline into genetic hearing loss and oncology, beyond its current strength in diabetes and obesity treatments. Eli Lilly, best known to many investors for its diabetes and obesity portfolio,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-expands-beyond-glp-141147815.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] FactSet Barclays Deal Highlights Role In Institutional Data And Analytics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-barclays-deal-highlights-role-141141687.html</link><description>FactSet Research Systems (NYSE:FDS) has entered a multiyear collaboration with Barclays to support Barclays' market data strategy. The agreement focuses on providing advanced analytics and technology to strengthen Barclays' data driven capabilities. The partnership adds a major global bank as a long term client for FactSet's analytics and data solutions platform. For investors watching NYSE:FDS, this new Barclays agreement comes at a time when the stock is trading at $268.66, with a 1 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-barclays-deal-highlights-role-141141687.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Snap seeks investments as new smart glasses unit takes on Meta</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snap-seeks-investments-smart-glasses-140250898.html</link><description>Jan 28 (Reuters) - Snap will create an independent subsidiary for its augmented reality smart glasses, as it looks to ​attract external investment and challenge bigger rival Meta in the fast-growing ‌wearables market. The launch of the Specs unit, announced on Wednesday, comes as the success of Ray-Ban Meta ‌smart glasses positions eyewear as an early frontrunner in the race for gadgets powered by artificial intelligence.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snap-seeks-investments-smart-glasses-140250898.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] ChatGPT Thinks Snowflake Stock Will Close At This Price In The Next 60 Days</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-snowflake-stock-close-140110684.html</link><description>Quick Summary ChatGPT thinks Snowflake stock could trade higher over the next 60 days, projecting an average price around $214.21 by mid-April. Investors looking to express a view can build exposure incrementally using commission-free fractional shares on SoFi, starting with...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-snowflake-stock-close-140110684.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly and Company (LLY): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-bull-140055177.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on Eli Lilly and Company on R. Dennis’s Substack by OppCost. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on LLY. Eli Lilly and Company’s share was trading at $1,039.51 as of January 27th. LLY’s trailing and forward P/E were 50.93 and 31.65 respectively according to Yahoo Finance. Eli Lilly and Company discovers, develops, and markets human pharmaceuticals in the United States, Europe, China, Japan, and internationally. LLY presents a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-bull-140055177.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Redwood attracts Google for its $425M Series E as AI power needs rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/redwood-attracts-google-425m-series-140000424.html</link><description>Google is the latest investor to back Redwood Materials as the battery recycling startup scales a new energy storage venture to power AI data centers and other industrial sites.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/redwood-attracts-google-425m-series-140000424.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Holding N.V. (ASML): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-n-v-asml-135750807.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on ASML Holding N.V. on Arya’s Substack by Arya. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on ASML. ASML Holding N.V.’s share was trading at $1,454.59 as of January 27th. ASML’s trailing and forward P/E were 50.55 and 45.66 respectively according to Yahoo Finance. ASML Holding N.V. (ASML) remains the centerpiece of advanced semiconductor manufacturing, commanding a near-monopoly in EUV lithography and benefiting from structural tailwinds driven by AI, l</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-n-v-asml-135750807.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Is This Chip Stock a Smart Long-Term Bet as Artificial Intelligence Scales Globally?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/is-chip-stock-smart-long-term-bet-ai-globally/</link><description>It may be time to start looking at Intel stock again.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/is-chip-stock-smart-long-term-bet-ai-globally/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] AMAT stock: Mizuho sees ‘significant acceleration’ in WFE, upgrades rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amat-stock-mizuho-sees-significant-133218199.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Applied Materials received an upgrade from Mizuho on Wednesday, with the firm citing a sharp rebound in semiconductor capital spending and strengthening foundry and logic demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amat-stock-mizuho-sees-significant-133218199.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] U.K. Competition Watchdog Plans New Rules for Google’s AI Overviews Under Tech Law</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/u-k-competition-watchdog-plans-new-rules-for-googles-ai-overviews-under-tech-law-a9ae3c5e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Under the plans, publishers could stop their content being used to power AI Overviews, or to train AI models outside of Google search and make sure their content is properly cited in AI results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/u-k-competition-watchdog-plans-new-rules-for-googles-ai-overviews-under-tech-law-a9ae3c5e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Earnings live: Starbucks stock pops, GE Vernova slips, ASML surges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-starbucks-stock-pops-ge-vernova-slips-asml-surges-133036401.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-starbucks-stock-pops-ge-vernova-slips-asml-surges-133036401.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Job Cuts Highlight Efficiency Focus As AI EUV Orders Build</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-job-cuts-highlight-efficiency-131842086.html</link><description>ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) plans to cut about 1,700 jobs, roughly 4% of its workforce. The reduction comes as the company reports record net profit and strong AI driven demand for its chip making tools. ASML highlights a growing order book for its extreme ultraviolet lithography systems and indicates expectations for another growth year in 2026. ASML Holding, trading at around $1,454.59, sits at the center of advanced semiconductor manufacturing, with its extreme ultraviolet lithography...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-job-cuts-highlight-efficiency-131842086.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) Stock Price Prediction for 2026: Where Will It Be in 1 Year (Jan 28)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</link><description>Nvidia remains the dominant AI chipmaker in the market, but where is the stock headed for the rest of this year and into the next?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Makes a Quiet Internal Move</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-makes-quiet-internal-move-130846722.html</link><description>A structural shift unfolds behind the scenes</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-makes-quiet-internal-move-130846722.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: AMD Stock Will Soar on Feb. 3</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/prediction-amd-stock-will-soar-on-february-3/</link><description>The chipmaker's management team has asserted that this year will be a turning point for the company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/prediction-amd-stock-will-soar-on-february-3/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here’s Why Eli Lilly (LLY) is Surging</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-eli-lilly-lly-surging-130314523.html</link><description>Hardman Johnston Global Advisors, an investment management company, released its “Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy” investor letter for the fourth quarter of 2025. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. Global equity markets delivered robust results in the quarter, backed by easing inflation trends and strong economic data. The Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-eli-lilly-lly-surging-130314523.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:03:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Stock: How To Find &amp; Own America's Greatest Opportunities</title><link>https://www.investors.com/how-to-invest/cisco-csco-stock-americas-greatest-opportunities/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Cisco Systems was one of the best-performing stocks of the 1990s, making its name as the leading supplier of networking gear.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/how-to-invest/cisco-csco-stock-americas-greatest-opportunities/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia AI Partner Monolithic Power Systems Etches Buy Point, Boosted By Big Demand</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/monolithic-power-mpwr-eyes-breakout-ai-data-center-nvidia-partner/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>As Nvidia works on a new setup, solid growth and strong demand for AI data centers has Monolithic Power etching a buy point.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/monolithic-power-mpwr-eyes-breakout-ai-data-center-nvidia-partner/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta Prepares Paid Tiers For Instagram, Facebook And WhatsApp, Offering Exclusive AI Features And Enhanced Control: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-prepares-paid-tiers-instagram-130109983.html</link><description>Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) is reportedly testing new paid subscriptions across Instagram, Facebook, and WhatsApp that would unlock premium features and expanded AI tools while keeping the core apps free. Meta Tests Subscription Model Across Core Apps Meta plans to roll out optional subscriptions that offer users a more advanced experience across its social apps, the company told TechCrunch. The Mark Zuckerberg-led company said it will test different subscription features and bundles, wit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-prepares-paid-tiers-instagram-130109983.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Will the Russell 2000 Continue to Outperform the S&amp;P 500?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russell-2000-continue-outperform-p-130009641.html</link><description>Examining whether or not small-cap outperformance tends to hold longer term</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russell-2000-continue-outperform-p-130009641.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Does Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT) have a Robust Long-Term Outlook?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-125138975.html</link><description>Hardman Johnston Global Advisors, an investment management company, released its “Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy” investor letter for the fourth quarter of 2025. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. Global equity markets delivered robust results in the quarter, backed by easing inflation trends and strong economic data. The Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-125138975.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] CMS selects next batch of 15 high-cost medicines for third negotiation cycle</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/cms-selects-next-batch-of-15-high-cost-medicines-for-third-negotiation-cycle/</link><description>The 15 drugs accounted for $27bn in spending via Medicare Part B and Part D between November 2024 and October 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/cms-selects-next-batch-of-15-high-cost-medicines-for-third-negotiation-cycle/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Gold Driven to Record Highs by Geopolitical Risk, Says HSBC's Steel</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/gold-driven-record-highs-geopolitical-124211097.html</link><description>James Steel, chief precious metals analyst at HSBC, expects increased volatility and frequent pullbacks ahead for gold with new money coming into the market as he sees geopolitical risk as the main factor driving the metal to record highs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/gold-driven-record-highs-geopolitical-124211097.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer Expresses Caution on Celestica Valuation Due to Potential Google Partnership Changes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-expresses-caution-celestica-122332408.html</link><description>Celestica Inc. (NYSE:CLS) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. When a caller expressed worry upon hearing that Google might be backing out of its relationship with the company, Cramer remarked: Yeah, I saw that too and was thinking, boy, Celestica is really too high if that happens. Why don’t […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-expresses-caution-celestica-122332408.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Jim Cramer on Arm Holdings: “I Think You Do Buy the Stock”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-122331963.html</link><description>Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. A caller inquired about Cramer’s thoughts on buying more ARM shares, and he replied: Okay, Arm’s very interesting here because they did see the big shortage coming. Rene Haas got it right. I think you do buy the stock, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-122331963.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Jim Cramer on Caterpillar: “I Would Like to See the Stock Lower”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-caterpillar-see-stock-122328861.html</link><description>Caterpillar Inc. (NYSE:CAT) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. Noting that the stock seems “richly valued,” a club member asked how much it needs to fall to start a position. In response, Cramer said: There are a lot of people who feel that this is a data center play […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-caterpillar-see-stock-122328861.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Jim Cramer Advises Caution on Nebius Due to Potential AI Infrastructure Slowdown</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-advises-caution-nebius-122311807.html</link><description>Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. A caller asked where Cramer sees the biggest risk in the company and his view on the AI infrastructure. In response, Cramer said: Well, I think that, I think that, you see, these stocks were all overvalued. What’s going […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-advises-caution-nebius-122311807.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Seagate, Texas Instruments, Nvidia, AT&amp;T, Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-01763d21?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Seagate Technology shares surge after the hard-disk-drive maker beats analysts’ fourth-quarter earnings estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-01763d21?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Greg Abel Signals New Berkshire Era With Kraft Heinz And Sirius XM Shakeup</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greg-abel-signals-berkshire-era-122300407.html</link><description>Greg Abel, in his first major move as Berkshire Hathaway CEO, is considering selling the company’s entire Kraft Heinz stake. Recent SEC filings, Kraft Heinz disclosures, and Berkshire’s board resignations at Kraft Heinz point to an intent to fully exit the investment. Berkshire is also exploring a sale of its position in Sirius XM as the business faces subscriber and competitive pressures. Berkshire Hathaway (NYSE:BRK.A), recently trading around $713,000.0 per Class A share, is entering a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greg-abel-signals-berkshire-era-122300407.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Is It Time To Reassess Cisco Systems (CSCO) After Strong Multi‑Year Share Price Gains?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-cisco-systems-csco-122224005.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Cisco Systems at around US$78.68 is offering fair value or a stretched price, it helps to break the story into recent performance, news flow, and a clear view of what the numbers say. The stock has returns of 7.3% over the last 7 days, 0.7% over 30 days, 3.5% year to date, 35.6% over 1 year, 76.0% over 3 years, and 98.4% over 5 years. These figures may catch the eye of anyone thinking about growth potential or changing risk perceptions. Recent coverage around...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-cisco-systems-csco-122224005.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Gains. How China and OpenAI News Could Break It Out of Its Rut.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-china-openai-359efcf7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock was rising as prospects brightened for sales of its AI chips in China and to ChatGPT-developer OpenAI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-china-openai-359efcf7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Faces EU DMA Scrutiny While Gemini Powers Apple Siri</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-faces-eu-dma-scrutiny-122115260.html</link><description>The European Commission has opened formal compliance proceedings against Google under the Digital Markets Act to review how it treats rival AI and search services. At the same time, Google has agreed with Apple to integrate its Gemini AI model as the default intelligence behind Siri. These developments arrive as Alphabet (NasdaqGS:GOOGL) continues to refine its role in global search, mobile ecosystems, and AI platforms. For investors watching Alphabet at a share price of $334.55, the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-faces-eu-dma-scrutiny-122115260.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Amazon to Cut 16,000 Corporate Positions to Trim Bureaucracy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-cut-16-000-corporate-122006515.html</link><description>The tech firm will offer US-based employees 90 days to search for a new role internally, as well as severance and other transition support, Beth Galetti, Amazon’s senior vice president of people experience and technology said Wednesday in a blog post.  Companies across industries have been trimming management layers in the name of becoming leaner and more productive.  Just as Amazon was announcing its own layoffs, the chip-making machine giant ASML Holding NV said it’s eliminating 1,700 positions largely targeting managerial roles.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-cut-16-000-corporate-122006515.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Is Jumping -- Record Orders Signal AI-Driven Chip Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-stock-jumping-record-orders-120645023.html</link><description>AI Momentum Boosts Confidence in 2026 Growth</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-stock-jumping-record-orders-120645023.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Trump Is Happy With a Diving Dollar. Why Stock Markets Should Be on Alert.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-dollar-stock-market-things-to-know-today-fbdf0649?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>What to know ahead of the Fed decision, ASML sales smash expectations, Meta’s AI spending spree weighs on earnings outlook, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-dollar-stock-market-things-to-know-today-fbdf0649?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Neocloud startup PaleBlueDot valued at $1 billion in B Capital-led round</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/neocloud-startup-palebluedot-valued-1-120431917.html</link><description>Artificial intelligence cloud startup PaleBlueDot AI has raised $150 million in a Series B funding round, valuing the company at more than $1 billion as it ​expands AI computing offerings in the United States and Asia, the company told Reuters.  The ‌round was led by B Capital, as PaleBlueDot joins a crowded field of so-called "neocloud" companies seeking to meet surging ‌demand for AI computing power.  PaleBlueDot said it planned to use the proceeds to buy Nvidia graphics processing units (GPUs) and related infrastructure and to hire staff to expand partnerships.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/neocloud-startup-palebluedot-valued-1-120431917.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly signs up to $1.12 billion deal with private gene-editing firm Seamless</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-signs-1-12-120320602.html</link><description>drugmaker Eli Lilly signed an agreement worth up to $1.12 billion with Seamless Therapeutics, ​the Germany-based startup said on Wednesday, to develop and commercialize ‌treatments for hearing loss using the biotech's gene-editing platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-signs-1-12-120320602.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Group (NBIS) Carries Strong Potential for Margin Expansion and Free Cash Flows</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-carries-strong-115722043.html</link><description>Nebius Group NV (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the best large cap stocks under $100 with huge upside potential. On January 15, Morgan Stanley analyst Josh Baer initiated coverage on Nebius Group NV (NASDAQ:NBIS), assigning an Equal Weight rating to the stock. He estimated over 33% upside potential based on a price target of $126. Despite […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-carries-strong-115722043.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Morning Bid: Making a weak dollar "great" again</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-bid-making-weak-dollar-114738670.html</link><description>and global markets today , Editor-At-Large, Finance and Markets The dollar managed to get a toehold on Wednesday after a withering drop to a four-year low overnight. President Donald Trump appeared to embrace the move, saying the ​dollar was "great.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-bid-making-weak-dollar-114738670.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Shares in Chip-Machine Giant ASML Jump as AI Spending Booms</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff</link><description>The company logged record quarterly orders, showing how tech clients continue to plow money into tools for making sophisticated semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Has Walk-Off Home Run in China</title><link>https://247wallst.com/technology-3/2026/01/28/nvidia-has-walk-off-home-run-in-china/</link><description>China reportedly has approved the sale of Nvidia H200 chips to certain tech companies there. This came despite its desire to build its own AI chips and not rely on America.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/technology-3/2026/01/28/nvidia-has-walk-off-home-run-in-china/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Health Care Roundup: Market Talk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/health-care-roundup-market-talk-76913f76?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>1131 GMT – Roche Holding’s results from a midstage study of its CT-388 obesity drug candidate look promising, UBS analysts say in a research note.  The drug the Swiss pharmaceutical company is developing achieved weight-loss efficacy that seems to be broadly similar to Eli Lilly’s Zepbound, but at an earlier timepoint, and the discontinuation rate looks similar too, UBS says.  “All that said, the weight loss looks robust and the safety profile looks generally consistent with the drug class.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/health-care-roundup-market-talk-76913f76?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Turns to Sakana AI for Gemini Push</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-turns-sakana-ai-gemini-113801642.html</link><description>Startup gains access to core AI models</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-turns-sakana-ai-gemini-113801642.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Week In AI Chips - AI Transforming Chip Design Insights From DVCon US Conference</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-ai-transforming-113759930.html</link><description>The 2026 Design and Verification Conference and Exhibition (DVCon U.S.) has unveiled its program, focusing on the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in alleviating the verification bottleneck within electronic design. The event, set to occur from March 2-5 at the Hyatt Regency Santa Clara, will feature a panel discussion addressing whether AI could revolutionize the design verification process or if it may be merely another over-hyped technology. Attendees will have access to keynotes,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-ai-transforming-113759930.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google faces making changes to search services under watchdog proposals</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/google-faces-making-changes-search-110629470.html</link><description>The CMA has tabled measures to improve Google Search in the UK after it designated the firm with so-called strategic market status.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/google-faces-making-changes-search-110629470.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] F&amp;C Investment Trust Update: Nevin Defends Global, AI-Linked Portfolio as Dollar Weakens</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/fc-investment-trust-update-nevin-defends-global-ai-linked-portfolio-as-dollar-weakens-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>F&amp;amp;C Investment Trust (LON:FCIT) used a shareholder update to outline portfolio positioning, recent performance, and key market themes, with fund manager Paul Nevin emphasizing a long-term, globally diversified approach spanning listed equities and private equity. Trust overview and portfolio st</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/fc-investment-trust-update-nevin-defends-global-ai-linked-portfolio-as-dollar-weakens-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Exclusive-Novo's Wegovy and Ozempic US advertising spend doubles rival Eli Lilly, data shows</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-novos-wegovy-ozempic-us-110653009.html</link><description>By Harshita Mary Varghese and Patrick Wingrove Jan 28 (Reuters) - Novo Nordisk spent nearly $500 million on U.S. advertising for its GLP-1 drugs Wegovy and Ozempic in the first nine months of 2025,</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-novos-wegovy-ozempic-us-110653009.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] India Obesity Drug Fight Is About to Intensify</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-obesity-drug-fight-intensify-113118752.html</link><description>Sun Pharma clears path for semaglutide generics</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-obesity-drug-fight-intensify-113118752.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ASML posts record orders on AI chip demand, SK Hynix soars</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-posts-record-orders-ai-113018436.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: The AI boom showed no signs of slowing down for majors ASML and SK Hynix on Wednesday (January 28).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASML logged record orders in the fourth quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the top computer chip equipment maker raised its outlook for the year as demand surged from its AI-focused customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fourth-quarter bookings leapt to a record $15.8 billion - well up from a year before and far ahead of analyst expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm also raised its sales guidance to between $46.8 billion to a near $54 billion - again ahead of analyst projections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares were up more than 4% in early trade - the stock is up close to 40% this year so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The orders beat comes as ASML customers like Samsung and SK Hynix boost investment plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those firms have seen major demand for AI logic and memory chips needed by cloud computing giants like Microsoft and Google.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea's SK Hynix also reported record quarterly earnings Wednesday amid the AI boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It smashed forecasts with&amp;amp;nbsp;a profit more than double its previous record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also predicted AI demand would keep pushing explosive growth in memory chip orders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-posts-record-orders-ai-113018436.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Texas Instruments shares jump as first-quarter outlook signals robust AI data center demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-instruments-shares-jump-first-112650774.html</link><description>Texas Instruments' shares gained 7% in premarket trading on Wednesday after its rosy quarterly forecast showed the AI data center ​boom was driving demand for chips beyond Nvidia's advanced processors.  TI on Tuesday ‌forecast first-quarter profit and revenue above estimates, powered by strong analog sales, especially in data center.  TI makes ‌analog chips for converting signals and managing power in data centers, unlike Nvidia's fast, high-priced AI graphics chips, and has benefited from a surge in demand from tech companies ramping up compute infrastructure to power their AI ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-instruments-shares-jump-first-112650774.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eikon ‍Therapeutics targets $908 million valuation in US IPO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eikon-therapeutics-targets-908-million-111855370.html</link><description>Jan 28 (Reuters) - Drug developer Eikon ‍Therapeutics said on Wednesday it was targeting a valuation of up to $908.2 million in its U.S. initial public offering, as biotech listings make a comeback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eikon-therapeutics-targets-908-million-111855370.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple’s Gemini AI Deal And China Risks Weigh On Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-ai-deal-china-111152846.html</link><description>Apple (NasdaqGS:AAPL) has agreed a partnership with Alphabet to use its Gemini AI model to power an upgraded Siri and other AI features. The Gemini powered capabilities are expected to sit at the center of Apple's next wave of on device and cloud based AI services. Separately, a shareholder proposal is urging Apple to publish a report on risks tied to its business exposure to China. Apple, trading at $258.27, has had a mixed share price record recently, with a 4.7% gain over the past week...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-ai-deal-china-111152846.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Waabi hauls in $750M Series C to become Canada’s newest autonomous vehicle unicorn</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waabi-hauls-750m-series-c-110000192.html</link><description>Oversubscribed round led by Khosla and G2 catapults Toronto startup into robotaxi race with massive Uber deal The post Waabi hauls in $750M Series C to become Canada’s newest autonomous vehicle unicorn appeared first on FreightWaves.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waabi-hauls-750m-series-c-110000192.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Chip Stocks Get Another Boost From ASML Earnings</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/chip-stocks-get-another-boost-from-asml-earnings-lMSqCA1JRMRfPdm6TVMA?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shares in ASML, the Dutch company that builds the world's most advanced chipmaking equipment, surged after it logged record quarterly orders and forecast healthy sales growth this year.    The stock gained more than 5% in Amsterdam, recently trading at 1,282.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/chip-stocks-get-another-boost-from-asml-earnings-lMSqCA1JRMRfPdm6TVMA?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Surges On Strong Sales Forecast For 2026</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/asml-stock-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Semiconductor equipment giant ASML provided a strong outlook for the current quarter and full year ahead. ASML stock rose on the news.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/asml-stock-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wall Street Bets a Rally in Riskiest Stocks Has Staying Power</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-bets-rally-riskiest-103000857.html</link><description>The Russell 2000 Index, home to some of the riskiest stocks in the market because of their strong ties to the business and credit cycles, just ended the longest run of beating large caps since 1996.  The bet is predicated on expectations for faster earnings growth, owing to a combination of falling interest rates and economic growth.  “This channel of strong enough growth – but not too strong – and lower or declining rates are two big macro forces that can push small caps higher,” said Sebastien Page, chief investment officer at T Rowe Price, which manages nearly $1.8 trillion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-bets-rally-riskiest-103000857.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] UK regulator proposes changes to Google search for publishers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-regulator-proposes-changes-google-102256121.html</link><description>LONDON, Jan 28 () - Britain's competition regulator on Wednesday proposed a package ​of measures that it said would ‌improve Google search services in the country, including making ‌sure publishers get a fairer deal over how their content is used in the engine's AI overviews. Google said in response it was "exploring" ⁠updates to ‌its controls to let sites specifically opt out of search generative ‍AI features.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-regulator-proposes-changes-google-102256121.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Intel, Micron and These Other Chip Stocks Are Rallying. Thank Texas Instruments and ASML.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-micron-texas-instruments-asml-7c977c33?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Chip makers’ shares rally after a solid batch of earnings report signal that the AI boom is still driving up demand for semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-micron-texas-instruments-asml-7c977c33?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Strong iPhone sales to power Apple's holiday quarter, Google AI deal in focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-iphone-sales-power-apples-102033119.html</link><description>By Akash Sriram Jan 28 (Reuters) - Apple is set to report its strongest iPhone sales growth in four years on Thursday, driven by robust demand for its premium Pro models as it prepares to roll out</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-iphone-sales-power-apples-102033119.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Bull of the Day: Lam Research (LRCX)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-lam-research-lrcx-102000424.html</link><description>Analysts have been behind the growth and valuation curves as TSM and MU signal WFE expansion into 2029</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-lam-research-lrcx-102000424.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] EC initiates steps for Google’s compliance with Digital Markets Act</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/ec-google-compliance-digital-markets-act/</link><description>The proceedings are part of EC’s efforts to address Google's compliance issues involving Android and online search data sharing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/ec-google-compliance-digital-markets-act/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks to Watch Wednesday: Nvidia, SoftBank, Alibaba</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-nvidia-softbank-YxSGpJ6KdlVJN9dpU0EI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↗️ Nvidia (NVDA): China has approved purchases of Nvidia’s popular H200 chip for the first time, giving authorization to several customers, including Alibaba (BABA, HK:9988). Nvidia shares rose in premarket trading, as did Alibaba's stock in Hong Kong.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-nvidia-softbank-YxSGpJ6KdlVJN9dpU0EI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Earnings in Focus Wednesday: ASML, GE Vernova, Meta</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/earnings-in-focus-wednesday-asml-ge-vernova-meta-ijXuh4m4ohBvRlVyh7lQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full swing, with 102 companies in the benchmark S&amp;amp;P 500 index reporting this week, according to LSEG. Microsoft, Meta Platforms and Tesla are among the companies due to report today.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/earnings-in-focus-wednesday-asml-ge-vernova-meta-ijXuh4m4ohBvRlVyh7lQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Rebrand Highlights AI Deals With Microsoft And Meta, Valuation Questions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-rebrand-highlights-ai-deals-100833339.html</link><description>Nebius Group, now trading as NasdaqGS:NBIS, has rebranded from Yandex and is repositioning itself as a dedicated AI infrastructure provider. The company has signed long term AI infrastructure agreements with Microsoft and Meta Platforms, signaling deeper involvement in large scale cloud and AI workloads. Nebius plans an international rollout of Nvidia’s next generation Rubin platform to serve rising demand for AI compute capacity. Nebius Group focuses on providing AI infrastructure,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-rebrand-highlights-ai-deals-100833339.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SoftBank in discussions for up to $30bn additional investment in OpenAI</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/softbank-additional-investment-openai/</link><description>SoftBank’s latest talks form part of a wider funding round that could significantly boost OpenAI’s valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/softbank-additional-investment-openai/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Weekly: EU targets Grok, Nvidia waves off AI bubble fears</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-weekly-eu-targets-grok-095535737.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: From the EU investigating Grok to Jensen Huang waving off AI bubble fears, this is AI Weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: AI Weekly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Commission launched an investigation into Grok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's looking at whether Elon Musk's AI chatbot spreads illegal content in the EU, including manipulated sexualised images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will see&amp;amp;nbsp;whether X properly assessed and lowered risks related to Grok's functionalities in the bloc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;X referred to a statement issued earlier this month where it said xAI had restricted image editing for Grok AI users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia boss Jensen Huang waved off fears about an AI bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And he encouraged everybody to get involved with the technology during a talk at the World Economic Forum in Davos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The AI bubble comes about because the investments are large. And the investments are large because we have to build the infrastructure necessary for all of the layers of AI above it. And so I think the opportunity is really quite extraordinary. And everybody ought to get involved."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also pushed back on concerns about AI taking human jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And instead said it will create lots of jobs, especially for those in trades like plumbing and construction.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intel shares plunged towards the end of last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors sold off after the company struggled to meet strong AI demand for data center chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It blamed that on supply constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm is a latecomer to the AI boom and had finally enjoyed a demand surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung aims to start production of its next-gen high-bandwidth memory chips - or HBM4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's what a source told Reuters, who added the South Korean firm plans to supply them to Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has tried to catch up with local rival SK Hynix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is a key supplier for advanced memory chips crucial for Nvidia's AI accelerators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Microsoft unveiled its second generation of in-house AI chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It took aim at one of Nvidia's main competitive advantages with developers.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new 'Maia 200' semiconductor comes online this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It comes as major cloud computing firms like Microsoft, Amazon and Google produce their own chips - which are increasingly competing&amp;amp;nbsp;with Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-weekly-eu-targets-grok-095535737.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix Profit Surges on Relentless Appetite for AI Memory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-profit-surges-relentless-075846431.html</link><description>Icheon-based SK Hynix also announced it will establish an AI data center solutions firm in the US, backed by $10 billion of capital, to pursue partnerships and investments in the sector.  The new company will operate out of a restructured Solidigm, the storage company SK Hynix acquired from Intel Corp., according to a statement.  Shares in SK Hynix, the leading supplier of high-bandwidth memory or HBM for Nvidia Corp.’s AI accelerators, have roughly tripled since the start of September.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-profit-surges-relentless-075846431.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Trending tickers: Nvidia, ASML, Texas Instruments, LVMH and Fresnillo</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-asml-texas-instruments-lvmh-fresnillo-trending-tickers-093532079.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-asml-texas-instruments-lvmh-fresnillo-trending-tickers-093532079.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] My Prediction For Nvidia Stock in 2025 Came True. Here's What I Expect to Happen Next.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/my-prediction-for-nvidia-stock-in-2025-came-true-h/</link><description>Nvidia has wowed investors with its growth during this AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/my-prediction-for-nvidia-stock-in-2025-came-true-h/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is AI Superstar Palantir Technologies Going to Plunge in 2026? History Offers 2 Undeniable Clues.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/ai-palantir-going-to-plunge-2026-history-2-clues/</link><description>When things seem too good to be true for Wall Street's hottest artificial intelligence (AI) stock, they often are.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/ai-palantir-going-to-plunge-2026-history-2-clues/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML made record $11.5 billion profit in 2025 thanks to AI-driven demand, plans to cut 1,700 jobs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-made-record-11-5-091520740.html</link><description>Dutch semiconductor chip machine maker ASML recorded a record net profit of 9.6 billion euros ($11.5 billion) in 2025 on sales of 32.7 billion euros fueled by AI-driven demand, the company reported Wednesday as it also announced plans to slash its workforce by about 1,700, about 4% of its workforce.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-made-record-11-5-091520740.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Expands AI Education And Patents As Enterprise Use Cases Grow</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-expands-ai-education-patents-091233373.html</link><description>IBM is expanding its role in AI education through a UK government partnership aimed at upskilling millions of workers in AI related skills. The company is taking a leadership role in open source patent protection via the updated Open Invention Network 2.0 framework. IBM is rolling out new AI products, including agentic AI tools for enterprise compliance and fan engagement platforms used at events like the Grammys. For investors tracking International Business Machines, NYSE:IBM, the current...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-expands-ai-education-patents-091233373.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Forget Intel: This Agile Chip Challenger Looks Far Better Positioned for the Next Wave of AI Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-intel-this-agile-chip-challenger-looks-far/</link><description>Intel could resume its turnaround. However, AMD appears to be the better pick for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-intel-this-agile-chip-challenger-looks-far/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] KeyBanc Sees Inflection Point for Alight (ALIT) After Volatile Year in Healthcare IT</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-sees-inflection-point-alight-085555070.html</link><description>Alight, Inc. (NYSE:ALIT) is included among the 13 Dividend Stocks with Over 8% Yield. On January 8, KeyBanc slashed its price target on Alight, Inc. (NYSE:ALIT) to $2.50 from $6, while sticking with an Overweight rating. After a rough and uneven year for healthcare IT stocks, the firm said the fundamentals tell a more encouraging […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-sees-inflection-point-alight-085555070.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Tech Stocks Rally Ahead of Fed Rate Call. Dollar Falls After Trump Rout.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-012826/card/tech-stocks-rally-ahead-of-fed-rate-call-dollar-falls-after-trump-rout--wUedUz6abaN5GNhsAPFV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks looked set to extend their record-breaking run on Wednesday following earnings reports from two chip companies, while the dollar looked set to carry on sliding after comments from President Donald Trump sparked a brutal selloff for the greenback.  The tech-heavy index was racking up gains after semiconductor manufacturer Texas Instruments and chip tool maker ASML both issued solid guidance, which investors took as a sign that the artificial-intelligence boom still has legs.  The Federal Reserve is also set to make its latest policy decision–the central bank is widely expected to keep interest rates unchanged, but Chair Jerome Powell’s comments could give the market a better idea of whether there’ll be scope for cuts to borrowing costs later in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-012826/card/tech-stocks-rally-ahead-of-fed-rate-call-dollar-falls-after-trump-rout--wUedUz6abaN5GNhsAPFV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates Models on AllianceBernstein (AB) as Fund Flows Remain Weak</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-models-alliancebernstein-ab-085330523.html</link><description>AllianceBernstein Holding L.P. (NYSE:AB) is included among the 13 Dividend Stocks with Over 8% Yield. On January 15, Barclays cut its price target on AllianceBernstein Holding L.P. (NYSE:AB) to $39 from $42. The firm maintained an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change followed an update to the firm’s asset manager models, which now […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-models-alliancebernstein-ab-085330523.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Exclusive-China gives nod to ByteDance, Alibaba and Tencent to buy Nvidia's H200 chips - sources</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</link><description>Jan 28 () - China has given the green light to three of its largest tech companies to buy Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips, four people familiar with the matter told , marking a shift in position as Beijing ​seeks to balance its AI needs against spurring domestic development. ByteDance, Alibaba and Tencent have been approved to purchase more than ‌400,000 H200 chips in total, with other firms now joining a queue for subsequent approvals, the sources said, speaking on condition of anon</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Looking at 'Record Quarter,' CEO Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-looking-record-quarter-ceo-082924056.html</link><description>ASML Chief Executive Officer Christophe Fouquet discusses the company's performance in the fourth quarter as orders far exceeded analysts' expectations. "We're looking at a record quarter, we're looking at a record year," Fouquet tells Bloomberg Television.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-looking-record-quarter-ceo-082924056.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Meta Earnings, Fed Decision, Venezuela Testimony: Still to Come This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-still-to-come-this-week-Iqs58QMElx48WGUCtczJ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full throttle, with results expected from a quartet of tech giants—Apple, Meta Platforms, Microsoft and Tesla. In Washington, the Federal Reserve will announce its first interest-rate decision of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-still-to-come-this-week-Iqs58QMElx48WGUCtczJ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix Caps Off Bumper Year With Record Quarter</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/sk-hynix-caps-off-bumper-year-with-record-quarter-866c37fc?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The memory chip maker posted record earnings for the final quarter of 2025 as the global artificial-intelligence boom continued to fuel strong demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/sk-hynix-caps-off-bumper-year-with-record-quarter-866c37fc?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia’s CoreWeave Bet Balances AI Growth Ambitions With Legal Scrutiny</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-coreweave-bet-balances-ai-081237980.html</link><description>Nvidia announced a US$2 billion investment in CoreWeave (NasdaqGS:CRWV), together with an expanded commercial partnership. CoreWeave is set to deepen its role as an infrastructure provider for Nvidia powered AI workloads. Multiple class action lawsuits have been filed alleging misrepresentations about CoreWeave's ability to scale infrastructure and meet customer demand. The combination of fresh capital, closer collaboration with Nvidia, and legal claims about prior disclosures has drawn...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-coreweave-bet-balances-ai-081237980.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Deepens AI Factory Push With CoreWeave Healthcare And Education Ties</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-deepens-ai-factory-push-081126978.html</link><description>Nvidia (NasdaqGS:NVDA) is investing an additional US$2b in CoreWeave to support the buildout of more than 5 gigawatts of AI data center capacity by 2030. The expanded partnership centers on large scale AI infrastructure, sometimes described as AI "factories," aimed at serving rising demand for compute power. Nvidia also announced collaborations with BoodleBox in education and Oath Surgical in healthcare, integrating its AI platforms into learning and surgical workflows. The developments...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-deepens-ai-factory-push-081126978.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China clears first NVIDIA H200 AI chips for import: sources</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/china-clears-first-nvidia-h200-081042104.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: China has approved its first batch of Nvidia’s H200 artificial intelligence chips for import.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to Reuters sources familiar with the matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a notable shift as Beijing tries to balance its AI development needs with support for its domestic semiconductor industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: File&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The approval covers several hundred thousand H200 chips and was granted during Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang’s visit to China this week, according to the sources, who requested anonymity due to the sensitivity of the matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two said the semiconductors would go to tech giants ByteDance, Alibaba and Tencent, with more firms waiting in line for future approvals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of the firms involved immediately responded to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The H200 is Nvidia’s second most powerful AI chip and a key flashpoint in U.S.-China relations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington has cleared it for export, but Beijing's hesitation to allow imports has been the main barrier to shipments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese firms have already ordered over two million H200 chips, far beyond Nvidia’s available inventory, and&amp;amp;nbsp;while domestic alternatives such as Huawei are improving, they still lag well behind the H200’s performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear how many additional approvals Beijing will grant as it weighs access to foreign chips against long‑term tech self‑reliance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/china-clears-first-nvidia-h200-081042104.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC’s US$56b AI Capex Push Tests Valuation And Growth Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-us-56b-ai-capex-080954371.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (NYSE:TSM) plans up to $56b in capital expenditures to expand chip manufacturing capacity, focused on AI chips. The company has opened a new U.S. plant and signed a major deal to further build out its U.S. footprint. These moves highlight TSMC’s role in AI chip production and ongoing shifts in the global semiconductor supply chain. For investors watching NYSE:TSM, this spending plan comes with the stock at $338.34 and trailing returns that include 68.9%...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-us-56b-ai-capex-080954371.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML’s Record Orders Smash Estimates as AI Spurs Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-record-orders-smash-estimates-080755988.html</link><description>Bookings in the fourth quarter were a record €13.2 billion ($15.8 billion), driven by demand for its most sophisticated equipment, the Veldhoven, Netherlands-based company said in a statement on Wednesday.  ASML is the only producer of cutting-edge lithography machines that are needed to make advanced semiconductors, and counts all the leading chip manufacturers as customers, including Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corp. and Intel Corp. Its machinery is integral to producing the Nvidia Corp. AI accelerators that are the backbone for training and running AI models in data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-record-orders-smash-estimates-080755988.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix vs. Alphabet Stock: Which Is the Better Growth Stock to Buy and Hold for the Next 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/netflix-vs-alphabet-stock-which-is-the-better-grow/</link><description>Both stocks are growing at similar rates and are trading at similar valuations, but one is still the clear winner when comparing the two.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/netflix-vs-alphabet-stock-which-is-the-better-grow/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Drives Q4 Gains as Pharma Fundamentals Shine Amid Sector Rotation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-drives-q4-080519997.html</link><description>Polen Capital Management Llc released its “Polen Focus Growth Strategy” Q4 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. In Q4 2025, the Polen Focus Growth strategy delivered a -1.37% gross return, underperforming the Russell 1000 Growth Index (+1.12%) and the S&amp;amp;P 500 (+2.66%), as concentrated mega‑cap leadership and AI valuation […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-drives-q4-080519997.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Earnings Are Coming. Watch the Software Business.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ibm-earnings-stock-price-d02d2add?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>IBM reports after the close Wednesday. Analysts expect software to drive results and provide support for the stock after a strong 12-month rally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ibm-earnings-stock-price-d02d2add?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Zacks Analyst Blog Oracle's, Amazon and Alphabet</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-oracles-amazon-075600750.html</link><description>Oracle is ramping cloud CapEx to nearly $50B, betting GPU infrastructure and AI demand will fuel faster revenue growth starting fiscal 2027.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-oracles-amazon-075600750.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix posts record quarterly profit on huge AI demand, trounces expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-posts-forecast-beating-074143710.html</link><description>South Korea's SK Hynix said on Wednesday that quarterly profit more than doubled ​to a record, comfortably beating forecasts on relentless ‌demand for artificial intelligence that has lifted prices for both advanced and ‌conventional memory chips.  The Nvidia supplier logged a 137% surge in operating profit to 19.2 trillion won ($13.5 billion) for the fourth quarter, according to Reuters calculations.  That compared with 8.1 trillion ⁠won a year earlier ‌and a 17.7 trillion won consensus prediction from LSEG SmartEstimate, which is weighted toward analysts ‍with a more consistent track record.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-posts-forecast-beating-074143710.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Will Crush the Market in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-ai-stock-will-crush-the-market-in-2026/</link><description>Microsoft released its in-house chip that will directly compete with Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-ai-stock-will-crush-the-market-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML: Q4 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-earnings-snapshot-071658583.html</link><description>DR VELDHOVEN, Netherlands (AP) — ASML Holding NV (ASML) on Wednesday reported fourth-quarter profit of $3.31 billion. On a per-share basis, the Dr Veldhoven, Netherlands-based company said it had profit of $8.55. The results fell short of Wall Street expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-earnings-snapshot-071658583.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/asml-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>ASML (NASDAQ:ASML) reported Q4 2025 net revenue of EUR 9.7 billion, a record quarter that included the recognition of revenue for two High-NA systems. For the full year 2025, the company reported revenue of EUR 32.7 billion, representing a 16% increase compared to 2024. Management said the quarter</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/asml-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SoftBank in talks to invest up to $30 billion more in OpenAI: source</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-065842056.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: SoftBank could be ramping up its bet on OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese firm is in talks to pour as much as $30 billion more into the ChatGPT owner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person familiar with the matter said that the money would be part of a funding round that could raise up to $100 billion, valuing OpenAI at about $830 billion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CEO Masayoshi Son has made what he calls an “all‑in” bet on OpenAI as it seeks to improve its position in the artificial intelligence race.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In December, the company said it had completed a $41 billion investment, giving it an 11% stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI is facing rising costs to train and run its AI models as the race against Google intensifies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SoftBank declined to comment, though its shares were up 3.5% in Tokyo morning trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters reported last month that Son had scrambled to gather funds for the earlier investment, slowing dealmaking at the company's Vision Fund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both OpenAI and SoftBank are backing Stargate, a $500 billion initiative to build AI data centers for training and inference that executives say is key to the U.S. government's ambitions to keep ahead of China in AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-065842056.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Ends 2025 With Record Orders as AI Spending Remains Healthy</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company logged record quarterly orders of its semiconductor-making equipment and said it expects healthy sales growth this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Dutch tech giant ASML posts bumper profits, eyes bright AI future</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dutch-tech-giant-asml-posts-063125401.html</link><description>Dutch tech giant ASML, which sells cutting-edge machines to make semiconductor chips, reported a significant gain in annual net profit Wednesday and predicted a bright future driven by demand for artificial intelligence.In a case unrelated to ASML, the Dutch government briefly seized control of Nexperia, a Chinese-owned company that makes low-tech semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dutch-tech-giant-asml-posts-063125401.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ASML Q4 bookings beat expectations as chipmakers order more to satisfy AI demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-bookings-beat-expectations-061654428.html</link><description>ASML reported stronger-than-expected bookings on Wednesday as the world's largest supplier of computer chip equipment received ​more orders thanks to larger investments in artificial-intelligence chipmaking capacity.  Fourth-quarter ‌bookings, the most watched metric in the industry, were 13.2 billion euros ($15.8 billion), ‌compared with 5.4 billion euros in the previous quarter.  "In the last months, many of our customers have shared a notably more ⁠positive assessment of the ‌medium-term market situation, primarily based on more robust expectations of the sustainability of AI-related demand," ASML's Chief ‍executive Christophe Fouquet said in a statement.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-bookings-beat-expectations-061654428.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should Rising Social Engineering Against Okta (OKTA) Identities Require Action From Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rising-social-engineering-against-okta-061325778.html</link><description>In recent days, Okta and external researchers have detailed a wave of sophisticated social engineering campaigns, including custom phishing-as-a-service kits and voice-phishing attacks, aimed at stealing single sign-on credentials and bypassing multi-factor authentication across Okta, Google, and Microsoft environments. Although these incidents are not rooted in product vulnerabilities, they spotlight how attackers increasingly exploit human behavior and real-time MFA interception,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rising-social-engineering-against-okta-061325778.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Best Artificial Intelligence (AI) Data Center Play You've Never Heard of for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-best-artificial-intelligence-ai-data-center-pl/</link><description>Microsoft and Google are trusting this company to ensure their data centers stay up and running.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-best-artificial-intelligence-ai-data-center-pl/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Top 3 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Chip Stocks to Buy With $50,000 in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-top-3-artificial-intelligence-ai-chip-stocks-t/</link><description>Semiconductor stocks look poised for further gains as investment in artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure accelerates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-top-3-artificial-intelligence-ai-chip-stocks-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Explainer-The $250 million ASML 'printer' behind Nvidia's chips</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/explainer-250-million-asml-printer-050227041.html</link><description>AMSTERDAM, Jan 28 (Reuters) - ASML has become Europe's most valuable company thanks to its dominance in making lithography systems, huge "chip printing" machines that cost $250 million each and are</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/explainer-250-million-asml-printer-050227041.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:05:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] 1 Surging  Stock Worth Your Attention and 2 We Turn Down</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-surging-stock-worth-attention-043540984.html</link><description>Great things are happening to the stocks in this article. They’re all outperforming the market over the last month because of positive catalysts such as a new product line, constructive news flow, or even a loyal Reddit fanbase.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-surging-stock-worth-attention-043540984.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 3 Market-Beating Stocks with Competitive Advantages</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-market-beating-stocks-competitive-043359713.html</link><description>Stocks that outperform the market usually share key traits such as rising sales, expanding margins, and increasing returns on capital. The select few that can do all three for many years are often the ones that make you life-changing money.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-market-beating-stocks-competitive-043359713.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] 2 Volatile Stocks with Competitive Advantages and 1 We Ignore</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-volatile-stocks-competitive-advantages-043320379.html</link><description>Volatility cuts both ways - while it creates opportunities, it also increases risk, making sharp declines just as likely as big gains. This unpredictability can shake out even the most experienced investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-volatile-stocks-competitive-advantages-043320379.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Assessing HSBC (LSE:HSBA) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-hsbc-lse-hsba-valuation-043302005.html</link><description>Event context and recent performance snapshot HSBC Holdings (LSE:HSBA) has been drawing attention after a period of strong recent returns, with the share price moving higher over the past week, month and past 3 months. See our latest analysis for HSBC Holdings. Zooming out, HSBC Holdings’ recent momentum sits on top of a 1-year total shareholder return of 63.45% and a 5-year total shareholder return above 3x. The latest £12.772 share price reflects strong shorter term share price returns that...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-hsbc-lse-hsba-valuation-043302005.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Exclusive-China gives green light to importing first batch of Nvidia's H200 AI chips, sources say</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</link><description>Jan 28 (Reuters) - China has approved its first batch of Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips for import, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters, marking a shift in position as China</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Top Valuation Expert Says AI Market Needs 'Trillions In Revenue' To Justify Valuations After Cashing Out Of Its Biggest Chipmaker</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-valuation-expert-says-ai-033111714.html</link><description>Aswath Damodaran, the ‘Dean of Valuation,’ has issued a stark warning to AI investors that the math simply does not add up. Citing a massive disconnect between upfront infrastructure spending and future earnings, the NYU finance professor revealed he has fully exited his position in Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA) while maintaining his stake in Microsoft Corp. (NASDAQ:MSFT). The ‘Big Market Delusion’ Damodaran argues that the current AI frenzy exhibits classic signs of a “Big Market Delusion,” a cycl</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-valuation-expert-says-ai-033111714.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Forget AI Stocks: This Energy Infrastructure Stock Is the Smarter Bet</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-ai-stocks-this-energy-infrastructure-stock/</link><description>Looking for a hedge against any AI bubble that may or may not be forming? Centrus Energy is a good choice.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-ai-stocks-this-energy-infrastructure-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] What To Expect From Caterpillar’s (CAT) Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/expect-caterpillar-cat-q4-earnings-031246311.html</link><description>Construction equipment company Caterpillar (NYSE:CAT) will be reporting results this Thursday before market hours. Here’s what to expect.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/expect-caterpillar-cat-q4-earnings-031246311.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Corporation Earnings: What To Look For From KLAC</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-earnings-look-klac-031118827.html</link><description>Semiconductor manufacturing equipment maker KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) will be announcing earnings results this Thursday after market hours. Here’s what to expect.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-earnings-look-klac-031118827.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Infrastructure Stock Will Be the Biggest Beneficiary of OpenAI's Growth by End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/prediction-this-ai-infrastructure-stock-will-be-th/</link><description>CoreWeave has a lot to gain from OpenAI's growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/prediction-this-ai-infrastructure-stock-will-be-th/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Prediction for Nvidia in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/1-prediction-for-nvidia-in-2026/</link><description>Market watchers are expecting $65 billion in Q4 revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/1-prediction-for-nvidia-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Osborne Partners Buys Another $4 Million Worth of MercadoLibre Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/27/osborne-partners-buys-another-usd4-million-worth-of-mercadolibre-stock/</link><description>MercadoLibre is a leading Latin American e-commerce and fintech platform, linking merchants and consumers through digital services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/27/osborne-partners-buys-another-usd4-million-worth-of-mercadolibre-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SoftBank in talks to invest up to $30 billion more in OpenAI, source says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-004740741.html</link><description>SoftBank Group Corp is in talks to invest as much as an additional $30 ​billion in OpenAI, a person familiar with the ‌matter said on Tuesday, as the Japanese conglomerate doubles down on its bet ‌on the ChatGPT owner.  The fresh investment would form part of a funding round that could raise up to $100 billion for OpenAI, valuing it at about $830 billion, the person said.  Seeking to improve SoftBank's position in the artificial intelligence race, ‍Chief Executive Masayoshi Son has made an "all-in" bet on OpenAI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-004740741.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SoftBank in Talks to Invest Up to $30 Billion More in OpenAI</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/softbank-in-talks-to-invest-up-to-30-billion-more-in-openai-8585dea3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Japanese conglomerate is exploring a further investment as part of the startup’s efforts to raise up to $100 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/softbank-in-talks-to-invest-up-to-30-billion-more-in-openai-8585dea3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wall Street Thinks This AI Stock Is the Next Big Thing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/wall-street-thinks-this-ai-stock-is-the-next-big-t/</link><description>While AI chip stocks continue to garner outsize attention, smart analysts are looking elsewhere for growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/wall-street-thinks-this-ai-stock-is-the-next-big-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Did Applied Digital Stock Jump 14.3% Today?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-did-applied-digital-stock-jump-143-today/</link><description>Nvidia just bought $2 billion worth of CoreWeave stock. Here's why it matters for Applied Digital.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-did-applied-digital-stock-jump-143-today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures rise as Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353507.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353507.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise as Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353801.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353801.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Just Gave You a $2 Billion Reason to Buy CoreWeave Stock</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37261483/nvidia-just-gave-you-a-2-billion-reason-to-buy-coreweave-stock</link><description>Nvidia’s $2 billion strategic investment in CoreWeave is a powerful endorsement of its AI infrastructure model, making CRWV a compelling stock to buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37261483/nvidia-just-gave-you-a-2-billion-reason-to-buy-coreweave-stock</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 27: Nvidia’s $2 Billion Bet Lifts CoreWeave and Refocuses the AI Infrastructure Trade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/27/stock-market-today-jan-27-coreweave-surges-after-nvidia-invests-2-billion/</link><description>CoreWeave rallied as Nvidia deepened its commitment to AI data center capacity, highlighting both the growth opportunity and the operational hurdles ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/27/stock-market-today-jan-27-coreweave-surges-after-nvidia-invests-2-billion/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] UK rolls out free AI training, but will it save your job?</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rolls-free-ai-training-230200819.html</link><description>Free artificial intelligence training is being made available to everyone in the UK as the government steps up efforts to prepare the workforce for rapid technological change.  From today, adults can access short, practical courses through the government's upgraded AI Skills Hub, designed to help people use AI tools in the workplace.  The training covers everyday tasks such as drafting text, creating content, and automating administrative work - with some courses taking less than 20 minutes to complete.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rolls-free-ai-training-230200819.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Futures: Stock Market Hits Highs; Tesla, Meta, Microsoft, Fed's Powell On Tap</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-meta-microsoft-fed-chief-powell/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Many stocks made bullish moves as the Nasdaq led and the S&amp;amp;P 500 hit a high, but Tesla, Microsoft, Meta and Fed's Powell loom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-meta-microsoft-fed-chief-powell/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Exceeds Market Returns: Some Facts to Consider</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-exceeds-market-224505205.html</link><description>In the latest trading session, CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) closed at $476.66, marking a +1.78% move from the previous day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-exceeds-market-224505205.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Laps the Stock Market: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-laps-stock-market-224504706.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw Nvidia (NVDA) settling at $188.52, representing a +1.1% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-laps-stock-market-224504706.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Systems (CSCO) Rises Higher Than Market: Key Facts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-rises-higher-224502702.html</link><description>Cisco Systems (CSCO) reached $78.68 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +2.17% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-rises-higher-224502702.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Berkshire Hathaway Will Lose Its Biggest Mutual-Fund Fan With Danoff’s Retirement</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-danoff-fidelity-44b3feb1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The mutual-fund industry will lose its biggest fan of  Berkshire Hathaway  with the retirement of Fidelity Contrafund manager Will Danoff at the end of 2026 after 35 years at its helm.  Danoff’s $176 billion fund probably was the single largest holder of Berkshire among actively managed mutual funds.  Contrafund’s stake in Berkshire is now worth about $10 billion, Barron’s calculates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-danoff-fidelity-44b3feb1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Forget Nebius Group: This Hyper-Growth Cloud Platform Is a Far Better Way to Play the AI Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-nebius-group-this-hyper-growth-cloud-platfo/</link><description>DigitalOcean offers more stable growth with higher profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-nebius-group-this-hyper-growth-cloud-platfo/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Best Stocks to Invest $2,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/the-best-stocks-to-invest-2000-right-now/</link><description>These companies are cashing in on how people are using AI every day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/the-best-stocks-to-invest-2000-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Trading Day: Extreme bifurcation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trading-day-extreme-bifurcation-220647090.html</link><description>ORLANDO, Florida, Jan 27 () - World stocks and the S&amp;amp;P; 500 hit new highs on Tuesday, boosted by a flood of strong U. earnings reports, while anxiety over U.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trading-day-extreme-bifurcation-220647090.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Earnings live: UnitedHealth stock falls 19%, American Airlines slides, Texas Instruments pops, Logitech edges higher</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-unitedhealth-stock-falls-19-american-airlines-slides-texas-instruments-pops-logitech-edges-higher-213941564.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-unitedhealth-stock-falls-19-american-airlines-slides-texas-instruments-pops-logitech-edges-higher-213941564.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] The Dow Is Getting Pummeled by UnitedHealth. Why the Rest of the Stock Market Is Fine.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/dow-jones-industrial-average-unitedhealth-stock-maket-77b52f96?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Just look at  UnitedHealth  The Dow tumbled more than 400 points, or 0.8%, Tuesday.  UnitedHealth, which reported earnings Tuesday morning, was hit by weaker-than-expected revenue and underwhelming guidance for 2026.  News late Monday that the Trump administration was proposing a smaller-than-forecast increase in Medicare Advantage reimbursements only served to make investors even more nervous.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/dow-jones-industrial-average-unitedhealth-stock-maket-77b52f96?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Are You Richer Than You Feel? Nearly 70% Of Millionaires Don't Consider Themselves Wealthy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/richer-feel-nearly-70-millionaires-213108064.html</link><description>If being a millionaire used to mean yacht parties and champagne toasts, someone forgot to tell today's millionaires. Turns out, having seven figures in the bank doesn't always come with a sense of financial comfort—or even confidence. According to the 2025 Planning &amp;amp; Progress Study by Northwestern Mutual, only 36% of U.S. adults with at least $1 million in investable assets actually consider themselves "wealthy." That means 64%—despite their millionaire status—feel like they're still chasing fin</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/richer-feel-nearly-70-millionaires-213108064.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Chip sector shifts: Nvidia to beat Apple as TSMC's top customer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/chip-sector-shifts-nvidia-to-beat-apple-as-tsmcs-top-customer-212618311.html</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) is set to surpass Apple (AAPL) as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company's (TSM) top 2026 customer.Creative Strategies CEO and principal analyst Ben Bajarin joins Market Domination host Josh Lipton to explain how the chip sector is evolving.To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/chip-sector-shifts-nvidia-to-beat-apple-as-tsmcs-top-customer-212618311.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here's Why I Wouldn't Touch Intel Stock With a 10-Foot Pole</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/heres-why-i-wouldnt-touch-intel-stock-with-a-10-fo/</link><description>There are key questions that have yet to be answered for its valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/heres-why-i-wouldnt-touch-intel-stock-with-a-10-fo/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] At Davos, CEOs said AI isn’t coming for jobs as fast as Anthropic CEO Dario Amodei thinks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/davos-ceos-said-ai-isn-211426569.html</link><description>The Anthropic CEO warns 50% of entry-level white collar jobs will be gone in five years. Other tech CEOs see that as unlikely.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/davos-ceos-said-ai-isn-211426569.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should Li Auto’s MEGA Milestone And Store Overhaul Require Action From Li Auto (LI) Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/li-auto-mega-milestone-store-210858822.html</link><description>Li Auto recently reported that cumulative deliveries of its flagship Li MEGA pure-electric MPV have surpassed 30,000 units, alongside new MEGA Home and Ultra editions featuring upgraded LiDAR, NVIDIA Thor-U–based driver assistance, and CATL’s Qilin 5C battery technology. At the same time, the company is closing about 100 underperforming stores and shifting toward lower-cost AutoPark formats and partner-led outlets in smaller cities, underscoring a push to improve sales efficiency while...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/li-auto-mega-milestone-store-210858822.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Iren Limited vs. CoreWeave: Accelerating AI Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iren-limited-vs-coreweave-accelerating-202600481.html</link><description>Iren Limited and CoreWeave Inc and both experiencing rising share price momentum as investors again rotate into the AI theme</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iren-limited-vs-coreweave-accelerating-202600481.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Microsoft Releases Powerful New AI Chip to Take on Nvidia</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/microsoft-releases-new-ai-chip-to-take-on-nvidia/</link><description>The software giant is vying for a bigger piece of the AI pie.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/microsoft-releases-new-ai-chip-to-take-on-nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron at 11.7 P/E: One of 2026's Best Buying Opportunities</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-11-7-p-e-200500634.html</link><description>MU shares surged on booming HBM demand, soaring revenue and earnings, and an attractive valuation that suggests its growth story isn't over yet.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-11-7-p-e-200500634.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] 3 Healthcare ETFs to Buy as Flat Medicare Rate Proposal Hits Insurers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-healthcare-etfs-buy-flat-195100377.html</link><description>Flat Medicare Advantage rate hikes hit insurers hard, but diversified healthcare ETFs may help investors weather the policy shock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-healthcare-etfs-buy-flat-195100377.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Roche Shares Rise After Obesity Drug Shows 18% Greater Weight Loss</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roche-shares-rise-obesity-drug-193530744.html</link><description>Mid-stage trial data showed Roche's experimental shot delivered weight loss on par with leading obesity treatments, supporting its late-stage trial plans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roche-shares-rise-obesity-drug-193530744.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] EU Gives Google Six Months to Open Android to Rival AI Search</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eu-gives-google-six-months-193251313.html</link><description>EU regulators begin DMA proceedings, warning Google to share Android access and search data or risk future penalties.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eu-gives-google-six-months-193251313.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] AI Power Needs Are Soaring: Is Vistra Energy, Vertiv, or Constellation The Better Buy?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/ai-power-needs-are-soaring-is-vistra-energy-vertiv-or-constellation-the-better-buy/</link><description>The AI revolution has a power problem. Training GPT-4 required as much electricity as 10,000 U.S. homes use in a year. Multiply that by thousands of models being trained simultaneously, plus billions of daily queries. The result? A data center energy boom reshaping power generation. Facilities drawing 100+ megawatts each, with some hyperscale campuses approaching ... AI Power Needs Are Soaring: Is Vistra Energy, Vertiv, or Constellation The Better Buy?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/ai-power-needs-are-soaring-is-vistra-energy-vertiv-or-constellation-the-better-buy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Billionaires Are Quietly Buying This AI Stock for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-billionaires-are-quietly-buying-this-ai-stock/</link><description>Several billionaires on Wall Street are pouring into one particular member of the "Magnificent Seven."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-billionaires-are-quietly-buying-this-ai-stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Could BigBear.ai Stock Go to $0?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/is-bigbearai-stock-going-to-0/</link><description>Not every AI stock is a runaway success story.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/is-bigbearai-stock-going-to-0/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is AI In A Bubble? What Wall Street Thinks Now</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/ai-bubble-what-wall-street-thinks-now/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Market headlines keep circling the same question: Are we in an AI bubble or boom?  Investors are pouring unprecedented capital into a technology that remains early in its profit cycle.  The stakes are already visible in the AI infrastructure trade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/ai-bubble-what-wall-street-thinks-now/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alibaba Stock Climbs -- New AI Model Matches Google and OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-stock-climbs-ai-model-185931208.html</link><description>Alibaba Cloud Shines as AI Model Competes With Global Leaders</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-stock-climbs-ai-model-185931208.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Faces EU Push to Open Search, AI Access</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-faces-eu-push-open-185719167.html</link><description>Regulators push for equal data access for competitors and AI developers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-faces-eu-push-open-185719167.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] U.S. Warns Korea Against Targeting American Tech Firms Amid Trade Escalation</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/u-s-warns-korea-against-targeting-american-tech-firms-amid-trade-escalation-7a8a5a3a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JD Vance warned Prime Minister Kim Min-seok against pursuing penalties and regulations on U.S.-based firms like Coupang</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/u-s-warns-korea-against-targeting-american-tech-firms-amid-trade-escalation-7a8a5a3a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Where Will SoundHound AI Stock Be in 5 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/where-will-soundhound-ai-stock-be-in-5-years/</link><description>SoundHound had a rough time in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/where-will-soundhound-ai-stock-be-in-5-years/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Stock Market Today, Jan 27: Tech lifts S&amp;P 500 to fresh record as TikTok outage, Trump Medicare surprise weigh in</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/latest-news/stock-market-today-jan-27-tiktok-outage-trump-surprise-health-care-decision-define-opening-trade</link><description>This live blog is refreshed periodically throughout the day with the latest updates from the market.To find the latest Stock Market Today threads, click here. Happy Tuesday. This is TheStreet’s Stock Market Today for Jan. 27, 2026. You can follow the latest updates on the market ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/latest-news/stock-market-today-jan-27-tiktok-outage-trump-surprise-health-care-decision-define-opening-trade</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Oath Surgical partners with NVIDIA to enhance AI in surgical workflow platform</title><link>https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/oath-surgical-partners-with-nvidia-to-enhance-ai-in-surgical-workflow-platform/</link><description>NVIDIA’s infrastructure will support the advancement of OathOS’s real-time surgical video and audio analysis and agentic AI workflows.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/oath-surgical-partners-with-nvidia-to-enhance-ai-in-surgical-workflow-platform/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Specialty Glassmaker’s Stock Is Soaring on an AI Data Center Deal With Meta</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/this-specialty-glassmaker-stock-is-soaring-on-an-ai-data-center-deal-with-meta-glw-11893239</link><description>Corning shares surged Tuesday, thanks to a $6 billion deal with Meta Platforms, in the latest piece of good news for the glass and fiber optic cable maker.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/this-specialty-glassmaker-stock-is-soaring-on-an-ai-data-center-deal-with-meta-glw-11893239</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Market Movers: Affirm Upgraded to a Buy Rating</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/market-movers-affirm-upgraded-to-a-buy-rating/</link><description>Shares of buy now, pay later stock Affirm (NASDAQ: AFRM) are gaining attention. All after analysts at Needham upgraded the stock to a buy with a $100 price target. The firm added that, “AFRM has submitted an application to establish Affirm Bank, a proposed Nevada-chartered industrial loan company,” as quoted by CNBC. We have to ... Market Movers: Affirm Upgraded to a Buy Rating</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/market-movers-affirm-upgraded-to-a-buy-rating/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Bernstein Reiterates Outperform on ASML Ahead of Key Q4 Bookings Print</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-reiterates-outperform-asml-ahead-180028917.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Bernstein SocGen Group analyst David Dai reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $1,642.00 price target. The firm anticipates a robust Q4 beat, with revenue and booking strength viewed as key upside drivers. With ASML […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bernstein-reiterates-outperform-asml-ahead-180028917.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] 1 Pharmaceutical Stock Set to Rebound in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/1-pharmaceutical-stock-set-to-rebound-in-2026/</link><description>Novo Nordisk stock will ride a wave of demand for Ozempic pills in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/1-pharmaceutical-stock-set-to-rebound-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] HSBC to Shut Raffles Place Retail Branch, Pivoting to Wealth Center</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-shut-raffles-place-retail-175406364.html</link><description>The bank will close one of six Singapore branches on Feb. 28 and open a new wealth center in the same building.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-shut-raffles-place-retail-175406364.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar is Set to Report Q4 Earnings: Buy, Sell or Hold the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-set-report-q4-earnings-175400879.html</link><description>CAT's Q4 earnings are set to decline for the sixth straight quarter, with weaker pricing and higher costs pressuring results despite higher volumes.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-set-report-q4-earnings-175400879.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA's Q2 Earnings Loom: Should the KLAC Stock Be in Your Portfolio?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/klas-q2-earnings-loom-klac-175100287.html</link><description>KLAC rides strong AI and chip packaging demand into fiscal Q2, with top-line growth and margin pressure in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/klas-q2-earnings-loom-klac-175100287.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Will Higher Ad Revenues Aid Meta Platforms Stock in Q4 Earnings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/higher-ad-revenues-aid-meta-174700559.html</link><description>META's Q4 ad revenues are set to surge on AI-driven tools and rising global engagement across its platforms.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/higher-ad-revenues-aid-meta-174700559.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML (ASML) is Facing a Shortage That Can’t Be Met, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-asml-facing-shortage-t-174632425.html</link><description>We recently published 13 Stocks Jim Cramer Commented On. ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer commanded on. ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the most important technology companies in the world. It is a semiconductor manufacturing equipment provider and the only company capable of manufacturing high-end EUV chip machines […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-asml-facing-shortage-t-174632425.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The 1 thing You Need to Watch in Amazon's Earnings</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/the-1-thing-you-need-to-watch-in-amazons-earnings/</link><description>This is a bellwether for the AI business.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/the-1-thing-you-need-to-watch-in-amazons-earnings/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Cycles Support Long-Term View on META Despite Near-Term Pressure</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-cycles-support-long-term-173312734.html</link><description>Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, KeyBanc analyst Justin Patterson lowered the price target on the stock to $835.00 (from $875.00) while maintaining an Overweight rating. The firm anticipates META to benefit from AI product cycles in 2026 alongside Alphabet (GOOGL). We believe OW-rated […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-cycles-support-long-term-173312734.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Price Target Lifted at KeyBanc on AI and Cloud Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-price-target-lifted-173033129.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, KeyBanc analyst Justin Patterson raised the price target on the stock to $360.00 (from $330.00) while maintaining an Overweight rating. The firm views AI and Cloud trends structurally favorable for GOOGL, justifying a higher valuation. According to the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-price-target-lifted-173033129.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones AI Giant Nvidia Set To Hit New Buy Point After This Bullish Move</title><link>https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/stocks-near-a-buy-zone/dow-jones-nvidia-nvda-stock-new-buy-point/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Dow Jones AI giant Nvidia stock is poised to hit a new buy point following last week's bullish retake of the 50-day line.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/stocks-near-a-buy-zone/dow-jones-nvidia-nvda-stock-new-buy-point/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Can AMD Reach a $1 Trillion Valuation in 2026?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/can-amd-reach-a-1-trillion-valuation-in-2026/</link><description>Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ:AMD) is growing faster than any bull would’ve predicted a year back. It is already up over 120% in one year, and some estimates are now getting very ambitious. The market cap is at $414 billion. If the stock repeats its one-year performance again, one can be forgiven for eyeing a $1 ... Can AMD Reach a $1 Trillion Valuation in 2026?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/27/can-amd-reach-a-1-trillion-valuation-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jefferies Flags App Store and Google Ad Risks for Apple (AAPL)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-flags-app-store-google-172321219.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Jefferies analyst Edison Lee lowered the price target on the stock to $276.47 (from $283.36) while maintaining a Hold rating. The firm believes AAPL’s long-term growth is capped due to slowing App Store growth and Google ad revenue […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-flags-app-store-google-172321219.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why CoreWeave Stock is Soaring (Again) Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-coreweave-stock-is-soaring-again-today/</link><description>The neocloud operator got some love from Wall Street.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-coreweave-stock-is-soaring-again-today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Freedom Fibre and Truespeed close to finalising altnet merger</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/freedom-fibre-truespeed-close-finalising-171500006.html</link><description>Two major broadband altnets are close to finalising a merger that will propel them into the ranks of the sector's largest players amid growing financial pressure to consolidate.  Sky News understands that Truespeed and Freedom Fibre are in advanced talks about a tie-up.  Truespeed has received £175m of funding from Aviva Investors, a division of the FTSE-100 insurer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/freedom-fibre-truespeed-close-finalising-171500006.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Will social media bans weigh on App Store revenue? Analyst sees limited impact</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/social-media-bans-weigh-app-164658862.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Restrictions preventing children under 16 from accessing major social media platforms in Australia, and a similar proposal now under consideration in the U.K., have prompted some to question whether Apple’s App Store and Google’s Play Store could face pressure on in-app purchase revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/social-media-bans-weigh-app-164658862.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia and Apple Stocks In Spotlight -- Pelosi Files New Disclosure</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/nvidia-apple-stocks-spotlight-pelosi-164201442.html</link><description>Pelosi Adds Tech Exposure With New Options in Alphabet and Amazon</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/nvidia-apple-stocks-spotlight-pelosi-164201442.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Benefits From Growing AI Infrastructure Demand: What's Ahead?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-benefits-growing-ai-infrastructure-164100304.html</link><description>KLAC gains from rising AI infrastructure demand as advanced packaging and WFE growth strengthen its position in key semiconductor markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-benefits-growing-ai-infrastructure-164100304.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Is Gaining Ahead of Earnings. It’s a Test for a Chip Sector Darling.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-earnings-stock-price-7f26b1a7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>ASML stock has more than doubled in the past year. Investors will be watching orders and High-NA adoption when it reports earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-earnings-stock-price-7f26b1a7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Launches AI Models to Speed Up Weather Forecasting</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-launches-ai-models-speed-164053368.html</link><description>Open-source tools aim to make predictions faster, cheaper, and more accurate.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-launches-ai-models-speed-164053368.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet just got a major Wall Street upgrade</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/alphabet-just-got-a-major-wall-street-upgrade</link><description>Alphabet does not need another “it’s cheap” argument; instead, Raymond James is putting its money on something more powerful, which is a revision cycle. Alphabet (GOOG, GOOGL) is now upped to a strong buy with a price target of $400, according to Barron's. Raymond James is making the argument that ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/alphabet-just-got-a-major-wall-street-upgrade</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Are Wall Street Analysts Bullish on Cisco Systems Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37253402/are-wall-street-analysts-bullish-on-cisco-systems-stock</link><description>As Cisco Systems has outperformed the broader market over the past 52 weeks, Wall Street analysts maintain a moderately optimistic outlook about the stock’s prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37253402/are-wall-street-analysts-bullish-on-cisco-systems-stock</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft Boosts Data Centers, Debuts Maia 200 AI Chip Before Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-boosts-data-centers-debuts-163048462.html</link><description>Major expansion positions Microsoft to meet AI demand as Q2 results approach.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-boosts-data-centers-debuts-163048462.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta to Test Paid Plans for Instagram, Facebook, WhatsApp</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-test-paid-plans-instagram-162914507.html</link><description>New plans aim to offer premium features and advanced AI tools across Meta's platforms.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-test-paid-plans-instagram-162914507.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Up 36%, Is Eli Lilly Still a Buy?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/up-36-is-eli-lilly-still-a-buy/</link><description>Thanks to its weight loss and diabetes products, the drug company has seen its shares soar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/up-36-is-eli-lilly-still-a-buy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Just Doubled Down on Its Largest AI Holding. Should Investors Follow Suit?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/nvidia-just-doubled-down-on-its-largest-ai-holding/</link><description>The AI-centric neocloud provider just got a huge vote of confidence.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/nvidia-just-doubled-down-on-its-largest-ai-holding/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Evercore ISI Reiterates Underperform on IBM Ahead of Earnings, Sees Results In Line</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-reiterates-underperform-ibm-161829590.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani reiterated an Underperform rating on the stock with a $330.00 price target. The rating affirmation comes ahead of IBM’s fourth-quarter earnings report scheduled for Wednesday, January 28. Evercore ISI expects IBM […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-reiterates-underperform-ibm-161829590.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Citi initiates coverage of European pharma stocks; AstraZeneca ‘best in class’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-initiates-coverage-european-pharma-161653376.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Citi launched broad coverage of major European pharmaceutical companies with a mixed outlook, issuing Buy ratings on AstraZeneca and Novartis while taking a more cautious stance on GSK, Novo Nordisk and Sanofi.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-initiates-coverage-european-pharma-161653376.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Nvidia stock is on sale</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-stock-is-on-sale-161506921.html</link><description>Time to nibble at Nvidia?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-stock-is-on-sale-161506921.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Does Georgetown’s Wi‑Fi 7 Overhaul With Cisco (CSCO) Redefine Its Campus AI Networking Edge?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-georgetown-wi-fi-7-160938310.html</link><description>Cisco announced in January 2026 that it will power a multi-year modernization of Georgetown University’s campus network, including one of higher education’s largest Wi‑Fi 7 rollouts across classrooms, dorms, stadiums, and research facilities. By combining high-density Wi‑Fi 7 infrastructure, campus-wide security, and AI-ready networking analytics, the partnership turns Georgetown into a live showcase for Cisco’s next-generation connectivity and data capabilities. With Cisco sharpening its...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-georgetown-wi-fi-7-160938310.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave Stock Pops After Deutsche Bank Hikes Price Target to $140</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-pops-deutsche-bank-160754614.html</link><description>Deutsche Bank Boosts CoreWeave to Buy</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-stock-pops-deutsche-bank-160754614.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Greg Abel Signals Shift as Berkshire Weighs Kraft Heinz Exit?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greg-abel-signals-shift-berkshire-160000641.html</link><description>BRK.B may exit its Kraft Heinz stake in Greg Abel's first major move, signaling a shift from Buffett's legacy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greg-abel-signals-shift-berkshire-160000641.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft to report Q2 earnings with investors eyeing AI growth and spending</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-to-report-q2-earnings-with-investors-eyeing-ai-growth-and-spending-154618156.html</link><description>Microsoft will report its second quarter earnings on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-to-report-q2-earnings-with-investors-eyeing-ai-growth-and-spending-154618156.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta to report Q4 earnings amid AI spending concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-to-report-q4-earnings-amid-ai-spending-concerns-154456088.html</link><description>Meta will report its fourth quarter earnings after the bell on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-to-report-q4-earnings-amid-ai-spending-concerns-154456088.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cloudflare Stock Pops On Anthropic's Claude AI Tools. Zoom Also Gets Anthropic Boost.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/cloudflare-stock-pops-on-anthropics-claude-ai-tools-zoom-also-gets-anthropic-boost/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Cloudflare stock popped amid investor enthusiasm over its artificial intelligence strategy and partnership with model builder Anthropic.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/cloudflare-stock-pops-on-anthropics-claude-ai-tools-zoom-also-gets-anthropic-boost/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius vs. Amazon: Which AI Cloud Stock is the Better Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-vs-amazon-ai-cloud-153300483.html</link><description>NBIS targets rapid AI cloud growth with major contracts and global expansion, while Amazon leverages scale and AI across cloud and retail.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-vs-amazon-ai-cloud-153300483.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron Slips After Rally as Samsung Nears Nvidia Chip Certification</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-slips-rally-samsung-nears-153147369.html</link><description>Stock dips after six-day surge on news of stronger HBM competition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-slips-rally-samsung-nears-153147369.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 'Almost Guaranteed': A Wall Street Legend Says Silver Will Drop 50%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/almost-guaranteed-wall-street-legend-153106623.html</link><description>Silver didn't just rally—it went parabolic. Now Marko Kolanovic is calling the comedown. The former JPMorgan chief strategist said silver is "almost guaranteed to drop ~50% from these levels within a year or so." That doesn’t sound like a cautious forecast. It sounds like a near-certainty. In a market where silver ETFs like iShares Silver ETF (NYSE:SLV), abrdn Physical Silver Shares ETF (NYSE:SIVR) and Sprott Physical Silver ETF (NYSE:PSLV) have become momentum trades for macro tourists, that's</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/almost-guaranteed-wall-street-legend-153106623.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017437.html</link><description>Nu Holdings Ltd. 6,960,728 18.38</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017437.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Analysts Expect Applied Materials Stock to Dominate in 2026. Should You Buy Shares Now?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37252145/analysts-expect-applied-materials-stock-to-dominate-in-2026-should-you-buy-shares-now</link><description>Applied Materials' stock offers upside potential, according to this investment firm.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37252145/analysts-expect-applied-materials-stock-to-dominate-in-2026-should-you-buy-shares-now</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is It Too Late To Invest In Google Stock? Here’s Why Some Experts Think It Can Still Rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-invest-google-stock-why-151707335.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) hit a $4 trillion market cap as AI fuels growth. Experts weigh the upside, risks and whether Google stock is still a smart buy for 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-invest-google-stock-why-151707335.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Gains Amid Microsoft's New AI Chip Launch ; Is Nvidia A Buy Or Sell Now?</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-january-2026-meta-microsoft-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock remains above its 50-day moving average with Meta and Microsoft scheduled to report earnings this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-january-2026-meta-microsoft-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>