<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 18:30:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 18:30:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO sends strong message on Taiwan Semiconductor</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-sends-strong-message-on-taiwan-semiconductor</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang has just cut through the big debate over AI chipmaking, saying that the future of advanced chips runs through Taiwan. By extension, it still runs through the crown jewel of the chipspace in Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (TSM), regardless of the number of ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-sends-strong-message-on-taiwan-semiconductor</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] What The Q3 Narrative Shift Means For Martin Marietta Materials's Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q3-narrative-shift-means-martin-171148582.html</link><description>What the New Fair Value Estimate Signals Analysts have nudged their modeled fair value for Martin Marietta Materials to US$676.43 from US$666.29, paired with a nearly unchanged 8.21% discount rate that keeps the core risk view steady. The forecast now blends slightly softer revenue growth of 7.22% versus 7.34% with a modestly higher implied valuation, reflecting the push and pull between optimism around Q3 themes like volume recovery and infrastructure demand, and caution around weather and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q3-narrative-shift-means-martin-171148582.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.B) Valuation Check After Steady Returns And A 16x P/E Multiple</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-b-valuation-171116334.html</link><description>Why Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.B) is on investors’ radar today Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.B) is drawing attention as investors reassess its recent share performance, business mix, and current valuation signals, using the latest financial metrics as a fresh reference point. See our latest analysis for Berkshire Hathaway. At a share price of US$499.10, Berkshire Hathaway’s short term share price return has been relatively steady, while a 1 year total shareholder return of 12.75% and 5 year total...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-b-valuation-171116334.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Brad Gerstner breaks from the crowd on one AI stock</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/brad-gerstner-breaks-from-the-crowd-on-one-ai-stock</link><description>Brad Gerstner isn't only talking about a "supercycle" of AI. He is softly revealing how pros are attempting to jump on it. The founder and CEO of Altimeter Capital is now one of the most carefully watched people in the AI sector. This is partly because he was one of the first to believe in Nvidia ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/brad-gerstner-breaks-from-the-crowd-on-one-ai-stock</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A 2025 security breach exposed over 184 million private passwords. How to stay safe while you browse</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2025-security-breach-exposed-over-161500826.html</link><description>'This is a cybercriminal’s dream working list.'</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2025-security-breach-exposed-over-161500826.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 5 Companies Racing to Dethrone Tesla—And the One Already Winning</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/5-companies-racing-to-dethrone-tesla-and-the-one-already-winning/</link><description>Tesla‘s (Nasdaq: TSLA) stock is at a crossroads. Investors are now more interested in fields like building a fleet of robotaxis, progress in robotics, and future addressable energy markets relative to how many car deliveries the company achieves in a given quarter. Overall, while Tesla’s 10-year chart is incredible, the company’s stock has underperformed the ... 5 Companies Racing to Dethrone Tesla—And the One Already Winning</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/5-companies-racing-to-dethrone-tesla-and-the-one-already-winning/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Walmart and Google bet on AI agents to reshape how people shop online</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2026/01/11/walmart-and-google-bet-on-ai-agents-to-reshape-how-people-shop-online</link><description>The retail giant said a new Gemini integration reflects a broader shift from search-based shopping to AI systems that can act on a customer’s behalf.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2026/01/11/walmart-and-google-bet-on-ai-agents-to-reshape-how-people-shop-online</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 'Americans Are Eager for a New Year's Reset.' Nearly Half of Adults' Finances Worsened in 2025 But Tax Season May Offer a Lifeline, Survey Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-eager-years-reset-nearly-153253636.html</link><description>Almost half of U.S. adults' finances worsened in 2025, but the upcoming tax season could help struggling homeowners even more than usual, an Intuit Credit Karma survey released last month found. The most common reason for Americans’ financial hardships in the past year was unexpected expenses, followed by decreased credit scores, falling behind on monthly payments like mortgages and credit card bills, and the inability to afford necessities like groceries, the survey said. Next year's tax refund</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-eager-years-reset-nearly-153253636.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Money Expert Is Sending Warning Signs About the Economy — and How To Protect Yourself</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/money-expert-sending-warning-signs-150720870.html</link><description>Several money experts have sounded the alarm, warning that today's economy isn't as strong as some headlines suggest.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/money-expert-sending-warning-signs-150720870.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Shopify Builds Momentum In Agentic AI Shopping At NRF 2026</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/shopify-stock-nrf-news-ai-agentic-shopping/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shopify at NRF 2026 launched new initiatives in artificial intelligence-based "agentic" shopping. Shopify stock climbed 51% in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/shopify-stock-nrf-news-ai-agentic-shopping/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Bets on AI-Based Shopping With New AI Agents for Retailers</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-bets-on-ai-based-shopping-with-new-ai-agents-for-retailers-45ad3f27?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The search giant is making its first foray into the agentic commerce market with AI tools for retailers. Meanwhile, major chains are already preparing for the wave of AI agent-based shopping.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-bets-on-ai-based-shopping-with-new-ai-agents-for-retailers-45ad3f27?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google unveils new agentic commerce protocol for retailers</title><link>https://www.americanbanker.com/payments/news/google-shopify-unveil-new-agentic-protocol-for-retailers</link><description>Universal Commerce Protocol is an open standard that establishes a common language for AI agents and systems to work together, and will allow consumers to purchase products from retailers directly through Google's AI Mode in the browser or the Gemini app.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.americanbanker.com/payments/news/google-shopify-unveil-new-agentic-protocol-for-retailers</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Shopify Stock Rallied On AI Shopping. Now It’s Doubling Down With Gemini and Copilot.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/shopify-stock-price-ai-gemini-copilot-8091a3bf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company’s new update allows users to buy products directly on Google Gemini and Microsoft Copilot.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/shopify-stock-price-ai-gemini-copilot-8091a3bf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wing to expand drone delivery to another 150 Walmart stores</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wing-expand-drone-delivery-another-150000701.html</link><description>The partnership will grow Wing's drone delivery service to more than 270 Walmart stores by 2027.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wing-expand-drone-delivery-another-150000701.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] This Healthcare Stock Could Be One of the Best Companies to Own in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/this-healthcare-stock-could-be-one-of-the-best-com/</link><description>It has strong momentum thanks to its current portfolio and several catalysts on the horizon.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/this-healthcare-stock-could-be-one-of-the-best-com/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] 5 AI Stocks That Could Replicate NVIDIA’s Decade of Dominance</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/5-ai-stocks-that-could-replicate-nvidias-decade-of-dominance/</link><description>NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA) has delivered a 23,000% return over the past decade has become the benchmark every tech investor measures against. The company created the infrastructure that made modern AI possible. Now the question: which company pulls off the next NVIDIA-like run? We analyzed 15 AI-adjacent stocks across semiconductors, software, and quantum computing to find the ... 5 AI Stocks That Could Replicate NVIDIA’s Decade of Dominance</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/5-ai-stocks-that-could-replicate-nvidias-decade-of-dominance/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Assessing ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) Valuation After Its Strong Recent Share Price Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-asml-141330967.html</link><description>ASML Holding overview and recent share performance ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) has attracted fresh attention after a strong run in its share price over the past month, putting its recent performance and fundamentals back in focus for many investors. See our latest analysis for ASML Holding. That sharp recent move sits on top of a much stronger run, with a 90 day share price return of 29.37% and a 1 year total shareholder return of 73.78%, which suggests that momentum has been building for...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-asml-141330967.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Corporation - Sticky MOAT Is The Best Type</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-sticky-moat-best-140850593.html</link><description>KLAC is setting itself apart as an indispensable cog in the machine that is chip production.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-sticky-moat-best-140850593.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Can Eli Lilly and Company's (NYSE:LLY) ROE Continue To Surpass The Industry Average?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-companys-nyse-lly-140025898.html</link><description>While some investors are already well versed in financial metrics (hat tip), this article is for those who would like...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-companys-nyse-lly-140025898.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Magnificent 7’s Stock Market Dominance Shows Signs of Cracking</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stock-market-dominance-140007016.html</link><description>For the first time since 2022, when the Federal Reserve started raising interest rates, the majority of the Magnificent 7 tech giants performed worse than the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index.  While the Bloomberg Magnificent 7 Index rose 25% in 2025, compared with 16% for the S&amp;amp;P 500, that was only because of the enormous gains by Alphabet Inc. and Nvidia Corp.  Suddenly stock picking within the group is crucial.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stock-market-dominance-140007016.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Surprising Stock About to Join the Nasdaq 100</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/the-surprising-stock-about-to-join-the-nasdaq-100/</link><description>The Nasdaq 100 is an index most often associated with technology stocks like Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) and Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) due to its historical focus on innovation and high-growth companies. While it is not a “pure” technology index — there is a separate Nasdaq 100 index devoted exclusively to tech stocks — its heavy tilt towards tech-driven ... The Surprising Stock About to Join the Nasdaq 100</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/the-surprising-stock-about-to-join-the-nasdaq-100/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia remains extraordinary</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-remains-extraordinary-133040712.html</link><description>The stock doesn't reflect it, but Nvidia delivered this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-remains-extraordinary-133040712.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] iShares ETF Has A ‘Set And Forget’ Investment For Retirees You Don’t Need To Overthink</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/ishares-etf-has-a-set-and-forget-investment-for-retirees-you-dont-need-to-overthink/</link><description>The hardest part of retirement investing isn’t picking stocks or timing the market – it’s resisting the urge to do either. iShares Core S&amp;amp;P Total U.S. Stock Market ETF (NYSEARCA:ITOT) solves this by offering exposure to the entire U.S. equity market in a single position, charging just 0.03% annually, and requiring no ongoing decisions beyond ... iShares ETF Has A ‘Set And Forget’ Investment For Retirees You Don’t Need To Overthink</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/11/ishares-etf-has-a-set-and-forget-investment-for-retirees-you-dont-need-to-overthink/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] How The Narrative Around Chipotle Mexican Grill (CMG) Is Shifting With Mixed Analyst Views</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/narrative-around-chipotle-mexican-grill-130732544.html</link><description>Chipotle Mexican Grill's fair value estimate has been adjusted from US$43.18 to US$44.12 per share, a small move that still reflects a meaningful debate around the story. This change lines up with mixed street research, where some analysts focus on brand strength and long term unit growth, while others highlight ongoing traffic and consumer pressure. Stay tuned to see how you can track these shifting views so you are not caught off guard as the Chipotle narrative evolves. Analyst Price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/narrative-around-chipotle-mexican-grill-130732544.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Top AI stock picks: Is it Nvidia or bust?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/top-ai-stock-picks-nvidia-130035690.html</link><description>Which stock is the best artificial intelligence (AI) play for investors: Nvidia (NVDA), Intel (INTC), or AMD (AMD)? D.A. Davidson head of technology research Gil Luria, Wedbush Securities managing director and global head of technology research Dan Ives, and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Ines Ferré join Opening Bid host Brian Sozzi to share their takes on the names. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/top-ai-stock-picks-nvidia-130035690.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Big banks kick off fourth quarter earnings season, inflation data on deck: What to watch this week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-kick-off-fourth-quarter-earnings-season-inflation-data-on-deck-what-to-watch-this-week-123603447.html</link><description>Investors will be watching for consumer and producer price data alongside bank earnings in the week ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-kick-off-fourth-quarter-earnings-season-inflation-data-on-deck-what-to-watch-this-week-123603447.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] With the global robotaxi industry projected to hit $105 billion by 2035, here's what potential investors need to know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-robotaxi-industry-projected-hit-123000005.html</link><description>Before investing in this potentially lucrative industry, be sure to do your homework.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-robotaxi-industry-projected-hit-123000005.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Ways Nvidia Will Make History in 2026 (Hint: You're Going to Want to Buy Now)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/2-ways-nvidia-will-make-history-in-2026-hint-youre/</link><description>Nvidia is set for monster growth again in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/2-ways-nvidia-will-make-history-in-2026-hint-youre/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Best Stocks to Invest $50,000 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/the-best-stocks-to-invest-50000-in-right-now/</link><description>These stocks should be good bets in the new year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/the-best-stocks-to-invest-50000-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Is Causing a Memory Shortage. Why Producers Aren’t Rushing to Make a Lot More.</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai-is-causing-a-memory-shortage-why-producers-arent-rushing-to-make-a-lot-more-8dd15194?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The world needs a lot more memory chips and hard drives.  The boom-and-bust memory business has been enjoying its biggest boom in years—perhaps ever.  The rapid build-out of infrastructure for artificial intelligence is consuming a large portion of available supply of NAND flash memory, DRAM memory and hard drives.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai-is-causing-a-memory-shortage-why-producers-arent-rushing-to-make-a-lot-more-8dd15194?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What to Expect in Markets This Week: Big Bank Earnings, December Inflation Data, Retail Sales, TSMC Earnings</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-big-bank-earnings-december-inflation-data-retail-sales-tsmc-earnings-jpm-bac-c-wfc-11882090</link><description>Coming up: Big Bank earnings, December CPI inflation, November retail sales, updated housing data, earnings from TSMC, Delta Air Lines</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/what-to-expect-in-markets-this-week-big-bank-earnings-december-inflation-data-retail-sales-tsmc-earnings-jpm-bac-c-wfc-11882090</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Should You Buy Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Stock Before Jan. 15?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/should-you-buy-taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing/</link><description>Expectations are high for the chipmaker's next earnings report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/should-you-buy-taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Forget Chip Stocks: The Best Way to Profit From AI Is This 31%-Yielding ETF</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/forget-chip-stocks-the-best-way-to-profit-from-ai/</link><description>Instead of just one chip stock, the VanEck Semiconductor ETF offers exposure to 26 chip stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/forget-chip-stocks-the-best-way-to-profit-from-ai/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 big analyst AI moves: ASML top semis pick for 2026, Adobe downgraded</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-big-analyst-ai-moves-093006786.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Here are the biggest analyst moves in the area of artificial intelligence (AI) for this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-big-analyst-ai-moves-093006786.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 Top Tech Stocks to Buy in January</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/3-top-tech-stocks-to-buy-in-january/</link><description>Historically, January has been a strong month for the stock market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/3-top-tech-stocks-to-buy-in-january/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: These 2 Unstoppable Stocks Will Join Nvidia, Alphabet, Apple, and Microsoft in the $3 Trillion Club by 2027</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/prediction-2-unstoppable-stocks-3-trillion/</link><description>These two industry powerhouses have a clear path to admission to the elite $3 trillion club.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/prediction-2-unstoppable-stocks-3-trillion/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] 3 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks That Could Go Parabolic in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/3-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-that-could-go/</link><description>Nebius, SoundHound AI, and IonQ are all still in the early stages of what could prove to be incredible growth stories.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/3-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-that-could-go/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Goldman Sachs Retains a Neutral Rating on Planet Labs PBC (PL)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-retains-neutral-rating-060340483.html</link><description>Planet Labs PBC (NYSE:PL) is among the 20 Best Performing Stocks in 2025. According to a research note dated December 17, 2025, TheFly reported that Goldman Sachs lifted its price target on Planet Labs PBC (NYSE:PL) from $10.90 to $12.30 and retained a Neutral rating. The firm reported third-quarter results that were better than anticipated. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-sachs-retains-neutral-rating-060340483.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:03:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] ABIVAX Société Anonyme (ABVX) Rumored To Attract Interest From Eli Lilly</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/abivax-soci-t-anonyme-abvx-060019166.html</link><description>ABIVAX Société Anonyme (NASDAQ:ABVX) is among the 20 Best Performing Stocks in 2025. According to a story in the French-language newspaper La Tribune on December 24, 2025, there have been rumors that Eli Lilly has been drawing interest in the French biotechnology business ABIVAX Société Anonyme (NASDAQ:ABVX), TheFly reported. Its shares surged after the release, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/abivax-soci-t-anonyme-abvx-060019166.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 6 Hypergrowth Tech Stocks to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/6-hypergrowth-tech-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</link><description>These six companies provide significant growth opportunities and are well-established leaders.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/11/6-hypergrowth-tech-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dan Ives: Trillions in AI Spending Are Just the Start of ‘Fourth Industrial Revolution’</title><link>https://www.thedailyupside.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/dan-ives-trillions-in-ai-spending-are-just-the-start-of-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><description>Dan Ives has traveled more than 3 million miles over 25 years, touring data centers, and meeting CEOs and CIOs where AI is being built.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thedailyupside.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/dan-ives-trillions-in-ai-spending-are-just-the-start-of-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Broadcom Stock a Buy for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/is-broadcom-stock-a-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Broadcom is coming off an incredible 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/is-broadcom-stock-a-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google, Meta, Amazon, Netflix And Microsoft Escape Tough New European Rules: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-meta-amazon-netflix-microsoft-043138571.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc.'s (NASDAQ:GOOG) (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google, Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META), Amazon.com, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN), Netflix Inc. (NASDAQ:NFLX) and Microsoft Corp (NASDAQ:MSFT) will reportedly avoid binding new obligations under the EU's upcoming Digital Networks Act. EU Digital Networks Act Prioritizes Telecom Investment Over Regulation The European Commission is preparing to unveil the Digital Networks Act on Jan. 20, reported Reuters on Thursday, citing people with direct knowledge of the</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-meta-amazon-netflix-microsoft-043138571.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] How Recent AI And Business Shifts Are Rewriting The Story For Arm Holdings (ARM)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-ai-business-shifts-rewriting-041331437.html</link><description>Why the Arm Holdings Price Target Just Shifted Arm Holdings recently saw its fair value estimate adjust from about US$164.85 to roughly US$163.25 per share, along with a small uptick in the discount rate from 11.25% to around 11.28% and a slight increase in modeled revenue growth from 22.13% to roughly 22.17%. This fine tuning reflects a market that is weighing positive signals around licensing strength, AI driven projects, and design wins against new questions on execution risk and how Arm’s...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-ai-business-shifts-rewriting-041331437.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] She Married Into $1M Of Debt And Asked, 'How Do I Not Murder Him?' Dave Ramsey Fires Back Without Sympathy. 'It's Not His Fault'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/she-married-1m-debt-asked-020114134.html</link><description>Leona from Fairbanks, Alaska, called into “The Ramsey Show” to confess she had married a man without ever asking about his financial past. Months into their new life together, she discovered the two of them were nearly $1 million in debt. ‘You Walked In Blindly’ “I’m pretty newly married. Not my first rodeo,” Leona began. She explained that she hadn't done a financial background check on her husband before tying the knot. “We got married in May, and by October, we realized we were close to a mil</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/she-married-1m-debt-asked-020114134.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 02:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The "Safest" Trillion-Dollar Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock to Invest $50,000 In Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-safest-trillion-dollar-artificial-intelligence/</link><description>There are currently nine technology stocks that boast valuations of at least $1 trillion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-safest-trillion-dollar-artificial-intelligence/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: Alphabet Will Soar Over the Next Decade. Here's 1 Reason Why.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/prediction-alphabet-soar-over-next-decade-1-reason/</link><description>The dominant internet business is poised to keep its growth going.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/prediction-alphabet-soar-over-next-decade-1-reason/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Inverse Cramer Wins Again: Opposite Picks Of Investor Beat Nancy Pelosi In 2025</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inverse-cramer-wins-again-opposite-003304004.html</link><description>When it comes to following stock picks of famous individuals, Jim Cramer and Rep. Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) are two of the most well-known people. A financial company that allows investors to invest alongside both individuals has crowned a 2025 winner and the answer may be surprising. Jim Cramer Vs. Nancy Pelosi 2025 Stock Picks Battle Former Speaker of the House Pelosi regularly discloses stock trades each year that are made by her husband Paul Pelosi. The disclosures have a strong history of bea</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inverse-cramer-wins-again-opposite-003304004.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should CoreWeave Investors Worry About Michael Intrator's Latest Move?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/should-coreweave-investors-worry-intrators-move/</link><description>CoreWeave stock has slipped in recent weeks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/should-coreweave-investors-worry-intrators-move/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Want to Buy Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks in 2026? These 2 Companies Could Net You Millions in Retirement.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/want-to-buy-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-2026/</link><description>Nvidia isn't the only AI name that can help investors reach financial independence over the long term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/want-to-buy-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mike Novogratz Tells Scaramucci Crypto Treasuries Will Trade Below NAV Without Real Strategy: 'Not Going To Get Shareholder Value Just By...'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-novogratz-tells-scaramucci-crypto-223244249.html</link><description>Galaxy Digital Inc. (NASDAQ: GLXY) CEO Mike Novogratz expressed concern Wednesday about the current state of cryptocurrency treasury companies, emphasizing the importance of creating shareholder value beyond just owning the underlying asset. Novogratz Questions Current Landscape Speaking to SkyBridge Capital...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-novogratz-tells-scaramucci-crypto-223244249.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Nvidia Stock a Buy for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/is-nvidia-stock-a-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Nvidia's stock is primed to rocket higher this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/is-nvidia-stock-a-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Futures: Do Your Stocks Reflect The Broad, Strong Rally? JPMorgan, Goldman, Delta, Taiwan Semi Loom</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market is at highs with JPMorgan, Goldman, Taiwan Semi and Delta earnings due. Two huge conferences, inflation data and perhaps a Trump tariffs ruling also are on tap.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cathie Wood Invest Dumps Over $10 Million Of Palantir Stock Amid Talk Of 'Cramer Curse' — Buys This Hot AI Stock Instead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-invest-dumps-over-203125995.html</link><description>On Thursday, Cathie Wood-led Ark Invest made significant trades involving Palantir Technologies Inc. (NASDAQ:PLTR), Broadcom Inc. (NASDAQ:AVGO), and Joby Aviation Inc. (NYSE:JOBY). These trades reflect Ark’s strategic positioning in the market amidst evolving geopolitical and technological landscapes. The Palantir Trade Ark Invest made a notable move by selling 58,741 shares of Palantir. through its ARK Next Generation Internet ETF (BATS: ARKW). The transaction, valued at approximately $10.4 mil</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-invest-dumps-over-203125995.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is It Too Late To Consider ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) After Its Strong Share Price Run?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-200803546.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether ASML Holding's share price still makes sense after its strong run, you are not alone, and valuation is the key question. The stock last closed at US$1,273.88, with returns of 9.5% over 7 days, 13.8% over 30 days, 9.5% year to date, 73.8% over 1 year, 97.6% over 3 years and 150.9% over 5 years. Recent attention on semiconductor equipment companies has kept ASML in focus, as investors weigh long term demand for advanced chip manufacturing tools. At the same time,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-200803546.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Berenberg Bank Remains Bullish on AstraZeneca PLC (AZN) – Here’s Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berenberg-bank-remains-bullish-astrazeneca-195715465.html</link><description>AstraZeneca PLC (NASDAQ:AZN) is one of the best performing pharma stocks in 2025. On January 7, Berenberg Bank reiterated a Buy rating on AstraZeneca PLC (NASDAQ:AZN) with a price target of $95. The rating update came after AstraZeneca PLC (NASDAQ:AZN) announced positive full results from the Phase III TULIP-SC trial on December 6, reporting that […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berenberg-bank-remains-bullish-astrazeneca-195715465.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly and Company (LLY) to Acquire Ventyx Biosciences</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-acquire-195713266.html</link><description>Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) is one of the best performing pharma stocks in 2025. Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) announced on January 7 that it entered into a definitive agreement to acquire Ventyx Biosciences, Inc., which is a clinical-stage biopharmaceutical company that develops innovative oral therapies for patients with inflammatory-mediated diseases. Ventyx Biosciences, Inc. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-acquire-195713266.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on Procter &amp; Gamble: “It Has the Opportunity to Shake Things Up”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-procter-gamble-opportunity-195641824.html</link><description>The Procter &amp;amp; Gamble Company (NYSE:PG) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. During the episode, Cramer noted that it is one of the few consumer packaged goods companies that “doesn’t have a GLP-1 problem,” as he said: “I can go over how NVIDIA or Broadcom are down huge too much, and they’re […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-procter-gamble-opportunity-195641824.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Jim Cramer Discusses CrowdStrike After Jensen Huang’s Endorsement</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-crowdstrike-jensen-195638777.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Cramer said that he was surprised to see the stock fall notably from November highs, as he commented: “Take my morning show, Squawk on the Street. Today, my co-host, Carl Quintanilla, turned to me and asked what looked interesting after so many […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-crowdstrike-jensen-195638777.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Want to Invest in Quantum Computing? These 3 Stocks Are Great Buys Right Now.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/want-to-invest-in-quantum-computing-these-3-stocks/</link><description>Investing in the pure-play start-ups is not the only way to gain exposure to this nascent technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/want-to-invest-in-quantum-computing-these-3-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Vistra Wins Mega Nuclear Deal With Meta, Stock Jumps</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vistra-wins-mega-nuclear-deal-193153850.html</link><description>Vistra Corp. (NYSE:VST) stock rose Friday after the company disclosed a 20-year power purchase agreement (PPAs) with Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META). Details The deal involves supplying over 2,600 MW of zero-carbon power from three nuclear plants to support Meta's regional operations. In particular, Meta will purchase 2,176 MW of nuclear energy from Vistra's operating Perry and Davis-Besse plants in Ohio, along with an additional 433 MW of capacity from uprates at Perry, Davis-Besse, and Beav</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vistra-wins-mega-nuclear-deal-193153850.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Jim Cramer on Nebius: “The Opportunities Are Better Elsewhere”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-nebius-opportunities-better-192436078.html</link><description>Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. A caller inquired about Cramer’s thoughts on the company in the “year of practical investing.” In response, Cramer commented: “Well, I’ll tell you, a younger person came to me, asked me about stocks that were losing money the other night… And I […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-nebius-opportunities-better-192436078.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Jim Cramer on Palo Alto: “I Think It Is a Buy”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-palo-alto-think-192434508.html</link><description>Palo Alto Networks, Inc. (NASDAQ:PANW) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Answering a caller’s query about the stock during the lightning round, Cramer said: “I think that Nikesh Arora does a great job. I slighted him too much. I said so many good things about CrowdStrike earlier. Palo Alto’s a terrific company […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-palo-alto-think-192434508.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This ETF Is the Simplest Path to $1 Million in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/this-etf-is-the-simplest-path-to-1-million-in-2026/</link><description>You don't need to be a stock market genius to build a million-dollar portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/this-etf-is-the-simplest-path-to-1-million-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Sam Altman Weighs An $830B–$1T IPO And Admits Running A Public Company Could Be 'Really Annoying'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sam-altman-weighs-830b-1t-190109072.html</link><description>A potential mega IPO is coming into focus, but enthusiasm for life as a public-company CEO appears limited. "Am I excited to be a public company CEO? 0%," OpenAI CEO Sam Altman said on the "Big Technology Podcast." "Am I excited for OpenAI to be a public company? In some ways, I am, and in some ways I think it'd be really annoying." He told host Alex Kantrowitz that while public markets can play a role in value creation, leading a public company comes with trade-offs he does not find appealing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sam-altman-weighs-830b-1t-190109072.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] AI's Next Bottleneck Isn't Hardware -- It's Efficiency. Here's the Stock to Watch.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/ais-next-bottleneck-isnt-hardware-its-efficiency-h/</link><description>Vertiv is playing a crucial role in managing AI data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/ais-next-bottleneck-isnt-hardware-its-efficiency-h/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>