<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:00:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research’s Q2, outlook beat helped by high chipmaking equipment demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-q2-outlook-beat-215316810.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Lam Research beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit and revenue on strong demand for chipmaking equipment tied to artificial intelligence, and forecast third-quarter results above expectations. Shares marginally up in extended trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-q2-outlook-beat-215316810.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cortland Associates Ditches First Advantage Shares in $5.6 Million Sale, According to Recent Filing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/cortland-associates-ditches-first-advantage-shares-in-usd5-6-million-sale-according-to-recent-filing/</link><description>First Advantage delivers technology-driven screening and compliance solutions for employers worldwide, serving a broad range of industries.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/cortland-associates-ditches-first-advantage-shares-in-usd5-6-million-sale-according-to-recent-filing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Investment Manager Sells $10.1 Million Worth of Blue Owl Stock, According to Recent SEC Filing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/investment-manager-sells-usd10-1-million-worth-of-blue-owl-stock-according-to-recent-sec-filing/</link><description>Blue Owl Capital delivers direct lending, GP capital, and real estate solutions, generating steady fee income from institutional clients.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/investment-manager-sells-usd10-1-million-worth-of-blue-owl-stock-according-to-recent-sec-filing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Less Than 10% of AI Investors Plan to Reduce Their Holdings in 2026, and 3 Stocks Worth Buying in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/why-ai-investors-reduce-holdings-2026-stocks/</link><description>Artificial intelligence is still in its early innings. These are the stocks to get behind for this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/why-ai-investors-reduce-holdings-2026-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia: Is China falling behind in AI chip production race?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-is-china-falling-behind-in-ai-chip-production-race-214432180.html</link><description>China has given its domestic tech companies approval to purchase Nvidia's (NVDA) H200 AI chips, according to Wall Street Journal reporting.Christopher Miller, professor at Tufts University's Fletcher School, speaks with Josh Lipton about China's ultimate goal to become self-sufficient around artificial intelligence semiconductors.Miller is also the author of "Chip War: The Fight for the World's Most Critical Technology."To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-is-china-falling-behind-in-ai-chip-production-race-214432180.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM (NYSE:IBM) Posts Better-Than-Expected Sales In Q4 CY2025, Stock Soars</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-nyse-ibm-posts-better-214253917.html</link><description>Technology and consulting giant IBM (NYSE:IBM) reported Q4 CY2025 results beating Wall Street’s revenue expectations, with sales up 12.1% year on year to $19.69 billion. Its non-GAAP profit of $4.52 per share was 5.4% above analysts’ consensus estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-nyse-ibm-posts-better-214253917.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Earnings live: IBM stock surges, Whirlpool slides; Meta, Microsoft, Tesla report beats across the board</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-ibm-stock-surges-whirlpool-slides-meta-microsoft-tesla-report-beats-across-the-board-213948822.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-ibm-stock-surges-whirlpool-slides-meta-microsoft-tesla-report-beats-across-the-board-213948822.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Stock Jumps As Software Growth Powers Earnings Beat</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/ibm-stock-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>IBM stock jumped late Wednesday after the tech giant reported fourth-quarter results ahead of expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/ibm-stock-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cortland Associates Sheds JD Shares Worth $11.7 Million, as Competition Heats Up</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/cortland-associates-sheds-373k-jd-shares-worth-usd11-7-million-as-competition-heats-up/</link><description>JD.com delivers a broad range of consumer and enterprise products through a technology-driven, supply chain-focused business model in China.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/cortland-associates-sheds-373k-jd-shares-worth-usd11-7-million-as-competition-heats-up/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Sales Rise 12% as Customers’ Appetite for AI Grows</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/ibm-sales-rise-12-as-customers-appetite-for-ai-grows-ff8f8442?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The tech company recorded higher revenue in the fiscal fourth quarter, as customers move to implement AI in more areas of their businesses.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/ibm-sales-rise-12-as-customers-appetite-for-ai-grows-ff8f8442?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research Stock Rises As Chip-Gear Firm Tops Targets</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/lrcx-stock-lam-research-fiscal-q2-2026-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Lam Research topped estimates for its fiscal second quarter and guided much higher than views for the current period. LRCX stock rose.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/lrcx-stock-lam-research-fiscal-q2-2026-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM: Q4 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-q4-earnings-snapshot-212356870.html</link><description>ARMONK, N.Y. (AP) — International Business Machines Corp. IBM) on Wednesday reported fourth-quarter net income of $5.6 billion. On a per-share basis, the Armonk, New York-based company said it had net income of $5.88.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-q4-earnings-snapshot-212356870.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) Posts Better-Than-Expected Sales In Q4</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-nasdaq-lrcx-posts-212309606.html</link><description>Semiconductor equipment maker Lam Research (NASDAQ:LRCX) announced better-than-expected revenue in Q4 CY2025, with sales up 22.1% year on year to $5.34 billion. On top of that, next quarter’s revenue guidance ($5.7 billion at the midpoint) was surprisingly good and 6.2% above what analysts were expecting. Its non-GAAP profit of $1.27 per share was 8.7% above analysts’ consensus estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-nasdaq-lrcx-posts-212309606.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft’s (NASDAQ:MSFT) Q4 CY2025 Sales Top Estimates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-nasdaq-msft-q4-cy2025-211944819.html</link><description>Technology giant Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) reported revenue ahead of Wall Streets expectations in Q4 CY2025, with sales up 16.7% year on year to $81.27 billion. Its GAAP profit of $5.16 per share was 34.1% above analysts’ consensus estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-nasdaq-msft-q4-cy2025-211944819.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar Earnings Are Coming. The Bar Is High Thanks to AI.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/caterpillar-earnings-stock-price-9fa7aa49?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Investors have been focused on the company’s power-generation business amid a boom in AI data center construction.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/caterpillar-earnings-stock-price-9fa7aa49?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research: Fiscal Q2 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-fiscal-q2-earnings-211803391.html</link><description>LRCX) on Wednesday reported fiscal second-quarter profit of $1.59 billion. The Fremont, California-based company said it had profit of $1.26 per share. Earnings, adjusted for one-time gains and costs, came to $1.27 per share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-fiscal-q2-earnings-211803391.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Recognition And Acquisitions Shape Outlook For Long Term Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-recognition-acquisitions-shape-outlook-211332447.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (NasdaqGS:CRWD) has been named Customers' Choice in the 2026 Gartner Peer Insights Voice of the Customer report for Endpoint Protection Platforms. The company is acquiring SGNL and Seraphic Security to broaden its cybersecurity offering. CrowdStrike is expanding its global data sovereignty program with new regional cloud deployments. CrowdStrike enters this news cycle with its shares at $476.66 and a very large 3 year return, alongside a 16.6% return over the past year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-recognition-acquisitions-shape-outlook-211332447.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM beats fourth-quarter revenue estimates as AI boosts software demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-beats-fourth-quarter-revenue-211254366.html</link><description>IBM beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue and profit on Wednesday, as the rapid adoption of artificial intelligence boosts demand for its software services, ranging ​from managing swaths of data to automating IT processes.  Businesses have doubled down on upgrading their software suites to develop data-intensive AI technology, helping sales for IT service ‌and software providers such as IBM.  Sales in its software segment stood at $9.03 billion in the quarter ‍ended December 31, also beating an estimate of $8.77 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-beats-fourth-quarter-revenue-211254366.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft's rising spending, slight cloud beat fan AI payoff worries</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-edges-past-cloud-growth-210400130.html</link><description>Microsoft only edged past estimates for quarterly revenue in its crucial cloud-computing business on Wednesday and ramped up spending on artificial intelligence, disappointing investors looking for ​better returns amid intense competition.  The company also reported that ‌the contracted backlog in its cloud business more than doubled to $625 billion, which was more than the $523 billion rival Oracle posted ‌in December.  But roughly 45% of Microsoft's backlog was driven by OpenAI alone, underscoring its reliance on the money-losing startup that has pledged around $1.4 trillion in overall AI expenditure with little details on how it plans to fund the spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-edges-past-cloud-growth-210400130.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Chip Makers Point to Accelerating Demand. It’s a Big Deal.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/barrons-tech-chip-makers-accelerating-demand-b364e97b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Robust earnings commentary suggests chip makers are seeing rising demand and are willing to invest to add capacity going into next year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/barrons-tech-chip-makers-accelerating-demand-b364e97b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Holding NV (ASML) Q4 2025 Earnings Call Highlights: Strong Net Sales and Robust Backlog ...</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-nv-asml-q4-210140335.html</link><description>ASML Holding NV (ASML) reports impressive Q4 2025 results with EUR9.7 billion in net sales and a solid EUR38.8 billion backlog, setting a strong foundation for future revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-nv-asml-q4-210140335.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500 slips from record as Fed stands pat, Nasdaq rises before Big Tech earnings flurry</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-slips-from-record-as-fed-stands-pat-nasdaq-rises-before-big-tech-earnings-flurry-210119313.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-slips-from-record-as-fed-stands-pat-nasdaq-rises-before-big-tech-earnings-flurry-210119313.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Only 2 "Magnificent Seven" Stocks Outperformed the S&amp;P 500 in 2025. Are They Both Buys for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/only-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-outperformed-the-s/</link><description>If you can stomach volatility, the long-term potential remains strong.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/only-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-outperformed-the-s/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] US robotaxi group Waymo aims to launch in London by fourth quarter of 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-robotaxi-group-waymo-aims-201106292.html</link><description>LONDON, Jan 28 (Reuters) - U.S. robotaxi company Waymo said on Wednesday it was aiming to launch its fully driverless ride-hailing service in London by the fourth quarter of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-robotaxi-group-waymo-aims-201106292.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] GLP drugs and peptides are changing more than weight loss</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/glp-drugs-peptides-changing-more-200252903.html</link><description>You can catch Trader Talk on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, YouTube, or wherever you get your podcasts. GLP drugs are about far more than weight loss—and the next wave of peptides could redefine preventative health. On this subclip from Trader Talk, Futurum CEO Daniel Newman explains how peptides act as biological signals that help restore functions the body no longer performs efficiently, from metabolism to recovery and cognitive health. The conversation also ties peptide innovation to AI-driven drug discovery and the growing role of companies like Eli Lilly (LLY) in advancing next-generation GLP therapies. Watch more episodes of Trader Talk here. Trader Talk with Kenny Polcari on Yahoo Finance delivers expert analysis and actionable insights, empowering you to navigate market volatility and secure your financial future. This post was written by Langston Sessoms.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/glp-drugs-peptides-changing-more-200252903.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Intel (INTC) Stock Is Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-today-200143411.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) jumped 10.2% in the afternoon session after reports surfaced that chip giants Nvidia and Apple were considering using Intel's foundry services for future chip production.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-today-200143411.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eaton Vance Worldwide Health Sciences Fund Reduces Stake in Novo Nordisk AS by 49.25%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eaton-vance-worldwide-health-sciences-200121844.html</link><description>Exploring Strategic Moves in the Health Sciences Sector</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eaton-vance-worldwide-health-sciences-200121844.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Up 30%+ in 2025 - 2 Profitable Semiconductor Stocks to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/30-2025-2-profitable-semiconductor-200000429.html</link><description>NVIDIA stands out in 2026 as a top profitable semiconductor pick, boasting a 53% net income ratio as investors favor companies with strong bottom lines.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/30-2025-2-profitable-semiconductor-200000429.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] RBC Calls International Business Machines Corporation (IBM) a Defensive AI Play as Red Hat Headwinds Ease</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-calls-international-business-machines-195431756.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 27, RBC Capital analyst Matthew Swanson reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $350.00 price target. The firm favors IBM’s secular positioning ahead of its earnings report on January 28. RBC anticipates that IBM will report […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-calls-international-business-machines-195431756.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] BofA Sees Limited China Risk for ASML Holding N.V. (ASML), Maintains Top Pick Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-sees-limited-china-risk-195350270.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 27, BofA Securities analyst Didier Scemama reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $1,672.00 price target. The firm maintains its “Top Pick” stance on ASML, seeing limited China threat and highlighting inflection in edge AI. Bofa highlighted […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-sees-limited-china-risk-195350270.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq waver as Fed holds rates steady, Big Tech earnings loom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-waver-as-fed-holds-rates-steady-big-tech-earnings-loom-190043947.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-waver-as-fed-holds-rates-steady-big-tech-earnings-loom-190043947.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Raymond James Reiterates Outperform on Microsoft (MSFT) Ahead of Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/raymond-james-reiterates-outperform-microsoft-194915292.html</link><description>Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Raymond James analyst Andrew Marok reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $600.00 price target. The rating affirmation comes ahead of the company’s fiscal second-quarter 2026 earnings report due today, January 28. Raymond James sees robust Azure […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/raymond-james-reiterates-outperform-microsoft-194915292.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google to Pay $135 Million to Settle Lawsuit Over Handling of Cellular Data</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/google-to-pay-135-million-to-settle-lawsuit-over-handling-of-cellular-data-7cb58598?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The settlement requires Google to change its Google Play terms of service and the setup screens for new Android mobile devices.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/google-to-pay-135-million-to-settle-lawsuit-over-handling-of-cellular-data-7cb58598?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why a $3 Million Shift Toward International Equities Stands Out in a Mega-Cap Portfolio</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/atwater-malick-loads-up-acwx-with-43k-shares-buy/</link><description>The iShares MSCI ACWI ex U.S. ETF offers diversified exposure to developed and emerging international equity markets through a single vehicle.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/atwater-malick-loads-up-acwx-with-43k-shares-buy/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This $8 Million ETF Buy Extends a Bond Ladder Spanning 2026 Through 2031</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/this-usd8-million-etf-buy-extends-a-bond-ladder-spanning-2026-through-2031/</link><description>This ETF targets investment-grade U.S. corporate bonds maturing in 2031, offering a defined maturity and predictable cash flow.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/this-usd8-million-etf-buy-extends-a-bond-ladder-spanning-2026-through-2031/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump’s Truth Social Brand Nabs Another ETF. It Has a Solid Record.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-truth-social-etf-yall-52b765e3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company that runs Truth Social ETFs is buying a conservative-leaning fund that doesn’t own Apple, Amazon or Meta.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-truth-social-etf-yall-52b765e3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] IREN Ltd. (IREN) Soars 14.6% on Further AI Bets</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iren-ltd-iren-soars-14-190640784.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names With Easy 10-30% Gains. IREN Ltd. (NASDAQ:IREN) was one of the best performers on Tuesday. IREN Ltd. saw its share prices jump by 14.57 percent to close at $59.99 apiece as investors loaded portfolios amid positive developments in the artificial intelligence industry and ahead of the results of its […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iren-ltd-iren-soars-14-190640784.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Applied Digital (APLD) Jumps 14% on AI Optimism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-digital-apld-jumps-14-190630306.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names With Easy 10-30% Gains. Applied Digital Corp. (NASDAQ:APLD) was one of the best performers on Tuesday. Applied Digital grew its share prices by 14.29 percent on Tuesday to close at $41.35 apiece amid positive developments surrounding the artificial intelligence industry, including higher funding from key players. Applied Digital Corp. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-digital-apld-jumps-14-190630306.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Cipher Mining (CIFR) Jumps 13.7% as Tech Giants Pour More Funds Into AI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cipher-mining-cifr-jumps-13-190623192.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names With Easy 10-30% Gains. Cipher Mining Inc. (NASDAQ:CIFR) was one of the best performers on Tuesday. Cipher Mining saw its share prices jump by 13.71 percent on Tuesday to finish at $18.75 apiece as investors poured funds in high-performance computing (HPC) operators, with sentiment bolstered by Nvidia Corp.’s ramped […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cipher-mining-cifr-jumps-13-190623192.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:06:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] T1 Energy (TE) Climbs 12% on Renewed AI Optimism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/t1-energy-te-climbs-12-190556019.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names With Easy 10-30% Gains. T1 Energy Inc. (NYSE:TE) was one of the best performers on Tuesday. T1 Energy soared by 12.04 percent on Tuesday to close at $9.12 apiece—a new two-year high—as investors took path from the rally in technology stocks, thanks to Nvidia Corp.’s ramped up investments in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/t1-energy-te-climbs-12-190556019.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] TeraWulf (WULF) Rebounds 11% on AI Bets</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/terawulf-wulf-rebounds-11-ai-190548338.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names With Easy 10-30% Gains. TeraWulf Inc. (NASDAQ:WULF) was one of the best performers on Tuesday. TeraWulf bounced back by 11.02 percent on Tuesday to finish at $15.31 apiece, after a semiconductor giant placed further bets on the artificial intelligence sector through a billion-dollar funding in a cloud computing services […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/terawulf-wulf-rebounds-11-ai-190548338.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave (CRWV) Jumps 10.7% on Billion-Dollar Backing</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-jumps-10-7-190532316.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Big Names With Easy 10-30% Gains. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) was one of the best performers on Tuesday. CoreWeave extended its winning streak to a third consecutive day on Tuesday, jumping 10.73 percent to close at $108.86 apiece after earning a billion-dollar backing from Nvidia Corp. In a statement, Nvidia announced the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-jumps-10-7-190532316.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Prediction: ARM Holdings Will Be 2026's Most Surprising AI Winner</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/prediction-arm-holdings-will-be-2026s-most-surpris/</link><description>It won't necessarily be its biggest winner, but investors will soon understand how integral it is to the artificial intelligence industry, and how resilient its business model is.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/prediction-arm-holdings-will-be-2026s-most-surpris/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why a New $11 Million Bet on 2030 Corporate Bonds Fits Into This Rate-Aware Portfolio</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/why-a-new-usd11-million-bet-on-2030-corporate-bonds-fits-into-this-rate-aware-portfolio/</link><description>This ETF tracks investment grade corporate bonds maturing in 2030, providing defined maturity exposure for fixed income portfolios.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/28/why-a-new-usd11-million-bet-on-2030-corporate-bonds-fits-into-this-rate-aware-portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:02:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500 touches 7,000 mark as Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-touches-7000-mark-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-143835876.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-touches-7000-mark-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-143835876.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave Stock Earns RS Rating Upgrade</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/coreweave-stock-earns-rs-rating-upgrade/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>On Wednesday, CoreWeave stock reached an important technical milestone, with its Relative Strength (RS) Rating climbing into the 90-plus percentile with an upgrade to 93, up from 90 the day before.    Looking For The Best Stocks To Buy And Watch? Start Here  This proprietary rating identifies technical performance by using a 1 (worst) to 99 (best) score that identifies how a stock's price performance over the trailing 52 weeks matches up against the rest of the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/coreweave-stock-earns-rs-rating-upgrade/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Forget Intel: This Dividend‑Rich Chip Powerhouse Is a Safer Way to Profit From AI and Cloud Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-intel-this-dividendrich-chip-powerhouse-is/</link><description>This AI chipmaker -- not Nvidia -- has been one of the best performers during this AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-intel-this-dividendrich-chip-powerhouse-is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] OpenAI's Backers May Be Doubling Down</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openais-backers-may-doubling-down-181324215.html</link><description>A massive funding effort quietly takes shape</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openais-backers-may-doubling-down-181324215.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones AI Giant Nvidia Set To Hit New Buy Point After This Bullish Move</title><link>https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/stocks-near-a-buy-zone/dow-jones-nvidia-nvda-stock-new-buy-point/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Dow Jones AI giant Nvidia stock is poised to hit a new buy point following last week's bullish retake of the 50-day line.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/stocks-near-a-buy-zone/dow-jones-nvidia-nvda-stock-new-buy-point/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Top Lessons from Rich 95-Year-Old Stock Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-lessons-rich-95-old-180000668.html</link><description>Warren Buffett, and Tracey's friend Ed, have invested for decades. What we've learned.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-lessons-rich-95-old-180000668.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer Believes “Broadcom Represents One of the Cheaper Ways to Play Artificial Intelligence”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-believes-broadcom-represents-175219397.html</link><description>Broadcom Inc. (NASDAQ:AVGO) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer answered questions about. Noting that the market expanded out of the tech stocks, a caller asked if they should hold or sell their position in the stock. Cramer replied: I’m going to make a suggestion, not hold, not sell, but buy. I think that Broadcom […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-believes-broadcom-represents-175219397.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer Says “Own NVIDIA, Don’t Trade It” Is the “Best Way to Play NVIDIA”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-own-nvidia-175218557.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer put under the microscope. Cramer showed bullish sentiment toward the stock during the episode, as he said: You know what didn’t matter at all to these bears, though? I got tremendous assurance that there could be some very big Chinese sales on the horizon. Jensen’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-own-nvidia-175218557.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Calls the NVIDIA Deal a “Fantastic Verification for CoreWeave”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-nvidia-deal-175216754.html</link><description>CoreWeave, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer put under the microscope. Cramer highlighted NVIDIA’s investment in the company, as he commented: … NVIDIA announced that it invested another $2 billion in CoreWeave, buying 22.9 million shares at $87.20 per share. It was a fantastic verification for CoreWeave, demonstrating that it’s the preferred […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-nvidia-deal-175216754.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Why Monolithic Power Systems (MPWR) Stock Is Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-monolithic-power-systems-mpwr-175049028.html</link><description>Shares of power management chips maker Monolithic Power Systems (NASDAQ:MPWR) jumped 5.7% in the afternoon session after a broad rally in the semiconductor sector lifted shares as industry bellwether ASML reported strong earnings and a positive outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-monolithic-power-systems-mpwr-175049028.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Pharma Stocks Are Close to ‘Breaking Out.’ Earnings Could Set Them Free.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/pharma-stocks-breaking-out-earnings-merck-f25b1335?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Pharmaceutical stocks just broke out to new highs—and earnings could push them even higher.  The  exchange-traded fund is up 32% in the past six months to almost $57.  Also helping the rally is that healthcare companies are investing in artificial intelligence to help them identify revenue opportunities with lower costs, potentially lifting profit margins.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/pharma-stocks-breaking-out-earnings-merck-f25b1335?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Applied Materials Is Back in the Spotlight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-back-spotlight-174432440.html</link><description>Chip spending momentum turns supportive</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-back-spotlight-174432440.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML's CEO Says AI Demand Is Accelerating. Is the Stock a Buy for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/asmls-ceo-says-ai-demand-is-accelerating-is-the-st/</link><description>Bookings surged in the fourth quarter, indicating strong demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/asmls-ceo-says-ai-demand-is-accelerating-is-the-st/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly outlays $1.12bn for hearing loss gene therapy partnership</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/eli-lilly-outlays-1-12bn-for-hearing-loss-gene-therapy-partnership/</link><description>Lilly and German biotech Seamless Therapeutics will develop recombinase-based treatments for hearing loss.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/eli-lilly-outlays-1-12bn-for-hearing-loss-gene-therapy-partnership/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Forget the Hype: This Stock Could Offer Better Long-Term Returns</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-the-hype-this-stock-could-offer-better-long/</link><description>Micron may be one of the most undervalued AI stocks right now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-the-hype-this-stock-could-offer-better-long/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Evercore ISI Reiterates Outperform on IBM Ahead of Earnings, Sees Results In Line</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-reiterates-underperform-ibm-161829590.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the AI Stocks in Focus on Wall Street. On January 26, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $330.00 price target. The rating affirmation comes ahead of IBM’s fourth-quarter earnings report scheduled for Wednesday, January 28. Evercore ISI expects IBM […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-reiterates-underperform-ibm-161829590.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Here’s What the Wall Street Thinks About Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-thinks-taiwan-semiconductor-173008939.html</link><description>​Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) is one of the High-Flying Tech Stocks to Buy. On January 19, DBS reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a price target of $391. Earlier, on January 16, TD Cowen maintained a Hold rating on the stock and raised the price target from $325 to $370. ​Analysts […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-thinks-taiwan-semiconductor-173008939.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] NRDS Shares Rise 12.6% in 6 Months: Should You Hold or Fold Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nrds-shares-rise-12-6-171900591.html</link><description>NerdWallet shares jump nearly 13% in six months as revenue diversification, margin expansion and cash flow gains drive investor interest. Is more upside left?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nrds-shares-rise-12-6-171900591.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] HSBC Raises Micron (MU) Price Target, William Blair Initiates With Outperform Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-raises-micron-mu-price-171721435.html</link><description>Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) is one of the 11 Most Profitable Cheap Stocks to Invest In Now. On January 23, HSBC increased its price target on Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) from $350 to $500 and kept its Buy rating. The firm noted that the sharp rise in DRAM prices was a major reason behind the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hsbc-raises-micron-mu-price-171721435.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] RBC Capital Remains a Buy on ​Celestica (CLS)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-capital-remains-buy-celestica-171721882.html</link><description>​Celestica Inc. (NYSE:CLS) is one of the High-Flying Tech Stocks to Buy. On January 23, RBC Capital reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $400 price target. Earlier, on January 20, Aletheia Capital also reiterated a Buy rating on Celestica Inc. (NYSE:CLS) and raised the price target from $330 to $410. ​Recently, on […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-capital-remains-buy-celestica-171721882.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Group N.V. (NBIS) Up More Than 60% in 6 Months, Here’s What You Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-n-v-nbis-171719973.html</link><description>​Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the High-Flying Tech Stocks to Buy. Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) has gained more than 80% over the past 6 months. Wall Street remains a Strong Buy with 75% of the 12 analysts covering the stock having a Buy rating. ​Recently, on January 15, Morgan Stanley initiated coverage of […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-n-v-nbis-171719973.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Will Lilly (LLY) Beat Estimates Again in Its Next Earnings Report?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lilly-lly-beat-estimates-again-171001552.html</link><description>Lilly (LLY) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lilly-lly-beat-estimates-again-171001552.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Intel Stock Popped Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/why-intel-stock-popped-today/</link><description>Even Apple and Nvidia combined can't make Intel stock a buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/why-intel-stock-popped-today/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple’s first quarter earnings will focus on iPhone sales, AI outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apples-first-quarter-earnings-will-focus-on-iphone-sales-ai-outlook-170801438.html</link><description>Apple will report its first quarter earnings after the bell on Thursday, with Wall Street expecting strong iPhone sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apples-first-quarter-earnings-will-focus-on-iphone-sales-ai-outlook-170801438.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] WisdomTree’s Growth ETF Puts 14% in NVIDIA and 31% in Just Six Stocks</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/wisdomtrees-growth-etf-puts-14-in-nvidia-and-31-in-just-six-stocks/</link><description>Most investors want growth. Fewer understand that not all growth is worth buying. Some companies expand revenue but burn cash. Others grow earnings but sacrifice margins. The best growth stocks do both while maintaining operational excellence. That distinction matters because it separates companies that compound wealth from those that simply ride momentum. WisdomTree U.S. Quality ... WisdomTree’s Growth ETF Puts 14% in NVIDIA and 31% in Just Six Stocks</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/wisdomtrees-growth-etf-puts-14-in-nvidia-and-31-in-just-six-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Push to Boost Search Growth: More Upside Ahead for GOOGL Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-push-boost-search-growth-170100403.html</link><description>Alphabet rides AI momentum in Search and Cloud, but rising competition from MSFT and AMZN may test its edge.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-push-boost-search-growth-170100403.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Rises As China Greenlights H200 Chip; Is Nvidia A Buy Or Sell Now?</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-january-2026-meta-microsoft-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock rises in a base amid news that China will allow the purchase of the H200 chip by Chinese tech companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-january-2026-meta-microsoft-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Broadcom Set To Dominate Custom AI Chip Market With 60% Share By 2027, Counterpoint Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/broadcom-set-dominate-custom-ai-163116560.html</link><description>Counterpoint Research says the race to build custom AI silicon is accelerating, with hyperscalers scaling internal chips to meet surging demand. Hyperscalers Ramp Custom AI Chips Leading cloud and AI providers, including Alphabet Inc.’s (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google; Amazon.com, Inc.’s (NASDAQ:AMZN) Amazon Web Services; Microsoft Corp (NASDAQ:MSFT); OpenAI; ByteDance and Apple Inc (NASDAQ:AAPL), are rapidly expanding deployments of AI server compute Application-Specific Integrated Circuit (ASIC) based s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/broadcom-set-dominate-custom-ai-163116560.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research and Generac have been highlighted as Zacks Bull and Bear of the Day</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-generac-highlighted-zacks-162900736.html</link><description>Lam Research and Generac have been highlighted as Zacks Bull and Bear of the Day</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-generac-highlighted-zacks-162900736.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Earnings Drive Early Market Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earnings-drive-early-market-moves-162300358.html</link><description>Earnings Drive Early Market Moves</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earnings-drive-early-market-moves-162300358.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These Stocks Will Win the 2026 World Cup if All Goes to Plan</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-winners-world-cup-fifa-d9b24f47?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Uber, Lyft, StubHub, Airbnb, Alphabet, and Meta should benefit from the World Cup, but the tournament faces growing political backlash.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stocks-winners-world-cup-fifa-d9b24f47?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stocks Supported by Solid Tech Earnings</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37276931/stocks-supported-by-solid-tech-earnings</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 Index ($SPX ) (SPY ) today is up +0.03%, the Dow Jones Industrials Index ($DOWI ) (DIA ) is up +0.02%, and the Nasdaq 100 Index ($IUXX ) (QQQ ) is up +0.43%. March E-mini S&amp;amp;P futures (ESH26 ) are up +0.02%, and March E-mini Nasdaq futures...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37276931/stocks-supported-by-solid-tech-earnings</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple-Heavy ETFs in Focus as iPhone Sales Power Holiday Quarter</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-heavy-etfs-focus-iphone-161500769.html</link><description>iPhone sales jump to a four-year high, along with AI optimism building and analysts staying bullish, putting Apple-heavy ETFs back in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-heavy-etfs-focus-iphone-161500769.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google to pay $135 million to settle Android data transfer lawsuit</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-pay-135-million-settle-161335622.html</link><description>Google will pay $135 million to settle a proposed class action by smartphone users who accused Google of ​programming its Android operating system to collect their cellular data without ‌permission.  A preliminary settlement with the Alphabet unit was filed late Tuesday night in the San ‌Jose, California, federal court, and requires a judge's approval.  Google denied wrongdoing in agreeing to the settlement, which covers users of Android-powered mobile devices since November 12, 2017.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-pay-135-million-settle-161335622.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Approves First Nvidia H200 AI Chip Imports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-approves-first-nvidia-h200-161146358.html</link><description>Move signals easing of restrictions to meet surging domestic AI demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-approves-first-nvidia-h200-161146358.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Reports Record Orders, Launches $12 Billion Buyback</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-reports-record-orders-launches-160706351.html</link><description>Strong AI-driven bookings lift outlook as chip equipment demand surges.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-reports-record-orders-launches-160706351.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia's Plans to Sell More Chips in China Just Cleared a Major Hurdle</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/nvidia-plans-to-sell-more-chips-in-china-just-cleared-a-major-hurdle-nvda-11894059</link><description>The Chinese government has cleared some of its top tech companies to buy thousands of Nvidia's H200 AI chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/nvidia-plans-to-sell-more-chips-in-china-just-cleared-a-major-hurdle-nvda-11894059</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 1 No-Brainer Artificial Intelligence (AI) ETF to Confidently Buy With $70 in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/1-no-brainer-ai-etf-confidently-buy-70-in-2026/</link><description>The Roundhill Generative AI and Technology ETF holds a narrow portfolio of the highest quality AI stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/1-no-brainer-ai-etf-confidently-buy-70-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Nasdaq Charges Higher Ahead Of Fed, Powell Comments; Nvidia Rises (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-federal-reserve-powell-tesla-earnings-tsla-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stock Market Today: The Dow Jones index rose Wednesday ahead of the Fed decisions and Powell's comments. Tesla earnings are due late.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-federal-reserve-powell-tesla-earnings-tsla-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Big Earnings Day Sandwich Fed's Interest Rate Decision</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-earnings-day-sandwich-feds-154000963.html</link><description>No changes are expected from the current Fed funds rate, but this will be the first presser since the DOJ launched a criminal campaign against Fed Chair Powell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-earnings-day-sandwich-feds-154000963.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Invesco’s $1.7 Billion Emerging Markets Fund Rides China Tech and Banks To Huge Gains</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/invescos-1-7-billion-emerging-markets-fund-rides-china-tech-and-banks-to-huge-gains/</link><description>The Invesco RAFI Emerging Markets ETF (NYSEARCA:PXH) has delivered exceptional returns, surging 42% over the past year to reach $28.10 as of January 27, 2026. This performance significantly outpaced the S&amp;amp;P 500’s 16% gain and slightly edged out the iShares MSCI Emerging Markets ETF (NYSEARCA:EEM) with its 46% return. The rally reflects renewed appetite for ... Invesco’s $1.7 Billion Emerging Markets Fund Rides China Tech and Banks To Huge Gains</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/invescos-1-7-billion-emerging-markets-fund-rides-china-tech-and-banks-to-huge-gains/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Reports Record Orders Amid AI Chip Boom. The Stock Is Dropping.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-earnings-stock-price-7f26b1a7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Orders for the December quarter were nearly double what analysts had forecast amid optimism about artificial intelligence.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/asml-earnings-stock-price-7f26b1a7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Amphenol Blows Past Earnings Estimates. The Stock Sinks 13%.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/amphenol-earnings-stock-price-4354bfb4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Amphenol  posted fourth-quarter earnings and sales that topped consensus views and issued a solid outlook for the current quarter.  Before the opening bell Wednesday,  Amphenol  reported adjusted earnings of 97 cents a share from sales of $6.4 billion, outstripping Wall Street’s forecasts.  Amphenol guided for adjusted earnings in the range of 91 cents to 93 cents a share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/amphenol-earnings-stock-price-4354bfb4?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018663.html</link><description>YY Group Holdings Ltd. 3,718,115 0.2391</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018663.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] The AI infrastructure boom shows no sign of slowing down</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-infrastructure-boom-shows-no-152135661.html</link><description>ASML’s record orders show chipmakers are still betting big on AI data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-infrastructure-boom-shows-no-152135661.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] S&amp;P 500 breaches 7,000 as tech giants Microsoft and Meta prep earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/p-500-breaches-7-000-152125045.html</link><description>Investing.com -- The S&amp;amp;P 500 breached the 7,000-point mark for the first time on Wednesday, driven by optimism over artificial intelligence and expectations of strong Big Tech earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/p-500-breaches-7-000-152125045.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv Targets AI Data Center Growth With Predictive Service And Cooling</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-targets-ai-data-center-151025681.html</link><description>Vertiv Holdings Co (NYSE:VRT) has launched Vertiv Next Predict, an AI-powered managed service for data center maintenance. The company has also introduced new configurations of its MegaMod HDX modular liquid cooling solution for high-density AI and high performance computing environments. These announcements expand Vertiv's portfolio of AI-focused services and infrastructure for data centers. Vertiv focuses on critical digital infrastructure, including power, cooling, and services for data...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-targets-ai-data-center-151025681.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Amazon to Cut 16,000 Jobs. What’s Behind Its Largest Ever Corporate Layoffs.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-job-cuts-stock-2a2a6398?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Amazon.com  said Wednesday it will cut 16,000 jobs as the online retailer completes its largest-ever corporate layoffs.  The latest cuts will bring Amazon’s total layoffs to roughly 30,000 after it said last October it would eliminate around 14,000 roles.  Put together, the announcements suggest Amazon is slashing nearly 10% of its corporate workforce.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-job-cuts-stock-2a2a6398?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Reports Next Week: Wall Street Expects Earnings Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-reports-next-week-150015296.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-reports-next-week-150015296.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) Reports Next Week: Wall Street Expects Earnings Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-goog-reports-next-150012688.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOG) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-goog-reports-next-150012688.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Reports Next Week: Wall Street Expects Earnings Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-reports-next-150008144.html</link><description>Lilly (LLY) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-reports-next-150008144.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google to pay $135 million to settle Android data transfer lawsuit</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-pay-135-million-settle-150002899.html</link><description>Google will pay $135 million to settle a proposed class action by smartphone users ​who accused Google of programming its Android operating system ‌to collect their cellular data without permission.  A preliminary settlement with the Alphabet unit ‌was filed late Tuesday night in the San Jose, California federal court, and requires a judge's approval.  Google denied wrongdoing in agreeing to the settlement, which covers users of Android-powered mobile devices since November ⁠12, 2017.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-pay-135-million-settle-150002899.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Jim Cramer Says “Chatter” About NVIDIA (NVDA)’s Circular Deals is “Nonsense”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-chatter-nvidia-145448319.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is a regular stock on Jim Cramer’s radar. The CNBC TV host is one of the stock’s biggest proponents. As January kicked off, Citi reiterated a Buy rating on the shares […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-chatter-nvidia-145448319.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research (LRCX) Has a Shortage That Can’t Be Met, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-shortage-t-145424180.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Lam Research Corporation (NASDAQ:LRCX) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Lam Research Corporation (NASDAQ:LRCX) is an American semiconductor manufacturing equipment provider. Its shares are up by 194% over the past year and by 20% year-to-date. Goldman Sachs started the year on a strong […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-shortage-t-145424180.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Corp (KLAC) Has a Shortage That Can’t Be Met, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corp-klac-shortage-t-145320779.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) makes and sells equipment used in the chip manufacturing process. Its shares are up by 119% over the past year and by 21% year-to-date. Morgan Stanley increased the stock’s rating to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corp-klac-shortage-t-145320779.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] “Alphabet (GOOGL)’s Extraordinary,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-extraordinary-says-jim-145114032.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is a stock that Jim Cramer has consistently discussed over the past couple of months. During this time period, his opinion about the firm has shifted from being wary due to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-extraordinary-says-jim-145114032.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Is Cheapest in Years -- Should You Buy NVDA Stock Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-cheapest-years-buy-nvda-145042256.html</link><description>What Analysts See After the Recent Pullback</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-cheapest-years-buy-nvda-145042256.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Rises After China Approves First H200 AI Chip Imports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-rises-china-approves-144922818.html</link><description>Nvidia Edge Strengthens as China Clears First Batch of H200 Chips</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-rises-china-approves-144922818.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] ADI's Communications Segment Surges 26% in FY25: What's Next?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adis-communications-segment-surges-26-144900333.html</link><description>Analog Devices' communications segment rebounds in FY25, surging 26% on wireline growth tied to AI data centers and setting the pace for expected momentum in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adis-communications-segment-surges-26-144900333.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Some of Pharma's Biggest Brands Face a New Reality</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pharmas-biggest-brands-face-reality-144809825.html</link><description>A government process quietly moves forward</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pharmas-biggest-brands-face-reality-144809825.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Confirms AI-Driven Strength With Record Orders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-confirms-ai-driven-strength-144805528.html</link><description>Q4 bookings surge as EUV demand signals sustained chip capex</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-confirms-ai-driven-strength-144805528.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SoftBank Weighs $30 Billion Investment in OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-weighs-30-billion-investment-144431004.html</link><description>Talks could value the AI developer at roughly $830 billion</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-weighs-30-billion-investment-144431004.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 🎧What Does a Weaker Dollar Mean for Businesses and the World?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/-what-does-a-weaker-dollar-mean-for-businesses-and-the-world--QjIdEIhnaU1rwOrPEaQV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The dollar is steadying following its biggest one-day decline since April’s tariff turmoil. That’s after President Trump said he wouldn't mind a weaker currency. WSJ editor Alex Frangos explains why that statement caused such a selloff.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/-what-does-a-weaker-dollar-mean-for-businesses-and-the-world--QjIdEIhnaU1rwOrPEaQV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] CEO hot takes: Elevator manufacturer on robots, AI data centers, and an economic boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ceo-hot-takes-elevator-manufacturer-on-robots-ai-data-centers-and-an-economic-boom-143927670.html</link><description>One of the world's largest makers of elevators is a great proxy on a lot of things happening in the US economy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ceo-hot-takes-elevator-manufacturer-on-robots-ai-data-centers-and-an-economic-boom-143927670.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500 breaches 7,000 mark Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-breaches-7000-mark-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-143835732.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-breaches-7000-mark-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-143835732.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Bet on These 4 Top-Performing Liquid Stocks to Maximize Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bet-4-top-performing-liquid-143400849.html</link><description>EVER, CIEN, LRCX and RELY make the cut as the top liquid stocks, each boasting strong liquidity, growth attributes and operational efficiency.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bet-4-top-performing-liquid-143400849.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Artificial Intelligence Stock Is a Must-Own for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-artificial-intelligence-stock-is-a-must-own-f/</link><description>The rise of artificial intelligence (AI) has only strengthened this tech powerhouse.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-artificial-intelligence-stock-is-a-must-own-f/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Is Analog Devices (ADI) a Buy as Wall Street Analysts Look Optimistic?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-adi-buy-wall-143002956.html</link><description>According to the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), one should invest in Analog Devices (ADI). It is debatable whether this highly sought-after metric is effective because Wall Street analysts' recommendations tend to be overly optimistic. Would it be worth investing in the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-adi-buy-wall-143002956.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China approves Nvidia H200 purchases, Starbucks US sales rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/china-approves-nvidia-h200-purchases-starbucks-us-sales-rise-142710084.html</link><description>Morning Brief Host Julie Hyman tracks several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including semiconductor stock reactions after China reportedly approves the purchase of Nvidia's (NVDA) H200 chips, Starbucks (SBUX) shares jumping on rising US sales, and GE Vernova (GEV) raising its guidance.To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Morning Brief.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/china-approves-nvidia-h200-purchases-starbucks-us-sales-rise-142710084.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Move Over NVIDIA. The Rest of the Mag 7 are Making Strides in the AI Chip Race</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/move-over-nvidia-the-rest-of-the-mag-7-are-making-strides-in-the-ai-chip-race/</link><description>Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) faces some intense competition in the AI chip scene, and that’s likely part of the reason why the shares have been flatlining since August. Of course, all it takes is one incredible, breakout quarterly earnings performance (a side of encouraging commentary from CEO Jensen Huang couldn’t hurt as well!) for Nvidia stock to ... Move Over NVIDIA. The Rest of the Mag 7 are Making Strides in the AI Chip Race</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/move-over-nvidia-the-rest-of-the-mag-7-are-making-strides-in-the-ai-chip-race/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You Had Gone All-In on Nvidia in 2016, Here’s How Much Richer You Would’ve Been</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/had-gone-nvidia-2016-much-142204443.html</link><description>Nvidia stock has soared over 23,000% since 2016. See how much an investment made then would be worth now and whether the AI giant is still a smart buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/had-gone-nvidia-2016-much-142204443.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML’s €12b Buyback Links AI Equipment Demand To Capital Returns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-12b-buyback-links-ai-141245271.html</link><description>ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML) has launched a new €12b share buyback program alongside record demand for its semiconductor equipment. The latest quarterly order intake was far ahead of expectations, with management pointing to sustained demand tied to AI-related chip production. Company leaders describe an AI-driven growth outlook that they view as durable, aligning capital returns with strong current business conditions. ASML Holding, trading at €1,217.6, sits at the center of the high end...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-12b-buyback-links-ai-141245271.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Expands Beyond GLP 1s With Gene Editing And Oncology Bets</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-expands-beyond-glp-141147815.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (NYSE: LLY) announced a global research collaboration with Seamless Therapeutics to develop programmable gene editing therapies for hearing loss. The company also received FDA Breakthrough Therapy designation for an antibody drug conjugate in ovarian cancer. Both developments expand Lilly’s pipeline into genetic hearing loss and oncology, beyond its current strength in diabetes and obesity treatments. Eli Lilly, best known to many investors for its diabetes and obesity portfolio,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-expands-beyond-glp-141147815.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] FactSet Barclays Deal Highlights Role In Institutional Data And Analytics</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-barclays-deal-highlights-role-141141687.html</link><description>FactSet Research Systems (NYSE:FDS) has entered a multiyear collaboration with Barclays to support Barclays' market data strategy. The agreement focuses on providing advanced analytics and technology to strengthen Barclays' data driven capabilities. The partnership adds a major global bank as a long term client for FactSet's analytics and data solutions platform. For investors watching NYSE:FDS, this new Barclays agreement comes at a time when the stock is trading at $268.66, with a 1 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factset-barclays-deal-highlights-role-141141687.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Lilly bets on Seamless, delving further into genetic medicine for hearing loss</title><link>https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/eli-lilly-seamless-deal-gene-editing-hearing-loss/810694/</link><description>The potentially $1 billion alliance centered around a flexible gene editing technology adds to a portfolio of cutting-edge treatments the company is developing for hearing disorders.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/eli-lilly-seamless-deal-gene-editing-hearing-loss/810694/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Roche Reports Upbeat Efficacy Data From Phase II Obesity Study</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roche-reports-upbeat-efficacy-data-140900895.html</link><description>RHHBY reports encouraging phase II data as CT-388 delivers strong, sustained weight loss and metabolic benefits in adults with obesity or overweight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roche-reports-upbeat-efficacy-data-140900895.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Well Done! Invesco’s Semiconductor ETF Returned 46% Without Just Chasing NVDA | PSI</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/well-done-invescos-semiconductor-etf-returned-46-without-just-chasing-nvda-psi/</link><description>When individual semiconductor stocks can swing from losses to profits within two years, or when analyst estimates miss by over 1,000%, individual semiconductor stocks can experience extreme volatility. The Invesco Semiconductors ETF (NYSEARCA:PSI) offers a diversified alternative with a momentum-driven approach that captures sector growth through 30 holdings. Diversified Sector Exposure Through 30 Holdings PSI ... Well Done! Invesco’s Semiconductor ETF Returned 46% Without Just Chasing NVDA | PS</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/28/well-done-invescos-semiconductor-etf-returned-46-without-just-chasing-nvda-psi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Snap seeks investments as new smart glasses unit takes on Meta</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snap-seeks-investments-smart-glasses-140250898.html</link><description>Jan 28 (Reuters) - Snap will create an independent subsidiary for its augmented reality smart glasses, as it looks to ​attract external investment and challenge bigger rival Meta in the fast-growing ‌wearables market. The launch of the Specs unit, announced on Wednesday, comes as the success of Ray-Ban Meta ‌smart glasses positions eyewear as an early frontrunner in the race for gadgets powered by artificial intelligence.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snap-seeks-investments-smart-glasses-140250898.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] ChatGPT Thinks Snowflake Stock Will Close At This Price In The Next 60 Days</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-snowflake-stock-close-140110684.html</link><description>Quick Summary ChatGPT thinks Snowflake stock could trade higher over the next 60 days, projecting an average price around $214.21 by mid-April. Investors looking to express a view can build exposure incrementally using commission-free fractional shares on SoFi, starting with...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-snowflake-stock-close-140110684.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly and Company (LLY): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-bull-140055177.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on Eli Lilly and Company on R. Dennis’s Substack by OppCost. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on LLY. Eli Lilly and Company’s share was trading at $1,039.51 as of January 27th. LLY’s trailing and forward P/E were 50.93 and 31.65 respectively according to Yahoo Finance. Eli Lilly and Company discovers, develops, and markets human pharmaceuticals in the United States, Europe, China, Japan, and internationally. LLY presents a […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-bull-140055177.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] How to Boost Your Portfolio with Top Medical Stocks Set to Beat Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boost-portfolio-top-medical-stocks-140004279.html</link><description>Investors looking for ways to find stocks that are set to beat quarterly earnings estimates should check out the Zacks Earnings ESP.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boost-portfolio-top-medical-stocks-140004279.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Redwood attracts Google for its $425M Series E as AI power needs rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/redwood-attracts-google-425m-series-140000424.html</link><description>Google is the latest investor to back Redwood Materials as the battery recycling startup scales a new energy storage venture to power AI data centers and other industrial sites.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/redwood-attracts-google-425m-series-140000424.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Holding N.V. (ASML): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-n-v-asml-135750807.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on ASML Holding N.V. on Arya’s Substack by Arya. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on ASML. ASML Holding N.V.’s share was trading at $1,454.59 as of January 27th. ASML’s trailing and forward P/E were 50.55 and 45.66 respectively according to Yahoo Finance. ASML Holding N.V. (ASML) remains the centerpiece of advanced semiconductor manufacturing, commanding a near-monopoly in EUV lithography and benefiting from structural tailwinds driven by AI, l</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-n-v-asml-135750807.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Is This Chip Stock a Smart Long-Term Bet as Artificial Intelligence Scales Globally?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/is-chip-stock-smart-long-term-bet-ai-globally/</link><description>It may be time to start looking at Intel stock again.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/is-chip-stock-smart-long-term-bet-ai-globally/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] AMAT stock: Mizuho sees ‘significant acceleration’ in WFE, upgrades rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amat-stock-mizuho-sees-significant-133218199.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Applied Materials received an upgrade from Mizuho on Wednesday, with the firm citing a sharp rebound in semiconductor capital spending and strengthening foundry and logic demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amat-stock-mizuho-sees-significant-133218199.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] U.K. Competition Watchdog Plans New Rules for Google’s AI Overviews Under Tech Law</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/u-k-competition-watchdog-plans-new-rules-for-googles-ai-overviews-under-tech-law-a9ae3c5e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Under the plans, publishers could stop their content being used to power AI Overviews, or to train AI models outside of Google search and make sure their content is properly cited in AI results.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/u-k-competition-watchdog-plans-new-rules-for-googles-ai-overviews-under-tech-law-a9ae3c5e?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Earnings live: Starbucks stock pops, GE Vernova slips, ASML surges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-starbucks-stock-pops-ge-vernova-slips-asml-surges-133036401.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear this week, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-starbucks-stock-pops-ge-vernova-slips-asml-surges-133036401.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Itron Partners With Snowflake to Advance AI-Driven Grid Planning</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/itron-partners-snowflake-advance-ai-132900552.html</link><description>ITRI teams up with Snowflake to power advanced grid planning, helping utilities manage DER complexity, modernize grids and cut costs with AI-driven analytics.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/itron-partners-snowflake-advance-ai-132900552.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Job Cuts Highlight Efficiency Focus As AI EUV Orders Build</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-job-cuts-highlight-efficiency-131842086.html</link><description>ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) plans to cut about 1,700 jobs, roughly 4% of its workforce. The reduction comes as the company reports record net profit and strong AI driven demand for its chip making tools. ASML highlights a growing order book for its extreme ultraviolet lithography systems and indicates expectations for another growth year in 2026. ASML Holding, trading at around $1,454.59, sits at the center of advanced semiconductor manufacturing, with its extreme ultraviolet lithography...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-job-cuts-highlight-efficiency-131842086.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) Stock Price Prediction for 2026: Where Will It Be in 1 Year (Jan 28)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</link><description>Nvidia remains the dominant AI chipmaker in the market, but where is the stock headed for the rest of this year and into the next?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Makes a Quiet Internal Move</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-makes-quiet-internal-move-130846722.html</link><description>A structural shift unfolds behind the scenes</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-makes-quiet-internal-move-130846722.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: AMD Stock Will Soar on Feb. 3</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/prediction-amd-stock-will-soar-on-february-3/</link><description>The chipmaker's management team has asserted that this year will be a turning point for the company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/prediction-amd-stock-will-soar-on-february-3/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here’s Why Eli Lilly (LLY) is Surging</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-eli-lilly-lly-surging-130314523.html</link><description>Hardman Johnston Global Advisors, an investment management company, released its “Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy” investor letter for the fourth quarter of 2025. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. Global equity markets delivered robust results in the quarter, backed by easing inflation trends and strong economic data. The Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-eli-lilly-lly-surging-130314523.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:03:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Stock: How To Find &amp; Own America's Greatest Opportunities</title><link>https://www.investors.com/how-to-invest/cisco-csco-stock-americas-greatest-opportunities/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Cisco Systems was one of the best-performing stocks of the 1990s, making its name as the leading supplier of networking gear.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/how-to-invest/cisco-csco-stock-americas-greatest-opportunities/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia AI Partner Monolithic Power Systems Etches Buy Point, Boosted By Big Demand</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/monolithic-power-mpwr-eyes-breakout-ai-data-center-nvidia-partner/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>As Nvidia works on a new setup, solid growth and strong demand for AI data centers has Monolithic Power etching a buy point.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/monolithic-power-mpwr-eyes-breakout-ai-data-center-nvidia-partner/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta Prepares Paid Tiers For Instagram, Facebook And WhatsApp, Offering Exclusive AI Features And Enhanced Control: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-prepares-paid-tiers-instagram-130109983.html</link><description>Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) is reportedly testing new paid subscriptions across Instagram, Facebook, and WhatsApp that would unlock premium features and expanded AI tools while keeping the core apps free. Meta Tests Subscription Model Across Core Apps Meta plans to roll out optional subscriptions that offer users a more advanced experience across its social apps, the company told TechCrunch. The Mark Zuckerberg-led company said it will test different subscription features and bundles, wit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-prepares-paid-tiers-instagram-130109983.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Will the Russell 2000 Continue to Outperform the S&amp;P 500?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russell-2000-continue-outperform-p-130009641.html</link><description>Examining whether or not small-cap outperformance tends to hold longer term</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russell-2000-continue-outperform-p-130009641.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Does Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT) have a Robust Long-Term Outlook?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-125138975.html</link><description>Hardman Johnston Global Advisors, an investment management company, released its “Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy” investor letter for the fourth quarter of 2025. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. Global equity markets delivered robust results in the quarter, backed by easing inflation trends and strong economic data. The Hardman Johnston Global Equity Strategy […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-125138975.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] CMS selects next batch of 15 high-cost medicines for third negotiation cycle</title><link>https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/cms-selects-next-batch-of-15-high-cost-medicines-for-third-negotiation-cycle/</link><description>The 15 drugs accounted for $27bn in spending via Medicare Part B and Part D between November 2024 and October 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmaceutical-technology.com/news/cms-selects-next-batch-of-15-high-cost-medicines-for-third-negotiation-cycle/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Gold Driven to Record Highs by Geopolitical Risk, Says HSBC's Steel</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/gold-driven-record-highs-geopolitical-124211097.html</link><description>James Steel, chief precious metals analyst at HSBC, expects increased volatility and frequent pullbacks ahead for gold with new money coming into the market as he sees geopolitical risk as the main factor driving the metal to record highs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/gold-driven-record-highs-geopolitical-124211097.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer Expresses Caution on Celestica Valuation Due to Potential Google Partnership Changes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-expresses-caution-celestica-122332408.html</link><description>Celestica Inc. (NYSE:CLS) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. When a caller expressed worry upon hearing that Google might be backing out of its relationship with the company, Cramer remarked: Yeah, I saw that too and was thinking, boy, Celestica is really too high if that happens. Why don’t […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-expresses-caution-celestica-122332408.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Jim Cramer on Arm Holdings: “I Think You Do Buy the Stock”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-122331963.html</link><description>Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. A caller inquired about Cramer’s thoughts on buying more ARM shares, and he replied: Okay, Arm’s very interesting here because they did see the big shortage coming. Rene Haas got it right. I think you do buy the stock, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-122331963.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Jim Cramer on Caterpillar: “I Would Like to See the Stock Lower”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-caterpillar-see-stock-122328861.html</link><description>Caterpillar Inc. (NYSE:CAT) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. Noting that the stock seems “richly valued,” a club member asked how much it needs to fall to start a position. In response, Cramer said: There are a lot of people who feel that this is a data center play […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-caterpillar-see-stock-122328861.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Jim Cramer Advises Caution on Nebius Due to Potential AI Infrastructure Slowdown</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-advises-caution-nebius-122311807.html</link><description>Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer discussed, along with market shortages. A caller asked where Cramer sees the biggest risk in the company and his view on the AI infrastructure. In response, Cramer said: Well, I think that, I think that, you see, these stocks were all overvalued. What’s going […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-advises-caution-nebius-122311807.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Seagate, Texas Instruments, Nvidia, AT&amp;T, Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-01763d21?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Seagate Technology shares surge after the hard-disk-drive maker beats analysts’ fourth-quarter earnings estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-01763d21?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Greg Abel Signals New Berkshire Era With Kraft Heinz And Sirius XM Shakeup</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greg-abel-signals-berkshire-era-122300407.html</link><description>Greg Abel, in his first major move as Berkshire Hathaway CEO, is considering selling the company’s entire Kraft Heinz stake. Recent SEC filings, Kraft Heinz disclosures, and Berkshire’s board resignations at Kraft Heinz point to an intent to fully exit the investment. Berkshire is also exploring a sale of its position in Sirius XM as the business faces subscriber and competitive pressures. Berkshire Hathaway (NYSE:BRK.A), recently trading around $713,000.0 per Class A share, is entering a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greg-abel-signals-berkshire-era-122300407.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Is It Time To Reassess Cisco Systems (CSCO) After Strong Multi‑Year Share Price Gains?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-cisco-systems-csco-122224005.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Cisco Systems at around US$78.68 is offering fair value or a stretched price, it helps to break the story into recent performance, news flow, and a clear view of what the numbers say. The stock has returns of 7.3% over the last 7 days, 0.7% over 30 days, 3.5% year to date, 35.6% over 1 year, 76.0% over 3 years, and 98.4% over 5 years. These figures may catch the eye of anyone thinking about growth potential or changing risk perceptions. Recent coverage around...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-cisco-systems-csco-122224005.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Gains. How China and OpenAI News Could Break It Out of Its Rut.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-china-openai-359efcf7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock was rising as prospects brightened for sales of its AI chips in China and to ChatGPT-developer OpenAI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-china-openai-359efcf7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Faces EU DMA Scrutiny While Gemini Powers Apple Siri</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-faces-eu-dma-scrutiny-122115260.html</link><description>The European Commission has opened formal compliance proceedings against Google under the Digital Markets Act to review how it treats rival AI and search services. At the same time, Google has agreed with Apple to integrate its Gemini AI model as the default intelligence behind Siri. These developments arrive as Alphabet (NasdaqGS:GOOGL) continues to refine its role in global search, mobile ecosystems, and AI platforms. For investors watching Alphabet at a share price of $334.55, the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-faces-eu-dma-scrutiny-122115260.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Amazon to Cut 16,000 Corporate Positions to Trim Bureaucracy</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-cut-16-000-corporate-122006515.html</link><description>The tech firm will offer US-based employees 90 days to search for a new role internally, as well as severance and other transition support, Beth Galetti, Amazon’s senior vice president of people experience and technology said Wednesday in a blog post.  Companies across industries have been trimming management layers in the name of becoming leaner and more productive.  Just as Amazon was announcing its own layoffs, the chip-making machine giant ASML Holding NV said it’s eliminating 1,700 positions largely targeting managerial roles.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-cut-16-000-corporate-122006515.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Is Jumping -- Record Orders Signal AI-Driven Chip Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-stock-jumping-record-orders-120645023.html</link><description>AI Momentum Boosts Confidence in 2026 Growth</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-stock-jumping-record-orders-120645023.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Trump Is Happy With a Diving Dollar. Why Stock Markets Should Be on Alert.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-dollar-stock-market-things-to-know-today-fbdf0649?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>What to know ahead of the Fed decision, ASML sales smash expectations, Meta’s AI spending spree weighs on earnings outlook, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-dollar-stock-market-things-to-know-today-fbdf0649?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Neocloud startup PaleBlueDot valued at $1 billion in B Capital-led round</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/neocloud-startup-palebluedot-valued-1-120431917.html</link><description>Artificial intelligence cloud startup PaleBlueDot AI has raised $150 million in a Series B funding round, valuing the company at more than $1 billion as it ​expands AI computing offerings in the United States and Asia, the company told Reuters.  The ‌round was led by B Capital, as PaleBlueDot joins a crowded field of so-called "neocloud" companies seeking to meet surging ‌demand for AI computing power.  PaleBlueDot said it planned to use the proceeds to buy Nvidia graphics processing units (GPUs) and related infrastructure and to hire staff to expand partnerships.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/neocloud-startup-palebluedot-valued-1-120431917.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly signs up to $1.12 billion deal with private gene-editing firm Seamless</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-signs-1-12-120320602.html</link><description>drugmaker Eli Lilly signed an agreement worth up to $1.12 billion with Seamless Therapeutics, ​the Germany-based startup said on Wednesday, to develop and commercialize ‌treatments for hearing loss using the biotech's gene-editing platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-signs-1-12-120320602.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Group (NBIS) Carries Strong Potential for Margin Expansion and Free Cash Flows</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-carries-strong-115722043.html</link><description>Nebius Group NV (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the best large cap stocks under $100 with huge upside potential. On January 15, Morgan Stanley analyst Josh Baer initiated coverage on Nebius Group NV (NASDAQ:NBIS), assigning an Equal Weight rating to the stock. He estimated over 33% upside potential based on a price target of $126. Despite […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-carries-strong-115722043.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Morning Bid: Making a weak dollar "great" again</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-bid-making-weak-dollar-114738670.html</link><description>and global markets today , Editor-At-Large, Finance and Markets The dollar managed to get a toehold on Wednesday after a withering drop to a four-year low overnight. President Donald Trump appeared to embrace the move, saying the ​dollar was "great.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-bid-making-weak-dollar-114738670.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Shares in Chip-Machine Giant ASML Jump as AI Spending Booms</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff</link><description>The company logged record quarterly orders, showing how tech clients continue to plow money into tools for making sophisticated semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Has Walk-Off Home Run in China</title><link>https://247wallst.com/technology-3/2026/01/28/nvidia-has-walk-off-home-run-in-china/</link><description>China reportedly has approved the sale of Nvidia H200 chips to certain tech companies there. This came despite its desire to build its own AI chips and not rely on America.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/technology-3/2026/01/28/nvidia-has-walk-off-home-run-in-china/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Health Care Roundup: Market Talk</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/health-care-roundup-market-talk-76913f76?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>1131 GMT – Roche Holding’s results from a midstage study of its CT-388 obesity drug candidate look promising, UBS analysts say in a research note.  The drug the Swiss pharmaceutical company is developing achieved weight-loss efficacy that seems to be broadly similar to Eli Lilly’s Zepbound, but at an earlier timepoint, and the discontinuation rate looks similar too, UBS says.  “All that said, the weight loss looks robust and the safety profile looks generally consistent with the drug class.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/health-care-roundup-market-talk-76913f76?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Turns to Sakana AI for Gemini Push</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-turns-sakana-ai-gemini-113801642.html</link><description>Startup gains access to core AI models</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-turns-sakana-ai-gemini-113801642.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Week In AI Chips - AI Transforming Chip Design Insights From DVCon US Conference</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-ai-transforming-113759930.html</link><description>The 2026 Design and Verification Conference and Exhibition (DVCon U.S.) has unveiled its program, focusing on the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in alleviating the verification bottleneck within electronic design. The event, set to occur from March 2-5 at the Hyatt Regency Santa Clara, will feature a panel discussion addressing whether AI could revolutionize the design verification process or if it may be merely another over-hyped technology. Attendees will have access to keynotes,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-ai-transforming-113759930.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google faces making changes to search services under watchdog proposals</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/google-faces-making-changes-search-110629470.html</link><description>The CMA has tabled measures to improve Google Search in the UK after it designated the firm with so-called strategic market status.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/google-faces-making-changes-search-110629470.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] F&amp;C Investment Trust Update: Nevin Defends Global, AI-Linked Portfolio as Dollar Weakens</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/fc-investment-trust-update-nevin-defends-global-ai-linked-portfolio-as-dollar-weakens-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>F&amp;amp;C Investment Trust (LON:FCIT) used a shareholder update to outline portfolio positioning, recent performance, and key market themes, with fund manager Paul Nevin emphasizing a long-term, globally diversified approach spanning listed equities and private equity. Trust overview and portfolio st</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/fc-investment-trust-update-nevin-defends-global-ai-linked-portfolio-as-dollar-weakens-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Exclusive-Novo's Wegovy and Ozempic US advertising spend doubles rival Eli Lilly, data shows</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-novos-wegovy-ozempic-us-110653009.html</link><description>By Harshita Mary Varghese and Patrick Wingrove Jan 28 (Reuters) - Novo Nordisk spent nearly $500 million on U.S. advertising for its GLP-1 drugs Wegovy and Ozempic in the first nine months of 2025,</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-novos-wegovy-ozempic-us-110653009.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] India Obesity Drug Fight Is About to Intensify</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-obesity-drug-fight-intensify-113118752.html</link><description>Sun Pharma clears path for semaglutide generics</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/india-obesity-drug-fight-intensify-113118752.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ASML posts record orders on AI chip demand, SK Hynix soars</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-posts-record-orders-ai-113018436.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: The AI boom showed no signs of slowing down for majors ASML and SK Hynix on Wednesday (January 28).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASML logged record orders in the fourth quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the top computer chip equipment maker raised its outlook for the year as demand surged from its AI-focused customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fourth-quarter bookings leapt to a record $15.8 billion - well up from a year before and far ahead of analyst expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm also raised its sales guidance to between $46.8 billion to a near $54 billion - again ahead of analyst projections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares were up more than 4% in early trade - the stock is up close to 40% this year so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The orders beat comes as ASML customers like Samsung and SK Hynix boost investment plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those firms have seen major demand for AI logic and memory chips needed by cloud computing giants like Microsoft and Google.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea's SK Hynix also reported record quarterly earnings Wednesday amid the AI boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It smashed forecasts with&amp;amp;nbsp;a profit more than double its previous record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also predicted AI demand would keep pushing explosive growth in memory chip orders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-posts-record-orders-ai-113018436.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Texas Instruments shares jump as first-quarter outlook signals robust AI data center demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-instruments-shares-jump-first-112650774.html</link><description>Texas Instruments' shares gained 7% in premarket trading on Wednesday after its rosy quarterly forecast showed the AI data center ​boom was driving demand for chips beyond Nvidia's advanced processors.  TI on Tuesday ‌forecast first-quarter profit and revenue above estimates, powered by strong analog sales, especially in data center.  TI makes ‌analog chips for converting signals and managing power in data centers, unlike Nvidia's fast, high-priced AI graphics chips, and has benefited from a surge in demand from tech companies ramping up compute infrastructure to power their AI ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-instruments-shares-jump-first-112650774.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eikon ‍Therapeutics targets $908 million valuation in US IPO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eikon-therapeutics-targets-908-million-111855370.html</link><description>Jan 28 (Reuters) - Drug developer Eikon ‍Therapeutics said on Wednesday it was targeting a valuation of up to $908.2 million in its U.S. initial public offering, as biotech listings make a comeback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eikon-therapeutics-targets-908-million-111855370.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple’s Gemini AI Deal And China Risks Weigh On Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-ai-deal-china-111152846.html</link><description>Apple (NasdaqGS:AAPL) has agreed a partnership with Alphabet to use its Gemini AI model to power an upgraded Siri and other AI features. The Gemini powered capabilities are expected to sit at the center of Apple's next wave of on device and cloud based AI services. Separately, a shareholder proposal is urging Apple to publish a report on risks tied to its business exposure to China. Apple, trading at $258.27, has had a mixed share price record recently, with a 4.7% gain over the past week...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-ai-deal-china-111152846.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] AI isn't a bubble but the real upside is shifting</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-isnt-bubble-real-upside-110057467.html</link><description>You can catch Trader Talk on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, YouTube, or wherever you get your podcasts. What if the AI boom is just getting started? On this episode of Trader Talk, Kenny Polcari sits down with tech analyst Daniel Newman to break down why AI is still in its earliest innings—and why market leadership is starting to broaden beyond the Magnificent Seven. They unpack the implications of the Nvidia (NVDA) and Eli Lilly (LLY) partnership, enterprise AI adoption, and where investors may find the next wave of alpha as the trade widens. Watch more episodes of Trader Talk here. Trader Talk with Kenny Polcari on Yahoo Finance delivers expert analysis and actionable insights, empowering you to navigate market volatility and secure your financial future. This post was written by Langston Sessoms.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-isnt-bubble-real-upside-110057467.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Waabi hauls in $750M Series C to become Canada’s newest autonomous vehicle unicorn</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waabi-hauls-750m-series-c-110000192.html</link><description>Oversubscribed round led by Khosla and G2 catapults Toronto startup into robotaxi race with massive Uber deal The post Waabi hauls in $750M Series C to become Canada’s newest autonomous vehicle unicorn appeared first on FreightWaves.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waabi-hauls-750m-series-c-110000192.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Chip Stocks Get Another Boost From ASML Earnings</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/chip-stocks-get-another-boost-from-asml-earnings-lMSqCA1JRMRfPdm6TVMA?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shares in ASML, the Dutch company that builds the world's most advanced chipmaking equipment, surged after it logged record quarterly orders and forecast healthy sales growth this year.    The stock gained more than 5% in Amsterdam, recently trading at 1,282.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/chip-stocks-get-another-boost-from-asml-earnings-lMSqCA1JRMRfPdm6TVMA?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Stock Surges On Strong Sales Forecast For 2026</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/asml-stock-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Semiconductor equipment giant ASML provided a strong outlook for the current quarter and full year ahead. ASML stock rose on the news.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/asml-stock-q4-2025-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wall Street Bets a Rally in Riskiest Stocks Has Staying Power</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-bets-rally-riskiest-103000857.html</link><description>The Russell 2000 Index, home to some of the riskiest stocks in the market because of their strong ties to the business and credit cycles, just ended the longest run of beating large caps since 1996.  The bet is predicated on expectations for faster earnings growth, owing to a combination of falling interest rates and economic growth.  “This channel of strong enough growth – but not too strong – and lower or declining rates are two big macro forces that can push small caps higher,” said Sebastien Page, chief investment officer at T Rowe Price, which manages nearly $1.8 trillion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-bets-rally-riskiest-103000857.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] UK regulator proposes changes to Google search for publishers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-regulator-proposes-changes-google-102256121.html</link><description>LONDON, Jan 28 () - Britain's competition regulator on Wednesday proposed a package ​of measures that it said would ‌improve Google search services in the country, including making ‌sure publishers get a fairer deal over how their content is used in the engine's AI overviews. Google said in response it was "exploring" ⁠updates to ‌its controls to let sites specifically opt out of search generative ‍AI features.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-regulator-proposes-changes-google-102256121.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Intel, Micron and These Other Chip Stocks Are Rallying. Thank Texas Instruments and ASML.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-micron-texas-instruments-asml-7c977c33?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Chip makers’ shares rally after a solid batch of earnings report signal that the AI boom is still driving up demand for semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-micron-texas-instruments-asml-7c977c33?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Strong iPhone sales to power Apple's holiday quarter, Google AI deal in focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-iphone-sales-power-apples-102033119.html</link><description>By Akash Sriram Jan 28 (Reuters) - Apple is set to report its strongest iPhone sales growth in four years on Thursday, driven by robust demand for its premium Pro models as it prepares to roll out</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/strong-iphone-sales-power-apples-102033119.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Bull of the Day: Lam Research (LRCX)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-lam-research-lrcx-102000424.html</link><description>Analysts have been behind the growth and valuation curves as TSM and MU signal WFE expansion into 2029</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bull-day-lam-research-lrcx-102000424.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] EC initiates steps for Google’s compliance with Digital Markets Act</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/ec-google-compliance-digital-markets-act/</link><description>The proceedings are part of EC’s efforts to address Google's compliance issues involving Android and online search data sharing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/ec-google-compliance-digital-markets-act/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks to Watch Wednesday: Nvidia, SoftBank, Alibaba</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-nvidia-softbank-YxSGpJ6KdlVJN9dpU0EI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↗️ Nvidia (NVDA): China has approved purchases of Nvidia’s popular H200 chip for the first time, giving authorization to several customers, including Alibaba (BABA, HK:9988). Nvidia shares rose in premarket trading, as did Alibaba's stock in Hong Kong.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-nvidia-softbank-YxSGpJ6KdlVJN9dpU0EI?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Earnings in Focus Wednesday: ASML, GE Vernova, Meta</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/earnings-in-focus-wednesday-asml-ge-vernova-meta-ijXuh4m4ohBvRlVyh7lQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full swing, with 102 companies in the benchmark S&amp;amp;P 500 index reporting this week, according to LSEG. Microsoft, Meta Platforms and Tesla are among the companies due to report today.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/earnings-in-focus-wednesday-asml-ge-vernova-meta-ijXuh4m4ohBvRlVyh7lQ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Rebrand Highlights AI Deals With Microsoft And Meta, Valuation Questions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-rebrand-highlights-ai-deals-100833339.html</link><description>Nebius Group, now trading as NasdaqGS:NBIS, has rebranded from Yandex and is repositioning itself as a dedicated AI infrastructure provider. The company has signed long term AI infrastructure agreements with Microsoft and Meta Platforms, signaling deeper involvement in large scale cloud and AI workloads. Nebius plans an international rollout of Nvidia’s next generation Rubin platform to serve rising demand for AI compute capacity. Nebius Group focuses on providing AI infrastructure,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-rebrand-highlights-ai-deals-100833339.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SoftBank in discussions for up to $30bn additional investment in OpenAI</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/softbank-additional-investment-openai/</link><description>SoftBank’s latest talks form part of a wider funding round that could significantly boost OpenAI’s valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/softbank-additional-investment-openai/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Weekly: EU targets Grok, Nvidia waves off AI bubble fears</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-weekly-eu-targets-grok-095535737.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: From the EU investigating Grok to Jensen Huang waving off AI bubble fears, this is AI Weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: AI Weekly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Commission launched an investigation into Grok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's looking at whether Elon Musk's AI chatbot spreads illegal content in the EU, including manipulated sexualised images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will see&amp;amp;nbsp;whether X properly assessed and lowered risks related to Grok's functionalities in the bloc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;X referred to a statement issued earlier this month where it said xAI had restricted image editing for Grok AI users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia boss Jensen Huang waved off fears about an AI bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And he encouraged everybody to get involved with the technology during a talk at the World Economic Forum in Davos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The AI bubble comes about because the investments are large. And the investments are large because we have to build the infrastructure necessary for all of the layers of AI above it. And so I think the opportunity is really quite extraordinary. And everybody ought to get involved."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also pushed back on concerns about AI taking human jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And instead said it will create lots of jobs, especially for those in trades like plumbing and construction.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intel shares plunged towards the end of last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors sold off after the company struggled to meet strong AI demand for data center chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It blamed that on supply constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm is a latecomer to the AI boom and had finally enjoyed a demand surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung aims to start production of its next-gen high-bandwidth memory chips - or HBM4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's what a source told Reuters, who added the South Korean firm plans to supply them to Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has tried to catch up with local rival SK Hynix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is a key supplier for advanced memory chips crucial for Nvidia's AI accelerators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Microsoft unveiled its second generation of in-house AI chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It took aim at one of Nvidia's main competitive advantages with developers.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new 'Maia 200' semiconductor comes online this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It comes as major cloud computing firms like Microsoft, Amazon and Google produce their own chips - which are increasingly competing&amp;amp;nbsp;with Nvidia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-weekly-eu-targets-grok-095535737.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix Profit Surges on Relentless Appetite for AI Memory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-profit-surges-relentless-075846431.html</link><description>Icheon-based SK Hynix also announced it will establish an AI data center solutions firm in the US, backed by $10 billion of capital, to pursue partnerships and investments in the sector.  The new company will operate out of a restructured Solidigm, the storage company SK Hynix acquired from Intel Corp., according to a statement.  Shares in SK Hynix, the leading supplier of high-bandwidth memory or HBM for Nvidia Corp.’s AI accelerators, have roughly tripled since the start of September.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-profit-surges-relentless-075846431.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Trending tickers: Nvidia, ASML, Texas Instruments, LVMH and Fresnillo</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-asml-texas-instruments-lvmh-fresnillo-trending-tickers-093532079.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-asml-texas-instruments-lvmh-fresnillo-trending-tickers-093532079.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] My Prediction For Nvidia Stock in 2025 Came True. Here's What I Expect to Happen Next.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/my-prediction-for-nvidia-stock-in-2025-came-true-h/</link><description>Nvidia has wowed investors with its growth during this AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/my-prediction-for-nvidia-stock-in-2025-came-true-h/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is AI Superstar Palantir Technologies Going to Plunge in 2026? History Offers 2 Undeniable Clues.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/ai-palantir-going-to-plunge-2026-history-2-clues/</link><description>When things seem too good to be true for Wall Street's hottest artificial intelligence (AI) stock, they often are.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/ai-palantir-going-to-plunge-2026-history-2-clues/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML made record $11.5 billion profit in 2025 thanks to AI-driven demand, plans to cut 1,700 jobs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-made-record-11-5-091520740.html</link><description>Dutch semiconductor chip machine maker ASML recorded a record net profit of 9.6 billion euros ($11.5 billion) in 2025 on sales of 32.7 billion euros fueled by AI-driven demand, the company reported Wednesday as it also announced plans to slash its workforce by about 1,700, about 4% of its workforce.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-made-record-11-5-091520740.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Expands AI Education And Patents As Enterprise Use Cases Grow</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-expands-ai-education-patents-091233373.html</link><description>IBM is expanding its role in AI education through a UK government partnership aimed at upskilling millions of workers in AI related skills. The company is taking a leadership role in open source patent protection via the updated Open Invention Network 2.0 framework. IBM is rolling out new AI products, including agentic AI tools for enterprise compliance and fan engagement platforms used at events like the Grammys. For investors tracking International Business Machines, NYSE:IBM, the current...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-expands-ai-education-patents-091233373.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Forget Intel: This Agile Chip Challenger Looks Far Better Positioned for the Next Wave of AI Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-intel-this-agile-chip-challenger-looks-far/</link><description>Intel could resume its turnaround. However, AMD appears to be the better pick for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/forget-intel-this-agile-chip-challenger-looks-far/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] KeyBanc Sees Inflection Point for Alight (ALIT) After Volatile Year in Healthcare IT</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-sees-inflection-point-alight-085555070.html</link><description>Alight, Inc. (NYSE:ALIT) is included among the 13 Dividend Stocks with Over 8% Yield. On January 8, KeyBanc slashed its price target on Alight, Inc. (NYSE:ALIT) to $2.50 from $6, while sticking with an Overweight rating. After a rough and uneven year for healthcare IT stocks, the firm said the fundamentals tell a more encouraging […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-sees-inflection-point-alight-085555070.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Tech Stocks Rally Ahead of Fed Rate Call. Dollar Falls After Trump Rout.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-012826/card/tech-stocks-rally-ahead-of-fed-rate-call-dollar-falls-after-trump-rout--wUedUz6abaN5GNhsAPFV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks looked set to extend their record-breaking run on Wednesday following earnings reports from two chip companies, while the dollar looked set to carry on sliding after comments from President Donald Trump sparked a brutal selloff for the greenback.  The tech-heavy index was racking up gains after semiconductor manufacturer Texas Instruments and chip tool maker ASML both issued solid guidance, which investors took as a sign that the artificial-intelligence boom still has legs.  The Federal Reserve is also set to make its latest policy decision–the central bank is widely expected to keep interest rates unchanged, but Chair Jerome Powell’s comments could give the market a better idea of whether there’ll be scope for cuts to borrowing costs later in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-012826/card/tech-stocks-rally-ahead-of-fed-rate-call-dollar-falls-after-trump-rout--wUedUz6abaN5GNhsAPFV?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates Models on AllianceBernstein (AB) as Fund Flows Remain Weak</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-models-alliancebernstein-ab-085330523.html</link><description>AllianceBernstein Holding L.P. (NYSE:AB) is included among the 13 Dividend Stocks with Over 8% Yield. On January 15, Barclays cut its price target on AllianceBernstein Holding L.P. (NYSE:AB) to $39 from $42. The firm maintained an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change followed an update to the firm’s asset manager models, which now […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-models-alliancebernstein-ab-085330523.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Exclusive-China gives nod to ByteDance, Alibaba and Tencent to buy Nvidia's H200 chips - sources</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</link><description>Jan 28 () - China has given the green light to three of its largest tech companies to buy Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips, four people familiar with the matter told , marking a shift in position as Beijing ​seeks to balance its AI needs against spurring domestic development. ByteDance, Alibaba and Tencent have been approved to purchase more than ‌400,000 H200 chips in total, with other firms now joining a queue for subsequent approvals, the sources said, speaking on condition of anon</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Looking at 'Record Quarter,' CEO Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-looking-record-quarter-ceo-082924056.html</link><description>ASML Chief Executive Officer Christophe Fouquet discusses the company's performance in the fourth quarter as orders far exceeded analysts' expectations. "We're looking at a record quarter, we're looking at a record year," Fouquet tells Bloomberg Television.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/asml-looking-record-quarter-ceo-082924056.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Meta Earnings, Fed Decision, Venezuela Testimony: Still to Come This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-still-to-come-this-week-Iqs58QMElx48WGUCtczJ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season is in full throttle, with results expected from a quartet of tech giants—Apple, Meta Platforms, Microsoft and Tesla. In Washington, the Federal Reserve will announce its first interest-rate decision of 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/fed-interest-rate-decision-01-28-2026/card/meta-earnings-fed-decision-venezuela-testimony-still-to-come-this-week-Iqs58QMElx48WGUCtczJ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix Caps Off Bumper Year With Record Quarter</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/sk-hynix-caps-off-bumper-year-with-record-quarter-866c37fc?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The memory chip maker posted record earnings for the final quarter of 2025 as the global artificial-intelligence boom continued to fuel strong demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/sk-hynix-caps-off-bumper-year-with-record-quarter-866c37fc?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia’s CoreWeave Bet Balances AI Growth Ambitions With Legal Scrutiny</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-coreweave-bet-balances-ai-081237980.html</link><description>Nvidia announced a US$2 billion investment in CoreWeave (NasdaqGS:CRWV), together with an expanded commercial partnership. CoreWeave is set to deepen its role as an infrastructure provider for Nvidia powered AI workloads. Multiple class action lawsuits have been filed alleging misrepresentations about CoreWeave's ability to scale infrastructure and meet customer demand. The combination of fresh capital, closer collaboration with Nvidia, and legal claims about prior disclosures has drawn...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-coreweave-bet-balances-ai-081237980.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Deepens AI Factory Push With CoreWeave Healthcare And Education Ties</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-deepens-ai-factory-push-081126978.html</link><description>Nvidia (NasdaqGS:NVDA) is investing an additional US$2b in CoreWeave to support the buildout of more than 5 gigawatts of AI data center capacity by 2030. The expanded partnership centers on large scale AI infrastructure, sometimes described as AI "factories," aimed at serving rising demand for compute power. Nvidia also announced collaborations with BoodleBox in education and Oath Surgical in healthcare, integrating its AI platforms into learning and surgical workflows. The developments...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-deepens-ai-factory-push-081126978.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China clears first NVIDIA H200 AI chips for import: sources</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/china-clears-first-nvidia-h200-081042104.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: China has approved its first batch of Nvidia’s H200 artificial intelligence chips for import.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to Reuters sources familiar with the matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a notable shift as Beijing tries to balance its AI development needs with support for its domestic semiconductor industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: File&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The approval covers several hundred thousand H200 chips and was granted during Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang’s visit to China this week, according to the sources, who requested anonymity due to the sensitivity of the matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two said the semiconductors would go to tech giants ByteDance, Alibaba and Tencent, with more firms waiting in line for future approvals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of the firms involved immediately responded to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The H200 is Nvidia’s second most powerful AI chip and a key flashpoint in U.S.-China relations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington has cleared it for export, but Beijing's hesitation to allow imports has been the main barrier to shipments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese firms have already ordered over two million H200 chips, far beyond Nvidia’s available inventory, and&amp;amp;nbsp;while domestic alternatives such as Huawei are improving, they still lag well behind the H200’s performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear how many additional approvals Beijing will grant as it weighs access to foreign chips against long‑term tech self‑reliance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/china-clears-first-nvidia-h200-081042104.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC’s US$56b AI Capex Push Tests Valuation And Growth Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-us-56b-ai-capex-080954371.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (NYSE:TSM) plans up to $56b in capital expenditures to expand chip manufacturing capacity, focused on AI chips. The company has opened a new U.S. plant and signed a major deal to further build out its U.S. footprint. These moves highlight TSMC’s role in AI chip production and ongoing shifts in the global semiconductor supply chain. For investors watching NYSE:TSM, this spending plan comes with the stock at $338.34 and trailing returns that include 68.9%...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-us-56b-ai-capex-080954371.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML’s Record Orders Smash Estimates as AI Spurs Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-record-orders-smash-estimates-080755988.html</link><description>Bookings in the fourth quarter were a record €13.2 billion ($15.8 billion), driven by demand for its most sophisticated equipment, the Veldhoven, Netherlands-based company said in a statement on Wednesday.  ASML is the only producer of cutting-edge lithography machines that are needed to make advanced semiconductors, and counts all the leading chip manufacturers as customers, including Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corp. and Intel Corp. Its machinery is integral to producing the Nvidia Corp. AI accelerators that are the backbone for training and running AI models in data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-record-orders-smash-estimates-080755988.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix vs. Alphabet Stock: Which Is the Better Growth Stock to Buy and Hold for the Next 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/netflix-vs-alphabet-stock-which-is-the-better-grow/</link><description>Both stocks are growing at similar rates and are trading at similar valuations, but one is still the clear winner when comparing the two.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/netflix-vs-alphabet-stock-which-is-the-better-grow/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Drives Q4 Gains as Pharma Fundamentals Shine Amid Sector Rotation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-drives-q4-080519997.html</link><description>Polen Capital Management Llc released its “Polen Focus Growth Strategy” Q4 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. In Q4 2025, the Polen Focus Growth strategy delivered a -1.37% gross return, underperforming the Russell 1000 Growth Index (+1.12%) and the S&amp;amp;P 500 (+2.66%), as concentrated mega‑cap leadership and AI valuation […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-drives-q4-080519997.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Earnings Are Coming. Watch the Software Business.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/ibm-earnings-stock-price-d02d2add?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>IBM reports after the close Wednesday. Analysts expect software to drive results and provide support for the stock after a strong 12-month rally.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/ibm-earnings-stock-price-d02d2add?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Zacks Analyst Blog Oracle's, Amazon and Alphabet</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-oracles-amazon-075600750.html</link><description>Oracle is ramping cloud CapEx to nearly $50B, betting GPU infrastructure and AI demand will fuel faster revenue growth starting fiscal 2027.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-oracles-amazon-075600750.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SK Hynix posts record quarterly profit on huge AI demand, trounces expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-posts-forecast-beating-074143710.html</link><description>South Korea's SK Hynix said on Wednesday that quarterly profit more than doubled ​to a record, comfortably beating forecasts on relentless ‌demand for artificial intelligence that has lifted prices for both advanced and ‌conventional memory chips.  The Nvidia supplier logged a 137% surge in operating profit to 19.2 trillion won ($13.5 billion) for the fourth quarter, according to Reuters calculations.  That compared with 8.1 trillion ⁠won a year earlier ‌and a 17.7 trillion won consensus prediction from LSEG SmartEstimate, which is weighted toward analysts ‍with a more consistent track record.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sk-hynix-posts-forecast-beating-074143710.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Will Crush the Market in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-ai-stock-will-crush-the-market-in-2026/</link><description>Microsoft released its in-house chip that will directly compete with Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/this-ai-stock-will-crush-the-market-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML: Q4 Earnings Snapshot</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-earnings-snapshot-071658583.html</link><description>DR VELDHOVEN, Netherlands (AP) — ASML Holding NV (ASML) on Wednesday reported fourth-quarter profit of $3.31 billion. On a per-share basis, the Dr Veldhoven, Netherlands-based company said it had profit of $8.55. The results fell short of Wall Street expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-earnings-snapshot-071658583.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Q4 Earnings Call Highlights</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/asml-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>ASML (NASDAQ:ASML) reported Q4 2025 net revenue of EUR 9.7 billion, a record quarter that included the recognition of revenue for two High-NA systems. For the full year 2025, the company reported revenue of EUR 32.7 billion, representing a 16% increase compared to 2024. Management said the quarter</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/asml-q4-earnings-call-highlights-2026-01-28/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SoftBank in talks to invest up to $30 billion more in OpenAI: source</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-065842056.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: SoftBank could be ramping up its bet on OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese firm is in talks to pour as much as $30 billion more into the ChatGPT owner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person familiar with the matter said that the money would be part of a funding round that could raise up to $100 billion, valuing OpenAI at about $830 billion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CEO Masayoshi Son has made what he calls an “all‑in” bet on OpenAI as it seeks to improve its position in the artificial intelligence race.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In December, the company said it had completed a $41 billion investment, giving it an 11% stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI is facing rising costs to train and run its AI models as the race against Google intensifies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SoftBank declined to comment, though its shares were up 3.5% in Tokyo morning trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters reported last month that Son had scrambled to gather funds for the earlier investment, slowing dealmaking at the company's Vision Fund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both OpenAI and SoftBank are backing Stargate, a $500 billion initiative to build AI data centers for training and inference that executives say is key to the U.S. government's ambitions to keep ahead of China in AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-065842056.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] ASML Ends 2025 With Record Orders as AI Spending Remains Healthy</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The company logged record quarterly orders of its semiconductor-making equipment and said it expects healthy sales growth this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/earnings/asml-ends-2025-with-record-orders-as-ai-spending-remains-healthy-802421ff?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Dutch tech giant ASML posts bumper profits, eyes bright AI future</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dutch-tech-giant-asml-posts-063125401.html</link><description>Dutch tech giant ASML, which sells cutting-edge machines to make semiconductor chips, reported a significant gain in annual net profit Wednesday and predicted a bright future driven by demand for artificial intelligence.In a case unrelated to ASML, the Dutch government briefly seized control of Nexperia, a Chinese-owned company that makes low-tech semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dutch-tech-giant-asml-posts-063125401.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] ASML Q4 bookings beat expectations as chipmakers order more to satisfy AI demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-bookings-beat-expectations-061654428.html</link><description>ASML reported stronger-than-expected bookings on Wednesday as the world's largest supplier of computer chip equipment received ​more orders thanks to larger investments in artificial-intelligence chipmaking capacity.  Fourth-quarter ‌bookings, the most watched metric in the industry, were 13.2 billion euros ($15.8 billion), ‌compared with 5.4 billion euros in the previous quarter.  "In the last months, many of our customers have shared a notably more ⁠positive assessment of the ‌medium-term market situation, primarily based on more robust expectations of the sustainability of AI-related demand," ASML's Chief ‍executive Christophe Fouquet said in a statement.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-q4-bookings-beat-expectations-061654428.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should Rising Social Engineering Against Okta (OKTA) Identities Require Action From Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rising-social-engineering-against-okta-061325778.html</link><description>In recent days, Okta and external researchers have detailed a wave of sophisticated social engineering campaigns, including custom phishing-as-a-service kits and voice-phishing attacks, aimed at stealing single sign-on credentials and bypassing multi-factor authentication across Okta, Google, and Microsoft environments. Although these incidents are not rooted in product vulnerabilities, they spotlight how attackers increasingly exploit human behavior and real-time MFA interception,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rising-social-engineering-against-okta-061325778.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Best Artificial Intelligence (AI) Data Center Play You've Never Heard of for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-best-artificial-intelligence-ai-data-center-pl/</link><description>Microsoft and Google are trusting this company to ensure their data centers stay up and running.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-best-artificial-intelligence-ai-data-center-pl/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Top 3 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Chip Stocks to Buy With $50,000 in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-top-3-artificial-intelligence-ai-chip-stocks-t/</link><description>Semiconductor stocks look poised for further gains as investment in artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure accelerates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/28/the-top-3-artificial-intelligence-ai-chip-stocks-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Explainer-The $250 million ASML 'printer' behind Nvidia's chips</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/explainer-250-million-asml-printer-050227041.html</link><description>AMSTERDAM, Jan 28 (Reuters) - ASML has become Europe's most valuable company thanks to its dominance in making lithography systems, huge "chip printing" machines that cost $250 million each and are</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/explainer-250-million-asml-printer-050227041.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:05:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] 1 Surging  Stock Worth Your Attention and 2 We Turn Down</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-surging-stock-worth-attention-043540984.html</link><description>Great things are happening to the stocks in this article. They’re all outperforming the market over the last month because of positive catalysts such as a new product line, constructive news flow, or even a loyal Reddit fanbase.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-surging-stock-worth-attention-043540984.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] 3 Market-Beating Stocks with Competitive Advantages</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-market-beating-stocks-competitive-043359713.html</link><description>Stocks that outperform the market usually share key traits such as rising sales, expanding margins, and increasing returns on capital. The select few that can do all three for many years are often the ones that make you life-changing money.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-market-beating-stocks-competitive-043359713.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] 2 Volatile Stocks with Competitive Advantages and 1 We Ignore</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-volatile-stocks-competitive-advantages-043320379.html</link><description>Volatility cuts both ways - while it creates opportunities, it also increases risk, making sharp declines just as likely as big gains. This unpredictability can shake out even the most experienced investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-volatile-stocks-competitive-advantages-043320379.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Assessing HSBC (LSE:HSBA) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-hsbc-lse-hsba-valuation-043302005.html</link><description>Event context and recent performance snapshot HSBC Holdings (LSE:HSBA) has been drawing attention after a period of strong recent returns, with the share price moving higher over the past week, month and past 3 months. See our latest analysis for HSBC Holdings. Zooming out, HSBC Holdings’ recent momentum sits on top of a 1-year total shareholder return of 63.45% and a 5-year total shareholder return above 3x. The latest £12.772 share price reflects strong shorter term share price returns that...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-hsbc-lse-hsba-valuation-043302005.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Exclusive-China gives green light to importing first batch of Nvidia's H200 AI chips, sources say</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</link><description>Jan 28 (Reuters) - China has approved its first batch of Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips for import, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters, marking a shift in position as China</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-china-gives-green-light-034839096.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Top Valuation Expert Says AI Market Needs 'Trillions In Revenue' To Justify Valuations After Cashing Out Of Its Biggest Chipmaker</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-valuation-expert-says-ai-033111714.html</link><description>Aswath Damodaran, the ‘Dean of Valuation,’ has issued a stark warning to AI investors that the math simply does not add up. Citing a massive disconnect between upfront infrastructure spending and future earnings, the NYU finance professor revealed he has fully exited his position in Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA) while maintaining his stake in Microsoft Corp. (NASDAQ:MSFT). The ‘Big Market Delusion’ Damodaran argues that the current AI frenzy exhibits classic signs of a “Big Market Delusion,” a cycl</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-valuation-expert-says-ai-033111714.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Forget AI Stocks: This Energy Infrastructure Stock Is the Smarter Bet</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-ai-stocks-this-energy-infrastructure-stock/</link><description>Looking for a hedge against any AI bubble that may or may not be forming? Centrus Energy is a good choice.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-ai-stocks-this-energy-infrastructure-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] What To Expect From Caterpillar’s (CAT) Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/expect-caterpillar-cat-q4-earnings-031246311.html</link><description>Construction equipment company Caterpillar (NYSE:CAT) will be reporting results this Thursday before market hours. Here’s what to expect.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/expect-caterpillar-cat-q4-earnings-031246311.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA Corporation Earnings: What To Look For From KLAC</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-earnings-look-klac-031118827.html</link><description>Semiconductor manufacturing equipment maker KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) will be announcing earnings results this Thursday after market hours. Here’s what to expect.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-corporation-earnings-look-klac-031118827.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Infrastructure Stock Will Be the Biggest Beneficiary of OpenAI's Growth by End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/prediction-this-ai-infrastructure-stock-will-be-th/</link><description>CoreWeave has a lot to gain from OpenAI's growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/prediction-this-ai-infrastructure-stock-will-be-th/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Prediction for Nvidia in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/1-prediction-for-nvidia-in-2026/</link><description>Market watchers are expecting $65 billion in Q4 revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/1-prediction-for-nvidia-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Osborne Partners Buys Another $4 Million Worth of MercadoLibre Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/27/osborne-partners-buys-another-usd4-million-worth-of-mercadolibre-stock/</link><description>MercadoLibre is a leading Latin American e-commerce and fintech platform, linking merchants and consumers through digital services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/27/osborne-partners-buys-another-usd4-million-worth-of-mercadolibre-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] SoftBank in talks to invest up to $30 billion more in OpenAI, source says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-004740741.html</link><description>SoftBank Group Corp is in talks to invest as much as an additional $30 ​billion in OpenAI, a person familiar with the ‌matter said on Tuesday, as the Japanese conglomerate doubles down on its bet ‌on the ChatGPT owner.  The fresh investment would form part of a funding round that could raise up to $100 billion for OpenAI, valuing it at about $830 billion, the person said.  Seeking to improve SoftBank's position in the artificial intelligence race, ‍Chief Executive Masayoshi Son has made an "all-in" bet on OpenAI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-talks-invest-30-billion-004740741.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] SoftBank in Talks to Invest Up to $30 Billion More in OpenAI</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/softbank-in-talks-to-invest-up-to-30-billion-more-in-openai-8585dea3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Japanese conglomerate is exploring a further investment as part of the startup’s efforts to raise up to $100 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/softbank-in-talks-to-invest-up-to-30-billion-more-in-openai-8585dea3?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wall Street Thinks This AI Stock Is the Next Big Thing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/wall-street-thinks-this-ai-stock-is-the-next-big-t/</link><description>While AI chip stocks continue to garner outsize attention, smart analysts are looking elsewhere for growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/wall-street-thinks-this-ai-stock-is-the-next-big-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Did Applied Digital Stock Jump 14.3% Today?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-did-applied-digital-stock-jump-143-today/</link><description>Nvidia just bought $2 billion worth of CoreWeave stock. Here's why it matters for Applied Digital.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/why-did-applied-digital-stock-jump-143-today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures rise as Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353507.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353507.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise as Wall Street braces for Fed decision, Big Tech earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353801.html</link><description>The Fed's rate decision and 'Magnificent Seven' earnings from Microsoft, Meta, and Tesla are in focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-as-wall-street-braces-for-fed-decision-big-tech-earnings-233353801.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Just Gave You a $2 Billion Reason to Buy CoreWeave Stock</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37261483/nvidia-just-gave-you-a-2-billion-reason-to-buy-coreweave-stock</link><description>Nvidia’s $2 billion strategic investment in CoreWeave is a powerful endorsement of its AI infrastructure model, making CRWV a compelling stock to buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37261483/nvidia-just-gave-you-a-2-billion-reason-to-buy-coreweave-stock</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 27: Nvidia’s $2 Billion Bet Lifts CoreWeave and Refocuses the AI Infrastructure Trade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/27/stock-market-today-jan-27-coreweave-surges-after-nvidia-invests-2-billion/</link><description>CoreWeave rallied as Nvidia deepened its commitment to AI data center capacity, highlighting both the growth opportunity and the operational hurdles ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/27/stock-market-today-jan-27-coreweave-surges-after-nvidia-invests-2-billion/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] UK rolls out free AI training, but will it save your job?</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rolls-free-ai-training-230200819.html</link><description>Free artificial intelligence training is being made available to everyone in the UK as the government steps up efforts to prepare the workforce for rapid technological change.  From today, adults can access short, practical courses through the government's upgraded AI Skills Hub, designed to help people use AI tools in the workplace.  The training covers everyday tasks such as drafting text, creating content, and automating administrative work - with some courses taking less than 20 minutes to complete.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-rolls-free-ai-training-230200819.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Futures: Stock Market Hits Highs; Tesla, Meta, Microsoft, Fed's Powell On Tap</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-meta-microsoft-fed-chief-powell/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Many stocks made bullish moves as the Nasdaq led and the S&amp;amp;P 500 hit a high, but Tesla, Microsoft, Meta and Fed's Powell loom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-meta-microsoft-fed-chief-powell/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Exceeds Market Returns: Some Facts to Consider</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-exceeds-market-224505205.html</link><description>In the latest trading session, CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) closed at $476.66, marking a +1.78% move from the previous day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-exceeds-market-224505205.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Laps the Stock Market: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-laps-stock-market-224504706.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw Nvidia (NVDA) settling at $188.52, representing a +1.1% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-laps-stock-market-224504706.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Systems (CSCO) Rises Higher Than Market: Key Facts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-rises-higher-224502702.html</link><description>Cisco Systems (CSCO) reached $78.68 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +2.17% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-rises-higher-224502702.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Berkshire Hathaway Will Lose Its Biggest Mutual-Fund Fan With Danoff’s Retirement</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-danoff-fidelity-44b3feb1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The mutual-fund industry will lose its biggest fan of  Berkshire Hathaway  with the retirement of Fidelity Contrafund manager Will Danoff at the end of 2026 after 35 years at its helm.  Danoff’s $176 billion fund probably was the single largest holder of Berkshire among actively managed mutual funds.  Contrafund’s stake in Berkshire is now worth about $10 billion, Barron’s calculates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-danoff-fidelity-44b3feb1?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Forget Nebius Group: This Hyper-Growth Cloud Platform Is a Far Better Way to Play the AI Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-nebius-group-this-hyper-growth-cloud-platfo/</link><description>DigitalOcean offers more stable growth with higher profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/forget-nebius-group-this-hyper-growth-cloud-platfo/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Best Stocks to Invest $2,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/the-best-stocks-to-invest-2000-right-now/</link><description>These companies are cashing in on how people are using AI every day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/27/the-best-stocks-to-invest-2000-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Trading Day: Extreme bifurcation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trading-day-extreme-bifurcation-220647090.html</link><description>ORLANDO, Florida, Jan 27 () - World stocks and the S&amp;amp;P; 500 hit new highs on Tuesday, boosted by a flood of strong U. earnings reports, while anxiety over U.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trading-day-extreme-bifurcation-220647090.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>