<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:30:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[GOOG] Cathie Wood Invest Dumps Over $10 Million Of Palantir Stock Amid Talk Of 'Cramer Curse' — Buys This Hot AI Stock Instead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-invest-dumps-over-203125995.html</link><description>On Thursday, Cathie Wood-led Ark Invest made significant trades involving Palantir Technologies Inc. (NASDAQ:PLTR), Broadcom Inc. (NASDAQ:AVGO), and Joby Aviation Inc. (NYSE:JOBY). These trades reflect Ark’s strategic positioning in the market amidst evolving geopolitical and technological landscapes. The Palantir Trade Ark Invest made a notable move by selling 58,741 shares of Palantir. through its ARK Next Generation Internet ETF (BATS: ARKW). The transaction, valued at approximately $10.4 mil</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-invest-dumps-over-203125995.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is It Too Late To Consider ASML Holding (NasdaqGS:ASML) After Its Strong Share Price Run?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-200803546.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether ASML Holding's share price still makes sense after its strong run, you are not alone, and valuation is the key question. The stock last closed at US$1,273.88, with returns of 9.5% over 7 days, 13.8% over 30 days, 9.5% year to date, 73.8% over 1 year, 97.6% over 3 years and 150.9% over 5 years. Recent attention on semiconductor equipment companies has kept ASML in focus, as investors weigh long term demand for advanced chip manufacturing tools. At the same time,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-asml-holding-nasdaqgs-200803546.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Berenberg Bank Remains Bullish on AstraZeneca PLC (AZN) – Here’s Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berenberg-bank-remains-bullish-astrazeneca-195715465.html</link><description>AstraZeneca PLC (NASDAQ:AZN) is one of the best performing pharma stocks in 2025. On January 7, Berenberg Bank reiterated a Buy rating on AstraZeneca PLC (NASDAQ:AZN) with a price target of $95. The rating update came after AstraZeneca PLC (NASDAQ:AZN) announced positive full results from the Phase III TULIP-SC trial on December 6, reporting that […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berenberg-bank-remains-bullish-astrazeneca-195715465.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly and Company (LLY) to Acquire Ventyx Biosciences</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-acquire-195713266.html</link><description>Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) is one of the best performing pharma stocks in 2025. Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) announced on January 7 that it entered into a definitive agreement to acquire Ventyx Biosciences, Inc., which is a clinical-stage biopharmaceutical company that develops innovative oral therapies for patients with inflammatory-mediated diseases. Ventyx Biosciences, Inc. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-company-lly-acquire-195713266.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on Procter &amp; Gamble: “It Has the Opportunity to Shake Things Up”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-procter-gamble-opportunity-195641824.html</link><description>The Procter &amp;amp; Gamble Company (NYSE:PG) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. During the episode, Cramer noted that it is one of the few consumer packaged goods companies that “doesn’t have a GLP-1 problem,” as he said: “I can go over how NVIDIA or Broadcom are down huge too much, and they’re […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-procter-gamble-opportunity-195641824.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Jim Cramer Discusses CrowdStrike After Jensen Huang’s Endorsement</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-crowdstrike-jensen-195638777.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Cramer said that he was surprised to see the stock fall notably from November highs, as he commented: “Take my morning show, Squawk on the Street. Today, my co-host, Carl Quintanilla, turned to me and asked what looked interesting after so many […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-crowdstrike-jensen-195638777.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Want to Invest in Quantum Computing? These 3 Stocks Are Great Buys Right Now.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/want-to-invest-in-quantum-computing-these-3-stocks/</link><description>Investing in the pure-play start-ups is not the only way to gain exposure to this nascent technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/want-to-invest-in-quantum-computing-these-3-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Vistra Wins Mega Nuclear Deal With Meta, Stock Jumps</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vistra-wins-mega-nuclear-deal-193153850.html</link><description>Vistra Corp. (NYSE:VST) stock rose Friday after the company disclosed a 20-year power purchase agreement (PPAs) with Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META). Details The deal involves supplying over 2,600 MW of zero-carbon power from three nuclear plants to support Meta's regional operations. In particular, Meta will purchase 2,176 MW of nuclear energy from Vistra's operating Perry and Davis-Besse plants in Ohio, along with an additional 433 MW of capacity from uprates at Perry, Davis-Besse, and Beav</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vistra-wins-mega-nuclear-deal-193153850.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Jim Cramer on Nebius: “The Opportunities Are Better Elsewhere”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-nebius-opportunities-better-192436078.html</link><description>Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. A caller inquired about Cramer’s thoughts on the company in the “year of practical investing.” In response, Cramer commented: “Well, I’ll tell you, a younger person came to me, asked me about stocks that were losing money the other night… And I […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-nebius-opportunities-better-192436078.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Jim Cramer on Palo Alto: “I Think It Is a Buy”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-palo-alto-think-192434508.html</link><description>Palo Alto Networks, Inc. (NASDAQ:PANW) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. Answering a caller’s query about the stock during the lightning round, Cramer said: “I think that Nikesh Arora does a great job. I slighted him too much. I said so many good things about CrowdStrike earlier. Palo Alto’s a terrific company […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-palo-alto-think-192434508.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This ETF Is the Simplest Path to $1 Million in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/this-etf-is-the-simplest-path-to-1-million-in-2026/</link><description>You don't need to be a stock market genius to build a million-dollar portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/this-etf-is-the-simplest-path-to-1-million-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Sam Altman Weighs An $830B–$1T IPO And Admits Running A Public Company Could Be 'Really Annoying'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sam-altman-weighs-830b-1t-190109072.html</link><description>A potential mega IPO is coming into focus, but enthusiasm for life as a public-company CEO appears limited. "Am I excited to be a public company CEO? 0%," OpenAI CEO Sam Altman said on the "Big Technology Podcast." "Am I excited for OpenAI to be a public company? In some ways, I am, and in some ways I think it'd be really annoying." He told host Alex Kantrowitz that while public markets can play a role in value creation, leading a public company comes with trade-offs he does not find appealing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sam-altman-weighs-830b-1t-190109072.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] AI's Next Bottleneck Isn't Hardware -- It's Efficiency. Here's the Stock to Watch.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/ais-next-bottleneck-isnt-hardware-its-efficiency-h/</link><description>Vertiv is playing a crucial role in managing AI data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/ais-next-bottleneck-isnt-hardware-its-efficiency-h/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Top Artificial Intelligence Stocks to Buy in January</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/3-top-artificial-intelligence-stocks-to-buy-in-jan/</link><description>The artificial intelligence ASICs market is heating up, and it's time to buy some top stocks in this field in January.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/3-top-artificial-intelligence-stocks-to-buy-in-jan/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump's 'Carrot And Stick' Defense Push: Which Stock Is Best Priced For $1.5 Trillion Budget?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-carrot-stick-defense-push-173121540.html</link><description>President Donald Trump may have grabbed headlines with buyback threats and a proposed $1.5 trillion defense budget, but for investors, the real question is simpler: which defense stock actually looks best priced if spending really accelerates? With policy noise largely digested, valuation is now doing the talking for Lockheed Martin Corp (NYSE:LMT), Rtx Corp (NYSE:RTX), and Northrop Grumman Corp (NYSE:NOC). Lockheed Martin: Execution Is Already Priced In Lockheed trades at a market cap of about</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-carrot-stick-defense-push-173121540.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Dumped Nvidia and Bought This Other Magnificent Stock Instead -- Even as Warren Buffett Was Selling It Before Retiring</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-dumped-nvidia-and/</link><description>Peter Thiel's hedge fund recently exited his entire stake in Nvidia stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/palantir-billionaire-peter-thiel-dumped-nvidia-and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bank Of America's Top 3 Commodity Stock Picks For 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bank-americas-top-3-commodity-160112290.html</link><description>Bank of America’s 2026 message for commodity investors is clear: stick with gold, don't miss uranium's rally and buy copper before the market fully reprices it. In a note shared Wednesday to clients, the firm’s commodity analyst Lawson Winder named three companies: Agnico Eagle Mines Ltd. (NYSE:AEM) as the preferred precious-metals name Cameco Corp. (NYSE:CCJ) as the top nuclear fuel pick, and Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (NYSE:FCX) as its favorite copper exposure. A Macro Backdrop Miners Rarely Get Ba</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bank-americas-top-3-commodity-160112290.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia takes on Tesla with what Jensen Huang calls the 'ChatGPT moment' for self-driving</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-takes-on-tesla-with-what-jensen-huang-calls-the-chatgpt-moment-for-self-driving-160045664.html</link><description>"The ChatGPT moment for physical AI is here — when machines begin to understand, reason, and act in the real world," Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang said from CES in Las Vegas, throwing down the robotic gauntlet in a statement about the GPU maker's latest autonomous move.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-takes-on-tesla-with-what-jensen-huang-calls-the-chatgpt-moment-for-self-driving-160045664.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2026’s Top Tech ETF Is Little Known, Cheap, Perfectly Positioned, and Ready To Rally</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/2026s-top-tech-etf-is-little-known-cheap-perfectly-positioned-and-ready-to-rally/</link><description>After years of delays, autonomous vehicles are shifting from pilot programs to commercial reality. At CES 2026, NVIDIA (NASDAQ:NVDA) unveiled partnerships with Mercedes-Benz (OTC:MBGAF) for city-street autonomy and a robotaxi alliance with Lucid (NASDAQ:LCID) and Uber (NYSE:UBER). Waymo plans to expand to 12 new cities this year while targeting over one million weekly rides. iShares ... 2026’s Top Tech ETF Is Little Known, Cheap, Perfectly Positioned, and Ready To Rally</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/2026s-top-tech-etf-is-little-known-cheap-perfectly-positioned-and-ready-to-rally/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] The Saturday Spread: Reading the Market’s Signals to Jump Ahead of the Crowd (HPE, SNOW, CRWD)</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36982018/the-saturday-spread-reading-the-markets-signals-to-jump-ahead-of-the-crowd-hpe-snow-crwd</link><description>Successful trading involves anticipating what might happen next just as much as reacting to evolving undercurrents.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/36982018/the-saturday-spread-reading-the-markets-signals-to-jump-ahead-of-the-crowd-hpe-snow-crwd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Corsair’s AI-Driven Stream Deck Ecosystem Might Change The Case For Investing In Corsair Gaming (CRSR)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corsair-ai-driven-stream-deck-151406365.html</link><description>Corsair Gaming recently used CES 2026 to showcase its shift from standalone gaming hardware to a connected ecosystem spanning gaming, streaming, content creation, productivity, and local AI computing, anchored by Stream Deck and the new GALLEON 100 SD keyboard with integrated controls. An important takeaway is Corsair’s early support for Model Context Protocol and collaboration with NVIDIA G-Assist, signaling a deeper push into AI-enabled, locally run system control that could broaden its...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corsair-ai-driven-stream-deck-151406365.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Looking At The Narrative For Snowflake After AI Deals And New Street Expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-narrative-snowflake-ai-deals-151312957.html</link><description>Snowflake’s fair value estimate has been nudged up from US$281.73 to US$283.52 per share, a small change that reflects slightly firmer assumptions around revenue growth while the discount rate and net profit margin expectations are essentially flat. This adjustment aligns with recent Street research that has become more constructive on Snowflake, pointing to AI related demand, expanding margins, and expectations for steadier execution as key supports for the updated narrative. Continue with...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-narrative-snowflake-ai-deals-151312957.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Is Now Able To Extract Value From Trash While Tariffs And Environmental Pressures Mount. 'We Shouldn't Expect People To Do That'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-now-able-extract-value-150131830.html</link><description>AI is stepping into one of the dirtiest jobs in the recycling business: sorting through trash to find what’s actually worth something. And with tariffs, environmental laws, and labor shortages piling on, the timing couldn't be better. AI-Powered Systems Are Revolutionizing Recycling At facilities like Murphy Road Recycling in Connecticut, AI-powered machines are helping sort up to 60 tons of curbside recycling an hour. Instead of humans standing over conveyor belts pulling out cans and bottles,</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-now-able-extract-value-150131830.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] AI is no ‘business killer’: Why Wall Street is buying software stocks in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-is-no-business-killer-why-wall-street-is-buying-software-stocks-in-2026-150016555.html</link><description>As "scared" money returns to the sector, top analysts at DA Davidson and Piper Sandler name the cloud and infrastructure plays set to lead a 2026 recovery.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-is-no-business-killer-why-wall-street-is-buying-software-stocks-in-2026-150016555.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Charlie Munger Says His Financial Success Came From These 'Tricks' He 'Got Into By Accident in Life'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/charlie-munger-says-financial-success-143216083.html</link><description>Charlie Munger was known for never taking credit for his achievements, despite spending decades as Warren Buffett's right-hand man and playing a key role in shaping the strategies behind Berkshire Hathaway Inc. Munger said during an interview at the Redlands Forum in California in 2020, sponsored by geographic information system software company Esri, the University of Redlands, and local nonprofit Town &amp;amp; Gown, that his financial success was not the result of exceptional ability, but instead cam</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/charlie-munger-says-financial-success-143216083.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] One Agriculture Equipment Giant Dominated Last Month Despite Sector Challenges</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/one-agriculture-equipment-giant-dominated-last-month-despite-sector-challenges/</link><description>The U.S. economy added just 50,000 jobs in December, marking the slowest labor market expansion in years and pushing unemployment to 4.4%. This cooling signals potential Federal Reserve flexibility on rates, creating a critical backdrop for capital-intensive industries like farm equipment. With mortgage rates hitting three-year lows following Trump’s $200 billion housing bond program and ... One Agriculture Equipment Giant Dominated Last Month Despite Sector Challenges</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/one-agriculture-equipment-giant-dominated-last-month-despite-sector-challenges/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stock Market Week Ahead: Key Health Care, Retail, Aerospace Conferences</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/investing-action-plan/stock-market-week-ahead-health-care-retail-aerospace-conferences/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan and Goldman Sachs launch the Q4 reporting season, in a mix of inflation data and key industry conferences.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/investing-action-plan/stock-market-week-ahead-health-care-retail-aerospace-conferences/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] China AI Leaders Warn of Widening Gap With US After $1B IPO Week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-ai-leaders-warn-widening-140555407.html</link><description>“A massive amount of OpenAI’s compute is dedicated to next-generation research, whereas we are stretched thin — just meeting delivery demands consumes most of our resources,” Lin said during a panel at the AGI-Next summit in Beijing on Saturday.  The event, co-organized by Zhipu and Tsinghua University, followed market debuts this week in which Zhipu and Shanghai-based MiniMax Group collectively raised more than $1 billion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-ai-leaders-warn-widening-140555407.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] The GLP-1 Blockbuster Maker Widens Its Lead as the Diversified Healthcare Giant Posts Steady Growth</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-glp-1-blockbuster-maker-widens-its-lead-as-the-diversified-healthcare-giant-posts-steady-growth/</link><description>Eli Lilly (NYSE: LLY) and Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (NYSE: JNJ) both delivered strong third-quarter results, but their earnings revealed two fundamentally different healthcare businesses. Lilly rode explosive GLP-1 drug demand to 53.9% revenue growth. Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson leaned on diversification across medical devices, pharmaceuticals, and consumer health to post 6.8% growth. GLP-1 Momentum Versus Diversified ... The GLP-1 Blockbuster Maker Widens Its Lead as the Diversified Healthcare Giant Posts Steady</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-glp-1-blockbuster-maker-widens-its-lead-as-the-diversified-healthcare-giant-posts-steady-growth/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Analysts See Nvidia’s AI Roadmap Driving EPS Upside Into 2027</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-analysts-see-nvidia-ai-135411494.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the AI Stocks Gaining Attention on Wall Street. On January 6, UBS analyst Timothy Arcuri reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $235.00 price target. The rating affirmation follows Nvidia’s recent Consumer Electronics Show (CES) at Las Vegas. Analyst Timothy Arcuri anticipates Nvidia’s stock price to be […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-analysts-see-nvidia-ai-135411494.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Analysts Turn More Bullish on Alphabet (GOOGL) After Favorable Antitrust Ruling</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-turn-more-bullish-alphabet-135004715.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the AI Stocks Gaining Attention on Wall Street. On January 7, Canaccord Genuity analyst Maria Ripps raised the price target on the stock to $390.00 (from $330.00) while maintaining a Buy rating. The firm is bullish on the tech giant, believing Google’s scale and data position will help extend […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-turn-more-bullish-alphabet-135004715.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Best Trillion-Dollar Stock to Buy for 2026, According to Wall Street</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/best-trillion-dollar-stock-buy-2026-microsoft/</link><description>This tech giant could have even more upside than analysts project.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/best-trillion-dollar-stock-buy-2026-microsoft/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google, Shopify Lead Big 2025 Winners Near New Buy Points</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/google-shopify-buy-points/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>This week offered up an array of stocks to buy from across several different industries. These five stocks all showed promising action in their own right. They include major tech names like Alphabet and Shopify, retail stalwart TJX Cos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/google-shopify-buy-points/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Optimism Prevails for Zillow Group (ZG) Despite Fears of Third-Party Real Estate Advertisements</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/optimism-prevails-zillow-group-zg-124929715.html</link><description>Zillow Group (NASDAQ:ZG) is one of the best communication services stocks according to Hedge Funds. RBC Capital analyst Brad Erickson reiterated his bullish call on Zillow Group (NASDAQ:ZG). The analyst assigned a Buy rating on December 15, with a $95.00 price target. As per Erickson’s forecasts, investors should expect an upside of almost 41%. Erickson’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/optimism-prevails-zillow-group-zg-124929715.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] CoreWeave (CRWV) Emerges as an AI Infrastructure Stock to Watch After Truist Initiation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-emerges-ai-infrastructure-124539079.html</link><description>CoreWeave, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is one of the AI Stocks Gaining Attention on Wall Street. On January 6, Truist Securities analyst Arvind Ramnani initiated coverage on the stock with a Hold rating and an $84 price target. Despite the cloud service provider’s revenue gains and high-end clients, the firm believes that CRWV suffers from lofty leverage […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-emerges-ai-infrastructure-124539079.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is Fidelity’s Health Care ETF A Good Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/is-fidelitys-health-care-etf-a-good-buy-right-now/</link><description>Healthcare investing offers defensive characteristics during market turbulence, yet regulatory uncertainty and political risk can trigger sudden selloffs. For investors seeking pure healthcare exposure without picking individual stocks, Fidelity MSCI Health Care Index ETF (NYSEARCA:FHLC) provides a low-cost entry point to this complex sector. What FHLC Delivers: Sector Exposure With a Concentration Problem FHLC tracks ... Is Fidelity’s Health Care ETF A Good Buy Right Now?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/10/is-fidelitys-health-care-etf-a-good-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Vs. Nvidia At CES 2026: Two Paths Into The $10 Trillion AI Era</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-nvidia-ces-2026-123108149.html</link><description>CES 2026 put a spotlight on how fractured the AI opportunity really is. On the same stage, Intel Corp (NASDAQ:INTC) and NVIDIA Corp (NASDAQ:NVDA) pitched radically different visions of how they plan to tap what investors broadly frame as a $10 trillion AI era. One focused on fixing what it lost. The other focused on expanding what it already owns. Intel's Pitch: AI Starts On Your Laptop Intel's CES narrative was all about execution. Panther Lake, part of the Core Ultra Series 3 lineup, marked th</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-nvidia-ces-2026-123108149.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Brad Gerstner Bets On This Stock To Benefit From Nvidia's Rubin Platform: 'A Really Interesting Opportunity'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brad-gerstner-bets-stock-benefit-120111790.html</link><description>Hedge funder Brad Gerstner, who is the CEO of Altimeter Capital, believes it is still the early innings of a super cycle for software and cloud companies benefiting from the growth of AI and data center spending. In a recent interview, he shared one of the beaten-down stocks that he's buying. Brad Gerstner's Cloud Pick In a recent appearance on CNBC's Halftime Report, Gerstner highlighted several stocks owned by Altimeter Capital, including NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA). While Nvidia is a top</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brad-gerstner-bets-stock-benefit-120111790.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: These 2 AI Stocks Will Be Worth More Than Palantir by the End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/prediction-these-2-ai-stocks-will-be-worth-more-th/</link><description>This is one of the easiest predictions ever.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/prediction-these-2-ai-stocks-will-be-worth-more-th/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Johnson Controls (JCI) Quietly Rewriting Its Core Story Around AI-Era Cooling and Smart Buildings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/johnson-controls-jci-quietly-rewriting-110852889.html</link><description>In recent days, Johnson Controls International has faced pressure after Nvidia’s CEO said future AI chips could sharply reduce traditional data-center cooling needs, while the company committed up to US$60.00 million over five years to expand its Singapore Innovation Centre for next-generation thermal management technologies. At the same time, Johnson Controls is highlighting growth initiatives such as AI-enabled retail loss-prevention tools and an expanded smart-building focus, underscoring...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/johnson-controls-jci-quietly-rewriting-110852889.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] The Smartest Growth Stock to Buy With $1,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor is a great choice for playing the AI race in a neutral way.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/the-smartest-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investing.com’s stocks of the week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-com-stocks-week-093005040.html</link><description>Investing.com – With the first week of full trading in 2026 in the bag, there has been much to assess, with various big-name stocks making strong moves.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investing-com-stocks-week-093005040.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AV.L] Aviva plc's (LON:AV.) Has Been On A Rise But Financial Prospects Look Weak: Is The Stock Overpriced?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-plcs-lon-av-rise-092601062.html</link><description>Aviva's (LON:AV.) stock is up by a considerable 5.1% over the past month. However, we decided to pay close attention to...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/aviva-plcs-lon-av-rise-092601062.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should You Be Worried About an AI Bubble in 2026? Here's What the Experts Have to Say.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/should-you-be-worried-about-an-ai-bubble-in-2026-h/</link><description>If more AI volatility is coming, here's how experts suggest you prepare.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/should-you-be-worried-about-an-ai-bubble-in-2026-h/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Says Rubin Architecture Is Now in Full Production. Here's Why That Matters.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-rubin-architecture-is/</link><description>These next-generation chips are available well ahead of expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/10/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-rubin-architecture-is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BofA Maintains Buy on Nvidia (NVDA) Following CES AI Updates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-maintains-buy-nvidia-nvda-082143740.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 6, Bank of America reiterated the stock as “Buy,” noting that the AI chipmaker is still a top AI pick following the company’s presentation at the Consumer Electronics Show on Monday. Analysts highlighted how CEO Jensen Huang highlighted robust demand […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-maintains-buy-nvidia-nvda-082143740.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Evercore Expects Tesla (TSLA) Shares to Trade Sideways in the Near Term</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-evercore-expects-tesla-tsla-081852605.html</link><description>Tesla, Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) is one of the AI Stocks Analysts Are Watching Closely. On January 6, Evercore ISI reiterated the stock as “In Line”. The firm believes that Tesla will likely “see-saw” for the foreseeable future. “For TSLA, who doesn’t guide, the stock is likely a short-term seesaw between lackluster legacy (~$100 of value; ~40c EPS […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-evercore-expects-tesla-tsla-081852605.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: 2 Ways To Capitalize on AI Stocks in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/prediction-3-ways-ai-stocks-will-change-in-2026/</link><description>The AI sector is set for some changes in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/prediction-3-ways-ai-stocks-will-change-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Could Investing $10,000 in ASML Make You a Millionaire?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/could-investing-10000-in-asml-make-you-a-millionai/</link><description>The company's backstory is exciting, but stories alone don't produce revenue or profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/09/could-investing-10000-in-asml-make-you-a-millionai/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Mark Zuckerberg's Mom Predicted It, His Sister Bet On It: The Story Behind Meta CEO's Harvard Dropout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-zuckerbergs-mom-predicted-sister-023105826.html</link><description>Mark Zuckerberg's exit from Harvard University in 2004 has become one of the most famous college dropouts in tech history, but according to the Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) CEO, it was hardly a surprise at home. Friends And Family Expected Him To Leave Harvard During a 2013 appearance at Y Combinator's Startup School, Zuckerberg reflected on his early college days and the fallout from Facemash, a website he built that allowed students to rate classmates' photos. The project briefly overwhe</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mark-zuckerbergs-mom-predicted-sister-023105826.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Is It Too Late To Consider Analog Devices (ADI) After A 44% One Year Rally?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-analog-devices-adi-021203357.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Analog Devices at around US$300.93 is priced for perfection or still offers value, this article will walk through what the current market price might be telling you. The stock has posted returns of 9.9% over the last week, 6.9% over the last month, 9.9% year to date and 44.0% over the past year, with longer-term returns of 87.6% over three years and 108.2% over five years. Recent coverage of Analog Devices has focused on its role as a major analog and mixed...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-analog-devices-adi-021203357.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Walmart To Join Nasdaq 100 on Jan. 20 as AstraZeneca Exits</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-join-nasdaq-100-jan-020910743.html</link><description>Walmart’s addition follows its move last year to shift its stock listing from the New York Stock Exchange to Nasdaq, the largest exchange transfer on record.  Jefferies Financial Group Inc. analysts estimated in December that Walmart’s inclusion could prompt nearly $19 billion of inflows as index-tracking funds and exchange-traded products rebalance their holdings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-join-nasdaq-100-jan-020910743.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix Stock Has A January Superpower — And The Numbers Prove It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-stock-january-superpower-numbers-013135887.html</link><description>Netflix Inc. (NASDAQ:NFLX) has developed a striking seasonal pattern that traders have come to recognize: January has historically been its strongest month of the year, and by a wide margin. Over the past two decades, Netflix shares have posted an average January gain of 14.7%, finishing the month higher in 71% of years. That performance meaningfully outpaces both the broader S&amp;amp;P 500 and most large-cap technology peers over the same period, cementing January as a recurring sweet spot for the str</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-stock-january-superpower-numbers-013135887.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google moonshot spinout SandboxAQ claims an ex-exec is attempting ‘extortion’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-moonshot-spinout-sandboxaq-claims-003759454.html</link><description>A former SandboxAQ executive filed a wrongful termination lawsuit filled with shocking allegations. The company is fighting back, hard.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-moonshot-spinout-sandboxaq-claims-003759454.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Investor Michael Burry Reveals Options Bet Against Oracle</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investor-michael-burry-reveals-options-003350357.html</link><description>Burry owns put options on Oracle shares, he said in a Substack post after markets closed on Friday.  Burry, who revealed bearish bets against AI chipmaker Nvidia Corp. and Palantir Technologies Inc. in November, also directly shorted Oracle during the last six months, he said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investor-michael-burry-reveals-options-003350357.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Assessing Analog Devices (ADI) Valuation After AI-Fueled Semiconductor Rally And CES Optimism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-analog-devices-adi-valuation-001523775.html</link><description>Analog Devices (ADI) is back on traders’ radar after a sector wide semiconductor rally, linked to artificial intelligence enthusiasm at CES and shifting expectations for a more accommodative Federal Reserve policy. See our latest analysis for Analog Devices. The recent CES driven AI buzz and hopes for easier Federal Reserve policy have coincided with strong momentum for Analog Devices, with a 7 day share price return of 9.93% and a 90 day share price return of 33.56%. The 1 year total...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-analog-devices-adi-valuation-001523775.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank earnings, CPI inflation data, Fed comments: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-cpi-inflation-data-000021240.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come next week, including earnings results reported by the Big Banks, December's Consumer Price Index (CPI) inflation data, and a slew of commentary from Federal Reserve officials. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bank-earnings-cpi-inflation-data-000021240.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Dow Jones Futures: It's A Broad, Strong Rally, Do Your Stocks Reflect That? JPMorgan, Goldman, Delta, Taiwan Semi Loom</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock market is at highs with JPMorgan, Goldman, Taiwan Semi and Delta earnings due. Two huge conferences, inflation data and perhaps a Trump tariffs ruling also are on tap.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-jpmorgan-goldman-delta-taiwan-semi-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why a $13 Million MercadoLibre Exit Means for Investors After a 25% Run</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/09/why-a-usd13-million-mercadolibre-exit-means-for-investors-after-a-25-run/</link><description>MercadoLibre runs a top e-commerce and fintech platform in Latin America, connecting marketplace, payments, and logistics in one ecosystem.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/filings/2026/01/09/why-a-usd13-million-mercadolibre-exit-means-for-investors-after-a-25-run/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) Outpaces Stock Market Gains: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-outpaces-225006810.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, Cadence Design Systems (CDNS) closed at $327.31, indicating a +2.67% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-cdns-outpaces-225006810.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Senator Dumps Apple, Google, Microsoft To End 2025—But Refuses To Sell This Mag 7 Underperformer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senator-dumps-apple-google-microsoft-223108948.html</link><description>When it comes to members of Congress’s trading activity, there is a strong focus on what's being bought and when stocks are sold. One senator recently disclosed the sale of three Magnificent Seven stocks sold in December, but a Mag7 stock that wasn't sold could be more telling. Senator Ditches Magnificent Seven Stocks Sen. Shelley Moore Capito (R-W.Va.) recently disclosed selling multiple stocks, including several Magnificent Seven stocks, according to the Benzinga Government Trades page. Here w</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senator-dumps-apple-google-microsoft-223108948.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Stock Market Today, Jan. 9: S&amp;P 500 Sets New High and Intel Rallies</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/09/stock-market-today-jan-9-s-and-p-500-sets-new-high-and-intel-rallies/</link><description>Positive jobs data and high-profile political backing for Intel pushed major U.S. indexes toward new highs, today, Jan. 9, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/09/stock-market-today-jan-9-s-and-p-500-sets-new-high-and-intel-rallies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Is It Too Late To Consider KLA (KLAC) After Its Strong Multi Year Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-kla-klac-strong-221012364.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether KLA's share price still offers value after a strong run, this article will walk through what the numbers say and how to think about the current price tag. With the stock at US$1,324.60 and returns of 9.0% over 7 days, 8.1% over 30 days, 3.9% year to date and 94.7% over 1 year, KLA has clearly been on many investors' radar. This is further reflected in a 225.5% return over 3 years and 360.0% over 5 years. Recent share price interest has been supported by ongoing...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-kla-klac-strong-221012364.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Stock Back In Focus After Long Slumber</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/swing-trading/eli-lilly-stock-back-after-long-slumber/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Here's how we employ swing trading strategies of selling into strength, selling into weakness and cutting a loss quickly.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/swing-trading/eli-lilly-stock-back-after-long-slumber/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:07:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CES 2026 was dominated by these 3 tech themes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ces-2026-dominated-3-tech-214500142.html</link><description>CES 2026 took place this week, where a number of tech companies announced new projects and unveiled new products, such as Nvidia's (NVDA) Alpamayo open-source model to train and improve autonomous driving programs, Qualcomm's (QCOM) Snapdragon X Plus 2 artificial intelligence (AI) chip for PCs, and more. Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley outlines the top three themes from the event. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Asking for a Trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ces-2026-dominated-3-tech-214500142.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>