<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:00:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike CEO says AI agents are unpredictable as company snaps up more cybersecurity startups</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-ceo-says-ai-agents-are-unpredictable-as-company-snaps-up-more-cybersecurity-startups-165836482.html</link><description>CrowdStrike has come out swinging in 2026 with some key deals. Here's why.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-ceo-says-ai-agents-are-unpredictable-as-company-snaps-up-more-cybersecurity-startups-165836482.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Keeps an Overweight Rating on Shake Shack Inc. (SHAK)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-keeps-overweight-rating-shake-165221562.html</link><description>Shake Shack Inc. (NYSE:SHAK) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. The Fly reported on January 7, 2026, that Barclays kept its Overweight rating on Shake Shack Inc. (NYSE:SHAK) and lowered the price goal to $110 from $115. The change reflects outlooks for the restaurant industry in 2026, where sales difficulties […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-keeps-overweight-rating-shake-165221562.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Prediction: These Could Be the Best-Performing Healthcare Stocks Through 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-best-performing-healthcare-stocks-2030/</link><description>Plenty of growth lies ahead for these top healthcare companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-best-performing-healthcare-stocks-2030/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The AI Boom Gets Its First Earnings Test of the Year. Watch TSMC Stock.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-taiwan-semi-earnings-stock-price-8ccafaeb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>When  Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing  reports fourth-quarter earnings on Thursday, investors will be watching for the company’s comments on revenue and capital expenditure for clarity on where the boom in artificial-intelligence processors goes from here.  TSMC is expected to report a net profit of 469.13 billion New Taiwan dollars ($14.86 billion), according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates, up 25% from the same period a year ago.  The Taiwanese chip manufacturer releases monthly revenue figures, which makes it easier for investors to calculate fourth-quarter revenue.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/tsmc-taiwan-semi-earnings-stock-price-8ccafaeb?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 2 "Magnificent Seven" Stocks May Announce Stock Splits in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/these-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-may-announce-stoc/</link><description>Stock splits can cause a stock to rally in the short term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/these-2-magnificent-seven-stocks-may-announce-stoc/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Citi Retains a Neutral Rating on Sysco Corporation (SYY)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-retains-neutral-rating-sysco-161618895.html</link><description>Sysco Corporation (NYSE:SYY) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. According to TheFly, on January 7, 2026, Citi reduced its price target for Sysco Corporation (NYSE:SYY) from $82 to $81. It kept a neutral rating on the stock. The revision was part of Citi’s overall 2026 projection upgrade for the food […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citi-retains-neutral-rating-sysco-161618895.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Deutsche Bank is Bullish on The Kroger Co. (KR)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/deutsche-bank-bullish-kroger-co-161552290.html</link><description>The Kroger Co. (NYSE:KR) is among the 12 Best Food Stocks to Buy in 2026. The Fly reported on January 8, 2026, that Deutsche Bank has resumed coverage of The Kroger Co. (NYSE: KR), with a $75 price target and a Buy rating. The firm anticipates 2026 to be a mixed year and has restored […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/deutsche-bank-bullish-kroger-co-161552290.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Robotics software maker Skild AI hits $14B valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/robotics-software-maker-skild-ai-161333284.html</link><description>Skild AI, which is building general-purpose robotic software, just raised a $1.4 billion funding round led by SoftBank.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/robotics-software-maker-skild-ai-161333284.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bank of America delivers sharp take on Apple stock after major shift</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-delivers-sharp-take-on-apple-stock-after-major-shift</link><description>Bank of America is leaning bullish on Apple (AAPL) stock ahead of a critical earnings test on Jan. 29. The sharper take comes right after a major shift in Apple’s AI future, following a breakthrough deal for Siri with Google, a unit of Alphabet (GOOGL). The bank sees multiple potent near-term ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-delivers-sharp-take-on-apple-stock-after-major-shift</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Chip Startup Etched Raises $500 Million in New Funding Round</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-etched-raises-160625909.html</link><description>Stripes-led financing values Etched at $5 billion as it develops AI processors to compete with Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-etched-raises-160625909.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:06:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Greenland Technologies Stock Soars. There Are Better Ways to Play the Geopolitical Tug-of-War.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/greenland-technologies-stock-price-trump-de794d1a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Greenland, the thinly populated island and territory of NATO member Denmark, has become the unexpected apple of President Trump’s eye.  Whatever happens, investors should remember that there is potential for heartache, too, when using stocks to bet on the outcome of an event.  Coming into Wednesday trading, shares of tiny  Greenland Technologies  Holding were up 31% over the past week despite having nothing to do with Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/greenland-technologies-stock-price-trump-de794d1a?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Jim Cramer on Arm Holdings: “I Think I’m a Buyer, Not a Seller”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-155750173.html</link><description>Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. A caller mentioned that they have held the stock for about a year but had a 23% loss. Here’s what Cramer had to say: “Oh, Arm Holdings, that’s Rene Haas. I think he’s doing a real good job. I don’t know […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-arm-holdings-think-155750173.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia stock falls as China reportedly restricts imports of H200 chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-falls-as-china-reportedly-restricts-imports-of-h200-chips-155203605.html</link><description>Chinese authorities have instructed customs agents to ban the entrance of Nvidia's H200 AI chips into the country, according to Reuters.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-falls-as-china-reportedly-restricts-imports-of-h200-chips-155203605.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike defeats shareholder lawsuit over huge software outage</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-155130284.html</link><description>A federal judge dismissed a lawsuit by CrowdStrike shareholders who said the cybersecurity company defrauded them by concealing its inadequate ​software testing and quality assurance procedures, before a July 2024 outage crashed more ‌than 8 million Microsoft Windows-based computers worldwide.  In a decision made public on Tuesday, U.S. District Judge Robert Pitman ‌in Austin, Texas said shareholders failed to plausibly allege that a large number of statements by CrowdStrike and top executives in regulatory filings, on earnings calls and on the company's website were materially false and misleading, or motivated by an intent to defraud.  Led by New York State ⁠Comptroller Thomas DiNapoli, the shareholders ‌alleged that CrowdStrike had "no test plans and no quality assurance team," citing former employees, and that executives at the Austin-based company prioritized "speed over ‍everything else" to maximize profit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-defeats-shareholder-lawsuit-over-155130284.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike CEO on M&amp;A: Identity security is the 'new perimeter'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/crowdstrike-ceo-m-identity-security-155100218.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) has closed a deal valued at $420 million to acquire Seraphic Security; this comes after acquiring identity security platform SGNL last week for $740 million. CrowdStrike also bought Pangea and Onum in 2025. CrowdStrike Co-Founder and CEO George Kurtz joins Yahoo Finance Executive Editor Brian Sozzi on Opening Bid to talk about the cybersecurity operator's goals to expand its identity security portfolio and the value these companies add to CrowdStrike. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Opening Bid.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/crowdstrike-ceo-m-identity-security-155100218.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bitdeer deploys NVIDIA GB200s for AI workloads in Malaysian data center</title><link>https://blockspace.media/insight/bitdeer-deploys-nvidia-gb200s-for-ai-workloads-in-malaysian-data-center/</link><description>Bitdeer is now operating NVIDIA GB200 NVL72 GPUs at a datacenter in Malaysia as the bitcoin miner dives into AI services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blockspace.media/insight/bitdeer-deploys-nvidia-gb200s-for-ai-workloads-in-malaysian-data-center/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA's Next Chip Isn't Just Faster -- It Could Make AI 10 Times Cheaper to Run</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidias-next-chip-ai-ten-times-cheaper/</link><description>The Rubin platform can significantly reduce token costs, opening up new use cases for AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidias-next-chip-ai-ten-times-cheaper/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple and Qualcomm Stocks Falls -- Report Says Companies Facing Potential Supply Issues</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-stocks-falls-report-153353729.html</link><description>The AI Supply Chain Has a New Choke Point. Apple and Qualcomm Are Exposed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-qualcomm-stocks-falls-report-153353729.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017534.html</link><description>Nu Holdings Ltd. 3,024,710 16.62</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153017534.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Hope for first time buyers as Nationwide and HSBC push through mortgage rate cuts</title><link>https://www.standard.co.uk/business/mortgage-first-time-buyers-nationwide-hsbc-rate-cuts-b1266488.html</link><description>New mortgage price war follows a period of falling gilt yields at the start of the year</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.standard.co.uk/business/mortgage-first-time-buyers-nationwide-hsbc-rate-cuts-b1266488.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Nvidia Stock Could Jump During the Period From Jan. 15 to Feb. 4</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-nvidia-stock-could-jump-jan-15-feb-4/</link><description>A series of events may shed light on Nvidia's future.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-nvidia-stock-could-jump-jan-15-feb-4/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sales of a powerful Nvidia AI chip to China gets the greenlight, with conditions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sales-powerful-nvidia-ai-chip-145354822.html</link><description>The Trump administration placed new security requirements on Nividia's semiconductor sales to China, but essentially greenlighted the export of its powerful H200 artificial intelligence chips to Chinese buyers.  Nvidia must ensure that there is an adequate supply in the U.S., and the H200 chips must undergo a third-party review before being exported to China, according to new rules set by the Commerce Department's Bureau of Industry and Security.  China won't be allowed to use the chips for military purposes and is not allowed to import more than 50% of the chips sold to U.S. customers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sales-powerful-nvidia-ai-chip-145354822.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Here's Why Eli Lilly (LLY) is a Strong Momentum Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-eli-lilly-lly-145004555.html</link><description>The Zacks Style Scores offers investors a way to easily find top-rated stocks based on their investing style. Here's why you should take advantage.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-eli-lilly-lly-145004555.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Micron Before 2027?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-you-buy-stock-before-year/</link><description>Demand for high-bandwidth memory is increasing exponentially, and Micron's investors will reap the reward.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-you-buy-stock-before-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] ARM's Self-Reinforcing Ecosystem Cements Its Industry Leadership</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arms-self-reinforcing-ecosystem-cements-144800087.html</link><description>Arm Holdings' self-reinforcing network ties developers and chipmakers, turning vast software compatibility into a mobile CPU moat rivals struggle to breach.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arms-self-reinforcing-ecosystem-cements-144800087.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls On Surprise Inflation Data; Nvidia Slides (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-inflation-data-wells-fargo-wfc-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Wednesday on surprise inflation data. Nvidia tumbled in morning trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-inflation-data-wells-fargo-wfc-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM vs. MSFT: Which Cloud &amp; AI Tech Giant is a Better Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-vs-msft-cloud-ai-143600677.html</link><description>Microsoft's AI edge and stronger growth outlook give it an edge over IBM, despite the latter's stronger valuation and stock gains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-vs-msft-cloud-ai-143600677.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Hardware Stock Could Become One of the Next $1 Trillion Companies</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-this-ai-hardware-stock-could-become-one/</link><description>AMD could regain some AI market share from Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/prediction-this-ai-hardware-stock-could-become-one/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why AMD's Least Hyped CES Announcement Could Be Its Most Important</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-amds-least-hyped-ces-announcement-could-be-its/</link><description>As AI inference shifts to local devices, AMD is ready.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/why-amds-least-hyped-ces-announcement-could-be-its/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Google stock is on fire in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-google-stock-is-on-fire-in-2026-142253886.html</link><description>Google's stock has picked up where it left off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-google-stock-is-on-fire-in-2026-142253886.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to acquire Seraphic Security, terms undisclosed</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-acquire-seraphic-security-terms-141633279.html</link><description>CrowdStrike (CRWD) announced it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire Seraphic Security. The purchase price is contemplated to be paid predominantly in cash and includes a portion to be delivered in the form of stock subject to vesting conditions. The proposed acquisition is expected to close during CrowdStrike’s first quarter of FY’27, subject to customary closing conditions. Claim 70% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper deci</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-acquire-seraphic-security-terms-141633279.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Looking for Stocks with Positive Earnings Momentum? Check Out These 2 Computer and Technology Names</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-stocks-positive-earnings-momentum-140004237.html</link><description>Why investors should use the Zacks Earnings ESP tool to help find stocks that are poised to top quarterly earnings estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/looking-stocks-positive-earnings-momentum-140004237.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Just Hit a $4T Market Cap. This Bull Sees More Gains Ahead</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-just-hit-a-4t-market-cap-this-bull-sees-more-gains-ahead/</link><description>Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOGL) surpassed the $4 trillion market cap mark and could be headed to a $5 trillion valuation at some point in 2026, especially if the latest parabolic move has gas in the tank. With shares of Alphabet hitting new highs on Tuesday’s session, effectively leaving many of its Magnificent Seven peers behind, questions linger ... Alphabet Just Hit a $4T Market Cap. This Bull Sees More Gains Ahead</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/alphabet-just-hit-a-4t-market-cap-this-bull-sees-more-gains-ahead/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence &amp; Microsoft Redefine Data Center Memory With Advanced Solutions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-microsoft-redefine-data-center-135600886.html</link><description>CDNS unveils the first LPDDR5X 9600Mbps enterprise memory IP with Microsoft, bringing DDR5-class reliability to low-power data center AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-microsoft-redefine-data-center-135600886.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is It Time to Dump Your Shares of Eli Lilly?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/is-it-time-to-dump-your-shares-of-eli-lilly/</link><description>What happens with Eli Lilly's GLP-1 shot now that Novo Nordisk has come out with a GLP-1 pill?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/is-it-time-to-dump-your-shares-of-eli-lilly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] CRWV Stock Beats Industry Returns in a Year: Buy, Hold or Fold in 2026?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwv-stock-beats-industry-returns-134600854.html</link><description>CoreWeave surges 119% in a year on booming AI cloud demand, but heavy CapEx, rising debt and valuation concerns raise questions about upside in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crwv-stock-beats-industry-returns-134600854.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Quantum Computing Stocks: Honeywell's Quantinuum Plans IPO</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-honeywell-quantinuum-plans-ipo/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Honeywell said its‌ quantum computing unit Quantinuum will filing for an IPO, adding to the growing number of quantum computing stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-honeywell-quantinuum-plans-ipo/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Slides -- China Approval for AI Chips Remains Uncertain</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-slides-china-approval-133723410.html</link><description>Nvidia Navigates Export Rules as AI Chip Sales to China Hang in Balance</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-slides-china-approval-133723410.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Blocks Nvidia H200 AI Chips From Entering Country, Sources Say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-blocks-nvidia-h200-ai-133609358.html</link><description>Move clouds Nvidia's China outlook just days after U.S. approved limited exports.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-blocks-nvidia-h200-ai-133609358.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Zillow Group, Inc. (ZG): A Bear Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zillow-group-inc-zg-bear-133522890.html</link><description>We came across a bearish thesis on Zillow Group, Inc. on investing subreddit by Guy_PCS. In this article, we will summarize the bears’ thesis on ZG. Zillow Group, Inc.’s share was trading at $67.80 as of January 13th. ZG’s forward P/E was 32.89 according to Yahoo Finance. Zillow Group, Inc. operates real estate brands in mobile applications and Websites in the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zillow-group-inc-zg-bear-133522890.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Tops $4 Trillion With Apple AI Deal -- Is GOOGL Stock Still a Buy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-apple-133509931.html</link><description>Google's AI Push Expands Through Apple Partnership</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-apple-133509931.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar Inc. (CAT): A Bull Case Theory</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-inc-cat-bull-case-133454104.html</link><description>We came across a bullish thesis on Caterpillar Inc. on Chip Stock Investor’s YouTube channel. In this article, we will summarize the bulls’ thesis on CAT. Caterpillar Inc.’s share was trading at $636.53 as of January 13th. CAT’s trailing and forward P/E were 32.35 and 28.49, respectively according to Yahoo Finance. Caterpillar, widely recognized for its construction […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-inc-cat-bull-case-133454104.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] CoreWeave's 2026 CapEx Spend to Double: High Risk or High Reward?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweaves-2026-capex-spend-double-133200147.html</link><description>CRWV expects significantly high 2026 capex as AI demand drives rapid scaling, but rising interest costs and margin pressure test execution.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweaves-2026-capex-spend-double-133200147.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Will LRCX's China Revenue Drop Below 30% Hurt 2026 Growth Outlook?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcxs-china-revenue-drop-below-132200026.html</link><description>Lam Research sees revenues from China falling below 30% in 2026 as export curbs ail, but AI-led demand outside China could help sustain growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcxs-china-revenue-drop-below-132200026.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Factors Led Mar Vista’s U.S. Quality Strategy’s New Addition: Taiwan Semiconductor (TSM)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factors-led-mar-vista-u-131539272.html</link><description>Mar Vista Investment Partners, LLC, an investment management company, released its “Mar Vista U.S. Quality Strategy” fourth-quarter 2025 investor letter. A copy of the letter can be downloaded here. US equities experienced a strong momentum in 2025 and marked their second consecutive year of double-digit gains. The market witnessed one of the fastest recoveries following its […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factors-led-mar-vista-u-131539272.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) Stock Price Prediction for 2026: Where Will It Be in 1 Year (Jan 14)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</link><description>Nvidia remains the dominant AI chipmaker in the market, but where is the stock headed for the rest of this year and into the next?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Boom Hits Energy Reality Check</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-boom-hits-energy-reality-130453342.html</link><description>Electricity rules may reshape data center buildouts</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-boom-hits-energy-reality-130453342.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM's 2026 Outlook Could Turn Brighter</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-2026-outlook-could-turn-130448250.html</link><description>2026 guidance may reflect steadier enterprise demand</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibms-2026-outlook-could-turn-130448250.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: AppLovin, Blackrock, Citigroup, DoorDash, Fabrinet, KLA Corp, Okta, Rivian, Uber and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-applovin-blackrock-citigroup-doordash-fabrinet-kla-corp-okta-rivian-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: Futures are trading lower after the January rally hit a wall on Wednesday, with all major indices falling, and the selling looks set to continue today. The main culprit yesterday was JPMorgan (NYSE: JPM) shares, which took a hit after missing analyst estimates for the quarter. The banking giant posted $4.63 per ... Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: AppLovin, Blackrock, Citigroup, DoorDash, Fabrinet, KLA Corp, Okta, Rivian, Uber and More</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-applovin-blackrock-citigroup-doordash-fabrinet-kla-corp-okta-rivian-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Nvidia Eyes First Breakout Of 2026. These Clues — And An Innovative Deal With Eli Lilly — Bode Well.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/nvidia-stock-eyes-first-breakout-of-2026-with-eli-lilly-ai-collaboration/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Now set to collaborate with Eli Lilly to develop drugs in the AI era, Nvidia looks to trigger a new climb.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/breakout-stocks-technical-analysis/nvidia-stock-eyes-first-breakout-of-2026-with-eli-lilly-ai-collaboration/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] BRK.B vs. CB: Which Insurer is a Safer Option for a Solid Portfolio?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brk-b-vs-cb-insurer-125100827.html</link><description>CB edges out BRK.B as the safer bet, with stronger ROE, dividend yield, and earnings momentum heading into 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brk-b-vs-cb-insurer-125100827.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What to Expect From Alphabet’s Next Quarterly Earnings Report</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37037320/what-to-expect-from-alphabets-next-quarterly-earnings-report</link><description>Here’s what analysts are expecting prior to Alphabet’s Q4 earnings, after the stock topped the $4 trillion market cap recently.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37037320/what-to-expect-from-alphabets-next-quarterly-earnings-report</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] PFE Market Cap Falls More Than $7B in a Month: How to Play the Stock</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pfe-market-cap-falls-more-124500360.html</link><description>Pfizer shares fall nearly 5% in a month after weak 2026 guidance, sparking debate over buying the dip or staying cautious.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pfe-market-cap-falls-more-124500360.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Should Nvidia Worry About the Rise of China’s New Optical AI Chips?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-nvidia-worry-about-the-rise-of-chinas-new-optical-ai-chips/</link><description>It’s been over a year since DeepSeek caused a bit of a panic across the AI stocks, as its distillation techniques caused many to question whether the frontier innovators needed all that hardware firepower. As it turned out, DeepSeek R1 wasn’t the disruptor that was meant to derail the AI trade for good. Fast forward ... Should Nvidia Worry About the Rise of China’s New Optical AI Chips?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/14/should-nvidia-worry-about-the-rise-of-chinas-new-optical-ai-chips/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Warren Buffett compares AI risks to those posed by nuclear weapons: 'The genie is out of the bottle'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-compares-ai-risks-to-those-posed-by-nuclear-weapons-the-genie-is-out-of-the-bottle-122210523.html</link><description>In comments during a two-hour CNBC special on his life and legacy, Warren Buffett compared the potential of AI technology to the threat of nuclear weapons.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-compares-ai-risks-to-those-posed-by-nuclear-weapons-the-genie-is-out-of-the-bottle-122210523.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Stock Surges Further Toward 2-Year High. What the Excitement’s About.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-chips-4ce48217?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday.  The chip company’s shares are on the brink of levels not seen for several years as investors bet President Donald Trump’s support for the company will boost its chip-manufacturing ambitions.  Intel was up 1.6% at $48.06 in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-apple-chips-4ce48217?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] US Moves Toward Allowing Nvidia AI Chip Sales to China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-moves-toward-allowing-nvidia-121655363.html</link><description>Revised Commerce Department rules shift AI chip export reviews to case-by-case approvals, easing prior presumptions of denial.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-moves-toward-allowing-nvidia-121655363.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Honeywell announces Quantinuum's plan to file for IPO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/honeywell-announces-quantinuums-plan-file-121011580.html</link><description>Honeywell said on Wednesday ​it plans for ‌its majority-owned quantum computing unit ‌Quantinuum to confidentially file draft IPO papers with the U.S. ⁠securities ‌regulator. The number of shares to be ‍offered and the price range for the proposed ​offering have not yet ‌been determined, the company said. Following the news, Honeywell's shares were up about 1% during ⁠premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/honeywell-announces-quantinuums-plan-file-121011580.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Warby Parker (WRBY) Soars 9.4% on Strong AI Glasses Demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warby-parker-wrby-soars-9-120943721.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Leaving Wall Street in the Dust; 4 Hit Fresh Records. Warby Parker Inc. (NYSE:WRBY) was one of the top performers on Tuesday. Warby Parker bounced back by 9.44 percent on Tuesday to close at $29.09 apiece, as news of strong demand for artificial intelligence glasses spilled over to its stock. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warby-parker-wrby-soars-9-120943721.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meet the Quantum Computing Stock That Billionaires Can't Get Enough Of (Hint: It's Not IonQ, Rigetti Computing, or D-Wave Quantum)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/meet-the-quantum-computing-stock-that-billionaires/</link><description>Several notable billionaire investors are buying the same quantum computing stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/meet-the-quantum-computing-stock-that-billionaires/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Braze Highlights ChatGPT SDK, Agent Console and AI Personalization Push at Needham Conference</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/braze-highlights-chatgpt-sdk-agent-console-and-ai-personalization-push-at-needham-conference-2026-01-14/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Braze (NASDAQ:BRZE) positions itself as a “reference architecture for the modern customer engagement stack,” emphasizing real-time, cross-channel messaging built on stream processing technology, Chief Financial Officer Isabelle Winkles said during a Needham conference discussion with analyst Scott B</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/braze-highlights-chatgpt-sdk-agent-console-and-ai-personalization-push-at-needham-conference-2026-01-14/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AMD Teams Up with Tata Consultancy Services to Boost Enterprise AI Adoption</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-teams-tata-consultancy-services-115409291.html</link><description>Collaboration targets faster, more secure deployment of AI solutions for global businesses.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-teams-tata-consultancy-services-115409291.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dow Jones Futures Fall As Wells Fargo, Bank Of America Report; Tesla To Stop Selling FSD</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp-500-citigroup-wells-fargo-bac-tesla-fsd-stop-selling/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Futures fell as Wells Fargo and BofA reported with Citigroup due. Tesla will stop selling Full Self-Driving, offering it only as a subscription.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp-500-citigroup-wells-fargo-bac-tesla-fsd-stop-selling/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The ‘Magnificent 7’ stocks are dying, and Wall Street is pretty happy about it</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stocks-dying-wall-113857386.html</link><description>But the dominance of the Mag 7 is likely to come to an end this year, many on Wall Street believe—if only because their valuations can’t exponentially go up forever.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/magnificent-7-stocks-dying-wall-113857386.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Week In AI Chips - TCS and AMD Unite to Boost AI Solutions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-tcs-amd-113759755.html</link><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) have announced a strategic collaboration aimed at enhancing AI accessibility and adoption across enterprises. This partnership focuses on co-developing industry-specific AI and GenAI solutions, leveraging TCS's systems integration capabilities and AMD’s high-performance computing technologies. The collaboration aims to modernize hybrid cloud and edge environments, deploy AI-powered solutions, and enhance AI performance for...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-tcs-amd-113759755.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks to Watch Wednesday: Netflix, Bank of America, Citi</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-netflix-bank-of-america-citi-4vjsTACY6ZhwFCTPHOuZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>🔎 Bank of America (BAC): The lender is due to post quarterly earnings, as are Wells Fargo (WFC) and Citigroup (C). ↗️ Netflix (NFLX): The streaming company is preparing an all-cash bid for Warner Bros.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-wednesday-netflix-bank-of-america-citi-4vjsTACY6ZhwFCTPHOuZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Most popular stocks and funds investors bought in 2025</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-popular-stocks-funds-investing-2025-113311183.html</link><description>Despite ongoing volatility and geopolitical events, 2025 delivered strong returns for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/most-popular-stocks-funds-investing-2025-113311183.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Women's, advocacy groups call on Apple, Google to drop X and Grok from app stores</title><link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/womens-advocacy-groups-call-apple-110255271.html</link><description>By Raphael Satter WASHINGTON, Jan 14 (Reuters) - A coalition of women's groups, tech watchdogs, and progressive activists is calling on Alphabet owner Google and Apple to remove the social media site</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/womens-advocacy-groups-call-apple-110255271.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Next Phase of the AI Boom May Not Come From Chipmakers</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/next-phase-ai-boom-not-come-chipmaker-ceg/</link><description>Chipmakers and data centers dominate the headlines for AI infrastructure, but another sector is set to profit big from the next phase of the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/next-phase-ai-boom-not-come-chipmaker-ceg/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] ‘The rejections are piling up’: why computer science graduates can’t get a job</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/rejections-piling-why-computer-science-110800679.html</link><description>Towards the end of last year, Rashik Parmar began getting calls from anxious students who had just graduated with degrees in computer science.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/rejections-piling-why-computer-science-110800679.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] The Returns At Analog Devices (NASDAQ:ADI) Aren't Growing</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/returns-analog-devices-nasdaq-adi-110007976.html</link><description>If you're not sure where to start when looking for the next multi-bagger, there are a few key trends you should keep an...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/returns-analog-devices-nasdaq-adi-110007976.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google's Apple AI deal marks 'huge loss' for OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-apple-ai-deal-marks-huge-loss-for-openai-110002996.html</link><description>Google and Apple announced a multi-year collaboration on AI Monday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-apple-ai-deal-marks-huge-loss-for-openai-110002996.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] These Stocks Are Today’s Movers: Bank of America, Netflix, Nvidia, Fortinet, Intel, Rivian, and More</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-5199a1f2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Bank of America, Wells Fargo, and Citigroup are set to report earnings Wednesday, a day after JPMorgan Chase posted a decline in quarterly profit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-movers-5199a1f2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Just Delivered Very Bad News for Tesla Stock Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidia-delivered-bad-news-tesla-stock-investors/</link><description>Tesla's long-awaited robotaxi is facing competitive threats before it even hits the road.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/nvidia-delivered-bad-news-tesla-stock-investors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Major factory construction projects to watch in 2026</title><link>https://www.manufacturingdive.com/news/major-factory-construction-projects-to-watch-in-2026/809448/</link><description>TSMC, Micron, Samsung, Lilly and others are set to break ground on or open new facilities this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.manufacturingdive.com/news/major-factory-construction-projects-to-watch-in-2026/809448/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Weekly: Nvidia's China chip twist and AI soulmates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-weekly-nvidias-china-chip-102933857.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: From Nvidia's China chip twist to an AI soulmate, this is AI Weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: AI Weekly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington gave permission to Nvidia to sell its second most powerful AI chip - the H200 - to China - but with conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chips will be reviewed for their AI capabilities before they're shipped off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Beijing can't get more than half of the total amount of chips sold to U.S. customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there was a further twist from China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sources said to Reuters Beijing told customs agents the H200 isn't permitted to enter China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They added Chinese authorities told domestic tech companies they weren't to buy the chips unless necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung forecast profits to jump three-fold to record highs over the latest quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It scored big as tight supply and AI-driven demand drove up prices for memory chips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The South Korean giant projected operating profit of almost $14 billion for the October to December period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number was well beyond analyst estimates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taiwan's TSMC also cashed in on the AI boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It said its fourth-quarter revenue flew up more than a fifth from a year earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters calculations found the number was over $33 billion - beating forecasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world's largest contract chipmaker counts Nvidia and Apple among its customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And AI continued to take center stage at the Consumer&amp;amp;nbsp;Electronics Show in Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tech big hitters like Nvidia were in town, and so were growing firms that showed off range of new offerings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Glyde debuted the world’s first smart hair clipper, the AI Stylist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It said it brings&amp;amp;nbsp;“GPS-level guidance” to DIY haircuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catherine Asberger is from Glyde.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It uses a band that wraps around your head, the clippers themselves, and a mobile app to create a perfect haircut in less than 15 minutes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Lepro's Ami is positioning itself as an AI soulmate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's marketed as a way to ease loneliness among flexible workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ami is a physical desk companion with a curved OLED display that tracks your gaze to feel present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-weekly-nvidias-china-chip-102933857.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike to acquire Seraphic Security for browser security boost</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acqusition-seraphic-security/</link><description>The acquisition will boost CrowdStrike's Falcon platform by integrating Seraphic’s protection, enabling advanced security in popular browsers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/crowdstrike-acqusition-seraphic-security/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trending tickers: Nvidia, Intel, Moderna, BP and Vistry</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-intel-moderna-bp-vistry-trending-tickers-101651287.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-intel-moderna-bp-vistry-trending-tickers-101651287.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Prudential PLC Picks HSBC Veteran Douglas Flint as Next Board Chair</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/business/c-suite/prudential-picks-former-hsbc-veteran-douglas-flint-as-next-board-chair-2e7f10de?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Flint is set to join the board in March as a nonexecutive director and chair-designate, succeeding the retiring Shriti Vadera.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/business/c-suite/prudential-picks-former-hsbc-veteran-douglas-flint-as-next-board-chair-2e7f10de?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] President Trump again eases restrictions on H200 chip exports to China</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/business/2026/01/14/president-trump-again-eases-restrictions-on-h200-chip-exports-to-china?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</link><description>While some lawmakers fear what Beijing will do with the advanced tech, others stress that restrictions will only force China’s homegrown industry to innovate.View on euronews</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.euronews.com/business/2026/01/14/president-trump-again-eases-restrictions-on-h200-chip-exports-to-china?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=feeds_business_articles_2024&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Will Nvidia Stock Fall Below $100 in 2026? Here's What History Has to Say.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/will-nvidia-stock-fall-below-100-2026-history-says/</link><description>Historical headwinds are mounting for the face of the artificial intelligence (AI) revolution.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/will-nvidia-stock-fall-below-100-2026-history-says/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Morgan Stanley flags further upside for UK banks as new targets come into focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-flags-further-upside-090213740.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Morgan Stanley said UK banks still have scope for further upside as new return targets, earnings forecasts and capital metrics come into focus, even after a period of strong share price performance, according to a recent note.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-flags-further-upside-090213740.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Bank Earnings, More Inflation Data, Fed Speakers: Still to Come This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/bank-earnings-more-inflation-data-fed-speakers-still-to-come-this-week-uC8cFXV2ayjktYVeF6Hr?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Key economic data are still due this week, including another inflation reading. More big banks, including Bank of America and Citigroup, are scheduled to report earnings, as is Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing, known as TSMC.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-14-2026/card/bank-earnings-more-inflation-data-fed-speakers-still-to-come-this-week-uC8cFXV2ayjktYVeF6Hr?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Gets U.S. Approval to Ship AI Chips to China. Now It Waits on Beijing.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-china-cef20023?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Trump administration had finalized the requirements for Nvidia to sell its H200 chips for the Chinese market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-china-cef20023?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bitfarms Conference: BITF Details Pivot From Bitcoin Mining to AI Data Centers and HPC Power Play</title><link>https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/bitfarms-conference-bitf-details-pivot-from-bitcoin-mining-to-ai-data-centers-and-hpc-power-play-2026-01-14/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</link><description>Bitfarms (NASDAQ:BITF) executives used a recent investor presentation to detail the company’s strategy to transition from Bitcoin mining toward high-performance computing (HPC) and artificial intelligence (AI) data center infrastructure, emphasizing the growing value of power and purpose-built facil</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.marketbeat.com/instant-alerts/bitfarms-conference-bitf-details-pivot-from-bitcoin-mining-to-ai-data-centers-and-hpc-power-play-2026-01-14/?utm_source=yahoofinance&amp;amp;utm_medium=yahoofinance</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Lilly, Novo test direct-to-employer approach that could cut out PBMs and lower costs</title><link>https://www.pharmavoice.com/news/lilly-novo-direct-employer-drug-cost-pbm-consumer/809575/</link><description>The GLP-1 giants are the first to try out this new model, but more companies may follow.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.pharmavoice.com/news/lilly-novo-direct-employer-drug-cost-pbm-consumer/809575/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] US approves Nvidia H200 chip exports to China with some conditions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/us-approves-nvidia-h200-chip-073111363.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORY: :: NVIDIA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration on Tuesday gave a formal green light to China-bound sales of Nvidia's second most powerful AI chip-- the H200.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Washington put in place some conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the new regulations, the chips will be reviewed by a third-party lab to confirm their AI capabilities before they can be shipped to China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, Beijing will not be allowed to receive more than 50% of the total amount of chips sold to American customers, and Nvidia will need to certify there are enough H200s in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: NVIDIA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese customers will also have to demonstrate "sufficient security procedures", and cannot use the chips for military purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technology companies in China have placed orders for more than 2 million H200 chips, exceeding Nvidia's inventory of 700,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;:: File&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump announced last month that he would allow the sales in exchange for a 25% fee for the U.S. government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision drew fire from China hawks across the U.S. political spectrum over concerns that it would supercharge Beijing's military and erode the U.S. advantage in artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia said the move "strikes a thoughtful balance that is great for America" and will help the company compete in the global chip market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chinese embassy in Washington did not immediately respond to a request&amp;amp;nbsp;for comment on the new moves.&amp;amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/us-approves-nvidia-h200-chip-073111363.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Is It Time To Reassess Kyndryl (KD) After Its IBM Separation And Mixed Share Performance?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-kyndryl-kd-ibm-070647298.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Kyndryl Holdings at around US$27.05 is starting to look like value or still carries too much uncertainty, you are not alone. The share price return sits at 1.2% over the last 7 days, 0.5% over the past month, 6.1% year to date and a 27.9% decline over the last year, while the 3 year return is 115.0%. This gives a mixed picture of how the market has been reassessing the company over different time frames. Recent headlines have focused on Kyndryl's position as an...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-kyndryl-kd-ibm-070647298.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China's customs agents told Nvidia's H200 chips are not permitted, sources say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinas-customs-agents-told-nvidias-065002620.html</link><description>Jan 14 (Reuters) - Chinese customs authorities told customs agents this week that Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips are not permitted to enter China, according to three people briefed on the</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinas-customs-agents-told-nvidias-065002620.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China's customs agents told Nvidia's H200 chips are not permitted, sources say</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinas-customs-agents-told-nvidias-065002091.html</link><description>Chinese customs authorities told customs agents this week that Nvidia's H200 artificial intelligence chips are not permitted to enter China, according to three people briefed on the matter.  Chinese government officials also summoned domestic  technology companies to ​meetings on Tuesday where they were explicitly instructed not to purchase the chips unless necessary, two of the people ‌and a third source said.  The H200, Nvidia's second most powerful AI chip, is one of the biggest flashpoints in current U.S.-Sino relations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinas-customs-agents-told-nvidias-065002091.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Big Investing Takeaways From CES 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/big-investing-takeaways-from-ces-2026/</link><description>CES is always an exciting event as new products -- both realistic and wild -- are introduced. This year, Uber and Nvidia stole the headlines and these Motley Fool contributors discuss what else they learned from CES.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/14/big-investing-takeaways-from-ces-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Proposed billionaires' tax in California rattles Silicon Valley, entangles Gov. Newsom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/proposed-billionaires-tax-california-rattles-051151812.html</link><description>A proposed billionaires' tax in California has ignited a political uproar in Silicon Valley, with tech titans threatening to leave the state while Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom maneuvers to defeat a levy that he fears will lead to an exodus of wealth.  A technology mecca, California has more billionaires than any other state — a few hundred, by some estimates.  Nearly half its personal income tax revenue, a financial backbone in the nearly $350 billion budget, comes from the top 1% of earners.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/proposed-billionaires-tax-california-rattles-051151812.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Wall Street sends message on Tesla after Nvidia self-driving move</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/automotive/wall-street-sends-message-on-tesla-after-nvidia-self-driving-move</link><description>Tesla's tale about cars that drive themselves is going in circles. A significant new announcement reaches the press, and investors start to fear that the "moat" is narrowing. Then the talk turns back to the laborious process of getting the cars on the road, and Tesla is back to square one. That ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/automotive/wall-street-sends-message-on-tesla-after-nvidia-self-driving-move</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel Rediscovers Key to Foundry Success</title><link>https://www.thedailyupside.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/intel-is-figuring-out-how-to-be-a-successful-foundry/</link><description>The progress has earned Intel praise from one particularly important member of the audience: President Trump.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thedailyupside.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/intel-is-figuring-out-how-to-be-a-successful-foundry/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] 1 Growth Stock with Explosive Upside and 2 We Avoid</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-growth-stock-explosive-upside-043125583.html</link><description>Growth is oxygen. But when it evaporates, the consequences can be severe - ask anyone who bought Cisco in the Dot-Com Bubble or newer investors who lived through the 2020 to 2022 COVID cycle.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-growth-stock-explosive-upside-043125583.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Elon Musk has strong words on new Apple-Google AI move</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/elon-musk-has-strong-words-on-new-apple-google-ai-move</link><description>Tech giants like to say they are “democratizing AI,” but the real game has always been control over the rails on which your data and attention run. That is what changes when Apple agrees to let Google’s Gemini models sit behind a revamped, more personalized Siri, according to CNBC. The “next ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/elon-musk-has-strong-words-on-new-apple-google-ai-move</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Wants to Arrest OnePlus CEO in Latest Step to Block China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-wants-arrest-oneplus-ceo-032737371.html</link><description>The Shilin district prosecutors’ office said it issued the warrant for CEO and co-founder Pete Lau, one of the Chinese mobile industry’s more prominent figures and a regular public pitchman for industry leader Oppo.  Prosecutors also indicted two Taiwanese citizens who worked for Lau and accused OnePlus of illegally recruiting more than 70 engineers across the island since 2014.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-wants-arrest-oneplus-ceo-032737371.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What Apple’s AI deal with Google means for the two tech giants, and for $500 billion ‘upstart’ OpenAI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ai-deal-google-means-014819582.html</link><description>The multi-year partnership validates Google's AI comeback, highlights Apple's AI struggles, and could spell trouble for OpenAI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ai-deal-google-means-014819582.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 01:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump Administration Enacts Security Rules for Nvidia’s China Chip Sales</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/trump-administration-enacts-security-rules-for-nvidias-china-chip-sales-e4438822?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  must meet new security requirements before sending its H200 artificial-intelligence chips to China, the Trump administration said.  Under the rules, Nvidia must make sure there is sufficient supply of AI chips in the U.S., and its customers have to demonstrate adequate security procedures before semiconductors are shipped, the Commerce Department’s Bureau of Industry and Security said in a rule published Tuesday.  Nvidia will also have to get its products tested by an outside lab in the U.S. to make sure they meet performance parameters.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/trump-administration-enacts-security-rules-for-nvidias-china-chip-sales-e4438822?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 01:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] US allows Nvidia to send advanced AI chips to China with restrictions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-allows-nvidia-send-advanced-013316921.html</link><description>The US Commerce Department on Tuesday opened the door for Nvidia to sell advanced artificial intelligence chips in China with restrictions, following through on a policy shift announced last month by President Donald Trump.Trump announced on December 9, 2025 that he had reached an agreement with Chinese President Xi Jinping to allow Nvidia to export its H200 chips to China, with the US government getting a 25-percent cut of sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-allows-nvidia-send-advanced-013316921.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 01:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] CoreWeave CEO Calls Nvidia Circular Financing Claims 'Ridiculous,' Says Stake Too Small To Prop Up $42 Billion Company</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-ceo-calls-nvidia-circular-013121853.html</link><description>CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) CEO Michael Intrator has forcefully rejected allegations that his company is engaged in “circular financing” with Nvidia Corp.(NASDAQ:NVDA), describing the narrative as “ridiculous” and mathematically unsound. ‘Ridiculous’ Narrative In a recent appearance on the Big Technology Podcast, Intrator argued that Nvidia's minority stake in the specialized cloud provider is “de minimis” compared to CoreWeave’s massive capital scale, dismissing the concerns as a distraction a</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-ceo-calls-nvidia-circular-013121853.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 01:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] How Investors Are Reacting To Natera (NTRA) NVIDIA-Backed Multimodal AI And Precision Diagnostics Advances</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-reacting-natera-ntra-nvidia-011046924.html</link><description>Natera recently reported a series of advances, including an upgraded multi-modal Signatera MRD model, expanded AI collaborations with NVIDIA, new clinical data readouts in colorectal cancer, and further validation plus panel expansion for its Fetal Focus single-gene NIPT. Together, these developments highlight how Natera is increasingly leveraging one of the world’s largest longitudinal oncology datasets and AI tools to strengthen its position in precision diagnostics across oncology, organ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-reacting-natera-ntra-nvidia-011046924.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 01:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq resume slide as more bank earnings, fresh economic data roll in</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-resume-slide-as-more-bank-earnings-fresh-economic-data-roll-in-000622793.html</link><description>Bank earnings set the tone this week as investors also remained on alert for developments in Iran.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-resume-slide-as-more-bank-earnings-fresh-economic-data-roll-in-000622793.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Breaking Down the Big 3 Investing Styles</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/breaking-down-big-3-investing-235500786.html</link><description>Investors typically gravitate toward several market strategies, with the common 'big three' including income, growth, and value.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/breaking-down-big-3-investing-235500786.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Recommends Everyone Uses This Type Of AI (And It's Free)</title><link>https://www.moneydigest.com/2074855/nvidia-ceo-recommends-everyone-uses-this-type-of-ai-and-its-free/</link><description>Nvidia is at the forefront of AI development, so it's unsurprising that CEO Jensen Huang thinks everyone should use AI. Here's the AI tool he recommends.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.moneydigest.com/2074855/nvidia-ceo-recommends-everyone-uses-this-type-of-ai-and-its-free/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This 1 Thing Will Make Nvidia the Biggest Winner of the AI Race. (Hint: It's Not the GPU.)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/prediction-this-will-make-nvidia-big-ai-winner/</link><description>Jensen Huang, speaking at CES, said something that supports the idea of ongoing leadership.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/prediction-this-will-make-nvidia-big-ai-winner/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 13: Nvidia Rises on H200 Export Developments</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/13/stock-market-today-jan-13-nvidia-rises-on-h200-export-developments/</link><description>Nvidia’s posts modest gains as authorities in China and the U.S. give green light with caveats to H200 chip exports, today, Jan. 13, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/13/stock-market-today-jan-13-nvidia-rises-on-h200-export-developments/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Why Atlassian (TEAM) Shares Are Plunging Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-atlassian-team-shares-plunging-225541930.html</link><description>Shares of collaboration software company Atlassian (NASDAQ:TEAM) fell 5.3% in the afternoon session after a wave of competitive anxiety hit the enterprise software sector sparked by a high-profile downgrade of Adobe, triggering a broader sell-off in high-valuation cloud stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-atlassian-team-shares-plunging-225541930.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Lam Research (LRCX) Sees a More Significant Dip Than Broader Market: Some Facts to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-sees-more-225006436.html</link><description>Lam Research (LRCX) closed the most recent trading day at $214.33, moving 2.75% from the previous trading session.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-sees-more-225006436.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv Holdings Co. (VRT) Advances While Market Declines: Some Information for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-advances-224506374.html</link><description>Vertiv Holdings Co. (VRT) closed at $172.72 in the latest trading session, marking a +1.58% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-advances-224506374.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) Advances While Market Declines: Some Information for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-goog-advances-while-224506249.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) concluded the recent trading session at $336.41, signifying a +1.11% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-inc-goog-advances-while-224506249.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Increases Despite Market Slip: Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-increases-despite-market-224506196.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw Alphabet (GOOGL) settling at $335.97, representing a +1.24% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-increases-despite-market-224506196.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The 3 AI Infrastructure Stocks Set to Triple Over the Next 5 Years</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/ai-infrastructure-stocks-set-to-triple-5-years/</link><description>The AI computing market is expected to expand through at least 2030.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/ai-infrastructure-stocks-set-to-triple-5-years/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 13: Advanced Micro Devices Jumps After Analyst Upgrade Highlights AI Server Chip Demand</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/13/stock-market-today-jan-13-advanced-micro-devices-jumps-after-analyst-upgrade-highlights-ai-server-chip-demand/</link><description>Today, Jan. 13, 2026, investors weigh AMD’s surging AI data center momentum against a somewhat lofty valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/13/stock-market-today-jan-13-advanced-micro-devices-jumps-after-analyst-upgrade-highlights-ai-server-chip-demand/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump's $1.5 Trillion Military Budget Is Sending This Drone Stock Soaring: Momentum Score Spikes</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-1-5-trillion-military-223132268.html</link><description>President Donald Trump’s pledge to increase the country’s military budget from $900 billion to $1.5 trillion has sent defense stocks soaring, including robotics and drone solutions provider, Red Cat Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:RCAT), over the past week. Shares of Red Cat Holdings are up 41.70% year-to-date, in just over a week of trading in the new year, a surge that is sending its Momentum score in Benzinga’s Edge Stock Rankings soaring. Don't Miss: The AI Marketing Platform Backed by Insiders from</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trumps-1-5-trillion-military-223132268.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 13: Intel Jumps on KeyBanc Upgrade Highlighting Strong AI Server CPU Demand</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/13/stock-market-today-jan-13-intel-jumps-on-keybanc-upgrade-highlighting-strong-ai-server-cpu-demand/</link><description>On Jan. 13, 2026, a bullish analyst call and sold-out AI server capacity reframed this chip giant’s turnaround potential.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/13/stock-market-today-jan-13-intel-jumps-on-keybanc-upgrade-highlighting-strong-ai-server-cpu-demand/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump’s power play risks slowing US in AI arms race</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-power-play-risks-slowing-220931408.html</link><description>Investing.com -- President Donald Trump’s latest push to shield Americans from higher power bills risks colliding with Washington’s drive to stay ahead in the AI arms race, with Wedbush warning that forcing Big Tech to “pay their own way” on soaring electricity costs could slow the buildout of data centers that underpin the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-power-play-risks-slowing-220931408.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Three stocks retail traders have been buying</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/three-stocks-retail-traders-buying-220027431.html</link><description>Charles Schwab's Schwab Trading Activity Index gives investors insight into what retail traders are buying and selling. Charles Schwab head trading &amp;amp; derivatives strategist Joe Mazzola shares what the report reveals about three of the stocks traders were buying in December. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/three-stocks-retail-traders-buying-220027431.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Worried About Nvidia’s China Business? CEO Jensen Huang Says This Is the Top Indicator to Watch.</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37027973/worried-about-nvidias-china-business-ceo-jensen-huang-says-this-is-the-top-indicator-to-watch</link><description>Nvidia is facing a great deal of uncertainty right now. Here's what to watch in 2026, according to Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37027973/worried-about-nvidias-china-business-ceo-jensen-huang-says-this-is-the-top-indicator-to-watch</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Wavers Following China Chip News; Is Nvidia A Buy Or Sell Now?</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-ai-tsm/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock falls on Tuesday after reports that the company will not require companies to pay upfront for its H200 China chip.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/nvidia-nvda-stock-ai-tsm/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] AstraZeneca CFO on M&amp;A Strategy and Obesity Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/astrazeneca-cfo-m-strategy-obesity-215137528.html</link><description>AstraZeneca CFO Aradhana Sarin discusses the company's M&amp;amp;A strategy and weight-loss portfolio with Katie Greifeld at the JPMorgan Health-Care Conference in San Francisco.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/astrazeneca-cfo-m-strategy-obesity-215137528.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Heard on the Street Recap: Powered Down</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-powered-down-HtE9Y5RxH8piVaiUPqdw?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow fell 398 points while the S&amp;amp;P 500 slipped 0.2%.  Oil prices jumped after President Trump appeared to hint at intervening in Iran's continuing internal upheaval.  President Trump wants the tech giants building massive artificial-intelligence data centers to "pay their own way" and not have higher energy bills fall on consumers because of booming AI data-center consumption.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/heard-on-the-street-recap-powered-down-HtE9Y5RxH8piVaiUPqdw?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dow Jones, S&amp;P 500 Fall From Highs; Google Leads AI Stocks In Buy Zones</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp-500-google-ai-stocks-buy-zones/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow led a market retreat from highs as financials and software slumped. But Google and other AI plays are in buy areas.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp-500-google-ai-stocks-buy-zones/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Is Now the AI Top Company. Alphabet Stock Keeps Rising Past $4 Trillion Milestone.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/google-stock-price-alphabet-4-trillion-74a8ba6b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Shares hit a record high on Monday, making Alphabet the fourth company ever to pass a $4 trillion market capitalization.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/google-stock-price-alphabet-4-trillion-74a8ba6b?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] US eases regulations on Nvidia H200 chip exports to China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-eases-regulations-nvidia-h200-212912709.html</link><description>WASHINGTON, Jan 13 (Reuters) - The U.S. on Tuesday eased regulations on the export of Nvidia H200 chips to China, putting in place a rule that will likely kickstart shipments of the advance AI chips,</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-eases-regulations-nvidia-h200-212912709.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Revenue Keeps Growing at Taiwan Semi. Should You Load Up on TSM Stock for 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37027043/revenue-keeps-growing-at-taiwan-semi-should-you-load-up-on-tsm-stock-for-2026</link><description>TSMC sits at the center of the AI chip boom, though its current valuation suggests gains may come more gradually.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37027043/revenue-keeps-growing-at-taiwan-semi-should-you-load-up-on-tsm-stock-for-2026</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] US greenlights Nvidia H200 chip exports to China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-eases-regulations-nvidia-h200-212819802.html</link><description>The Trump administration on ​Tuesday gave the ‌greenlight to exports to China ‌of Nvidia's second most powerful AI chips, putting in place a ⁠rule that ‌will likely kickstart shipments of the ‍H200, the federal register showed. According to the regulations, the ​chips will be reviewed by ‌a third party testing lab to confirm their technical AI capabilities before they can be ⁠shipped to China. Nvidia will ​need to certify there are enough H200s in ‍the ⁠U.S. and Chinese customers must demonstrate "sufficient security procedures."</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-eases-regulations-nvidia-h200-212819802.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Billionaire Peter Thiel Made a Big Bet on Two Stocks for 2026 (Hint: It's Not Nvidia)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/billionaire-peter-thiel-made-a-big-bet-on-two-stoc/</link><description>Thiel has sold his hedge fund's entire stake in Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/billionaire-peter-thiel-made-a-big-bet-on-two-stoc/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Stocks to Watch Tuesday: JPMorgan, Delta, L3Harris</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-tuesday-jpmorgan-tsmc-orsted-IpQZNnCjVxXQtZhAIWJg?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>↘️JPMorgan Chase (JPM): The Wall Street bastion posted a 7% drop in quarterly profit, while revenue missed forecasts. Investment-banking fees fell. JPMorgan took an extra $2.2 billion charge for potential futures losses related to buying Apple (AAPL)'s credit-card program.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/stocks-to-watch-tuesday-jpmorgan-tsmc-orsted-IpQZNnCjVxXQtZhAIWJg?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Caterpillar Briefly Tops $300 Billion Valuation on AI Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-crosses-300-billion-market-154856489.html</link><description>Because of its business selling power-generation equipment, Caterpillar has been a runaway winner in a market where investors are hungry for secondary AI plays after the valuations of major technology and semiconductor companies soared.  Exuberance around data-center-driven demand for power generation has helped the company “support a record backlog,” Bloomberg Intelligence analyst Christopher Ciolino said.  Investors are buying into economically sensitive stocks after a report last month showed US growth has been stronger than expected, said Steve Sosnick, chief strategist at Interactive Brokers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/caterpillar-crosses-300-billion-market-154856489.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How The Google Case And Q3 Results Are Rewriting The Story For USA TODAY (TDAY)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-case-q3-results-rewriting-211822967.html</link><description>What Is Driving The Updated Fair Value Range? The higher fair value estimate for USA TODAY stock, from US$5.76 to US$6.22 per share, mainly reflects fresh inputs from recent Q3 results combined with a more explicit treatment of the Google legal case in analyst models. By assigning a 50% probability to a potential US$230m award and treating that as a possible cash inflow, bullish analysts now have more scope to factor in balance sheet flexibility and future capital allocation options alongside...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-case-q3-results-rewriting-211822967.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Siemens (XTRA:SIE) Is Up 5.9% After Expanding Its NVIDIA AI Digital Twin Alliance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-siemens-xtra-sie-5-211625247.html</link><description>Earlier this month, Siemens expanded its AI partnership with NVIDIA, launched its Digital Twin Composer industrial metaverse platform, showcased new robotics integrations at CES 2026, and deepened client collaborations with companies like PepsiCo and Commonwealth Fusion Systems. The Digital Twin Composer launch, paired with Siemens' AI-driven factory blueprint with NVIDIA, signals a push to make photorealistic, physics-accurate digital replicas a core tool for designing and operating complex...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-siemens-xtra-sie-5-211625247.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC (TSM) Gets Price Target Hike as JPMorgan Sees Strong AI-Led Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-tsm-gets-price-target-210710185.html</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited (NYSE:TSM) is one of the AI Stocks Investors Are Watching Closely. On January 7, JPMorgan analyst Gokul Hariharan raised the price target on the stock to NT$2,100.00 (from NT$1,700.00) while maintaining an Overweight rating. The firm anticipates 2026 to be another strong year for TSM, forecasting 30% USD revenue growth. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-tsm-gets-price-target-210710185.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Gets Price Target Hike as Scotiabank Stays Bullish on AI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-gets-price-target-210519093.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the AI Stocks Investors Are Watching Closely. On January 9, Scotiabank analyst Nat Schindler raised the price target on the stock to $375.00 (from $336.00) while maintaining a Sector Outperform rating. With AI tailwinds, the firm remains confident in continued outperformance for GOOGL. “OUR TAKE: Positive. Google is up […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-gets-price-target-210519093.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Chip Startup Etched Raises $500 Million to Take on Nvidia</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-etched-raises-205348019.html</link><description>The round, which was led by investment firm Stripes LLC and includes participation from billionaire entrepreneur Peter Thiel, valued the company at $5 billion, said the people, who asked not to be identified because the agreement hasn’t been announced.  Positive Sum and Ribbit Capital also invested, they said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-chip-startup-etched-raises-205348019.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Why Asana (ASAN) Stock Is Trading Lower Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-asana-asan-stock-trading-204542606.html</link><description>Shares of work management platform Asana (NYSE:ASAN) fell 7.5% in the afternoon session after a wave of competitive anxiety hit the enterprise software sector sparked by a high-profile downgrade of Adobe, triggering a broader sell-off in high-valuation cloud stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-asana-asan-stock-trading-204542606.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Domo, Amplitude, and LiveRamp Stocks Trade Down, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/domo-amplitude-liveramp-stocks-trade-204541451.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after a wave of competitive anxiety hit the enterprise software sector sparked by a high-profile downgrade of Adobe, triggering a broader sell-off in high-valuation cloud stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/domo-amplitude-liveramp-stocks-trade-204541451.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Why DocuSign (DOCU) Stock Is Falling Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-docusign-docu-stock-falling-204541942.html</link><description>Shares of electronic signature company DocuSign (NASDAQ:DOCU) fell 5.6% in the afternoon session after a wave of competitive anxiety hit the enterprise software sector sparked by a high-profile downgrade of Adobe, triggering a broader sell-off in high-valuation cloud stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-docusign-docu-stock-falling-204541942.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Why Salesforce (CRM) Shares Are Plunging Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-salesforce-crm-shares-plunging-204538086.html</link><description>Shares of CRM software giant Salesforce (NYSE:CRM) fell 6.3% in the afternoon session after a wave of competitive anxiety hit the enterprise software sector sparked by a high-profile downgrade of Adobe, triggering a broader sell-off in high-valuation cloud stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-salesforce-crm-shares-plunging-204538086.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Why Snowflake (SNOW) Stock Is Falling Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-snowflake-snow-stock-falling-204049762.html</link><description>Shares of cloud data platform provider Snowflake (NYSE:SNOW) fell 5.5% in the afternoon session after Barclays downgraded the stock to Equal Weight from Overweight and lowered its price target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-snowflake-snow-stock-falling-204049762.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] How Nvidia’s Rubin Chips Could Boost Bittensor Adoption in 2026</title><link>https://beincrypto.com/nvidia-rubin-chips-bittensor-ai-crypto-markets/</link><description>Nvidia’s Rubin chips make AI cheaper and scalable. Here’s why that shift strengthens Bittensor’s open AI market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://beincrypto.com/nvidia-rubin-chips-bittensor-ai-crypto-markets/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] AI, Defense &amp; Quantum Drive 2026 Investment: NVDA and 2 More to Lead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-defense-quantum-drive-2026-200000382.html</link><description>NVDA sits at the crossroads of AI, defense and sovereign tech spending, as geopolitical shifts push governments to lock in advanced computing power for 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-defense-quantum-drive-2026-200000382.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly CFO: Weight-loss pill could have 20% global penetration</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/eli-lilly-cfo-weight-loss-200000803.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (LLY) says its weight-loss pill is on track to be approved in the US, lagging behind Novo Nordisk (NVO). Eli Lilly CFO and executive vice president Lucas Montarce sits down with Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman to outline the company's expectations for its weight-loss pill and its anticipated impact on market penetration. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/eli-lilly-cfo-weight-loss-200000803.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] 1 Quantum Computing Stock to Buy that Could Soar in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/1-quantum-computing-stock-to-buy-that-could-soar-i/</link><description>IonQ achieved a world record in two-qubit gate fidelity in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/1-quantum-computing-stock-to-buy-that-could-soar-i/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Novo Nordisk CEO warns of international competition headwinds, cites Lilly</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/novo-nordisk-ceo-warns-international-192532796.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Novo Nordisk CEO Mike Doustdar said the company faces headwinds in its international operations in 2026 as competition increases following the loss of market exclusivity in several countries.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/novo-nordisk-ceo-warns-international-192532796.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Brent crude oil price rebounds, Caterpillar hits $300B market cap</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/brent-crude-oil-price-rebounds-191943941.html</link><description>Yahoo Finance anchor Josh Lipton tracks Tuesday's top moving stocks and biggest market stories in this Market Minute. Oil (CL=F, BZ=F) prices are rallying on geopolitical tensions, with Brent crude oil crossing $65 for the first time since November. Caterpillar (CAT) crossed $300 billion in market capitalization for the first time. Stay up to date on the latest market action, minute-by-minute, with&amp;amp;nbsp;Yahoo Finance's Market Minute.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/brent-crude-oil-price-rebounds-191943941.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Quantum Promises AI-Level Disruption. Don’t Panic Just Yet.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/quantum-computing-ai-disruption-future-1185c1b0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>There’s no guarantee quantum catches on once it moves beyond a research setting, UBS says. Here are four scenarios for the future.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/quantum-computing-ai-disruption-future-1185c1b0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI &amp; Business Newsletter | Hey Google. Make Siri Work Better</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/ai-business-newsletter-hey-google-make-siri-work-better-NQGAOAKKf4KJPjcyQZ5f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Google and Apple have long been among the more awkward relationships in tech.  The two companies announced a deal Monday that will effectively have Google’s Gemini acting as a foundation for Apple’s AI offerings, including “a more personalized Siri coming this year.”</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-cpi-today-inflation-01-13-2026/card/ai-business-newsletter-hey-google-make-siri-work-better-NQGAOAKKf4KJPjcyQZ5f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Popular Growth Stock Just Hit a Wall. What Comes Next?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/popular-growth-stock-hit-wall-what-next-amd/</link><description>The drop came as AMD announced new products at the annual CES trade show.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/popular-growth-stock-hit-wall-what-next-amd/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nasdaq Turns Lower Amid Mag 7 Struggles</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011326/card/nasdaq-turns-lower-amid-mag-7-struggles-4vGq9hGLL286U56OCRYa?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>So much for the Nasdaq Composite’s turnaround. The tech-heavy index was back down 0.2% on Tuesday after briefly turning positive. The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.3%. The Dow sank 337 points, or 0.7%. Salesforce, down 6.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011326/card/nasdaq-turns-lower-amid-mag-7-struggles-4vGq9hGLL286U56OCRYa?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] MCHP Rises 29% in a Year: How Should You Approach the Stock in 2026?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mchp-rises-29-approach-stock-182000133.html</link><description>Microchip gains from AI momentum, product launches and a revised sales outlook signaling end-market recovery.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mchp-rises-29-approach-stock-182000133.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Nvidia's New Rubin Chips Could Spell Big Gains For This Under-the-Radar AI Stock</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/why-nvidias-new-rubin-chips-could-spell-big-gains/</link><description>Is this a pick-and-shovel play hiding in plain sight?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/why-nvidias-new-rubin-chips-could-spell-big-gains/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 Growth Stocks With Big Catalysts in 2026</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/2-growth-stocks-with-big-catalysts-in-2026/</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 has been so incredibly resilient in 2026. It’s been less than two weeks since we rang in the new year, but the broad market has already been rocked with a number of macro events, which I would have thought would pave the way for greater volatility and perhaps downside to kick off ... 2 Growth Stocks With Big Catalysts in 2026</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/2-growth-stocks-with-big-catalysts-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] The Best Dow Jones Stock Over The Past Year Is In A Buy Zone, Riding AI Boom</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stock-caterpillar-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The stock is up 77% over the past 52 weeks, making it the top-performing stock in the Dow Jones Industrial Average in that period.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stock-caterpillar-ai/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google joins a rare valuation milestone club on Wall Street</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/markets/google-joins-a-rare-valuation-milestone-club-on-wall-street</link><description>Alphabet just joined one of the rarest clubs in markets, companies worth roughly $4 trillion or more, according to Reuters and real-time quote data. The company’s class A shares pushed its market value to around $4 trillion in intraday trading on Monday, Jan. 12, as the stock traded near a record ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/markets/google-joins-a-rare-valuation-milestone-club-on-wall-street</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm Stock Is Falling. Its Biggest Customer Might Be Masking Larger Problems.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/arm-softbank-stock-price-9352cbfa?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings from  Arm Holdings  have consistently met or exceeded Wall Street’s expectations in recent quarters.  Japan’s  SoftBank Group  owns around 90% of Arm, and it is also the company’s cornerstone customer.  Once SoftBank’s purchases are taken out of the equation, Arm’s growth prospects look dim heading into 2026, BofA said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/arm-softbank-stock-price-9352cbfa?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Five factors that could make Alphabet the world’s most valuable company</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/five-factors-could-alphabet-world-180312961.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Bank of America said Alphabet’s momentum entering 2026 reflects a shift in AI sentiment and a strengthening competitive position, arguing that several catalysts could help push the company’s valuation higher, potentially making it the world’s most valuable firm.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/five-factors-could-alphabet-world-180312961.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] US Nears Taiwan Trade Deal Tied to Major TSMC Arizona Expansion</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-nears-taiwan-trade-deal-175859956.html</link><description>Proposed agreement would cut US tariffs on Taiwanese goods to 15% and add at least four new TSMC chip fabs in Arizona.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-nears-taiwan-trade-deal-175859956.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Hyundai Motor Shares Hit Records as Robotics Drive $24 Billion Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hyundai-motor-shares-hit-records-175641807.html</link><description>Hyundai Motor group stocks surge after Atlas robot debut and Nvidia partnership lifts robotics optimism.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hyundai-motor-shares-hit-records-175641807.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Quantum Computing Stocks: UBS Eyes IBM, Google, IonQ. Infleqtion To Go Public.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-ubs-eyes-ibm-google-ionq/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Add UBS to the growing number of Wall Street firms paying attention to quantum computing stocks. UBS says IBM and Google bear watching.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/quantum-computing-stocks-ubs-eyes-ibm-google-ionq/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Market Movers: Wall Street Loves Big Tech as 2026 Kicks Off</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/market-movers-wall-street-loves-big-tech-as-2026-kicks-off/</link><description>Analysts at KeyBanc just upgraded Intel (NASDAQ: INTC) and Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ: AMD) to an overweight rating, noting that both are benefiting from hyperscaler demand. As a result, AMD is up about $7.67 in premarket. INTC is up about $1.80 a share. The firm raised its price target on INTC. “Analyst John Vinh pointed ... Market Movers: Wall Street Loves Big Tech as 2026 Kicks Off</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/13/market-movers-wall-street-loves-big-tech-as-2026-kicks-off/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Tops $4 Trillion as AI Revival Fuels Record Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-ai-175514217.html</link><description>New deal with Apple and strong Gemini adoption drive momentum in record-setting year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-tops-4-trillion-ai-175514217.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Clarifies No Upfront Payment Required for H200 AI Chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-clarifies-no-upfront-payment-175436676.html</link><description>Chipmaker says customers won't pay before delivery amid China trade scrutiny.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-clarifies-no-upfront-payment-175436676.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Spotify Is Fighting Listener Fatigue. AI Is Central to the Plan</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-fighting-listener-fatigue-ai-174617931.html</link><description>Spotify Turns to AI and Video as User Boredom Grows</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spotify-fighting-listener-fatigue-ai-174617931.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel Stock Jumps After Top Analyst Boosts Rating to 'Overweight'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-jumps-top-analyst-174224790.html</link><description>Intel Stock Jumps on Strong AI Infrastructure Orders</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-jumps-top-analyst-174224790.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft and Apple Could Join the $4 Trillion Club in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-apple-could-join-4-173405211.html</link><description>Tech Titans Eye $4 Trillion Market Value Amid Enterprise AI Boom</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-apple-could-join-4-173405211.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Alphabet Stock Jumped 65% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/why-alphabet-stock-jumped-65-in-2025/</link><description>The emergence of AI and a legal victory lifted the stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/13/why-alphabet-stock-jumped-65-in-2025/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Crypto Billionaire Michael Saylor Names Nvidia, Bitcoin Among 'Best Performing Assets' Of The Decade: Here's How They've Performed</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-billionaire-michael-saylor-names-173115271.html</link><description>Strategy Inc. (NASDAQ:MSTR) Executive Chair Michael Saylor highlighted on Sunday that the company has surpassed Wall Street giants since adopting the Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC)-focused approach, trailing only Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA). ‘Best-Performing Assets’ Of The Decade Saylor posted a chart on...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-billionaire-michael-saylor-names-173115271.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nasdaq Is Getting a Boost From Some Big Tech Names</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011326/card/nasdaq-gets-a-boost-from-some-big-tech-names-lKJ52KHXyyhgp7tsQC0C?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Nasdaq Composite turned back around in early Tuesday afternoon trading.  The Dow, which was weighed down by struggles among its larger stocks like Salesforce, Visa, and JPMorgan Chase, was down 275 points, or 0.6%.  A rally in Alphabet, up 2.4%, and Nvidia, up 1.4%, helped lift the Nasdaq.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-011326/card/nasdaq-gets-a-boost-from-some-big-tech-names-lKJ52KHXyyhgp7tsQC0C?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China limits Nvidia chip purchases to special circumstances, Information reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-limits-nvidia-chip-purchases-172555875.html</link><description>The Chinese government this week told some tech companies it would only approve ​their purchases of Nvidia's H200 AI chips under special ‌circumstances, such as for university research, the Information reported on Tuesday, ‌citing two people with direct knowledge of the situation.  The move signals Beijing is remaining cautious about fully reopening the Chinese market to Nvidia, whose semiconductors are pivotal in operating ⁠the most advanced ‌artificial intelligence applications and data centers.  China's government issued a "deliberately vague" directive, the report said, telling ‍some technology firms to buy chips only when "necessary" but was unclear as to what that means.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-limits-nvidia-chip-purchases-172555875.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] VRT's Robust Portfolio Fuels Revenue Growth: More Upside Ahead?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vrts-robust-portfolio-fuels-revenue-171600047.html</link><description>Vertiv's broad data center portfolio and focus on innovation are driving growth momentum, despite competition heating up across the industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vrts-robust-portfolio-fuels-revenue-171600047.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Greenfield site development will lead to changes in data centre design in 2026</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/greenfield-site-development-data-centre-design-2026/</link><description>2026 will witness strong growth in inference-optimised chips, alongside traditional, more expensive, GPUs for foundation models.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/greenfield-site-development-data-centre-design-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly teams up with Nvidia on AI lab: CFO explains why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/eli-lilly-teams-nvidia-ai-171233886.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (LLY) is teaming up with Nvidia (NVDA) to invest in an artificial intelligence (AI) innovation lab. Eli Lilly CFO and executive vice president Lucas Montarce joins Market Catalysts host Julie Hyman to discuss how the pharmaceutical company is leveraging AI to expedite drug discovery. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Catalysts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/eli-lilly-teams-nvidia-ai-171233886.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Will Vertiv (VRT) Beat Estimates Again in Its Next Earnings Report?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-beat-estimates-again-171003520.html</link><description>Vertiv (VRT) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-beat-estimates-again-171003520.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] AstraZeneca to acquire Modella AI to speed oncology drug research</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/astrazeneca-acquire-modella-ai-speed-170943466.html</link><description>AstraZeneca has agreed to buy Boston-based Modella AI, the companies said on Tuesday, as the drug industry ​increases its use of artificial intelligence to accelerate the discovery of ‌new drugs.  The companies did not disclose financial terms.  In a press release, Modella AI said its "foundation ‌models" and AI agents would be integrated into oncology research and development to support clinical development and biomarker discovery.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/astrazeneca-acquire-modella-ai-speed-170943466.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia is a 'very boring idea' and could lose its market cap crown, says market veteran</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-is-a-very-boring-idea-and-could-lose-its-market-cap-crown-says-market-veteran-170753022.html</link><description>A "nasty" 15% sell-off could hit crowded trades this spring, says Tom Sosnoff.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-is-a-very-boring-idea-and-could-lose-its-market-cap-crown-says-market-veteran-170753022.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Dow Jones Retail Giant Amazon Stock Eyes Latest Buy Point</title><link>https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/stocks-near-a-buy-zone/dow-jones-amazon-amzn-stock-buy-point-eli-lilly/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Dow Jones retail giant Amazon is approaching a fresh buy point, as the stock market holds near record highs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/stocks-near-a-buy-zone/dow-jones-amazon-amzn-stock-buy-point-eli-lilly/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:06:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Intel (INTC) Stock Is Trading Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-trading-170120072.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) jumped 6.2% in the morning session after Keybanc upgraded the stock's rating to 'Overweight' from 'Sector Weight' and set a new price target of $60.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-intel-intc-stock-trading-170120072.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>