<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[ASML] Prediction: ASML Stock Could Surge 70%, According to a Wall Street Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/prediction-asml-stock-could-surge-70-according-to/</link><description>ASML's key role in the global chip market could help the company land more orders as its customers increase their capital spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/prediction-asml-stock-could-surge-70-according-to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Rocket Lab's Path To Neutron Launch: Breaking Tanks To Break Records</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rocket-labs-path-neutron-launch-163226528.html</link><description>In the high-stakes world of aerospace development, the difference between a successful orbit and a catastrophic mission failure is often found at the absolute edge of a pressure gauge. Rocket Lab's latest update on its medium-lift Neutron rocket serves as a reminder of this reality: to build a vehicle that breaks industry records, the company must first be willing to break it on the ground. During a scheduled qualification trial on Tuesday evening, Neutron's Stage 1 tank experienced a structural</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rocket-labs-path-neutron-launch-163226528.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You'd Invested $1,000 in Nvidia 5 Years Ago, Here's How Much You'd Have Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/if-youd-invested-1000-in-nvidia-5-years-ago-heres/</link><description>It would've been one of the smartest moves you could've made at the time.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/if-youd-invested-1000-in-nvidia-5-years-ago-heres/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI Data Center Power Deal With Alphabet Could Be A Game Changer For NextEra Energy (NEE)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-data-center-power-deal-160545699.html</link><description>In recent months, NextEra Energy has been highlighted as a high‑growth clean energy utility at the center of AI‑driven power demand, underpinned by stable cash flows from Florida Power &amp;amp; Light and a large renewables backlog, while also entering a 25‑year nuclear power supply deal with Alphabet for data centers. An interesting angle is how this blend of regulated utility earnings, long‑dated AI data‑center contracts, and heavy investment in wind, solar, nuclear, and transmission is reshaping...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-data-center-power-deal-160545699.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Predicted TSMC Would Be a Must-Own Stock in 2025. I Still Think It's a Fantastic Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/predict-tsmc-would-be-must-own-stock-buy-2026/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing will benefit from the same tailwinds in 2026 as it did in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/predict-tsmc-would-be-must-own-stock-buy-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Discusses President Trump &amp; CoreWeave (CRWV)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-president-trump-153422838.html</link><description>We recently published 14 Stocks Jim Cramer Talked About. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV), along with Oracle, is a key player in the AI infrastructure space. Cramer has discussed the stock several times over the past couple of months and commented on the firm’s close […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-president-trump-153422838.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel Won't Rush Costly Chip Capacity Buildout Despite AI Boom, Even As Rivals TSMC And Samsung Spend Big Bucks: Here's Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-wont-rush-costly-chip-153108516.html</link><description>On Thursday, Intel Corp. (NASDAQ:INTC) said it will not accelerate major chip capacity investments without clearer customer commitments, even as rivals Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (NYSE:TSMC) and Samsung Electronics Co. (OTC:SSNLF) ramp up spending. Intel Prioritizes Discipline Over Speed In AI Expansion During the company's fourth-quarter earnings call, Intel struck a cautious tone on capacity expansion, pushing back against concerns that it could fall behind in the intensifying AI-d</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-wont-rush-costly-chip-153108516.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] How to Give Away $150 Billion: Warren Buffett’s Kids Face Task of Unloading His Fortune Over a Decade</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-warren-buffett-stock-estate-planning-children-b7ee7288?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The former Berkshire Hathaway CEO’s three children probably will become the most influential philanthropists in the world after their father dies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-warren-buffett-stock-estate-planning-children-b7ee7288?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] This Tech Stock Could Turn $1,000 Into $16,000</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/this-tech-stock-could-turn-1000-into-16000/</link><description>A little patience could go a long way for investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/this-tech-stock-could-turn-1000-into-16000/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Says FSD's $99/Month Subscription Fee Will Rise As Tesla Scraps Autopilot In US: 'You Can Be On Your Phone…'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-fsds-99-143103862.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared that the company's Full Self-Driving (FSD) system will record a price hike as technology gets better. FSD Price Hike On Thursday, Musk took to the social media platform X to share the news. "The $99/month for supervised FSD will rise as FSD's capabilities improve," the billionaire shared. He added that the "value jump" would happen once Unsupervised FSD comes into play. "You can be on your phone or sleeping for the entire ride," he said. I should</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-fsds-99-143103862.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang Frames AI as the Largest Infrastructure Buildout in Human History</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-ceo-jensen-huang-142926253.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the best stocks to buy and hold for 20 years. On January 21, 2026, NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang appeared on the World Economic Forum stage in Davos, framing AI as “the largest infrastructure buildout in human history.” He sees AI not as a single technology cycle but […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-ceo-jensen-huang-142926253.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Guggenheim Reduces PT on Eli Lilly and Company (LLY) to $1,161, Reiterates ‘Buy’ Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/guggenheim-reduces-pt-eli-lilly-142916084.html</link><description>Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) is one of the best stocks to buy and hold for 20 years. On January 20, 2026, Guggenheim reduced its price target on Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) from $1,163 to $1,161, while reiterating a ‘Buy’ rating. The update came as the firm made a routine model update ahead of […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/guggenheim-reduces-pt-eli-lilly-142916084.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway (BRK-B) Looks to Exit Its 27.5% Stake in Kraft Heinz</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-b-looks-142914725.html</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway Inc. (NYSE:BRK-B) is included in our list of the best stocks to buy and hold for 20 years. On January 20, 2026, Reuters reported that Berkshire Hathaway Inc. (NYSE:BRK-B) is possibly exiting its 27.5% stake in Kraft Heinz. The company has made investments in the food and beverage stock for the past ten years. However, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-b-looks-142914725.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VEA] VEA vs. ACWX: Cheap International Exposure or Full Global Access?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/etfs/2026/01/24/vea-vs-acwx-cheap-international-exposure-or-full-global-access/</link><description>Explore how key differences in sector exposure, holdings, and cost structure could impact your international ETF strategy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/etfs/2026/01/24/vea-vs-acwx-cheap-international-exposure-or-full-global-access/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Trump Adviser Says Crypto Market Structure Bill Is A 'Question Of When, Not If,' Argues Industry Cannot Continue To Run Without It</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-adviser-says-crypto-market-140211314.html</link><description>The cryptocurrency industry has been chided for its obstinacy over the Senate’s cryptocurrency market structure bill by Patrick Witt, executive director of the President’s Council of Advisors for Digital Assets. "‘No bill is better than a bad bill,'" Witt said...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-adviser-says-crypto-market-140211314.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Notable open interest changes for January 23rd</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/notable-open-interest-changes-january-140135546.html</link><description>Thursday’s total option volume of 66.7 million contracts resulted in net open interest growth of 9.22 million calls and 6.95 million puts. NVIDIA (NVDA), Intel (INTC), Tesla (TSLA) and Netflix (NFLX) saw the greatest growth. Top five new positions opened include 145k Netflix (NFLX) Sep-26 100 calls, 127k NVIDIA (NVDA) 1/30 weekly 165 puts, 122k Netflix (NFLX) Sep-26 120 calls, 60k Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) 1/30 weekly 220 puts and 48k Broadcom (AVGO) 1/30 weekly 297.5 puts.Claim 50% Off TipRa</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/notable-open-interest-changes-january-140135546.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Morning Movers: Nvidia up after report of potential China move on H200 chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-movers-nvidia-report-potential-135536896.html</link><description>Stock futures are modestly lower, pressured in part by Intel’s sharp pre-market slide following a weak outlook from the chipmaker and ongoing geopolitical uncertainty. Markets are trading mixed and cautiously softer on Friday after a volatile week that has reflected shifting investor sentiment around geopolitics, earnings, and economic data. Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing tools for smarter, sharper decisions Stay ahead of the market with the lat</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morning-movers-nvidia-report-potential-135536896.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 7 Stocks Are Analyst Favorites For Magnificent Earnings Growth; Google Stock Holds Near Buy Point</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/best-stocks-seven-magnificent-stocks-earnings-growth/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Among the best stocks in earnings performance, Broadcom boasts a 98 EPS Rating, one of the highest in the chip sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/best-stocks-seven-magnificent-stocks-earnings-growth/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet vs. Meta Platforms: Which AI Stock Will Make You Richer?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/alphabet-meta-platforms-ai-stock-make-you-rich/</link><description>These powerful internet companies are thriving in the age of AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/alphabet-meta-platforms-ai-stock-make-you-rich/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] 1 Vanguard ETF I'm Buying in 2026 and Holding Forever</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/1-vanguard-etf-im-buying-in-2026-holding-forever/</link><description>The U.S. stock market is experiencing a big rotation in 2026 that's been great for small caps and cyclicals, but not so much for tech. That makes this Vanguard ETF an ideal pick-up in the new year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/1-vanguard-etf-im-buying-in-2026-holding-forever/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Stays Constructive on Cognex (CGNX) as Industrial Tech Demand Holds Up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-stays-constructive-cognex-cgnx-114958829.html</link><description>Cognex Corporation (NASDAQ:CGNX) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 12, Barclays trimmed its price target on Cognex Corporation (NASDAQ:CGNX) to $54 from $56, while keeping an Overweight rating on the stock. The move came as part of the firm’s broader 2026 outlook for industrial technology and distribution […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-stays-constructive-cognex-cgnx-114958829.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Updates First American Financial (FAF) in Broader Coverage Reset</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-first-american-financial-114754482.html</link><description>First American Financial Corporation (NYSE:FAF) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 6, Barclays slightly lowered its price target on First American Financial Corporation (NYSE:FAF) to $68 from $71, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The firm’s broader 2026 outlook suggests it still sees opportunity […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-updates-first-american-financial-114754482.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] What Are the 3 Top Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks to Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/what-are-the-3-top-artificial-intelligence-stock/</link><description>AI chip stocks still have a lot of upside from here.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/what-are-the-3-top-artificial-intelligence-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 No-Brainer AI Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/3-no-brainer-ai-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>The AI race is still heating up.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/3-no-brainer-ai-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Initiates Badger Meter (BMI) Coverage, Citing Valuation and Growth Concerns</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-initiates-badger-meter-bmi-112352633.html</link><description>Badger Meter, Inc. (NYSE:BMI) is included among the 14 Best Mid-Cap Dividend Stocks to Buy Now. On January 7, Barclays analyst William Grippin launched coverage of Badger Meter, Inc. (NYSE:BMI) with an Underweight rating and a $157 price target. In his view, Badger is a “solid company with a difficult setup.” He argued that the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-initiates-badger-meter-bmi-112352633.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Oracle's Cash Is Vanishing — But Larry Ellison's Dividend Check Still Clears Tomorrow</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oracles-cash-vanishing-larry-ellisons-110121309.html</link><description>Oracle Corp (NYSE:ORCL) is torching cash to build its AI cloud—but it's still sending billions back to shareholders. That tension is becoming one of the most underappreciated capital allocation stories in Big Tech. On Friday, Oracle will pay out roughly $1.4 billion in dividends, even as analysts expect nearly $23 billion in cash burn this fiscal year. On paper, cutting the dividend looks logical. In reality, it's complicated. Larry Ellison’s Stake Raises The Bar For A Cut Co-founder and executi</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oracles-cash-vanishing-larry-ellisons-110121309.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Is Cadence Design Systems (NASDAQ:CDNS) A Risky Investment?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-nasdaq-cdns-110010098.html</link><description>Warren Buffett famously said, 'Volatility is far from synonymous with risk.' So it seems the smart money knows that...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-design-systems-nasdaq-cdns-110010098.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] TD Cowen Trims Coty Inc. (COTY) Target Ahead of Q4, Keeps Hold Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/td-cowen-trims-coty-inc-104835503.html</link><description>Coty Inc. (NYSE:COTY) is among the overlooked penny stocks to invest in. On January 21, TD Cowen cut the price target on Coty Inc. (NYSE:COTY) to $3.40 from $3.50, and maintained a Hold rating, according to TheFly. This revision, suggesting upside potential of nearly 4%, was part of the firm’s Q4 preview, during which it […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/td-cowen-trims-coty-inc-104835503.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Alphabet Stock Before Feb. 4?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/should-you-buy-alphabet-stock-before-feb-4/</link><description>Alphabet has rocketed to the top of the artificial intelligence (AI) industry over the last few months.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/should-you-buy-alphabet-stock-before-feb-4/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Stock Is Quietly Becoming a Cornerstone of the Artificial Intelligence Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/stock-quietly-becoming-cornerstone-ai-micron/</link><description>Micron Technology's advanced memory chips are proving essential in the AI race.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/stock-quietly-becoming-cornerstone-ai-micron/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The 4 Best AI Stocks to Buy as Trillion-Dollar Tech Shapes a Once-in-a-Lifetime Investment Opportunity</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/4-best-ai-stocks-buy-once-in-lifetime-investment/</link><description>Robotaxis could revolutionize the transportation industry unlike any technology since the automobile was invented.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/4-best-ai-stocks-buy-once-in-lifetime-investment/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Is There An Opportunity With AstraZeneca PLC's (LON:AZN) 46% Undervaluation?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/opportunity-astrazeneca-plcs-lon-azn-092618452.html</link><description>Key Insights Using the 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity, AstraZeneca fair value estimate is UK£250 AstraZeneca's UK£136...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/opportunity-astrazeneca-plcs-lon-azn-092618452.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Poised to Approve Nvidia's H200 Chips for Import. Here's What It Means for Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/china-poised-to-approve-nvidias-h200-chips-for-imp/</link><description>This could be a major catalyst for the AI chipmaker.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/china-poised-to-approve-nvidias-h200-chips-for-imp/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This AI Stock Could Outperform the "Magnificent Seven" by 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/prediction-this-ai-stock-could-outperform-the-magn/</link><description>IREN might be one of the biggest winners as gigawatts become a crucial AI bottleneck.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/prediction-this-ai-stock-could-outperform-the-magn/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2 AI Stocks to Buy Before They Soar to $20 Trillion, According to Wall Street Experts</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/2-ai-stocks-buy-before-soar-20-trillion-wall-stree/</link><description>Nvidia and Tesla could deliver monster returns for shareholders as the AI revolution continues.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/2-ai-stocks-buy-before-soar-20-trillion-wall-stree/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Infrastructure Could Triple to $1.4 Trillion by 2030: Here's the Best Stock to Buy for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/ai-infrastructure-could-triple-to-14-trillion-by-2/</link><description>The data center boom continues to gain steam. There's one clear winner.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/24/ai-infrastructure-could-triple-to-14-trillion-by-2/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How Google’s TPU Assembly Shift Could Reshape Celestica’s Hyperscaler Exposure (TSX:CLS) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-tpu-assembly-shift-could-080829186.html</link><description>In recent days, reports that Google is shifting some tensor processing unit (TPU) server assembly work from Celestica to additional suppliers have raised questions about the company’s role in future AI infrastructure programs. Amid this customer-sourcing uncertainty, Celestica’s strong positioning in AI data center hardware and networking keeps attention firmly on how much hyperscaler demand it can retain and win. We’ll now examine how Google’s reported TPU server assembly shift shapes...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-tpu-assembly-shift-could-080829186.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 08:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang in Shanghai amid China regulatory headwinds</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-shanghai-054808546.html</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang is in Shanghai, a person briefed on the matter said ​on Saturday, as the U.S. chip giant faces fierce ‌competition from local rivals and scrutiny from Chinese authorities.  The timing of Huang's trip, ‌to kick off annual celebrations with Nvidia's China employees, is routine.  He is expected to attend an Nvidia party in Shanghai on Saturday before travelling to Beijing, Shenzhen and then Taiwan, another person with ⁠knowledge of the plans ‌said.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-shanghai-054808546.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Legal AI giant Harvey acquires Hexus as competition heats up in legal tech</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-ai-giant-harvey-acquires-052722699.html</link><description>Hexus founder and CEO Sakshi Pratap, who previously held engineering roles at Walmart, Oracle, and Google, tells TechCrunch that her San Francisco-based team has already joined Harvey, while the startup's India-based engineers will come onboard once Harvey establishes a Bangalore office.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/legal-ai-giant-harvey-acquires-052722699.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Assessing Whether Lam Research (LRCX) Still Offers Value After Strong Recent Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-whether-lam-research-lrcx-042146140.html</link><description>Lam Research stock performance snapshot Lam Research (LRCX) has seen mixed short term moves, with a 1 day return of about a 1.3% decline and a 7 day return of roughly a 2.3% decline, while longer horizons look very different. See our latest analysis for Lam Research. Despite the recent 1 day and 7 day share price pullback, Lam Research’s latest share price of $217.94 sits against a strong backdrop, with a 1 month share price return of 22.90% and a very large 1 year total shareholder return...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-whether-lam-research-lrcx-042146140.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] What Catalysts Are Shifting The Story For ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML)?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/catalysts-shifting-story-asml-holding-042024954.html</link><description>The latest update to ASML Holding has centered on a revised price target, reflecting a shift in how the market is framing the stock’s potential and risks. Without a specific prior or new target disclosed, the key story here is the reasoning behind this adjustment and what it suggests about expectations for the company. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of future changes in the ASML narrative as new targets and commentary emerge. Analyst Price Targets don't always capture the full...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/catalysts-shifting-story-asml-holding-042024954.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How To Earn $500 A Month From SLB Stock Ahead Of Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earn-500-month-slb-stock-033110187.html</link><description>SLB N.V. (NYSE:SLB) will release earnings for the fourth quarter before the opening bell on Friday, Jan. 23. Analysts expect the company to report fourth-quarter earnings of 74 cents per share. That's down from 92 cents per share in the year-ago period. The consensus estimate for SLB's quarterly revenue is $9.55 billion (it reported $9.28 billion last year), according to Benzinga Pro. On Wednesday, Stifel analyst Stephen Gengaro maintained SLB with a Buy rating and raised the price target from $</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earn-500-month-slb-stock-033110187.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] GE Aerospace Backlog Nears $190 Billion As Airlines Spend Big On Engine Upkeep</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ge-aerospace-backlog-nears-190-013133464.html</link><description>GE Aerospace (NYSE:GE) on Thursday reported strong fourth-quarter 2025 results, reflecting continued momentum across its businesses. It posted total revenue (GAAP) of $12.717 billion, up 18% year over year. Sales of $12.717 billion beat the $11.177 billion estimate, and adjusted EPS of $1.57 beat the $1.43 estimate. Continuing EPS (GAAP) was $2.31, up 32%, and adjusted EPS was $1.57, up 19%. Cash from operating activities was $2.096 billion, up 59%, and free cash flow was $1.760 billion, up 15%.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ge-aerospace-backlog-nears-190-013133464.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Is It Time To Reassess IBM (IBM) After Its Recent Share Price Pullback?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-ibm-ibm-recent-011244357.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether International Business Machines (IBM) is still reasonably priced after its long run in tech, this article walks through what the current share price may be implying about value. IBM closed at US$292.44, with a 4.3% decline over the last 7 days and a 4.0% decline over the last 30 days, while its returns stand at 0.3% year to date, 33.5% over 1 year, 142.8% over 3 years and 216.2% over 5 years. These moves have come alongside continued attention on IBM's position...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/time-reassess-ibm-ibm-recent-011244357.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] A Winter Storm Is on Track to Hit Insurers. Why the Damage Could Be Huge.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/winter-storm-us-news-auto-insurance-progressive-eb23a9f0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>A major winter storm advancing across the southern and eastern United States this weekend won’t just test municipal snow crews and utility companies’ gridlines.  With freezing temperatures, snow, sleet, and ice expected to sweep through millions of households, policyholders will likely file loss reports in the weeks and months ahead, ranging from auto accidents and property damage to burst pipes and roof collapses.  Although winter storms are often viewed as less severe weather events than hurricanes or earthquakes, they can lead to meaningful losses for residential and commercial property owners and impact automobiles and infrastructure across a broad swath of the country.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/winter-storm-us-news-auto-insurance-progressive-eb23a9f0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Overlooked Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Could Be a Long-Term Compounder</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/overlooked-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-asml/</link><description>This high-quality business, unfortunately, trades at a lofty valuation.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/overlooked-artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-asml/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Is Daiichi Sankyo (TSE:4568) Turning ENHERTU’s China Approval Into a Durable Oncology Moat?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/daiichi-sankyo-tse-4568-turning-002002430.html</link><description>Earlier this week, Daiichi Sankyo and AstraZeneca received approval in China for ENHERTU as the first HER2-directed antibody-drug conjugate for second-line treatment of HER2 positive metastatic gastric cancer, based on the DESTINY-Gastric04 phase 3 trial showing a survival benefit over ramucirumab plus paclitaxel. This decision opens access to ENHERTU in a country that accounts for more than one third of global gastric cancer cases, highlighting the importance of Daiichi Sankyo’s oncology...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/daiichi-sankyo-tse-4568-turning-002002430.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What Ultra Clean Holdings (UCTT)'s Rising AI Chip Supply-Chain Profile Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-rising-001840733.html</link><description>In the past week, Ultra Clean Holdings drew attention as enthusiasm around the AI chip supply chain lifted suppliers tied to advanced semiconductor manufacturing, following TSMC’s plans to ramp up spending on AI and high-performance chips. Because Ultra Clean provides specialized subsystems and ultra-high purity manufacturing services essential for leading-edge fabs, many investors now view it as a critical enabler of AI-related semiconductor production rather than just a traditional...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-clean-holdings-uctt-rising-001840733.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Mag 7 earnings, Fed's rate decision: What to Watch</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mag-7-earnings-feds-rate-000012663.html</link><description>Market Domination Overtime Host Josh Lipton previews several of the biggest stories to come throughout next week, including a wide array of earnings results due out from major companies like Microsoft (MSFT), Meta Platforms (META), Apple (AAPL), Tesla (TSLA), and many more; and the Federal Reserve's latest interest rate decision followed by a press conference with chairman Jerome Powell. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/mag-7-earnings-feds-rate-000012663.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Bubble or Sustainable Growth? Here Are 2 Healthcare Companies Harnessing AI for the Long Term.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/ai-bubble-growth-healthcare-stocks-bmy-isrg/</link><description>Artificial intelligence may be all the rage in the technology sector, but it's also having a huge impact on healthcare.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/ai-bubble-growth-healthcare-stocks-bmy-isrg/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Surprising Reason Nvidia Looks Recession-Proof in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/the-surprising-reason-nvidia-looks-recession-proof/</link><description>The AI leader is insulated from the machinations of the consumer-level economy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/the-surprising-reason-nvidia-looks-recession-proof/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 catalysts that could drive Nvidia stock higher in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/3-catalysts-could-drive-nvidia-230000225.html</link><description>The Chinese government tells tech companies to prep their Nvidia (NVDA) H200 chip orders, according to Bloomberg. Bernstein managing director and senior analyst Stacy Rasgon — who has a Buy rating on Nvidia — reacts to the headline and compares the supply-demand dynamic for chips in China. Catch Stacy Rasgon also weigh in on the leadership of Intel (INTC) CEO Lip-Bu Tan. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/3-catalysts-could-drive-nvidia-230000225.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway B (BRK.B) Stock Dips While Market Gains: Key Facts</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-b-brk-b-224505646.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, Berkshire Hathaway B (BRK.B) closed at $478.97, indicating a -1.14% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-b-brk-b-224505646.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Stock Sinks As Market Gains: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-stock-sinks-224503485.html</link><description>Eli Lilly (LLY) closed at $1 in the latest trading session, marking a -2.12% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-stock-sinks-224503485.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Waymo Probed by US Safety Agency Over Austin School Bus Mishaps</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-probed-us-safety-agency-224442046.html</link><description>The National Transportation Safety Board will “examine the interaction between Waymo vehicles and school buses stopped for loading and unloading students,” the agency said in a social media post.  The issue had occurred about two dozen times as of earlier this month, according to the Austin Independent School District.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-probed-us-safety-agency-224442046.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 23: Intel's Weak Outlook Weighs on Dow While Nasdaq Edges Higher</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-s-weak-outlook-weighs-on-dow-while-nasdaq-edges-higher/</link><description>Intel's downbeat outlook knocked the Dow while strength in mega-cap and AI names kept the Nasdaq in the green, today, Jan. 23, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-s-weak-outlook-weighs-on-dow-while-nasdaq-edges-higher/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 23: Intel Plunges After Weak Outlook Highlights Supply Constraints and Foundry Losses</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-plunges-after-weak-outlook-highlights-supply-constraints-and-foundry-losses/</link><description>Today, Jan. 23, 2026, investors are weighing whether Intel’s supply snags and foundry losses threaten its AI data-center ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/23/stock-market-today-jan-23-intel-plunges-after-weak-outlook-highlights-supply-constraints-and-foundry-losses/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Dethrones Apple As Taiwan Semiconductor's Largest Customer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dethrones-apple-taiwan-semiconductors-223132958.html</link><description>Nvidia Corp's (NASDAQ:NVDA) surge in artificial intelligence demand is reshaping the global semiconductor supply chain. Nvidia has overtaken Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) as Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd's (NYSE:TSM) largest customer. Nvidia chief Jensen Huang confirmed the change publicly for the first time during a recent podcast. Nvidia now ranks as Taiwan Semiconductor's biggest client—an outcome he suggested would please Taiwan Semiconductor founder Morris Chang. Don't Miss: Missed</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dethrones-apple-taiwan-semiconductors-223132958.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 AI Infrastructure Stocks to Buy as the Market Heads Toward $1.4 Trillion by 2030</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/3-ai-infrastructure-stocks-to-buy-as-the-market-he/</link><description>Nvidia, Equinix, and Digital Realty will profit from the AI boom.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/3-ai-infrastructure-stocks-to-buy-as-the-market-he/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investing $13,000 in These 3 Stocks in 2020 Would Have Made You a Millionaire Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/investing-13000-in-these-3-stocks-in-2020-would-ha/</link><description>All three stocks have soared more than 1,400% since the start of the decade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/investing-13000-in-these-3-stocks-in-2020-would-ha/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Stock Market Today: Dow Falls While Nasdaq Is The Day's Bright Spot (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index slides Friday despite a rise in Nvidia. Small caps sold off after hitting a high on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-greenland-deal-intel-stock-intc/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Dow Jones Futures: Tesla, Microsoft, Meta, Apple Lead Earnings Wave After Whipsaw Trump Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings-wave-trump-week/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Tesla, Microsoft, Meta and Apple lead an earnings wave after the stock market weathered whipsaw action from President Trump's moves</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-tesla-microsoft-meta-apple-earnings-wave-trump-week/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Earnings live: Intel stock plunges, with more Big Tech earnings from Apple, Microsoft, and Tesla ahead</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-intel-stock-plunges-with-more-big-tech-earnings-from-apple-microsoft-and-tesla-ahead-213536730.html</link><description>The fourth quarter earnings season kicks into high gear in the week ahead, with Big Tech results from Microsoft, Meta, Tesla, and Apple headlining the earnings calendar.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/earnings-live-intel-stock-plunges-with-more-big-tech-earnings-from-apple-microsoft-and-tesla-ahead-213536730.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Cathie Wood Thinks AMD Will Challenge Nvidia This Year</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-cathie-wood-thinks-amd-will-challenge-nvidia/</link><description>Should investors be wary of AMD's cheaper data center GPUs?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/why-cathie-wood-thinks-amd-will-challenge-nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Energy Firms Backed by Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates Look to Go Public</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/energy-ai-gates-bezos-ipo-98cd8911?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Two novel energy companies just filed papers to go public, giving investors a chance to buy into trends that could reshape electricity generation in the coming decade—if they work.  Fervo, a geothermal energy company that generates electricity from underground heat, filed confidentially with the SEC to go public, according to Axios.  Fervo is one of the most talked-about clean energy companies in private markets, and just raised $462 million in a Series E fund-raising in December.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/energy-ai-gates-bezos-ipo-98cd8911?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500 cap volatile week with back-to-back weekly losses</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-cap-volatile-week-with-back-to-back-weekly-losses-210233078.html</link><description>Wall Street is faltering as it heads into the end of holiday shortened but rollercoaster week defined by Trump's moves on Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-cap-volatile-week-with-back-to-back-weekly-losses-210233078.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Baillie Gifford's Strategic Moves: Cloudflare Inc. Reduction by 23%</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/baillie-giffords-strategic-moves-cloudflare-210021123.html</link><description>Exploring Baillie Gifford (Trades, Portfolio)'s Fourth Quarter 2025 Investment Adjustments</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/baillie-giffords-strategic-moves-cloudflare-210021123.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Terex, Caterpillar, Titan International, Ryder, and Littelfuse Shares Are Falling, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/terex-caterpillar-titan-international-ryder-205044687.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell as much as 0.7%, reflecting lingering uncertainty, and capping off a volatile week which saw stocks enjoy some relief as President Donald Trump reduced tensions with European allies by backing off his threat of imposing new tariffs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/terex-caterpillar-titan-international-ryder-205044687.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Top Stocks to Double Up on Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/top-stocks-to-double-up-on-right-now/</link><description>These stocks look like market-beaters over the next five years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/top-stocks-to-double-up-on-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Intel stock plunges as hopes for a 'clean' turnaround story meet reality</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-plunges-as-hopes-for-a-clean-turnaround-story-meet-reality-202949131.html</link><description>Intel stock plunged on Friday following the chipmaker's disappointing first quarter outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-plunges-as-hopes-for-a-clean-turnaround-story-meet-reality-202949131.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] These Two Charts Sum Up the AI Stock Rally in 2026</title><link>https://www.investopedia.com/these-two-charts-sum-up-the-ai-stock-rally-in-2026-11891429</link><description>Artificial intelligence is once again fueling a scorching tech stock rally, but the rising tide is notably not lifting all boats.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investopedia.com/these-two-charts-sum-up-the-ai-stock-rally-in-2026-11891429</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel vs. TSMC: Can Intel Close the Gap?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-tsmc-intel-close-195400413.html</link><description>Intel stock is selling off following its earnings report, but is there more to this story?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-vs-tsmc-intel-close-195400413.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Stock Plunges: Time To Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-stock-plunges-time-to-buy-the-dip/</link><description>Intel's guidance disappointed the market. Is the turnaround story still alive?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/intel-stock-plunges-time-to-buy-the-dip/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 6 of My Top 10 Stocks for 2025 Increased by More Than 25%. Are They Still Buys Now?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/6-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-increased-by-more-t/</link><description>The market delivered a strong gain in 2025, but it was no match for these stock picks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/6-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-increased-by-more-t/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Ripple CEO Weighs In On Crypto Bill: 'We're So Close We Can't Give Up Now'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ripple-ceo-weighs-crypto-bill-193110821.html</link><description>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse on Thursday commented on the CLARITY Act, saying ” “we’re so close we can’t give up now” with regards to delayed crypto bill after Coinbase Global Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) withdrew support. Garlinghouse Defends The Bill Garlinghouse called...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ripple-ceo-weighs-crypto-bill-193110821.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 2 AI Stocks Make Excellent Long-Term Plays to Buy in January</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-ai-stocks-make-excellent-long-term-plays-to-buy/</link><description>The best AI stocks aren't always the hidden gems.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/2-ai-stocks-make-excellent-long-term-plays-to-buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tesla is a 'believe or not' religion, not a stock based on fundamentals: Robinhood exec</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-a-believe-or-not-religion-not-a-stock-based-on-fundamentals-robinhood-exec-192320023.html</link><description>As the EV giant prepares to report fourth quarter earnings on Jan. 28, retail sentiment remains detached from traditional valuation metrics.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-a-believe-or-not-religion-not-a-stock-based-on-fundamentals-robinhood-exec-192320023.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Investor Bets $100k On David v Goliath Matchup With Altimmune and Eli Lilly</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investor-bets-100k-on-david-v-goliath-matchup-with-altimmune-and-eli-lilly/</link><description>Shares of Altimmune (NASDAQ:ALT) surged 35.4% over the past week, coinciding with a dramatic shift in retail investor sentiment on Reddit. The clinical-stage biotech develops treatments for metabolic diseases and became one of the highest-rated stocks in social sentiment tracking after the FDA granted Breakthrough Therapy Designation for its lead drug pemvidutide on January 16. ... Investor Bets $100k On David v Goliath Matchup With Altimmune and Eli Lilly</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investor-bets-100k-on-david-v-goliath-matchup-with-altimmune-and-eli-lilly/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock Could Define the Next Chapter of the Tech Market</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-next-tech-uipath/</link><description>UiPath could be set to define the AI agent market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/artificial-intelligence-ai-stock-next-tech-uipath/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Stocks: Nvidia, Amgen Are Near Buy Points But This Longtime Loser Is Winning The Week</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stocks-nvidia-amgen-buy-points-procter-gamble/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>JPMorgan upgraded long-ailing consumer goods giant Procter &amp;amp; Gamble. Nvidia and Amgen are among several Dow Jones stocks near buy points.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/dow-jones-stocks-nvidia-amgen-buy-points-procter-gamble/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Forget Quantum Computing Stock: Buy This Dividend‑Paying Quantum Pioneer, And Never Sell</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-quantum-computing-stock-buy-this-dividendpa/</link><description>IBM is a more balanced play on this secular trend.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-quantum-computing-stock-buy-this-dividendpa/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] TSLA: Tesla Stock Slides as Robotaxi Autonomy Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsla-tesla-stock-slides-robotaxi-181400328.html</link><description>Musk's No-Monitor Claim Faces Scrutiny; TSLA Investors Cautious</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsla-tesla-stock-slides-robotaxi-181400328.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Fei-Fei Li's World Labs Discusses Funding at $5 Billion Valuation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fei-fei-lis-world-labs-181347025.html</link><description>AI startup World Labs is in talks to raise hundreds of millions, potentially adding about $500 million to its balance sheet.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fei-fei-lis-world-labs-181347025.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Applied Materials Stock Rises On Deutsche Bank Upgrade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-stock-rises-deutsche-181343411.html</link><description>Applied Materials Gains Analyst Support Amid Rising Memory Capex</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/applied-materials-stock-rises-deutsche-181343411.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Morgan Stanley Names ASML and ASMI as Top Pick Ahead of Q4 Results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-names-asml-asmi-181200829.html</link><description>ASML and ASMI Set to Surge as Morgan Stanley Calls Breakthrough Quarter Ahead</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-names-asml-asmi-181200829.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China--Nvidia Ties Appear Back On</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-nvidia-ties-appear-back-180834649.html</link><description>Officials move to restart H200 order preparations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-nvidia-ties-appear-back-180834649.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Should You Forget Eli Lilly and Buy These Unstoppable Stocks Instead?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-eli-lilly-buy-these-unstoppable-stock/</link><description>Eli Lilly's valuation has been driven higher by investor excitement around GLP-1 drugs, leaving other drugmakers languishing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/forget-eli-lilly-buy-these-unstoppable-stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia, IBD Stock Of The Day, Looks To Finally Score China Sales</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/nvidia-stock-nvda-looks-to-score-china-sales/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia is the IBD Stock Of The Day as signs point to the AI chipmaker finally regaining access to the China market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/nvidia-stock-nvda-looks-to-score-china-sales/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] LRCX Likely to Beat Q2 Earnings Estimates: Should You Buy the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcx-likely-beat-q2-earnings-174700059.html</link><description>Lam Research's Q2 results are likely to reflect benefits from strong demand for AI chips and rising DRAM spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lrcx-likely-beat-q2-earnings-174700059.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investors Are Acting As if QQQ Is the Perfect Investment Right Now (And Maybe It Actually Is)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investors-are-acting-as-if-qqq-is-the-perfect-investment-right-now-and-maybe-it-actually-is/</link><description>Shares of the Invesco QQQ Trust (NASDAQ:QQQ) are having a good week, coinciding with a surge in retail investor sentiment on Reddit and X. The fund now carries a social sentiment score of 90, one of the highest readings tracked across all ETFs and stocks. This optimism centers on aggressive options positioning, particularly in the ... Investors Are Acting As if QQQ Is the Perfect Investment Right Now (And Maybe It Actually Is)</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/23/investors-are-acting-as-if-qqq-is-the-perfect-investment-right-now-and-maybe-it-actually-is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Is Arm Holdings' High Valuation Testing Market Patience?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-high-valuation-testing-174400152.html</link><description>ARM faces pressure as a premium valuation demands near-term proof, with delayed licensing revenues and thin patience testing today's expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-high-valuation-testing-174400152.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] NVIDIA (NVDA) Invests $150 million in Baseten</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-invests-150-million-173323306.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the Best Quantum Computing Stocks to Buy for 2026. On January 20, WSJ reported that the company is investing $150 million in Baseten, a startup that specializes in AI inference. Baseten has raised $300 million at a $5 billion valuation. This deal demonstrates NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA)’s aggressive push into […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-invests-150-million-173323306.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] At 22, He's Making $120K And Asks If He Should Buy A Duplex And Continue Living With His Parents. 'I Wanna Make My Money Work For Me'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/22-hes-making-120k-asks-173109029.html</link><description>A 22-year-old with a $120,000 annual salary turned to Reddit for advice on whether to buy a duplex while continuing to live rent-free with his parents. The poster has already maxed out his 401(k), saved $32,000 in cash, and built up $6,000 in an investment account. “I wanna make my money work for me and make more money,” he wrote on r/personalfinance recently. Redditors Say He’s Crushing It Financially Commenters were quick to praise his financial habits, with many encouraging him to stay with h</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/22-hes-making-120k-asks-173109029.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] China Signals H200 Purchase Preparations for Alibaba, Tencent, ByteDance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-signals-h200-purchase-preparations-172248794.html</link><description>Regulators gave in-principle approval for talks on Nvidia's H200 orders, with domestic chip buying encouraged as a condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-signals-h200-purchase-preparations-172248794.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel’s High-Flying Stock Wasn’t Priced for Reality</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-s-high-flying-stock-wasn-t-priced-for-reality-3Yfq0Pade7OOtd1bIAN2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel is on pace for its worst selloff in nearly 18 months.  Intel was down nearly 17% Friday.  The selloff came after the company’s fourth-quarter report made clear that Intel’s turnaround is still a work in progress.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-01-23-2026/card/intel-s-high-flying-stock-wasn-t-priced-for-reality-3Yfq0Pade7OOtd1bIAN2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Invests in Japan's Sakana AI to Boost Gemini</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-invests-japans-sakana-ai-170657856.html</link><description>Partnership aims to speed AI adoption in secure sectors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-invests-japans-sakana-ai-170657856.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:06:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly Stock Rebounds As Weight-Loss Drug Battle Continues</title><link>https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/sector-leaders/eli-lilly-stock-lly-orforglipron-weight-loss-drugs/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Eli Lilly stock has been climbing back from a recent pullback and nearing a buy point. The drugmaker teamed up with Nvidia on a new project.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/stock-lists/sector-leaders/eli-lilly-stock-lly-orforglipron-weight-loss-drugs/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] This Semiconductor Stock Could Be at the Center of the Artificial Intelligence Spending Boom</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/semiconductor-stock-center-ai-spending-micron/</link><description>Micron is in a prime position to benefit from the increasing demand for high-bandwidth memory.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/23/semiconductor-stock-center-ai-spending-micron/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>