<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[TSM] Where Will TSMC Stock Be in 1 Year?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/where-will-tsmc-stock-be-in-1-year/</link><description>TSMC's latest quarterly results make it clear that the stock is poised for more gains in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/where-will-tsmc-stock-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Nvidia, Broadcom, Micron Stocks Jump -- JPMorgan Flags as Top Chip Picks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-micron-stocks-jump-192512678.html</link><description>Chip Stocks Rise After JPMorgan Names Nvidia, Broadcom, Micron Top Picks</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-micron-stocks-jump-192512678.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Links AI Expansion to Data Center Jobs Boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-links-ai-expansion-data-192041942.html</link><description>CEO Jensen Huang says AI-driven data center buildouts are boosting vocational wages as Nvidia's data center sales surge.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-links-ai-expansion-data-192041942.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Colgate-Palmolive (CL) Valuation Check After Defensive Rotation And Upgraded Analyst Views</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</link><description>Recent commentary from Barclays and Wells Fargo has pushed Colgate-Palmolive (CL) into focus, as both banks highlight growing investor interest in the stock as a defensive option while maintaining a cautious stance on fundamentals. See our latest analysis for Colgate-Palmolive. The recent analyst comments and Colgate-Palmolive’s new four year collaboration with the WHO Foundation come as the shares trade at US$85.44. The 30 day share price return is 9.04% and the year to date share price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colgate-palmolive-cl-valuation-check-191617935.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Says AI Buildout Will Run Into Trillions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-buildout-191613051.html</link><description>CEO Jensen Huang forecasts trillion-dollar AI buildout at Davos.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-buildout-191613051.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT) Valuation Check After Recent Share Price Pullbacks And Longer Term Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-valuation-191434706.html</link><description>Vertiv Holdings Co: recent performance snapshot Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT) has kept investors busy recently, with the stock showing a mix of short term pullbacks and longer term strength. This has prompted closer attention to how its fundamentals line up with its current price. Over the past day, Vertiv’s share price recorded a 0.99% decline, while the past week shows a 1.42% gain and roughly 9.61% return over the past month. This highlights uneven but positive recent momentum. See our latest...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-holdings-co-vrt-valuation-191434706.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How President Trump and Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang's Davos moves helped dip-buying investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/how-president-trump-and-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huangs-davos-moves-helped-dip-buying-investors-191036008.html</link><description>Welcome back, "buy the dip" fans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/how-president-trump-and-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huangs-davos-moves-helped-dip-buying-investors-191036008.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Veteran analyst revisits key semiconductor stock amid tech earnings season</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/veteran-analyst-revisits-key-chip-stock-amid-earnings-season</link><description>Shares of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM) slid 4.45% on Jan. 20, erasing most of last week’s post-earnings gains amid a broader market slump. The company is the world’s largest chip foundry and a critical manufacturer for Nvidia (NVDA), AMD (AMD), and Broadcom (AVGO). Its earnings ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/veteran-analyst-revisits-key-chip-stock-amid-earnings-season</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Confirms AI4-Powered Cars Can Achieve Unsupervised Self-Driving Without Additional Upgrades</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has confirmed that the automaker's vehicles equipped with the AI4 (HW4) chip will be able to achieve unsupervised autonomous driving without requiring upgrades. AI4 Will Be Capable Of Self-Driving On Monday, user @iliketeslas shared a post on the social media platform X, stating that the current AI4 chips are capable of running Unsupervised FSD without "better hardware." Anyone using AI4 right now knows that better hardware is not needed for unsupervised dr</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-ai4-powered-190115481.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] 2026’s Biggest AI Trends: The Rise of AI Factories | VRT Stock, NVT Stock, MOD Stock</title><link>https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</link><description>24/7 Wall St. Analysts Eric Bleeker and Austin Smith are kicking the New Year off in style with 12 trends for AI investors to watch in 2026. Over the course of 12 videos, the two will share their thoughts on everything from the memory explosion to software stocks to robotics. In this video, Eric takes a deeper look at the rise of AI factories, massive data centers with a capacity of more than 1 gigawatt. As Eric notes, it's not just Oracle's Stargate getting into the race. There are also new super factories from Microsoft, Amazon, Meta, and many others. Companies with data center cooling portfolios like Vertiv (NYSE: VRT), nVent Electric (NYSE: NVT), Modine Manufacturing (NYSE: MOD) could be winners as the construction of this new generation of data centers takes off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/videos/2026s-biggest-ai-trends-the-rise-of-ai-factories-vrt-stock-nvt-stock-mod-stock/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Dives Deeper Into AI Inference</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dives-deeper-ai-inference-185420811.html</link><description>Inference startup draws heavyweight backing</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-dives-deeper-ai-inference-185420811.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Plans China Visit as AI Chip Sales Face New Limits</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-plans-184842739.html</link><description>Trip aims to strengthen key relationships amid trade restrictions and easing H200 shipments.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-plans-184842739.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tom Nash Says This Energy Stock Could Solve AI's Power Crisis: Sees 7x Upside And 1,400% Revenue Growth In 5 years 'If They Execute'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tom-nash-says-energy-stock-183108000.html</link><description>Investor Tom Nash says this California-based energy company will play a pivotal role in solving AI’s “greatest bottleneck,” that is, reliable power for data centers. Sees 7x Upside Through 2030 Nash, known for earlier bullish calls on Palantir Technologies Inc. (NASDAQ:PLTR) and Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA), is now highlighting fuel-cell maker Bloom Energy Corp. (NYSE:BE) as his next major bet, projecting significant upside in the coming years. On his YouTube channel last week, Nash said that the co</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tom-nash-says-energy-stock-183108000.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Financial Advisor Told Him To Move $50K Out Of His 401(k) Into A Traditional IRA In 2021. Five Years Later, He's Only Up $2K</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financial-advisor-told-him-move-183108073.html</link><description>In 2021, a 34-year-old investor followed what sounded like standard advice. He rolled about $50,000 from his 401(k) into a Traditional IRA with the help of a local financial advisor. Then he did what many people are told to do with retirement money. “I've for the most part ignored it as that was always the advice I was given,” he wrote in Reddit’s personal finance community recently. Five years later, when he finally checked, the account balance was just over $52,000. After one of the strongest</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financial-advisor-told-him-move-183108073.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Why Eli Lilly Is The IBD Stock Of The Day — Again — As Its Novo Nordisk Rivalry Deepens</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/eli-lilly-stock-fda-weight-loss-pill-orforglipron/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Eli Lilly is Wednesday's IBD Stock Of The Day. Lilly shares are bounding off their 50-day line with a new buying opportunity in sight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-of-the-day/eli-lilly-stock-fda-weight-loss-pill-orforglipron/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Dave (DAVE) Quietly Recasting Its Board for an AI-Centric Fintech Strategy?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dave-dave-quietly-recasting-board-181928513.html</link><description>Dave Inc. recently announced that Nima Khajehnouri, a senior artificial intelligence and data engineering leader currently serving as Vice President of Engineering at Meta and formerly at Google and Snap, has joined its Board of Directors and Audit Committee, while Imran Khan has stepped down and several board leadership roles have been reshuffled. This move signals an effort by Dave to deepen its technical governance and innovation capabilities at the board level as it applies advanced...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dave-dave-quietly-recasting-board-181928513.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Is Vertiv (VRT) Still Reasonably Priced After Its Strong Multi Year Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-still-reasonably-priced-181541179.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Vertiv Holdings Co at around US$175.18 is still priced reasonably after its strong run, this article walks through what the numbers are actually saying about value. The stock has returned 1.4% over the past week, 9.6% over the last 30 days, is roughly flat year to date with a 0.2% decline, and has a 22.6% return over the last year, with a very large gain over three and five years. Recent coverage has highlighted Vertiv's role as a provider of power and thermal...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-still-reasonably-priced-181541179.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] How Investors May Respond To Albemarle (ALB) After HSBC Upgrade And Stronger Balance Sheet Focus</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-albemarle-alb-181510476.html</link><description>Earlier this week, HSBC upgraded Albemarle, highlighting expectations of tighter lithium supply and improved company fundamentals including stronger free cash flow and a healthier balance sheet. The bank also pointed to Albemarle’s recent capital raising and operational efficiency efforts as key factors enhancing its leverage in upcoming lithium contract negotiations. Next, we’ll examine how HSBC’s focus on Albemarle’s bolstered balance sheet and lithium market backdrop shapes the company’s...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-may-respond-albemarle-alb-181510476.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI-Enabled Impersonation Scams Drove Record $17B In Crypto Losses In 2025, Chainalysis Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-enabled-impersonation-scams-drove-180809657.html</link><description>A record $17 billion was lost to cryptocurrency scams last year, according to blockchain intelligence company Chainalysis. Chainalysis in a Jan. 13 report said the figure was up from $14 billion in 2024, attributing the surge to an increase in...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-enabled-impersonation-scams-drove-180809657.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron knows something the market is only starting to see</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/economy/micron-knows-something-the-market-is-only-starting-to-see</link><description>Nvidia supplier Micron Technology is airing its opinion regarding an "unprecedented" issue regarding AI, and Wall Street is standing up and taking notice. For now, the chipmaker believes the biggest issue facing the AI sector is a memory shortage that won't go away. Micron believes the issue is ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/economy/micron-knows-something-the-market-is-only-starting-to-see</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Red-Hot Growth Stocks to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-red-hot-growth-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</link><description>These companies boast different strengths that help them succeed with AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/3-red-hot-growth-stocks-to-buy-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Scott Black's Strategic Moves: M&amp;T Bank Corp Leads the Way with 1.48% Portfolio Impact</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/scott-blacks-strategic-moves-m-180122620.html</link><description>Insight into Scott Black (Trades, Portfolio)'s Fourth Quarter 2025 Investment Strategy</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/scott-blacks-strategic-moves-m-180122620.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Did Nvidia’s CEO Just Deliver the Ultimate Buy Signal for Nebius?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/did-nvidias-ceo-just-deliver-the-ultimate-buy-signal-for-nebius/</link><description>Nebius Group (NASDAQ:NBIS) is forecasting up to 1,600% revenue growth by the end of 2026, driven by surging demand for AI compute infrastructure. The company projects an annualized run rate in revenue of $900 million to $1.1 billion for the end of 2025 and $7 billion to $9 billion by the end of 2026, as ... Did Nvidia’s CEO Just Deliver the Ultimate Buy Signal for Nebius?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/did-nvidias-ceo-just-deliver-the-ultimate-buy-signal-for-nebius/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] OpenEvidence hits $12B valuation, with new round led by Thrive, DST</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openevidence-hits-12b-valuation-round-180111298.html</link><description>The medical info database has doubled in valuation since last raise in October, despite encroachment from model makers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/openevidence-hits-12b-valuation-round-180111298.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Vertiv (VRT) is an Incredible Growth Stock: 3 Reasons Why</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-incredible-growth-stock-174502172.html</link><description>Vertiv (VRT) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertiv-vrt-incredible-growth-stock-174502172.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Super Semiconductor Stock Crushed Nvidia in 2025, and Jan. 28 Could Be a Very Big Day for Its Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</link><description>This semiconductor equipment powerhouse could be set for another strong year in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-super-semiconductor-stock-crushed-nvidia-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Her Husband Is Facing Up To 10 Years In Prison. 'Ramsey Show' Hosts Urge Her To Take Over His Business, But It's Not That Simple</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/her-husband-facing-10-years-173113681.html</link><description>A recent call to “The Ramsey Show” revealed the emotional and financial chaos one Louisiana woman is trying to navigate after her husband was arrested and could be facing years behind bars. Rental Properties, Two Kids And A Failing Business Plan Megan, a mother of two from Baton Rouge told hosts Jade Warshaw and Ken Coleman that her husband had been arrested just the week before their call. The timeline of his potential sentence isn't yet clear, but it could be anywhere from two to 10 years. Tha</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/her-husband-facing-10-years-173113681.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Big Tech earnings put spotlight on AI and memory shortage as Trump tariff threats loom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</link><description>Big Tech earnings will put a spotlight on the continued AI build-out, memory shortage, and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-earnings-put-spotlight-on-ai-and-memory-shortage-as-trump-tariff-threats-loom-172319701.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Is Micron (MU) Stock Soaring Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</link><description>Shares of memory chips maker Micron (NYSE:MU) jumped 5.9% in the afternoon session after analysts at multiple firms, including Barclays, Stifel, and TD Cowen, raised their price targets on the stock, citing strong demand for its AI-related memory chips.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-micron-mu-stock-soaring-172135089.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Why Fluence Energy (FLNC) Stock Is Trading Lower Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</link><description>Shares of electricity storage and software provider Fluence (NASDAQ:FLNC) fell 1.8% in the afternoon session after Goldman Sachs maintained its 'Buy' rating on the stock and raised its price target.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-fluence-energy-flnc-stock-172102485.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why AMD (AMD) Stock Is Trading Up Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-amd-amd-stock-trading-172043151.html</link><description>Shares of computer processor maker AMD (NASDAQ:AMD) jumped 6.2% in the afternoon session after it received a series of positive developments, including upbeat analyst commentary, a new board appointment, and bullish sentiment on artificial intelligence spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-amd-amd-stock-trading-172043151.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Is CrowdStrike (CRWD) Fairly Priced After Recent Pullback And Cybersecurity Spotlight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether CrowdStrike Holdings is still worth the price you see on your screen, the key question is how that price lines up with what the business may realistically be worth. The stock last closed at US$442.73, after a 5.4% decline over the past week and an 8.0% decline over the past month, although the 1 year return sits at 20.8% and the 3 year return is very large. Recent attention on CrowdStrike has focused on its role as a major cybersecurity provider, as investors...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-crwd-fairly-priced-recent-171056002.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO's Davos message: The AI boom is a data center boom</title><link>https://qz.com/jensen-huang-nvidia-speech-davos-2026</link><description>The Nvidia CEO called AI “the largest infrastructure buildout in human history,” outlining a five-layer stack from energy to applications</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://qz.com/jensen-huang-nvidia-speech-davos-2026</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] TSMC (TSM) Is Up 5.80% in One Week: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-tsm-5-80-one-170003065.html</link><description>Does TSMC (TSM) have what it takes to be a top stock pick for momentum investors? Let's find out.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-tsm-5-80-one-170003065.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway Looks Poised to Break a Buffett Rule With Kraft-Heinz Sale</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-kraft-heinz-sale-3117c936?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Warren Buffett has famously said investors should be “fearful when others are greedy and greedy when others are fearful.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-kraft-heinz-sale-3117c936?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Takes Another Dig At Michael O'Leary Over Buying Ryanair, Says He'll Put A 'Ryan' In Charge: 'It Is Your Destiny'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-takes-another-dig-163110881.html</link><description>Billionaire entrepreneur and Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk once again joked about acquiring Irish ultra-low-cost airline, Ryanair Holdings PLC (NASDAQ:RYAAY). Will Appoint A ‘Ryan’ To Lead The Airline On Monday, in a post on X, Musk replied to Ryanair’s official X account, asking, “How much would it cost to buy you?” in response to the airline dismissing “Wi-Fi on planes” as a propaganda that it wasn’t falling for, in a subtle dig against Musk and his Starlink satellite internet service</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-takes-another-dig-163110881.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia Will Soar in 2026 Thanks to This 1 Thing</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/prediction-nvidia-will-soar-in-2026-thanks-to-this/</link><description>A current trend in the AI market may boost Nvidia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/prediction-nvidia-will-soar-in-2026-thanks-to-this/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Serve Enters Healthcare With Diligent Robotics Acquisition</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/serve-enters-healthcare-diligent-robotics-161400132.html</link><description>SERV enters healthcare with a $29M stock deal for Diligent Robotics, adding Moxi hospital robots and expanding its platform into indoor environments.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/serve-enters-healthcare-diligent-robotics-161400132.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco Systems (CSCO) Valuation Check After New Wi Fi 7 And AI Infrastructure Partnerships</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-valuation-check-161014228.html</link><description>Cisco Systems (CSCO) just announced two high-profile deals, a campus-wide Wi-Fi 7 buildout at Georgetown University and an AI infrastructure tie up with SharonAI and Digital Alpha in Asia Pacific, drawing fresh attention to the stock. See our latest analysis for Cisco Systems. Despite the fresh Georgetown and SharonAI announcements, Cisco’s share price has eased in the short term, with a 1 month share price return of 6.47% decline and a year to date share price return of 3.54% decline. Longer...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cisco-systems-csco-valuation-check-161014228.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI startups are losing talent; Are defections the de facto?</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/ai-startups-losing-talent/</link><description>AI companies have an employee retention problem.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/ai-startups-losing-talent/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] NVTS vs. ADI: Which Semiconductor Stock Should You Buy Right Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvts-vs-adi-semiconductor-stock-155400668.html</link><description>Analog Devices' AI-driven data center momentum and earnings visibility give it an edge over Navitas Semiconductor amid near-term revenue uncertainty.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvts-vs-adi-semiconductor-stock-155400668.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] 4 Stocks Guy Spier Was Selling in Q4</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-stocks-guy-spier-was-selling-in-q4/</link><description>Guy Spier of Aquamarine Capital is an incredibly intelligent value investor who’s heavily influenced by the great Warren Buffett. Just have a look at the Aquamarine portfolio, and you’ll notice many Buffett stocks as well as names that the Oracle of Omaha probably would have liked. With Buffett now retired, perhaps it’s Guy Spier and ... 4 Stocks Guy Spier Was Selling in Q4</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-stocks-guy-spier-was-selling-in-q4/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Accounting software platform Pennylane raises $205m</title><link>https://www.internationalaccountingbulletin.com/news/accounting-software-platform-pennylane/</link><description>Pennylane plans to channel the fresh capital into R&amp;amp;D.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.internationalaccountingbulletin.com/news/accounting-software-platform-pennylane/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO says AI boom is fueling the 'largest' infrastructure buildout in history</title><link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-boom-fueling-largest-infrastructure-buildout-history</link><description>AI infrastructure spending could reach $85 trillion over 15 years, creating massive job opportunities across construction, tech and manufacturing sectors, according to Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-boom-fueling-largest-infrastructure-buildout-history</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Can Vertiv's International Expansion Drive More Upside in the Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertivs-international-expansion-drive-more-153800913.html</link><description>VRT's overseas momentum accelerates as AI demand lifts sales, expands backlog to $9.5B, and supports continued double-digit organic growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vertivs-international-expansion-drive-more-153800913.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] FDA Grants Breakthrough Therapy Tag to LLY's Ovarian Cancer Candidate</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fda-grants-breakthrough-therapy-tag-153100294.html</link><description>Eli Lilly wins FDA Breakthrough Therapy status for sofetabart mipitecan in certain patients with platinum-resistant ovarian cancer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fda-grants-breakthrough-therapy-tag-153100294.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153016698.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153016698.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Will Lower Active Accounts Impact Synchrony's Q4 Earnings Potential?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lower-active-accounts-impact-synchronys-151700709.html</link><description>SYF heads into Q4 with higher margins and purchase volumes, but declining active accounts and average interest-earning assets cloud earnings upside.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lower-active-accounts-impact-synchronys-151700709.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is Eli Lilly (LLY) Pricing Look Stretched After A Strong Multi Year Share Price Run</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-pricing-look-151302414.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Eli Lilly's current share price reflects its true worth, you are not alone. This article is built to help you frame that question clearly. The stock recently closed at US$1,041.29, with returns of a 3.3% decline over 7 days, a 2.8% decline over 30 days, a 3.6% decline year to date, but a 41.3% gain over 1 year and a very large 5 year return of about 4x. Those moves come as Eli Lilly continues to be a regular focus of long term investors and large index funds...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eli-lilly-lly-pricing-look-151302414.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang: 'Trillions of dollars of AI infrastructure needs to be built'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-trillions-of-dollars-of-ai-infrastructure-needs-to-be-built-144212721.html</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang told an audience at the gathering of the World Economic Forum that the world needs to build trillions of dollars of AI infrastructure to meet demand.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-trillions-of-dollars-of-ai-infrastructure-needs-to-be-built-144212721.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Is Greg Abel Making His First Move to Redefine Berkshire Hathaway?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-greg-abel-making-his-first-move-to-redefine-berkshire-hathaway/</link><description>Investors have long anticipated how Greg Abel, Warren Buffett’s successor as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway (NYSE:BRK-A)(NYSE:BRK-B), would influence the company following Buffett’s departure. With Abel now at the helm, we may be getting the first glimpse. Yesterday, Kraft Heinz (NASDAQ:KHC) revealed in an SEC filing a prospectus supplement registering the potential resale of up to ... Is Greg Abel Making His First Move to Redefine Berkshire Hathaway?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-greg-abel-making-his-first-move-to-redefine-berkshire-hathaway/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Intel Stock Rises Ahead of Earnings. Why Optimism Is Growing.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report.  Intel shares were up 5.8% at $51.35 in early trading.  Intel is expected to report adjusted earnings of eight cents a share on revenue of $13.42 billion for the fourth quarter of 2025, according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Kraft Heinz Spills Beans on Berkshire's Possible Share Sale; Stock Drops</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/kraft-heinz-spills-beans-on-berkshire-s-possible-share-sale-stock-drops-jJDQr87x9xukeNcLy2wZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Kraft Heinz shares dropped after the food company said in a regulatory filing that its biggest stockholder—Berkshire Hathaway—could sell nearly all of its shares.  Kraft Heinz’s Securities and Exchange Commission filing said Berkshire could sell up to 325.4 million shares.  Shares in the maker of Heinz Tomato Ketchup and Kraft Mac and Cheese fell roughly 7% Wednesday morning.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/kraft-heinz-spills-beans-on-berkshire-s-possible-share-sale-stock-drops-jJDQr87x9xukeNcLy2wZ?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] No One’s Talking About This AI Chip Stock That Can Easily 5X</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/no-ones-talking-about-this-ai-chip-stock-that-can-easily-5x/</link><description>Most investors on Wall Street are aware of Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA), AMD (NASDAQ:AMD), Broadcom (NASDAQ:AVGO), and the like. However, have you looked into ACM Research (NASDAQ:ACMR)? Very few will say yes, as the company is still rather under-the-radar. I called it out back in August 2023 as a stock with massive upside potential, and it has ... No One’s Talking About This AI Chip Stock That Can Easily 5X</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/no-ones-talking-about-this-ai-chip-stock-that-can-easily-5x/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm upgraded, Flutter downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-upgraded-flutter-downgraded-wall-143555244.html</link><description>Arm upgraded, Flutter downgraded: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-upgraded-flutter-downgraded-wall-143555244.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang: AI infrastructure buildout is 'sensible'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-ai-143500353.html</link><description>Speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang explains how the AI infrastructure buildout is "sensible." Hear his full comments, including on how AI is like a 5-layer cake, in the video above. Watch the full conversation with Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-ai-143500353.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Wall Street Analysts Think Vertiv (VRT) Is a Good Investment: Is It?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-analysts-think-vertiv-143004094.html</link><description>Based on the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), Vertiv (VRT) should be added to one's portfolio. Wall Street analysts' overly optimistic recommendations cast doubt on the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric. So, is the stock worth buying?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-analysts-think-vertiv-143004094.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Nvidia (NVDA) a Buy as Wall Street Analysts Look Optimistic?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-buy-wall-street-143003586.html</link><description>According to the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), one should invest in Nvidia (NVDA). It is debatable whether this highly sought-after metric is effective because Wall Street analysts' recommendations tend to be overly optimistic. Would it be worth investing in the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-buy-wall-street-143003586.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Here’s why HSBC remains bullish on global stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-hsbc-remains-bullish-global-142621932.html</link><description>Investing.com -- HSBC is staying firmly positive on global equities, arguing that rising geopolitical tensions and fresh U.S. tariffs do not alter the underlying outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-hsbc-remains-bullish-global-142621932.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Sandisk the Smartest Investment You Can Make Today?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-sandisk-the-smartest-investment-you-can-make-to/</link><description>Management aims to capitalize on growth in the data center market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/is-sandisk-the-smartest-investment-you-can-make-to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Is Most-Watched Stock Caterpillar Inc. (CAT) Worth Betting on Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-caterpillar-inc-140005060.html</link><description>Zacks.com users have recently been watching Caterpillar (CAT) quite a bit. Thus, it is worth knowing the facts that could determine the stock's prospects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-watched-stock-caterpillar-inc-140005060.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The NYSE’s big tokenization plan is vaporware dressed up as innovation</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nyse-big-tokenization-plan-vaporware-140000082.html</link><description>A Columbia business professor says the stock exchange's ambitious blockchain plan lacks details and is designed to uphold the status quo.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nyse-big-tokenization-plan-vaporware-140000082.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI robotics a "key opportunity" for Europe, says Nvidia’s Huang</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-robotics-key-opportunity-europe-135911727.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang described AI robotics as a "once-in-a-generation" opportunity for Europe during his Wednesday address at the World Economic Forum in Davos on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-robotics-key-opportunity-europe-135911727.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM Q4 Earnings Loom: Buy, Sell or Hold the Stock Ahead of Results?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-q4-earnings-loom-buy-135500274.html</link><description>IBM gears up for Q4 earnings with AI and cloud momentum, but premium valuation and stiff competition weigh on the outlook.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-q4-earnings-loom-buy-135500274.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] 4 Dividend ETFs Perfect For Retirees On Social Security</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-dividend-etfs-perfect-for-retirees-on-social-security/</link><description>When you are living on Social Security, it goes without saying that every dollar matters, and finding a way to supplement income can go a long way to not just covering basic expenses, but also helping out when emergency medical expenses happen. This is where dividend income becomes a central part of any investment portfolio, ... 4 Dividend ETFs Perfect For Retirees On Social Security</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/4-dividend-etfs-perfect-for-retirees-on-social-security/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Drops Ahead Of Trump Speech; Netflix Dives On Earnings (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-speech-netflix-stock-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index dropped Wednesday ahead of Trump's Davos speech. Netflix stock plunged on earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-trump-speech-netflix-stock-nflx/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Alibaba, Applied Digital, ARM Holdings, FedEx, Flutter Entertainment, Ulta Beauty, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading lower again after a dreadful risk-off day across Wall Street, where all major indices finished the day solidly lower. The combination of President Trump’s pursuit of Greenland, multiple geopolitical hotspots, both foreign and domestic, and a market that remains very overbought led to the biggest selling day we ... Here Are Wednesday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Alibaba, Applied Digital, ARM Holdings, FedEx, Flutter Entertainment, Ult</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/here-are-wednesdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is ASML Holding (ENXTAM:ASML) Losing Its Appeal After Strong Share Price Momentum?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-enxtam-asml-losing-131140478.html</link><description>With ASML Holding trading at around €1,140, this article examines what that price could mean for value-minded investors and whether it still represents a sensible entry or more of a stretch. The stock has recently shown strong momentum, with returns of 3.4% over 7 days, 26.4% over 30 days, 15.6% year to date, 57.2% over 1 year, 90.4% over 3 years and 160.1% over 5 years. Recent news coverage has centered on ASML Holding's role as a key supplier of advanced semiconductor manufacturing...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asml-holding-enxtam-asml-losing-131140478.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Wall Street's Wild Week</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/wall-streets-wild-week/</link><description>The biggest news was the U.S. government potentially spending $1.5 trillion on defense. Of course, there are strings attached, which investors don't like, but this could be an opportunity long-term.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/wall-streets-wild-week/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Says AI Needs More Investment in Defiance of Bubble Fears</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-needs-more-investment-in-defiance-of-bubble-fears-9dabba63?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Speaking at Davos, Jensen Huang said AI’s application—how the technology is used in a specific industry—is the most critical element, and where economic benefits lie.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-ceo-says-ai-needs-more-investment-in-defiance-of-bubble-fears-9dabba63?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[AZN.L] Tempus AI's Key 2025 Milestones Continue to Gain Industry Attention</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tempus-ais-key-2025-milestones-125700580.html</link><description>TEM hits $1.1B TCV, signs 70+ pharma data deals and posts its first positive adjusted EBITDA in Q3 2025 as adoption accelerates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tempus-ais-key-2025-milestones-125700580.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Daily Profit Alert: Netflix Business Model Under Fire, NVIDIA Lock-in Accelerates</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/daily-profit-alert-netflix-business-model-under-fire-nvidia-lock-in-accelerates/</link><description>1. Netflix’s Business Model Under Fire Despite Q4 Beat Netflix beat Q4 earnings estimates but the stock dropped 7% anyway, revealing what Wall Street really cares about: future growth, not past performance. The company reported $11.51 billion in revenue with 17% year-over-year growth, but EPS missed by 15.8% at $5.87 versus the $6.97 estimate. A ... Daily Profit Alert: Netflix Business Model Under Fire, NVIDIA Lock-in Accelerates</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/21/daily-profit-alert-netflix-business-model-under-fire-nvidia-lock-in-accelerates/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) Stock Price Prediction for 2026: Where Will It Be in 1 Year (Jan 21)</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</link><description>Nvidia remains the dominant AI chipmaker in the market, but where is the stock headed for the rest of this year and into the next?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2025/10/22/nvidia-nasdaq-nvda-stock-price-prediction-for-2025-where-will-it-be-in-1-year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel results to spotlight turnaround efforts as AI data centers boost chip demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-spotlight-turnaround-efforts-123156720.html</link><description>Intel shareholders are optimistic about the company's results like they have not been for many quarters, betting the turnaround CEO Lip-Bu Tan promised was taking root and that rapid data center build outs were fueling strong demand ​for its traditional server chips.  A slew of high-profile investments engineered by Tan last year piqued investor interest in a stock that ‌had crashed in 2024 following years of management missteps, including a botched AI product roadmap that led to deep competitive losses and thousands of job cuts.  Intel's stock gained 84% in 2025, ‌far outperforming the benchmark semiconductor index's 42% rise.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-results-spotlight-turnaround-efforts-123156720.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Amgen (AMGN) Expands Obesity Strategy With Ro Collaboration on GLP-1 Therapies</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amgen-amgn-expands-obesity-strategy-121101061.html</link><description>Amgen Inc. (NASDAQ:AMGN) is one of the best undervalued wide moat stocks. On January 13, 2026, an announcement came regarding the Ro and Amgen Inc. (NASDAQ:AMGN) collaboration. Ro, a U.S. telehealth firm, alongside Amgen, aims to investigate barriers patients face in accessing obesity treatments, including GLP-1 drugs such as Novo Nordisk’s Ozempic and Eli Lilly’s […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amgen-amgn-expands-obesity-strategy-121101061.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] AbbVie (ABBV) Looks to Deepen Its Push Into Rapidly Growing Obesity-Treatment Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/abbvie-abbv-looks-deepen-push-121045476.html</link><description>AbbVie Inc. (NYSE:ABBV) is one of the 10 Goldman Sachs undervalued stocks to invest in. On January 14, 2026, Reuters reported that AbbVie Inc. (NYSE:ABBV) is looking to deepen its push into the rapidly growing obesity-treatment market, outlining its plans at the JPMorgan Healthcare Conference. The company’s plans center on GUBamy, an amylin-mimetic weight-loss drug […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/abbvie-abbv-looks-deepen-push-121045476.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] OpenAI, SpaceX Shares In Demand. Private Markets Boom As Investors Chase Next Nvidia.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/private-markets-nvidia-stock-openai-spacex/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Private markets are booming as investors seek equity in buzzy startups like OpenAI and SpaceX while IPOs remain scarce.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/private-markets-nvidia-stock-openai-spacex/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Huang Heads to China at a Sensitive Moment for Nvidia</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/huang-heads-china-sensitive-moment-115559680.html</link><description>Huang's trip highlights rising uncertainty after H200 customs setback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/huang-heads-china-sensitive-moment-115559680.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Shares Gain After Report of CEO's China Visit</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-shares-gain-report-ceos-114603627.html</link><description>Nvidia Stock Rises. CEO Plans China Visit to Revive AI Chip Sales</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-shares-gain-report-ceos-114603627.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia's Huang Heads Back to China</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidias-huang-heads-back-china-114352964.html</link><description>CEO looks to steady AI chip business</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidias-huang-heads-back-china-114352964.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] The Chip Technology That Finally Gives Intel an Edge Over TSMC</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-chip-technology-that-finally-gives-intel-an-ed/</link><description>Intel was first to market with backside power delivery.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-chip-technology-that-finally-gives-intel-an-ed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Week In AI Chips - Innovative Cooling Solutions Fuel Next-Gen AI Data Centers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-innovative-cooling-113745338.html</link><description>Motivair by Schneider Electric has unveiled the MCDU-70, a cutting-edge 2.5MW Coolant Distribution Unit (CDU), designed to address the cooling needs of next-generation AI data centers. This new CDU model supports scalability up to 10MW and is engineered to handle the intense heat generated by advanced GPUs, which power AI Factories. By integrating with Schneider Electric’s EcoStruxure software, the unit promises reliable and efficient cooling solutions for high-density data centers at a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/week-ai-chips-innovative-cooling-113745338.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang pushes back against AI bubble worries</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-pushes-113729636.html</link><description>Speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang defended the billions of dollars being spent on AI and pushed back on worries that there may be an AI bubble forming. Watch the full conversation with Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-pushes-113729636.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Trump Got a Warning From Treasuries Selloff. How It Could Curb Greenland Tariff Threats.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-treasuries-greenland-tariff-threats-things-to-know-today-4ce1fbff?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Trump addresses Davos today, Mag 7 stocks reflect fear over AI trade, Netflix’s softer margin guidance overshadows earnings beat, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/trump-treasuries-greenland-tariff-threats-things-to-know-today-4ce1fbff?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Intel Stock Rises Again After Upgrades. Why Wall Street Is Warming to It.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-upgrade-chips-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was gaining again early Wednesday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report.  Intel shares were up 2.4% at $49.73 in premarket trading.  As Barron’s has written, several Wall Street analysts have turned more positive on Intel stock in recent weeks, after the company unveiled new processors and comments from President Donald Trump praising CEO Lip-Bu Tan.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-stock-price-upgrade-chips-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Exclusive: Alphabet’s CapitalG names Jill Chase and Alex Nichols as general partners</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-alphabet-capitalg-names-jill-112823962.html</link><description>For the first time since CapitalG was started in 2013, the firm is promoting two general partners, Jill Chase and Alex Nichols, Fortune has exclusively learned.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-alphabet-capitalg-names-jill-112823962.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI will create jobs, Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang argues</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-create-jobs-nvidia-ceo-112051212.html</link><description>Speaking with BlackRock CEO Larry Fink at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Nvidia (NVDA) CEO Jensen Huang spoke about how AI will help create more jobs, not eliminate them as many fear. Watch the full conversation with Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-create-jobs-nvidia-ceo-112051212.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 1 Magnificent Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stock to Buy in 2026 and Hold Forever (Hint: It's Not Nvidia)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-magnif/</link><description>Alphabet is beginning to emerge as Wall Street's new favorite artificial intelligence (AI) growth stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-magnif/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Nvidia and Broadcom Look Attractive Again. Citi Names Top Chip Picks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-look-attractive-again-111909812.html</link><description>Semiconductor Stocks Are in Focus. Citi Sees Upside in Nvidia and Broadcom</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-broadcom-look-attractive-again-111909812.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Alphabet (GOOGL) Fairly Priced After Recent Share Price Pullback?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-fairly-priced-recent-110908107.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Alphabet's current share price lines up with its underlying worth, you are not alone. That is exactly what this article will unpack. Alphabet closed at US$322.00 recently, after a 4.2% decline over the last 7 days, a 4.8% gain over 30 days, a 2.2% return year to date and a 63.2% return over the past year, with a 232.1% return over 3 years and 240.1% over 5 years. These moves have kept Alphabet in the spotlight, as investors weigh how its core businesses and long...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-fairly-priced-recent-110908107.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 7 Stocks Rallied More Than 200% Since Trump's Inauguration Day</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/7-stocks-rallied-more-200-110112579.html</link><description>A year after President Donald Trump returned to the White House, seven stocks in the Russell 1000 ETF have delivered staggering returns, each topping 200% gains. The performance table reads like a mood board for the market narrative of the past year: space, defense, AI supply constraints, precious metals and a national-security scramble for critical minerals. 7) MP Materials: Rare Earths Become A National Security Matter MP Materials Corp. (NYSE:MP) has rallied 225.84% since Jan. 20, 2025, as Wa</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/7-stocks-rallied-more-200-110112579.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Zinnia collaborates with Snowflake on real-time insurance analytics and AI</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/zinnia-collaborates-snowflake-insurance-analytics/</link><description>As part of the arrangement, Zinnia has deployed Snowflake’s data platform across its operations to underpin ML and AI-driven applications.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/zinnia-collaborates-snowflake-insurance-analytics/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2 No-Brainer AI Stocks to Buy Hand Over Fist for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/2-no-brainer-ai-stocks-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</link><description>These chip companies are well positioned for the growing investment in AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/2-no-brainer-ai-stocks-buy-hand-over-fist-2026/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Investors Bet on AWS to Pull the Stock Out of Its Malaise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-investors-bet-aws-pull-103914610.html</link><description>The optimism starts with demand for the Amazon Web Services cloud-computing business, which is positioned to benefit from the explosion of artificial intelligence technology.  “An improvement in AWS should help materially in terms of the perception of the stock as being the relative loser in cloud,” said Pat Burton, a portfolio manager at Winslow Capital Management, who counts Amazon as one of his biggest overweights among the Magnificent Seven tech giants.  Amazon shares were the worst performers among the Mag Seven in 2025, their seventh straight year trailing the group.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-investors-bet-aws-pull-103914610.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] CGI adopts Google’s Gemini Enterprise for enterprise AI integration</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/cgi-adopts-google-gemini-enterprise/</link><description>The agreement will enable CGI consultants to use Gemini Enterprise AI tools and support client digital transformation projects.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/cgi-adopts-google-gemini-enterprise/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Netflix defends Warner Bros bid as shares drop on tepid results</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-101203336.html</link><description>Jan 21 (Reuters) - "YouTube is not just user-generated content and cat videos anymore," Netflix CEO Ted Sarandos said on Tuesday.  Making a compelling case for why the streaming giant wanted Warner Bros Discovery's studio and streaming assets, Sarandos noted how tech giants such ​as Alphabet's YouTube had changed what television viewing meant and forced Netflix to change tack to keep up.  Sarandos and his co-CEO Greg Peters spent a large portion of the post-earnings call talking effusively about how strong and complementary Warner Bros' services were, a sharp change from the long-held company credo: build, don't buy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-defends-warner-bros-bid-101203336.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Best Momentum Stock to Buy for January 21st</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-momentum-stock-buy-january-100500196.html</link><description>LRCX, BNPQY and LRLCY made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) momentum stocks list on January 21, 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/best-momentum-stock-buy-january-100500196.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] US insurtech company Ethos begins IPO roadshow, seeks up to $1.3bn valuation</title><link>https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/ethos-ipo-roadshow-valuation/</link><description>The US-based insurer and its shareholders intend to raise up to $210.5m by offering approximately 10.5 million shares.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lifeinsuranceinternational.com/news/ethos-ipo-roadshow-valuation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Down 40%, Is CoreWeave a Buy on the Dip?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/down-40-is-coreweave-a-buy-on-the-dip/</link><description>CoreWeave launched its IPO last March.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/down-40-is-coreweave-a-buy-on-the-dip/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Chainlink Enables 24/5 On-Chain Trading for Stocks, Gold, and Silver as Crypto Volatility Fades</title><link>https://www.ccn.com/news/crypto/chainlink-on-chain-trading-gold-silver-crypto/</link><description>Chainlink launches 24/5 U.S. equities data streams, enabling continuous on-chain trading of stocks and ETFs. The feeds provide real-time prices for assets such as Nvidia, ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ccn.com/news/crypto/chainlink-on-chain-trading-gold-silver-crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] The Zacks Analyst Blog Highlights Sandisk, Amphenol, ASML Holding and Corning</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-sandisk-092800762.html</link><description>Sandisk, Amphenol, ASML Holding and Corning are tech names positioned to beat Q4 earnings as AI-driven demand lifts chips and data centers.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zacks-analyst-blog-highlights-sandisk-092800762.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] How Arm’s AI-Focused Reorganization Amid Valuation Questions At Arm Holdings (ARM) Has Changed Its Investment Story</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-ai-focused-reorganization-amid-091149667.html</link><description>In recent weeks, Arm Holdings has faced analyst downgrades, questions about valuation, and concern over SoftBank’s margin loan tied to Arm shares, even as it reorganized around new Cloud and AI, Edge, and Physical AI divisions targeting robotics and autonomous vehicles. This restructuring marks a shift in Arm’s story from its traditional smartphone base toward longer-horizon opportunities in data centers, intelligent machines, and “physical AI” applications. Next, we’ll examine how Arm’s...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-ai-focused-reorganization-amid-091149667.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trump at Davos, Intel Earnings, Supreme Court: What to Watch This Week</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/trump-at-davos-intel-earnings-supreme-court-what-to-watch-this-week-5msZk5NpuZWckBchQvar?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Earnings season kicked up a gear this week, with results still due from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and Intel, among other companies. Plus, President Trump is at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, where he is due to speak on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-fed-lisa-cook-trump-nvidia-01-21-2026/card/trump-at-davos-intel-earnings-supreme-court-what-to-watch-this-week-5msZk5NpuZWckBchQvar?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 3 Quantum Computing Stocks to Buy and Hold</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-3-quantu/</link><description>A few years from now, many investors could look back and wish they had bought these stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-3-quantu/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Invests in AI Start-up Baseten. It Shows a Shift in the Market.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-baseten-dff85821?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia  has backed a funding round in artificial-intelligence start-up Baseten.  Baseten helps companies deploy and run large AI models.  The deal comes hot on the heels of Nvidia’s big licensing agreement with Groq, a privately held chip start-up focusing on hardware for AI inference.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-ai-chips-baseten-dff85821?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Assessing Arm Holdings (NasdaqGS:ARM) Valuation After Recent Share Price Weakness</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-arm-holdings-nasdaqgs-arm-080818609.html</link><description>Why Arm Holdings (ARM) is Back in Focus Arm Holdings (NasdaqGS:ARM) is back on many watchlists after recent trading, where the stock has seen a 6% decline over the past month and roughly 35% decline over the past 3 months. See our latest analysis for Arm Holdings. At the latest share price of US$107.17, Arm’s recent moves reflect fading momentum, with a 30 day share price return of 6.02% and a 90 day share price return of 35.33%. The 1 year total shareholder return of 30.95% highlights how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-arm-holdings-nasdaqgs-arm-080818609.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Nebius Group (NBIS) Falls Below $100 on Trade Worries</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-falls-below-073928842.html</link><description>We recently published 10 Stocks Investors Are Dumping. Nebius Group NV (NASDAQ:NBIS) was one of the worst performers on Tuesday. Nebius fell below the $100 territory on Tuesday, shedding 8.68 percent to close at $99.29 apiece and mirroring an overall market pessimism after President Donald Trump triggered another round of geopolitical tensions with the European […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nebius-group-nbis-falls-below-073928842.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] What Rigetti Computing (RGTI)'s Quantum Roadmap Delay and India Deployment Deal Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-computing-rgti-quantum-roadmap-071220431.html</link><description>In early January 2026, Rigetti Computing revised its roadmap for the Cepheus-1-108Q system, pushing general availability of the 108-qubit, twelve-chiplet modular quantum computer to around the end of the first quarter of 2026 while reaffirming its broader scaling plans. An on-premises 108-qubit system order from India’s Centre for Development of Advanced Computing adds real-world deployment momentum to Rigetti’s modular architecture ambitions. With the Cepheus-1-108Q launch delay and fresh...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rigetti-computing-rgti-quantum-roadmap-071220431.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Is Arm Holdings (ARM) Pricing Reflect Future Growth After Recent Share Price Weakness</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-arm-pricing-reflect-071211611.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Arm Holdings' current share price lines up with its underlying value, you are not alone. This article will walk through what the numbers actually say. Over the last year the stock has seen a 30.9% decline, with returns of 0.6% over 7 days, 6.0% over 30 days and 6.6% year to date. These figures can change how investors think about both risk and potential opportunity. Recent coverage has focused on Arm Holdings as a key semiconductor licensing business...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-arm-pricing-reflect-071211611.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Microsoft clicks on Formula One grid with new Mercedes deal</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-clicks-formula-one-grid-064000998.html</link><description>Microsoft, the $3.4trn computing behemoth, will this week unveil a partnership with the Mercedes Formula One team that will underline the sport's resurgent appeal among the world's biggest technology companies.  Sky News understands that Microsoft will be announced as a major sponsor of the Brackley-based outfit when it unveils its 2026 car livery and design at an event on Thursday.  The deal will make Microsoft the latest tech company to sign a big commercial agreement in F1, with rivals such as Google already having a presence through a partnership with McLaren Racing, the reigning world champions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/microsoft-clicks-formula-one-grid-064000998.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] The Ultimate Growth Stock to Buy With $1,000 Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-ultimate-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</link><description>This company's stock is up 200% over the last year -- and is still rising.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/the-ultimate-growth-stock-to-buy-with-1000-right-n/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What Berkshire’s Greg Abel Should Do With All That Cash</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-greg-abel-buffett-cash-ffcbba65?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The new CEO could enhance the company’s returns on its massive cash position with a simple options strategy: cash-secured put sales.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-greg-abel-buffett-cash-ffcbba65?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is FICO’s (FICO) GPU-Powered Xpress Upgrade Quietly Rewiring Its Long-Term Moat In Analytics?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fico-fico-gpu-powered-xpress-052109531.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, FICO released version 9.8 of its FICO Xpress Optimization suite, integrating NVIDIA CUDA-X libraries to accelerate its hybrid gradient algorithm and delivering much faster solutions for extremely large, dense optimization problems on supported NVIDIA GPUs. This move pushes FICO Xpress further into high-performance computing, widening its appeal for organizations tackling massive, complex optimization workloads across data-intensive operations. Next, we’ll examine how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fico-fico-gpu-powered-xpress-052109531.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 05:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] US futures edge higher and gold hits another record as markets swoon over Greenland dispute</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-edge-higher-gold-045146410.html</link><description>Asian shares mostly extended their losses on Wednesday and gold prices hit a record high as concerns over U.S. President Donald Trump’s tariff threats on Greenland fueled unease among investors.  U.S. futures rose after steep losses Tuesday on Wall Street.  Gold prices crossed the $4,800 mark for the first time, gaining 1.7% as money flowed into assets considered to be safe havens at times of uncertainty.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-futures-edge-higher-gold-045146410.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Is Tesla a Good AI Growth Stock to Buy and Hold For the Next 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-tesla-a-good-ai-growth-stock-to-buy-and-hold-fo/</link><description>Tesla CEO Elon Musk believes its AI-powered Robotaxi service will fundamentally change the nature of transport.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-tesla-a-good-ai-growth-stock-to-buy-and-hold-fo/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 2 Undervalued AI Stocks to Buy in 2026 and Hold for Decades</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-undervalued-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-hold/</link><description>These stocks have incredible long-term opportunities.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-undervalued-ai-stocks-to-buy-in-2026-and-hold/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Huang plans to visit China as he seeks to reopen market, Bloomberg reports</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-huang-plans-visit-030251592.html</link><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang plans to travel to China in ​late January as he seeks to ‌reopen a critical market for the company's artificial intelligence ‌chips, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing a person familiar with the matter.  Huang is expected to attend company events ahead of ⁠the Lunar New ‌Year holidays in February, and may also visit Beijing, according to ‍the report.  Nvidia declined to comment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-huang-plans-visit-030251592.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] What growth?: Taiwan's traditional manufacturers miss out on export boom</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/growth-taiwans-traditional-manufacturers-miss-024145018.html</link><description>Taiwan's economy soared last year on skyrocketing exports of AI hardware and semiconductors, but companies in more traditional manufacturing sectors could only look on with envy as they were clobbered by US tariffs and a strong local currency.Taiwan's information and communication technology (ICT) sector, which includes semiconductor chips, has become by far the biggest driver of the island's export-dependent economy. </description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/growth-taiwans-traditional-manufacturers-miss-024145018.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AMD Stock Soared Past Nvidia Last Year. Will That Trend Continue in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/amd-stock-soared-past-nvidia-last-year-will-that-t/</link><description>This past year was the first time AMD's stock outperformed Nvidia's since 2019.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/amd-stock-soared-past-nvidia-last-year-will-that-t/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Warren Buffett Sent a Clear Multibillion-Dollar Message About Artificial Intelligence That Investors Shouldn't Ignore</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/warren-buffett-sent-a-clear-multibillion-dollar/</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway finally invested in a company with some AI chops.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/warren-buffett-sent-a-clear-multibillion-dollar/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia’s Huang Plans to Visit China as He Works to Reopen Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-plans-visit-china-021000843.html</link><description>Huang will be in the country to attend company parties ahead of the Lunar New Year holidays, according to a person familiar with the matter.  The executive is also expected to visit Beijing, though it’s unclear whether he will meet with senior Chinese officials, said the person, who asked not to be identified because the plans are private.  Huang’s itinerary could still change, depending on whether prospective meetings come through.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-plans-visit-china-021000843.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Oklo Stock a Buy in 2026 After Its Nuclear Deal With Meta?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oklo-stock-a-buy-after-its-nuclear-deal-with-me/</link><description>Oklo and Meta announced a partnership to support 1.2 gigawatts of power in Ohio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oklo-stock-a-buy-after-its-nuclear-deal-with-me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Once-in-a-Decade Investment Opportunity: 1 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Semiconductor Stock to Buy Hand Over Fist Before It Soars Up to 32%, According to a Wall Street Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-artifi/</link><description>Wall Street is calling for massive upside in Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing stock.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-once-in-a-decade-investment-opportunity-1-artifi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Anthropic’s CEO stuns Davos with Nvidia criticism</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-ceo-stuns-davos-nvidia-013958947.html</link><description>Anthropic CEO Dario Amodei unloaded on both the administration and U.S. chip companies over plans to sell to China. The criticism was particularly notable because one of those chipmakers, Nvidia, is a major partner and investor in Anthropic.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/anthropic-ceo-stuns-davos-nvidia-013958947.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Elon Musk Says He Hasn't Sold Tesla Stock For Over Three Years: 'Bought A Billion Dollars...'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-hasnt-sold-013105702.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared that he has not sold any of the EV giant's stock in the past three years. Bought A Billion Dollars Worth Of Stock Responding to a now-deleted post by influencer Mario Nawfal on the social media platform X on Sunday, the billionaire shared that he hadn't "sold stock for about 3 years." Musk also added that instead, he has invested in acquiring more Tesla shares. "bought a billion dollars of Tesla stock last year," he said in the post. I have not s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-hasnt-sold-013105702.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Predicted Nvidia Would Be a $5 Trillion Company in 2025. Here's Why I Was Right (and Wrong).</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-said-nvidia-would-be-a-5-trillion-company-2025/</link><description>Nvidia breifly crossed the $5 trillion mark in 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/i-said-nvidia-would-be-a-5-trillion-company-2025/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Will Intel Stock Keep Soaring as Q4 Earnings Approach?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-keep-soaring-q4-010400690.html</link><description>Analyst upgrades and bullish commentary have piled up ahead of Intel's Q4 results on Thursday, January 22, pushing its stock to a two-year high of $50 a share.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-keep-soaring-q4-010400690.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What Nvidia didn’t show at CES, and whether AMD should care</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/what-nvidia-didnt-show-at-ces-and-whether-amd-should-care</link><description>Nvidia (NVDA) stock is trading about 3.39% lower near $180, at the time of writing, Tuesday afternoon, Jan. 20, according to Yahoo Finance. And as if the worries about the AI bubble weren’t enough, other big tech stocks, including Apple, Meta, Microsoft, Tesla, and Google, are also down, as ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/technology/what-nvidia-didnt-show-at-ces-and-whether-amd-should-care</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway May Sell Stock in Kraft Heinz, Filing States</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-sell-kraft-heinz-087ba49f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway  may sell shares from its $7.8 billion equity stake in  Kraft Heinz  according to a prospectus filed late Tuesday with the Securities and Exchange Commission.  The front page of the prospectus says that Berkshire, which received the Kraft Heinz equity as part of a merger of Kraft and Heinz in 2015, may “offer to sell from time to time” shares from that stake.  Berkshire now holds a 27.5% stake in the food company—or 325.4 million shares.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/berkshire-hathaway-sell-kraft-heinz-087ba49f?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Should You Buy Rivian Automotive Stock While It's Below $17?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/should-you-buy-rivian-automotive-stock-while-its-b/</link><description>The upstart electric vehicle maker is failing to generate a profit, but has large ambitions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/should-you-buy-rivian-automotive-stock-while-its-b/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] One-time hot insurance tech Ethos poised to be first tech IPO of the year</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-time-hot-insurance-tech-233632607.html</link><description>Ethos was backed by a who's who of VCs and celebs through 2021. It is currently profitable, it says.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-time-hot-insurance-tech-233632607.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks slide after Trump threatens European allies with tariffs</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stock-market-down-january-20-trump-greenland/?ftag=YHF4eb9d17</link><description>U.S. stocks sank on Tuesday following President Trump's weekend threats to impose tariffs on some NATO trading partners.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stock-market-down-january-20-trump-greenland/?ftag=YHF4eb9d17</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] With Gemini Powering Apple's Siri, Alphabet Could Soon Be the Undisputed AI Leader</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/with-gemini-powering-apples-siri-alphabet-could-so/</link><description>The new collaboration gives Alphabet the AI momentum it needs.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/with-gemini-powering-apples-siri-alphabet-could-so/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] What International Business Machines (IBM)'s New Enterprise AI Platform Push Means For Shareholders</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/international-business-machines-ibm-enterprise-231130146.html</link><description>IBM recently announced several AI initiatives, including IBM Enterprise Advantage for building internal AI platforms, an enterprise-grade agentic AI collaboration with e&amp;amp;, and GRAMMY IQ built with watsonx to power interactive fan experiences using historical Recording Academy data. Together, these moves highlight IBM's push to embed governed, agentic AI across both mission-critical enterprise workflows and high-visibility consumer-facing experiences, underscoring its ambition to be an...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/international-business-machines-ibm-enterprise-231130146.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 20: Intel Rises on Analyst Upgrades Highlighting AI Server CPU Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-intel-rises-on-analyst-upgrades-highlighting-ai-server-cpu-growth/</link><description>On Jan. 20, 2026, Wall Street's AI server growth upgrades put this legacy chipmaker's turnaround narrative under a brighter spotlight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-intel-rises-on-analyst-upgrades-highlighting-ai-server-cpu-growth/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Why CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Dipped More Than Broader Market Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-dipped-225504568.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) closed at $442.73 in the latest trading session, marking a -2.46% move from the prior day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-crowdstrike-holdings-crwd-dipped-225504568.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Sees a More Significant Dip Than Broader Market: Some Facts to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-sees-more-significant-225504162.html</link><description>Alphabet (GOOGL) reached $322 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a -2.42% change compared to its last close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-sees-more-significant-225504162.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here's Why Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) Fell More Than Broader Market</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-alphabet-inc-goog-225504674.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (GOOG) concluded the recent trading session at $322.16, signifying a -2.48% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heres-why-alphabet-inc-goog-225504674.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) Stock Moves -1.98%: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-stock-moves-225503787.html</link><description>The latest trading day saw Snowflake Inc. (SNOW) settling at $206.21, representing a -1.98% change from its previous close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-inc-snow-stock-moves-225503787.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Falls More Steeply Than Broader Market: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-falls-more-steeply-225502967.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, Nvidia (NVDA) closed at $178.18, indicating a -4.32% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-falls-more-steeply-225502967.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] IBM (IBM) Suffers a Larger Drop Than the General Market: Key Insights</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-suffers-larger-drop-225501587.html</link><description>In the most recent trading session, IBM (IBM) closed at $291.35, indicating a -4.68% shift from the previous trading day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ibm-ibm-suffers-larger-drop-225501587.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] YouTube TV faces growing backlash as users demand key upgrade</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/entertainment/youtube-tv-faces-growing-backlash-as-users-demand-live-button-upgrade</link><description>No streaming platform can satisfy every subscriber's needs. That’s why many households subscribe to multiple services simultaneously, while others switch between platforms seasonally. Each one has something slightly different, but enough to make users want to have it as well. For ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/entertainment/youtube-tv-faces-growing-backlash-as-users-demand-live-button-upgrade</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Dow Jones Tumbles As Trump's Greenland Threats Spur Sell The U.S. Trade; Tesla, Nvidia Skid</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-greenland-davos-speech-nvidia-tesla-netflix-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq broke key support on Trump's Greenland push with his Davos speech on tap. Nvidia, Tesla and other megacaps slumped. Netflix fell late.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-greenland-davos-speech-nvidia-tesla-netflix-earnings/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today, Jan. 20: Markets Slide After Trump Tariff Threats Spark Selloff</title><link>https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-markets-slide-after-trump-tariff-threats-spark-selloff/</link><description>On Jan. 20, 2026, Trump's Greenland-linked tariff threats rattled megacap tech as geopolitics, not earnings, drove Wall Street's pullback.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/coverage/stock-market-today/2026/01/20/stock-market-today-jan-20-markets-slide-after-trump-tariff-threats-spark-selloff/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Serve Robotics Buying Fellow Nvidia-Powered Bot Maker</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/serve-robotics-buying-diligent-robotics/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Serve Robotics has agreed to acquire Diligent Robotics, a maker of robot assistants for the health care industry.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/serve-robotics-buying-diligent-robotics/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA ascends to Aa1 status at Moody’s on AI infrastructure dominance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ascends-aa1-status-moody-223046310.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Moody’s Ratings has elevated NVIDIA Corporation’s (NASDAQ:NVDA) senior unsecured rating to Aa1, marking a significant milestone in the chipmaker’s financial evolution. The credit agency simultaneously maintained a positive outlook, suggesting further upward mobility is possible as the firm solidifies its grip on the artificial intelligence sector. The upgrade is underpinned by NVIDIA’s formidable presence within the rapidly expanding data center ecosystem and its robust liquidit</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ascends-aa1-status-moody-223046310.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Bold Predictions to Start 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/3-bold-predictions-to-start-2026/</link><description>It's the most wonderful time of the year. No, not the holdiays. We're talking about making stock investing predictions for 2026. This week, the Fools each give their 2026 hot takes on specific parts of the stock market along with three stocks on their radar</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/3-bold-predictions-to-start-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Valuation Check After Cooling Momentum And Conflicting Fair Value Signals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-valuation-check-cooling-220835113.html</link><description>Recent performance snapshot NVIDIA (NVDA) has seen mixed share performance recently, with a 0.4% decline over the past day, a small gain over the past week, and low single digit positive returns over the past month and past 3 months. Over longer periods, NVIDIA shows a 1.4% negative return year to date but a 32.3% total return over the past year and a very large multi year total return over 3 and 5 years. This helps frame how current moves sit against its longer run record. See our latest...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-valuation-check-cooling-220835113.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] xAI Just Raised $20 Billion. Can Grok Keep Up With Google Gemini?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/xai-just-raised-20-billion-can-grok-keep-up-with-google-gemini/</link><description>Elon Musk’s xAI rang in the new year by raising $20 billion in its latest funding round. Undoubtedly, as the AI race intensifies and the use cases of the technology become more apparent (Claude Code and its Cowork agent seem to have sparked a panic in software), perhaps we’ll begin to hear a bit less ... xAI Just Raised $20 Billion. Can Grok Keep Up With Google Gemini?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/20/xai-just-raised-20-billion-can-grok-keep-up-with-google-gemini/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Wall Street sees worst day since October after Trump tariff threats</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-sees-worst-day-215357399.html</link><description>Sell-off hits US stocks in first trading day since president threatened tariffs against eight countries</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-sees-worst-day-215357399.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Big Tech Stocks Hit Hard in Selloff</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/big-tech-stocks-hit-hard-in-selloff-AwsGv5yl8bMI2P5nHa2x?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>All seven of the giant tech stocks known as the Magnificent Seven fell at least 1% Tuesday. That was the first time that has happened since October.    Microsoft was down the least, about 1.2%, with Tesla and Nvidia down 4% or more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/big-tech-stocks-hit-hard-in-selloff-AwsGv5yl8bMI2P5nHa2x?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why Serve Robotics is acquiring a hospital assistant robot company</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-serve-robotics-acquiring-hospital-213000945.html</link><description>Serve Robotics is expanding beyond its sidewalk delivery roots by acquiring Diligent Robotics, which makes a hospital assistant bot named Moxi.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-serve-robotics-acquiring-hospital-213000945.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] FTC Appeals Loss in Antitrust Case Against Meta</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/ftc-appeals-loss-in-antitrust-case-against-meta-BcOxWhUDjwnqKQUqiGBG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Federal Trade Commission said Tuesday it would appeal a court's decision last year dismissing its claims that Facebook-owner Meta Platforms built an illegal monopoly through the acquisitions of Instagram and WhatsApp.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-netflix-01-20-2026/card/ftc-appeals-loss-in-antitrust-case-against-meta-BcOxWhUDjwnqKQUqiGBG?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Does Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A) Still Offer Value After Its Strong Multi‑Year Run?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-berkshire-hathaway-brk-still-210816051.html</link><description>This article examines what Berkshire Hathaway's current share price may be implying about the business for investors wondering if the shares still offer value after years of strong compounding. The stock recently closed at US$740,750, with returns of 5.4% over 1 year and 57.3% and 112.1% across the last 3 and 5 years. Shorter term moves have been quieter, with a 0.2% decline over 7 days, 0.7% over 30 days, and 0.5% year to date. Recent attention has focused on Berkshire Hathaway as a...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-berkshire-hathaway-brk-still-210816051.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] RBC Initiates Astera Labs (ALAB) at Outperform, Sees Retimer Growth and Scorpio Ramp Driving Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-astera-labs-alab-210610190.html</link><description>Astera Labs, Inc. (NASDAQ:ALAB) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage of the stock with an Outperform rating and a price target of $225. The analyst sees robust retimer growth and Scorpio-P switch ramp for ALAB, which they believe should support […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-astera-labs-alab-210610190.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Intel Stock Is Already Up 19% in 2026. Can Q4 Earnings Propel It Higher in 2026?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37135682/intel-stock-is-already-up-19-in-2026-can-q4-earnings-propel-it-higher-in-2026</link><description>Intel’s Q4 earnings could determine the stock’s next move. Here's what to watch when the company reports on Jan. 22.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37135682/intel-stock-is-already-up-19-in-2026-can-q4-earnings-propel-it-higher-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Morgan Stanley Initiates Nebius (NBIS) at Equalweight, Flags Long-Term AI Infrastructure Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-initiates-nebius-nbis-210437033.html</link><description>Nebius Group N.V. (NASDAQ:NBIS) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 15, Morgan Stanley analyst Josh Baer initiated coverage on the stock with an “Equalweight” rating and a price target of $126. The analyst highlights AI infrastructure scale-up potential for NBS, urging investors to focus on long-term metrics for […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-initiates-nebius-nbis-210437033.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow plummets 800 points, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq sink over 2% as Trump's Greenland threats clobber stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-plummets-800-points-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-over-2-as-trumps-greenland-threats-clobber-stocks-210046255.html</link><description>The market is on edge over Trump's threatened tariffs over Greenland and a Japan-led global bond sell-off.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-plummets-800-points-sp-500-nasdaq-sink-over-2-as-trumps-greenland-threats-clobber-stocks-210046255.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] RBC Sees Multiple Secular and Cyclical Drivers Supporting ASML Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-sees-multiple-secular-cyclical-205413330.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage on the stock with an Outperform rating and a price target of $1,550. The analyst sees multiple secular and cyclical growth drivers across ASML’s memory and logic businesses. According to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-sees-multiple-secular-cyclical-205413330.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] RBC Initiates Intel (INTC) at Sector Perform, Awaits Proof on Margins and Foundry Execution</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-intel-intc-sector-205239771.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage of the stock with a “Sector Perform” rating and a price target of $50. Firm analysts see strategic progress for Intel, but are awaiting proof of execution on gross margins and […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-intel-intc-sector-205239771.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Could Buying Tesla Stock Today Set You Up for Life?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/could-buying-tesla-stock-today-set-you-up-for-life/</link><description>Tesla has delivered 30x gains over the last 10 years. Can it do even better in the next decade?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/could-buying-tesla-stock-today-set-you-up-for-life/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Wall Street Analyst Just Revealed Her Top Artificial Intelligence (AI) Chip Stock for 2026 -- and It's Not Nvidia. Here's Why I Think She Could Be Right.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-wall-street-analyst-just-revealed-her-top-artifi/</link><description>Beth Kindig of the I/O Fund is calling for Micron to have a big year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/a-wall-street-analyst-just-revealed-her-top-artifi/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia's place in AI, Apple downgrade, JPMorgan cautious on oil</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidias-place-ai-apple-downgrade-204706772.html</link><description>Market Domination Host Josh Lipton and Yahoo Finance Senior Reporter Brooke DiPalma track several of the day's top trending stock tickers, including Nvidia's (NVDA) position in the AI ecosystem, Citi analysts cutting their price target on Apple (AAPL), and JPMorgan's cautious outlook on the oil industry (CL=F, BZ=F). To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/nvidias-place-ai-apple-downgrade-204706772.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Himax, Broadcom, KLA Corporation, Impinj, and Qualcomm Stocks Trade Down, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/himax-broadcom-kla-corporation-impinj-204554608.html</link><description>A number of stocks fell in the afternoon session after rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Europe over control of Greenland sparked a broad, risk-off mood in asset markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/himax-broadcom-kla-corporation-impinj-204554608.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Nvidia (NVDA) Stock Is Down Today</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-nvda-stock-down-204542603.html</link><description>Shares of leading designer of graphics chips Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) fell 3.8% in the afternoon session after rising geopolitical tensions between the US and Europe over control of Greenland sparked a broad, risk-off mood in asset markets.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-nvidia-nvda-stock-down-204542603.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] RBC Initiates Nvidia (NVDA) at Outperform, Cites $500B+ AI Backlog and Ecosystem Dominance</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-nvidia-nvda-outperform-203907038.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 14, RBC Capital analyst Srini Pajjuri initiated coverage on the stock with an “Outperform” rating and a price target of $240. He sees robust AI demand for Nvidia, a backlog exceeding $500 billion, and ecosystem dominance. The analyst said […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rbc-initiates-nvidia-nvda-outperform-203907038.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon (AMZN) Seen as One of the Strongest AI Bull Cases Heading Into 2026, Bernstein Says</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-amzn-seen-one-strongest-203638058.html</link><description>Amazon.com, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) is one of the AI Stocks Making Waves on Wall Street. On January 15, Bernstein SocGen Group analyst Nikhil Devnani reiterated an “Outperform” rating on the stock with a $300.00 price target. The analyst sees 2026 as the strongest bull case story ever since the pandemic, citing a palatable entry point for […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-amzn-seen-one-strongest-203638058.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] 2 Clear AI Winners Investors Should Buy for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-clear-ai-winners-investors-should-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor and Micron Technology are at the core of AI investing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/2-clear-ai-winners-investors-should-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bill Gates Recalls Warren Buffett Treating Him to McDonald's — Then Paying With Coupons</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bill-gates-recalls-warren-buffett-203108944.html</link><description>Being rich doesn't always mean acting rich. Just ask the two men who've taken turns wearing the crown of richest person alive. Bill Gates and Warren Buffett could afford just about any lunch they wanted—but when they grabbed McDonald's in Hong Kong, one of them reached into his pocket and pulled out coupons. Spoiler: it wasn't Bill Gates. Gates told the story himself in a letter he wrote to Buffett in 2017. "Remember the laugh we had when we traveled together to Hong Kong and decided to get lunc</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bill-gates-recalls-warren-buffett-203108944.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] What Happened to Viking Therapeutics in 2025, And Is it a Buy for 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/what-happened-to-viking-therapeutics-in-2025-and-i/</link><description>Despite a challenging year, the company has a lot to look forward to in the coming years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/what-happened-to-viking-therapeutics-in-2025-and-i/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Navitas Semiconductor (NVTS) Deepens AI Data Center Ties With Nvidia 800V Platform Is The Story Shifting?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/navitas-semiconductor-nvts-deepens-ai-200951299.html</link><description>In mid-January 2026, Navitas Semiconductor’s CEO Chris Allexandre presented at the 28th Annual Needham Growth Conference in New York, outlining the company’s latest power semiconductor initiatives. This appearance comes as Navitas pivots toward higher‑power gallium nitride and silicon carbide chips for AI data centers, including work aligned with Nvidia’s next‑generation 800V architecture. We’ll now examine how this renewed emphasis on AI data center partnerships, particularly around...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/navitas-semiconductor-nvts-deepens-ai-200951299.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is Oral Wegovy a Game Changer for Novo Nordisk?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oral-wegovy-a-game-changer-for-novo-nordisk/</link><description>The past couple of years have been challenging for the company. But this could be the beginning of a new chapter.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/20/is-oral-wegovy-a-game-changer-for-novo-nordisk/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>