<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang Says, "The Race Is On for AI." Here's What It Means for Nvidia Stock.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-the-race-is-on-for-ai/</link><description>AI development hit an inflection point that will power Nvidia into the future.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-the-race-is-on-for-ai/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] What If SpaceX Does Not IPO in 2026? 1 Surprise Trick Elon Musk Might Have Up His Sleeve</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/what-if-spacex-does-not-ipo-in-2026/</link><description>SpaceX might not actually IPO in 2026. Can I interest you in a Starlink IPO instead?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/what-if-spacex-does-not-ipo-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Taiwan’s Flagship Chip Maker Charts a Future Beyond Taiwan</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/taiwan-semiconductor-tscm-us-investment-d96f77f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>TSMC has for decades provided a “Silicon Shield” to its namesake island. Now it sees both business and geopolitical reasons for going big in the U.S.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/tech/taiwan-semiconductor-tscm-us-investment-d96f77f9?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] This Is My No. 1 Recommended Vanguard ETF to Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/this-is-my-no-1-recommended-vanguard-etf-to-buy-in/</link><description>The stars could be aligning for healthcare stocks this year. This Vanguard ETF is a great way to play it.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/this-is-my-no-1-recommended-vanguard-etf-to-buy-in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] 5 big analyst AI moves: Nvidia top 2026 pick, ASML gets big price target hike</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-big-analyst-ai-moves-093006427.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Here are the biggest analyst moves in the area of artificial intelligence (AI) for this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-big-analyst-ai-moves-093006427.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Will humanoids be the growth engine of the 21st century?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/humanoids-growth-engine-21st-century-093005481.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Humanoid robots are moving rapidly from experimental prototypes to real-world workers, a shift Barclays says could redefine global labor markets and industrial supply chains.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/humanoids-growth-engine-21st-century-093005481.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Street Calls of the Week</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/street-calls-week-091530595.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Here is your Pro Recap of the top takeaways from Wall Street analysts for the past week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/street-calls-week-091530595.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] The Smartest Quantum Computing Stock to Buy for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/the-smartest-quantum-computing-stock-buy-for-2026/</link><description>Alphabet's Willow chip addresses a key challenge with advancing quantum computing technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/the-smartest-quantum-computing-stock-buy-for-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is quantum the next great tech revolution?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/quantum-next-great-tech-revolution-083002166.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Quantum computing could achieve "quantum advantage,” where quantum systems significantly outperform classical computers, around 2033, according to UBS Global Research in a recent note. However, the technology "has consistently been ’5 years away’ for the last 20 years," the report cautions.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/quantum-next-great-tech-revolution-083002166.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 08:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: 1 Unstoppable Stock to Buy Before It Soars 976%, According to 1 World-Renowned Analyst</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/prediction-1-unstoppable-stock-to-buy-before-it-so/</link><description>Strong secular tailwinds, a track record of innovation, and a market-leading position could drive this tech titan to new heights.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/prediction-1-unstoppable-stock-to-buy-before-it-so/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Why the iShares Semiconductor ETF (SOXX) Jumped 40% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-the-ishares-semiconductor-etf-soxx-jumped-40/</link><description>AI stocks continued to soar last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-the-ishares-semiconductor-etf-soxx-jumped-40/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Global X Artificial Intelligence and Technology ETF (AIQ) Jumped 31% in 2025</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-global-x-artificial-intelligence-and-technolog/</link><description>The AIQ ETF outpaced the Nasdaq for nearly the whole year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/18/why-global-x-artificial-intelligence-and-technolog/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Analysts Bullish on Lam Research Corporation (LRCX) as Semiconductor Capex and Memory Investments Rise</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-bullish-lam-research-corporation-055506724.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 10 Best Investments During A Recession. The fourth stock on our list of best investments is Lam Research Corporation. TheFly reported on January 9 that Goldman Sachs analyst James Schneider raised the LRCX price target to $180 from $160 while maintaining a Buy rating. Improved semiconductor industry circumstances, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-bullish-lam-research-corporation-055506724.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. (TMO) and NVIDIA Partner to Bring Advanced AI to Lab Workflows</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/thermo-fisher-scientific-inc-tmo-055425606.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 10 Best Investments During A Recession. Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. is placed second on our list. TheFly reported on January 9 that Stifel analyst Daniel Arias maintained a Buy rating on TMO and significantly raised the price target to $700 from $583, an increase of $117. According to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/thermo-fisher-scientific-inc-tmo-055425606.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Predicted That Nvidia Would Beat the S&amp;P 500 for the 3rd Consecutive Year in 2025. Here's Why the Streak Can Continue in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/nvidia-outperform-sp-500-2025-2026-buy-stock/</link><description>Nvidia continues to be a fundamentals-led growth story rather than one of hype and hot air.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/nvidia-outperform-sp-500-2025-2026-buy-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 04:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Clearway Energy (CWEN.A) Is Up 12.7% After Major New Google PPAs - Has The Bull Case Changed?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearway-energy-cwen-12-7-041040158.html</link><description>In January 2026, Clearway Energy Group announced that in 2025 it executed three long-term PPAs with Google totaling 1.17 GW of carbon-free energy projects across Missouri, Texas, and West Virginia, representing over US$2.40 billions in planned investment and expected to begin construction this year with initial operations in 2027 and 2028. This expansion lifts the Google–Clearway partnership to 1.24 GW and underscores Big Tech’s growing role in supporting large-scale, long-duration clean...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearway-energy-cwen-12-7-041040158.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 04:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] A Once-in-a-Generation Investment Opportunity: Here's My Top AI Stock for 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/a-once-in-a-generation-investment-opportunity-here/</link><description>AI is a once-in-a-generation investment opportunity investors cannot afford to miss.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/a-once-in-a-generation-investment-opportunity-here/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why Silicon Valley is really talking about fleeing California (it’s not the 5%)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-silicon-valley-really-talking-011711652.html</link><description>If you’ve been following the billionaire exodus from California with some confusion, here’s what’s actually driving the nervousness: it’s not the 5% rate. As highlighted Friday in the New York Post, the proposed wealth tax would hit founders on their voting shares rather than the actual equity they own. Take Larry Page, who about 3% […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-silicon-valley-really-talking-011711652.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Is SoftBank (TSE:9984) Quietly Pivoting Into an AI and Energy Infrastructure Powerhouse?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-tse-9984-quietly-pivoting-010658065.html</link><description>BofA Securities recently downgraded Arm Holdings to Neutral ahead of its fiscal third-quarter 2026 results, citing near-term smartphone-related headwinds that could weigh on Arm’s client royalty revenue. At the same time, SoftBank Group is drawing fresh attention as it steps up high-profile AI and energy commitments tied to OpenAI and SB Energy, which are reshaping how investors view its role as an AI and infrastructure holding company. We’ll now examine how SoftBank’s heightened AI and...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/softbank-tse-9984-quietly-pivoting-010658065.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] If You'd Invested $500 in Nvidia Stock 10 Years Ago, Here's How Much You'd Have Today</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/if-youd-invested-500-in-nvidia-stock-10-years-ago/</link><description>Nvidia has delivered life-changing returns for long-term shareholders.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/if-youd-invested-500-in-nvidia-stock-10-years-ago/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Memory Shortage Threatens Nvidia's China AI Chip Ambitions</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/memory-shortage-threatens-nvidias-china-003139128.html</link><description>Nvidia Corp. (NASDAQ:NVDA) faces a fresh constraint on its China business as a global shortage of advanced memory chips threatens to limit U.S. export licenses for its H200 AI processors, raising near-term risks to sales growth just as demand for AI hardware remains red-hot. Tight supplies of advanced memory are likely to cap how many export licenses Nvidia can obtain to sell its H200 artificial intelligence processors to customers in China, according to Rep. John Moolenaar, the top Republican o</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/memory-shortage-threatens-nvidias-china-003139128.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Gary Black Likes Elon Musk's Tesla But Not TSLA, Draws Comparison With Amazon—Says Nvidia 'Democratizes Autonomy'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gary-black-likes-elon-musks-235124088.html</link><description>Investor Gary Black, managing director of The Future Fund LLC, has shared that Tesla Inc.'s (NASDAQ:TSLA) stock valuation has caused him to exit his position in the automaker. Gary Black Offers Insight Into Tesla Valuation Criticism The investor, in a post on the social media platform X, offered an insight into his outlook on Tesla, drawing comparisons with Amazon.com Inc.'s (NASDAQ:AMZN) stock during the e-commerce giant's early days. Black shared that he held Amazon stock before it was profita</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gary-black-likes-elon-musks-235124088.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Amazon Loses Fight To Block Saks Bankruptcy Financing, Says Report: Company Warns Of 'Drastic Remedies'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-loses-fight-block-saks-235124308.html</link><description>A U.S. bankruptcy judge has dismissed Amazon.com Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:AMZN) attempt to block a proposed financing deal to aid Saks Global Enterprises during its Chapter 11 bankruptcy. On Thursday, Judge Alfredo Perez approved a preliminary $400 million financing package for Saks following a courtroom battle between the retailer and several creditors, including Amazon, reported Reuters. Saks is seeking $1.75 billion to continue operations, but will need further approvals from the U.S. District &amp;amp; Bankru</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-loses-fight-block-saks-235124308.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] YouTuber MKBHD Hails Tesla Model Y Performance, Calls EV Giant's Self-Driving Technology 'The Best'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</link><description>YouTuber Marques Brownlee, aka MKBHD, has shared his thoughts on the Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) Model Y Performance trim, as well as the company's self-driving technology. Tesla Self-Driving Is The Best Ever, MKBHD Says The YouTuber, in a review of the Model Y Performance on Thursday, hailed the crossover's software on the 16-inch touchscreen infotainment display, which is also a real-time representation of the car. "This is the best software in a car that is not Android Auto or Apple CarPlay," bo</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youtuber-mkbhd-hails-tesla-model-215345892.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 3 Growth Stocks to Invest $1,000 in Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/3-growth-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</link><description>Nvidia, Amazon, and Dutch Bros are top growth stocks to invest in now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/3-growth-stocks-to-invest-1000-in-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Reason Why Now Is a Great Time to Buy Vistra</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-reason-why-now-is-a-great-time-to-buy-vistra/</link><description>Vistra is ready to capitalize as tech and AI giants search for more electricity.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/1-reason-why-now-is-a-great-time-to-buy-vistra/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Prediction: This Will Be Alphabet's Stock Price by the End of 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-this-will-be-alphabets-stock-price-by-t/</link><description>The primary factors that were boosting Alphabet's stock price last year are gone.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-this-will-be-alphabets-stock-price-by-t/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Bank of America revamps Alphabet stock after Google enters two key partnerships</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</link><description>Investors are taking a fresh look at Google, as new partnerships tied to its Gemini models help push the stock higher. On Jan. 11, Google and Walmart (WMT) said they plan to roll out a new shopping experience inside Google’s Gemini chatbot, highlighting a potential new revenue path for Google. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/bank-of-america-revamps-alphabet-stock-after-google-enters-two-key-partnerships</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 203 Billion Reasons Why Microsoft Is a Buy in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/203-billion-reasons-why-microsoft-is-a-buy-in-2026/</link><description>Microsoft's OpenAI investment could infuse cash into its business at the right time.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/203-billion-reasons-why-microsoft-is-a-buy-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jamie Dimon Rules Out Fed Chair Role, But Would Consider 'Secretary of The Treasury' If The President Asks: 'I Like Being My Own Boss'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimon-rules-fed-chair-193104450.html</link><description>Banking giant JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co.’s (NYSE:JPM) CEO, Jamie Dimon, firmly ruled out any possibility of leading the Federal Reserve in the near future, but is open to serving as the Secretary of the Treasury, if asked by the President. Dimon Might Consider Treasury Secretary Role Dimon said there was “positively no chance” that he would serve as the Chairman of the Federal Reserve, even if he were asked by “a President” of the U.S., in an interview with Bloomberg’s David Rubenstein on Thursday. Wh</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jamie-dimon-rules-fed-chair-193104450.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Could Acquiring Ventyx Biosciences Send Eli Lilly Stock Soaring in 2026?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/could-acquiring-ventyx-biosciences-send-eli-lilly/</link><description>The pharmaceutical leader has plenty of cash and is using it effectively.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/could-acquiring-ventyx-biosciences-send-eli-lilly/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Silver Swings Wildly After Trump Holds Back On Critical Mineral Tariffs: Dow Futures In The Green After Strong Tech Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/silver-swings-wildly-trump-holds-183108773.html</link><description>U.S. stock futures are in the green on Thursday night, following a rally during the regular session, powered by the strong earnings performance of chipmaker Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd. (NYSE:TSM). The S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures are up 0.15%, or 10.75 points, trading at 6,992.25, followed by Nasdaq Futures at 25,767.50, up 0.24%, or 63.25 points and finally Dow Futures, trading at 49,667.00, up 0.06% or 28 points. Silver prices witnessed a steep pullback on Thursday, after President Donald T</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/silver-swings-wildly-trump-holds-183108773.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA (KLAC) Gets Upgrade as Foundry-Led WFE Demand Accelerates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-gets-upgrade-foundry-175739387.html</link><description>KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) is one of the Trending AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 13, TD Cowen analyst Krish Sankar upgraded the stock from Hold to “Buy” and raised the price target to $1,800.00 from $1,300. With foundry-led WFE demand accelerating, firm analysts have raised CY27 EPS to $50 and driving the PT lift. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-gets-upgrade-foundry-175739387.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Arm (ARM) Downgraded by BofA on Smartphone and Royalty Headwinds</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-arm-downgraded-bofa-smartphone-175635979.html</link><description>Arm Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARM) is one of the Trending AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 13, BofA Securities analyst Vivek Arya downgraded the stock from Buy to Neutral and lowered the price target to $120 from $145. The rating downgrade comes ahead of ARM’s third quarter fiscal year 2026 results on Feb. 4. BofA […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-arm-downgraded-bofa-smartphone-175635979.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Where Will Nvidia Stock Be in 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/where-will-nvidia-stock-be-in-10-years/</link><description>Does the chipmaker have a future after generative AI?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/where-will-nvidia-stock-be-in-10-years/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia (NVDA) Added to Wolfe Alpha List as Favorite AI Idea for 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-added-wolfe-alpha-175339419.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the Hot AI Stocks to Keep on Your Radar. On January 13, Wolfe reiterated the stock as “Outperform,” noting that the idea is its favorite for 2026. Analyst Chris Caso noted that the AI chip maker is being added to the Wolfe Alpha List, replacing Micron. This is despite […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-nvda-added-wolfe-alpha-175339419.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet (GOOGL) Gets $350 Target From Truist as Search Momentum Holds</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-gets-350-target-175244828.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the Hot AI Stocks to Keep on Your Radar. On January 13, Truist Securities analyst Youssef Squali reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with a $350.00 price target. The rating affirmation comes ahead of the tech giant’s fourth-quarter earnings report scheduled for February 4. Despite an increase in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-googl-gets-350-target-175244828.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Apple’s (AAPL) AI Roadmap Strengthens With Google Deal, Says Evercore</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-roadmap-strengthens-174853486.html</link><description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is one of the Hot AI Stocks to Keep on Your Radar. On January 12, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani reiterated an Outperform rating on the stock with a $330.00 price target. Firm analysts highlight Apple’s new AI partnership with Google Gemini, citing monetization upside and custom AI experiences ahead. The firm […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-aapl-ai-roadmap-strengthens-174853486.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Rothschild Redburn Stays Bullish on ASML on Strong Order Intake</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rothschild-redburn-stays-bullish-asml-174500753.html</link><description>ASML Holding N.V. (NASDAQ:ASML) is one of the Hot AI Stocks to Keep on Your Radar. On January 13, Rothschild Redburn analyst Timm Schulze-Melander raised the price target on the stock to EUR1, 250.00 (from EUR1, 200.00) while maintaining a Buy rating. The research firm lifted its Q4 2025 order intake forecast for ASML to […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rothschild-redburn-stays-bullish-asml-174500753.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] KeyBanc Turns Bullish on Intel (INTC), Citing Server CPU Tightness and Foundry Yield Gains</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-turns-bullish-intel-intc-173853702.html</link><description>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is one of the Trending AI Stocks on Wall Street. On January 13, KeyBanc analyst John Vinh upgraded the stock from Sector Weight to Overweight with a price target of $60.00. Firm analysts see improving foundry yield gains and robust hyperscaler-driven data center demand. Despite several headwinds in the server CPU market, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-turns-bullish-intel-intc-173853702.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Gene Munster Warns Wall Street Is Underestimating 2026 AI Demand As Nvidia And TSMC Signal Strong Upside</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gene-munster-warns-wall-street-173110396.html</link><description>On Thursday, Deepwater Asset Management's managing partner Gene Munster said new signals from Nvidia Corp (NASDAQ:NVDA) and its key chip supplier suggest artificial intelligence growth is accelerating into 2026, not slowing. AI Infrastructure Growth Seen Beating Expectations Munster took X and said that key indicators point to stronger-than-expected AI fundamentals this year, prompting him to forecast Nvidia revenue growth of more than 65% year over year in 2026, well above Wall Street's roughly</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gene-munster-warns-wall-street-173110396.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dow Jones Futures: Trump To Impose Tariffs On NATO Nations Over Greenland; Google In Buy Zone</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-tariffs-nato-nations-greenland-google/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Dow Jones futures: President Donald Trump said that eight NATO members face escalating tariffs unless a deal is struck for the U.S. buying Greenland.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-tariffs-nato-nations-greenland-google/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] VOO vs VTI: What's the Better U.S. Stock ETF Buy?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/voo-vs-vti-whats-the-better-us-stock-etf-buy/</link><description>Choosing between the Vanguard S&amp;amp;P 500 ETF (VOO) and the Vanguard Total Stock Market ETF (VTI) comes down to your opinion on small caps.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/voo-vs-vti-whats-the-better-us-stock-etf-buy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Says Elon Musk's OpenAI Lawsuit Is 'The Real Deal' As Kalshi Bettors Raise Odds Of xAI CEO Winning</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-elon-musks-163112321.html</link><description>On Thursday, market commentator and CNBC personality Jim Cramer said that Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk's lawsuit against OpenAI poses serious risks for the artificial intelligence company, particularly if it ever pursues a public listing. Jim Cramer Flags High Stakes For OpenAI "This Musk suit against OpenAI is the real deal — and not a good one for OpenAI if and when it wants to go public," Cramer wrote on X. He added that OpenAI may need to complete a large private fundraising round</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-says-elon-musks-163112321.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This Chipmaker Is One of the Largest Companies by Market Cap. But Is Its Stock a Buy?</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/this-chipmaker-is-one-of-the-largest-companies-by/</link><description>This company is one of 11 companies with a market above $1 trillion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/this-chipmaker-is-one-of-the-largest-companies-by/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] TSMC Says 'No More' To Nvidia: Why That Is Intel's Golden Ticket</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-says-no-more-nvidia-161151468.html</link><description>The AI boom just hit a constraint investors don't talk about enough: you can't ship what you can't build. Demand for AI chips is still surging, but the world's leading foundry, Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd (NYSE:TSM), or TSMC, is starting to run out of room. That matters — because when supply, not demand, becomes the bottleneck, the entire power structure of the AI trade begins to shift. When The Kingmaker Runs Out Of Capacity According to a report first published by The Information</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsmc-says-no-more-nvidia-161151468.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Investors Worried About Large Cap Concentration Risk Have a Great Option in MDY</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/investors-worried-about-large-cap-concentration-risk-have-a-great-option-in-mdy/</link><description>The SPDR S&amp;amp;P 500 ETF Trust (NYSEARCA:SPY) tells a story of increasing concentration. The S&amp;amp;P 500 has become a technology-dominated index, with information technology representing over a third of its weight. This concentration intensifies at the top, where just three mega-cap tech companies control more than a fifth of the entire index’s value—creating a portfolio ... Investors Worried About Large Cap Concentration Risk Have a Great Option in MDY</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/investors-worried-about-large-cap-concentration-risk-have-a-great-option-in-mdy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 'Ramsey Show' Caller Says His Wife Secretly Took Out $300K In 'Predatory Loans' Over 10 Years And 'Blew' It On Amazon</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ramsey-show-caller-says-wife-150105725.html</link><description>A recent caller to “The Ramsey Show” stunned the hosts when he revealed his wife had taken out nearly $300,000 in high-interest loans over the span of a decade, all without his knowledge. “My wife over the last eight to 10 years has taken on a series of, I guess the term is predatory loans,” Jeff from Jacksonville, Florida, told hosts George Kamel and John Delony. “Now totaling right around $300,000. All without my knowledge, of course.” Don't Miss: The AI Marketing Platform Backed by Insiders f</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ramsey-show-caller-says-wife-150105725.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Got $1,000? 2 Top Growth Stocks to Buy That Could Double Your Money.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/got-1000-2-top-growth-stocks-that-could-double/</link><description>These companies are growing at a faster pace than the broader market and trading at attractive valuations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/got-1000-2-top-growth-stocks-that-could-double/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] 3 Reasons to Buy IBM Stock Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/3-reasons-to-buy-ibm-stock-right-now/</link><description>AI, quantum computing, and a reliable dividend should be enticing to long-term investors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/3-reasons-to-buy-ibm-stock-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 2 Artificial Intelligence (AI) Stocks That Can Beat the Market in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/2-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-that-can-beat/</link><description>Investors are underestimating the growth potential of these leading tech companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/2-artificial-intelligence-ai-stocks-that-can-beat/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] From $5.38 to 17 Cents: Inside Senator McConnell's 97% Stock Wipeout</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-38-17-cents-inside-143139913.html</link><description>When it comes to tracking the stock trading activity of members of Congress, investors often pay attention to the stocks that gain or may raise conflicts of interest. A senator disclosed selling a stock for a significant loss in 2025 that might not get as much attention. Senator McConnell Sells Luminar Stock In 2025 Sen. Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) reported selling shares of Luminar Technologies (OTC:LAZRQ) in two transactions in 2025, according to the Benzinga Government Trades page. Here are the t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-38-17-cents-inside-143139913.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Is Micron Technology the Cheapest AI Stock?</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/is-micron-technology-the-cheapest-ai-stock/</link><description>The artificial intelligence (AI) revolution has sparked a new wave of high-performing investments, including Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA), which has become the face of the industry, while Alphabet (NASDAQ:GOOG)(NASDAQ:GOOGL) has advanced its position in the space, leapfrogging over rivals with the release of Gemini 3 in November. Other companies, like Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ:AMD), have also benefited ... Is Micron Technology the Cheapest AI Stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/17/is-micron-technology-the-cheapest-ai-stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] My Favorite Artificial Intelligence Stock to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/favorite-artificial-intelligence-stock-buy-goog/</link><description>Alphabet is emerging as a leader in the AI race, even among other big tech companies, and it's looking like the strongest horse in that race.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/favorite-artificial-intelligence-stock-buy-goog/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Wall Street Is Starting to Like Intel Stock Again</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/wall-street-is-starting-to-like-intel-stock-again/</link><description>The once-hated stock is starting to win some fans.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/wall-street-is-starting-to-like-intel-stock-again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] These 7 Stocks Are Analyst Favorites For Magnificent Earnings Growth; Google Stock Trades Near Buy Point</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/best-stocks-seven-magnificent-stocks-earnings-growth/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Among the best stocks in earnings performance, Broadcom boasts a 98 EPS Rating, one of the highest in the chip sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/best-stocks-seven-magnificent-stocks-earnings-growth/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] My 3 Favorite Stocks to Buy Right Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/my-3-favorite-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</link><description>These offer a mix of growth and value.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/my-3-favorite-stocks-to-buy-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Dan Ives Calls It 1996, Not 1999 — 3 AI Stocks Wall Street Still Isn't Pricing In</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dan-ives-calls-1996-not-132148405.html</link><description>Dan Ives is pushing back on the market's biggest AI anxiety. As tech earnings kick off, the Wedbush analyst says this isn't a 1999-style excess cycle — it's mid-1996, when spending accelerates, doubts linger, and the biggest gains are still ahead. His message is clear: upcoming results should validate a massive AI buildout that the Street continues to underestimate in both scale and duration. Why Earnings Matter More Than Valuations Right Now Ives expects a strong fourth-quarter earnings season</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dan-ives-calls-1996-not-132148405.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 No-Brainer Growth Stock to Buy in 2026 With $200</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/buy-growth-stock-nvidia-2026-right-now/</link><description>Buying just one share of Nvidia would be a simple way to start betting on AI in the new year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/buy-growth-stock-nvidia-2026-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Billionaire Bill Ackman Has 39.5% of His Portfolio Invested in These 3 Unstoppable Stocks</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/billionaire-bill-ackman-has-395-of-his-portfolio-i/</link><description>You don't need to be a hedge fund manager to see the value in these stocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/billionaire-bill-ackman-has-395-of-his-portfolio-i/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Like DoorDash and Google’s CEOs, $7.6 billion Informatica boss is a McKinsey alum—he says being ‘pushed around’ by smart consultants helped him grow</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/doordash-google-ceos-7-6-120300867.html</link><description>The CEO of Informatica, Amit Walia, says he encountered imposter syndrome and critiques at the consulting giant. And McKinsey has proved itself as a training hotbed for future leaders, creating more Fortune 500 CEOs than anywhere else.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/doordash-google-ceos-7-6-120300867.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] BMO Reaffirms Eli Lilly and Company (LLY) as an Obesity Market Leader</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bmo-reaffirms-eli-lilly-company-114530772.html</link><description>Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) is among the stocks with the best earnings growth for the next 5 years. On January 14, BMO Capital reaffirmed an ‘Outperform’ rating on Eli Lilly and Company (NYSE:LLY) with a price target of $1,200. Matching the consensus 1-year median target price, the stock has an upside potential of 16.36%. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bmo-reaffirms-eli-lilly-company-114530772.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] NVIDIA Corporation (NVDA) Faces China H200 Tariff Headwind, Yet Wolfe Stays Bullish</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-corporation-nvda-faces-china-114521535.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is among the stocks with the best earnings growth for the next 5 years. On January 15, Wolfe Research maintained an ‘Outperform’ rating on NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) with a price target of $250. In line with the consensus 1-year median price target, the price target reflects an upside potential of 33.60%. This […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-corporation-nvda-faces-china-114521535.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: Nvidia Will Become the First $6 Trillion Company in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-nvidia-will-become-the-first-6-trillion/</link><description>High demand marches on for Nvidia's AI products and services.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/17/prediction-nvidia-will-become-the-first-6-trillion/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Verizon Outage Ends — And The Stock Is Bracing For The Damage</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/verizon-outage-ends-stock-bracing-110105558.html</link><description>Verizon Communications (NYSE:VZ) suffered a nationwide outage in the United States on Wednesday that upset customers, led to some unwanted emergency alerts being sent out, and prevented people from calling or texting. While the outage is over, the impact on Verizon stock is still to come with the company promising account credits. Verizon Outage Could Hurt VZ Stock Verizon customers were unable to use text, voice or data services for hours on Wednesday, leading to complaints across the country.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/verizon-outage-ends-stock-bracing-110105558.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>