<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Watchlist News</title><link>https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml</link><description>Aggregated news for my potential investments</description><atom:link href="https://alfwro13.github.io/my-stock-feed/watchlist_news_rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>StockBot-v1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>[GOOG] CEO Luca de Meo Outlines Tech Ambitions for Kering</title><link>https://wwd.com/business-news/technology/kering-ceo-luca-de-meo-strategic-plan-for-technology-1238485796/</link><description>The former car executive plans to use technology to improve design, supply chain and customer experience in luxury fashion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://wwd.com/business-news/technology/kering-ceo-luca-de-meo-strategic-plan-for-technology-1238485796/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] OpenAI, SpaceX Shares In Demand. Private Markets Boom As Investors Chase Next Nvidia.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/private-markets-nvidia-stock-openai-spacex/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Private markets are booming as investors seek equity in buzzy startups like OpenAI and SpaceX while IPOs remain scarce.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/private-markets-nvidia-stock-openai-spacex/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel shares plunge on earnings expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-plunge-earnings-expectations-223932017.html</link><description>Intel shares dove more than 10 percent Thursday despite the struggling US chip maker doing better than expected in the recently ended quarter, as its revenue forecast disappointed investors.While the depth of losses beat market expectations, Intel's revenue forecast for the current quarter fell far short of what Wall Street analysts were predicting amid recently raised expectations for the company.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-shares-plunge-earnings-expectations-223932017.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Michael Burry Warns Government Intervention Won't Stop AI Bubble Burst: 'The Problem Is Too Big To Save'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-burry-warns-government-intervention-223106727.html</link><description>‘The Big Short’ investor Michael Burry has issued a dire warning regarding the artificial intelligence (AI) sector, predicting a systemic collapse that not even federal intervention can prevent. Defining The Mania In a scathing post on X, Burry characterized the current AI investment frenzy as a “mania” that is mathematically destined to fail. Burry, famous for betting against the housing market before the 2008 crash, argues that the massive capital expenditures by the world's wealthiest corpora</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/michael-burry-warns-government-intervention-223106727.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Have $10,000? These 3 Stocks Could Be Bargain Buys for 2026 and Beyond.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/10k-stocks-bargain-buys-2026-tsm-meta-crm/</link><description>There are still solid bargains to be found in the tech sector.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/10k-stocks-bargain-buys-2026-tsm-meta-crm/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Taiwan Semiconductor's 2026 Outlook Is a Clear Sign to Buy the Stock Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductors-2026-outlook-is-a-clear-sign/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor expects another year of 30% revenue growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductors-2026-outlook-is-a-clear-sign/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Michael Saylor’s Bitcoin Playbook: What He Says Will Win</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/michael-saylors-bitcoin-playbook-what-he-says-will-win/</link><description>When the world’s most vocal Bitcoin maximalist names a stock alongside BTC as a “best performing asset of the decade,” you pay attention. Michael Saylor doesn’t do diversification. He does conviction. His two bets for the next ten years are Bitcoin and Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA). That pairing reveals how he sees digital transformation playing out. A ... Michael Saylor’s Bitcoin Playbook: What He Says Will Win</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/michael-saylors-bitcoin-playbook-what-he-says-will-win/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Zuckerberg Vs. Musk: Meta's Threads Now More Popular Than X</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zuckerberg-vs-musk-metas-threads-213109420.html</link><description>A new report shows that when it comes to social media usage, an app from Meta Platforms Inc (NASDAQ:META) is seeing strong daily user growth, while X from Elon Musk's xAI is falling behind. Here's the latest in the battle for users on social media. Threads Vs. X: New Winner Emerges For Mobile Use Launched in July 2023 and quickly gaining 100 million sign-ups in five days, Threads from Meta has been called an X killer and an X copycat. Whatever you call Threads, the social media platform is showi</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zuckerberg-vs-musk-metas-threads-213109420.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Micron &amp; NVIDIA: The Kings of AI Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-nvidia-kings-ai-stocks-212000384.html</link><description>Even if 2026 is filled with AI 'losers', Micron and NVIDIA's critcal role in the buildout insulate them nicely from any sudden shocks, underpinned by visibly strong demand pictures.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/micron-nvidia-kings-ai-stocks-212000384.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel struggles to meet AI demand</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-forecasts-first-quarter-sales-210224582.html</link><description>Intel said on Thursday it struggled to satisfy demand for its server chips used in AI data centers, and forecast quarterly revenue and profit below market estimates, sending shares down 7% ​in after-hours trading.  Investors and analysts ‌have hoped that rapid data center buildouts commissioned by large tech companies to advance their AI businesses will drive sales for Intel's traditional server chips that are used alongside Nvidia's market-leading graphics processing units (GPU).  Demand for AI surprised some of the cloud-computing giants, which have had to scramble in order to upgrade aging fleets of chips because of an "erosion in networking performance," finance chief David Zinsner told Reuters in an interview.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-forecasts-first-quarter-sales-210224582.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tesla testing robotaxis without a human safety monitor</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tesla-testing-robotaxis-without-human-204005519.html</link><description>Tesla (TSLA) CEO Elon Musk confirmed that some of the company's robotaxis in Austin are being tested without a safety monitor. Yahoo Finance Senior Autos Reporter Pras Subramanian discuss the details. He also discusses Waymo expanding its service into Miami. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/tesla-testing-robotaxis-without-human-204005519.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] New Governors Abigail Spanberger, Mikie Sherrill Congratulated By Brian Armstrong: Coinbase CEO Calls It 'Another Milestone' For Pro-Crypto Advocates</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/governors-abigail-spanberger-mikie-sherrill-203118697.html</link><description>Coinbase Global Inc. (NASDAQ:COIN) CEO Brian Armstrong celebrated the inaugurations of Abigail Spanberger as Governor of Virginia and Mikie Sherrill as Governor of New Jersey, framing it as a win for pro-cryptocurrency politicians Armstrong Congratulates ‘Pro-Crypto’ Advocates In an X...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/governors-abigail-spanberger-mikie-sherrill-203118697.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] I Nailed My Nvidia Market Cap Prediction in 2025. Here's Where I Predict It's Going in 2026 (Hint: You're Going to Want to Buy Now)</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/i-nailed-my-nvidia-market-cap-prediction-in-2025-h/</link><description>At one point in 2025, Nvidia's value hit $5 trillion. I foresee it going much higher in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/i-nailed-my-nvidia-market-cap-prediction-in-2025-h/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Do Tariff Jitters Versus Locked-In AI Deals Reveal Nebius Group’s True Edge (NBIS)?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tariff-jitters-versus-locked-ai-201153890.html</link><description>In recent days, Nebius Group has come under pressure after new U.S. tariff threats on European countries unnerved global markets and weighed on technology names, even as the company continues to ramp up its AI-focused cloud infrastructure business with large, long-term contracts. These headlines contrast sharply with Nebius’s capacity being effectively sold out and its multi-year infrastructure agreements with Microsoft and Meta, which together total over US$20.00 billion and highlight how...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tariff-jitters-versus-locked-ai-201153890.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Snowflake Stock Is Struggling, But This Bull Put Spread Bets There's A Limit To The Bleeding</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/options/snowflake-stock-snow-options-trade-bull-put-spread-income-investing-markets/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Snowflake stock is now down 16% in the last three months, but there's a good chance that shares of the artificial intelligence software maker won't drop much more between now and mid-June.  Now it's time to look at a slightly longer-term bull put spread.  Longer-term option trades tend to move a little slower than shorter-term trades.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/options/snowflake-stock-snow-options-trade-bull-put-spread-income-investing-markets/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Is It Too Late To Consider Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (NYSE:TSM) After Its Strong Run?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-201004194.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing is still reasonably priced after its strong run, you are not alone. The stock last closed at US$326.12, with a 0.3% decline over the past 7 days, an 11.2% return over 30 days, and returns of 2.0% year to date, 47.6% over 1 year, 266.0% over 3 years, and 186.0% over 5 years. Recent headlines have focused on Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing's role as a key chip producer for global technology companies and its central position in...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-consider-taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-201004194.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] TRAY CEO Peter Kellis on Hospitality Tech Trends: ICR Conference 2026</title><link>https://tech.yahoo.com/business/articles/tray-ceo-peter-kellis-hospitality-200549207.html</link><description>Exec Edge hosted a fireside chat at the ICR Conference 2026 with Peter Kellis, Chief Executive Officer of TRAY. The in-person interview was joined by Editor-in-Chief John Jannarone and they discussed AI’s growth across the restaurant industry and its impact moving forward at a high level for restaurants, the top trends in the hospitality technology […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tech.yahoo.com/business/articles/tray-ceo-peter-kellis-hospitality-200549207.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Waymo Begins Robotaxi Service in Miami</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-begins-robotaxi-miami-195433536.html</link><description>Alphabet subsidiary expands autonomous fleet into another major US city.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/waymo-begins-robotaxi-miami-195433536.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Big Tech Floods Washington With Record Lobbying as Trump Embraces AI Agenda</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-floods-washington-record-194903115.html</link><description>Tech and AI firms spent $109 million on lobbying in 2025 as the Trump administration aligned policy with industry priorities.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-tech-floods-washington-record-194903115.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google DeepMind CEO is ‘surprised’ OpenAI is rushing forward with ads in ChatGPT</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-deepmind-ceo-surprised-openai-194101107.html</link><description>Google DeepMind CEO Demis Hassabis says the tech giant isn't pressuring him to insert ads into the AI chatbot experience.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-deepmind-ceo-surprised-openai-194101107.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VTI] Want to Be a Millionaire? Buy This ETF and Never Sell.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/want-to-be-a-millionaire-buy-this-etf-and-never-se/</link><description>If you want to build a million-dollar investment portfolio, you don't need to do anything extraordinary.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/want-to-be-a-millionaire-buy-this-etf-and-never-se/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Forget BigBear.ai: This "Picks and Shovels" Data Streaming Stock Looks Built for Long‑Term AI Upside</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/forget-bigbearai-this-picks-and-shovels-data-strea/</link><description>IBM is a more reliable AI play in this unpredictable market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/forget-bigbearai-this-picks-and-shovels-data-strea/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Just Delivered Fantastic News to Nvidia and Broadcom Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-just-delivered/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor just published an impressive fourth-quarter earnings report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductor-manufacturing-just-delivered/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tesla stock pops as Elon Musk posts video claiming no safety monitor in Austin robotaxi</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-stock-pops-as-elon-musk-posts-video-claiming-no-safety-monitor-in-austin-robotaxi-191059641.html</link><description>Tesla (TSLA) CEO Elon Musk said the company started robotaxi rides with no safety monitor present in the car in Austin, a long awaited move. This comes after Waymo announced another expansion of its robotaxi service in the US, hammering home its lead in the autonomous space - for now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-stock-pops-as-elon-musk-posts-video-claiming-no-safety-monitor-in-austin-robotaxi-191059641.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 'He Brings Down Prices' — CNBC's Jim Cramer Pushes Back On Claims That 'The President Makes Investing So Difficult' That 'People Feel Like Giving Up'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brings-down-prices-cnbcs-jim-190543470.html</link><description>Jim Cramer is pushing back against the idea that President Donald Trump is scaring people away from the stock market. In a post on X on Wednesday, the CNBC host acknowledged that many feel discouraged by market conditions but said those emotions may be misplaced. Not All Market Drops Are Bad News, Cramer Says “I know lots of people ALREADY feel like giving up because the President makes investing so difficult,” Cramer wrote. “I disagree. He makes trading hard, but he brings down prices that shou</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brings-down-prices-cnbcs-jim-190543470.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Elon Musk Drops Major Cybercab, Optimus Production Update: 'Insanely Fast'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-drops-major-cybercab-190110898.html</link><description>Tesla Inc. (NASDAQ:TSLA) CEO Elon Musk has shared an update regarding the upcoming Cybercab, as well as the Optimus Humanoid Robot's production timelines. Elon Musk Says Tesla Has Revamped Cybercab Production In a response to influencer Sawyer Merritt's post on the social media platform X, Musk, on Tuesday, shared that the initial production for any product "is always very slow and follows an S-curve." Merritt's post shared a video that showcased the Tesla Cybercab being produced with the "unbox</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-drops-major-cybercab-190110898.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Advanced Micro Devices’ Winning Streak Continues. How High Can the Chip Stock Go?</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/advanced-micro-devices-ai-chip-stock-7d9318d0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>AMD shares are up 25% over that eight-day period and have soared more than 100% over the past year.  The iShares Semiconductor exchange-traded fund is up 51% over the past 12 months, bolstered in recent weeks by Intel’s sudden surge.  Intel is getting love for its new processors and positive comments from President Donald Trump, while AMD has, in comparison, flown under the radar to start 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/advanced-micro-devices-ai-chip-stock-7d9318d0?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Stock Rises -- Raymond James Hikes Price Target to $400</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-stock-rises-raymond-james-183530541.html</link><description>Google's AI Ecosystem Fuels Gains in Alphabet Shares Thursday</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-stock-rises-raymond-james-183530541.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] Why Arm Holdings Stock Was Climbing This Week</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/why-arm-holdings-stock-was-climbing-this-week/</link><description>Arm bounced back after a long sell-off late last year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/why-arm-holdings-stock-was-climbing-this-week/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Wine, Water and No Chairs: Inside Trump’s Private Reception With CEOs in Davos</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/inside-trumps-private-reception-with-ceos-in-davos-543ef7d8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Apple’s Tim Cook, BlackRock’s Larry Fink and dozens more CEOs stood and waited for over an hour for a meet and greet with the president.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/inside-trumps-private-reception-with-ceos-in-davos-543ef7d8?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Is the 2026 Market Rotation Already Underway? Here’s What Could Lead After the Magnificent 7</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/is-the-2026-market-rotation-already-underway-heres-what-could-lead-after-the-magnificent-7/</link><description>It feels like a great rotation out of the Magnificent Seven has already kicked off just over a quarter ago. Undoubtedly, the group that’s helped lead the S&amp;amp;P 500 to impressive gains in the past several years has shown signs of slowing down. Collectively, the group of seven AI-driven tech leaders has stalled, but underneath ... Is the 2026 Market Rotation Already Underway? Here’s What Could Lead After the Magnificent 7</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/is-the-2026-market-rotation-already-underway-heres-what-could-lead-after-the-magnificent-7/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet’s Google Awards PPAs to Clearway Energy to Receive Carbon-Free Energy For Its Data Centers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-google-awards-ppas-clearway-180859057.html</link><description>Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Stocks to Look For in 2026. On January 15, Alphabet Inc.’s (NASDAQ:GOOGL) Google recently awarded three new long-term power purchase agreements (PPAs) to Clearway Energy Group, Inc. (NYSE:CWEN), as reported by Clearway Energy. This development is part of Clearway’s 2025 plan, which includes three […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-google-awards-ppas-clearway-180859057.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jefferies Raises PT on NVIDIA Corporation From $250 to $275, Keeps Buy Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-raises-pt-nvidia-corporation-180857534.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Stocks to Look For in 2026. On January 15, Jefferies raised its price target on NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) from $250 to $275, according to TheFly. Blayne Curtis at Jefferies raised the price target on the AI chipmaker and maintained a Buy rating on the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jefferies-raises-pt-nvidia-corporation-180857534.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway Specialty Insurance Launches First Executive D&amp;O Liability+ Offering in the U.K.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-specialty-insurance-launches-180846178.html</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway Inc. (NYSE:BRK-B) is one of the 15 Best S&amp;amp;P 500 Stocks to Look For in 2026. On January 13, Berkshire Hathaway Specialty Insurance (BHSI), a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway’s National Indemnity group of insurance companies, announced the launch of Executive First D&amp;amp;O Liability+ offering in the United Kingdom. This is an enhanced directors’ […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-specialty-insurance-launches-180846178.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Suze Orman Says Retirees Should Keep At Least 5 Years Of Cash On Hand—Warns Not To Invest It All Because 'Sometimes Everything Can Go Down'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/suze-orman-says-retirees-keep-180110528.html</link><description>Suze Orman doesn't think your retirement plan should depend on the market behaving. If everything drops—and she says it can—she wants you holding cash, not regrets. On her "Women &amp;amp; Money" podcast, Orman said retirees should keep three to five years of living expenses in cash. Not stocks. Not bonds. Just money you can reach for when everything else is falling apart. "It's not always that stocks go down and bonds go up," she said. "Sometimes everything can go down." That's why she tells listeners</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/suze-orman-says-retirees-keep-180110528.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta (META) Stock Is Up, What You Need To Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-meta-stock-know-180036080.html</link><description>Shares of social network operator Meta Platforms (NASDAQ:META) jumped 4.7% in the afternoon session after investor optimism grew following positive analyst commentary and the company's announcement that it would begin showing ads on its Threads platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meta-meta-stock-know-180036080.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Bill Gates--Backed Fund Leads $110 Million AI Chip Investment</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bill-gates-backed-fund-leads-175437755.html</link><description>Neurophos Inc. raises funding from Gates Frontier, Microsoft's M12, and Aramco Ventures to develop optical AI processors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bill-gates-backed-fund-leads-175437755.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] SNOW Expands Cloud Infrastructure Reach: A Sign for More Upside?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snow-expands-cloud-infrastructure-reach-174500194.html</link><description>Snowflake's revenue growth is driven by AI adoption, partnerships, and cloud expansion.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snow-expands-cloud-infrastructure-reach-174500194.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] AMD Rides on Expanding Enterprise Partner Base: More Upside to Come?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-rides-expanding-enterprise-partner-173500117.html</link><description>Advanced Micro Devices targets a CAGR of 80% in AI revenues as Helios racks, Instinct GPUs and key global partnerships power data center growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-rides-expanding-enterprise-partner-173500117.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] D-Wave (QBTS) Q4 2024 Earnings Call Transcript</title><link>https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/22/d-wave-qbts-q4-2024-earnings-call-transcript/</link><description>It’s a remarkable time to be leading one of the world’s preeminent quantum computing companies, and it is incredible how much has happened since we spoke to you last quarter.  Big companies like Google, Nvidia, Amazon and Microsoft all made quantum headlines recently, fueling debate among quantum industry skeptics, enthusiasts and undecideds as to when quantum will be able to solve real problems.  At D-Wave, we are seeing firsthand the value that quantum is providing today for hundreds of companies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/22/d-wave-qbts-q4-2024-earnings-call-transcript/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Eli Lilly (LLY) Q2 2025 Earnings Call Transcript</title><link>https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/22/eli-lilly-lly-q2-2025-earnings-call-transcript/</link><description>Q2 was a strong quarter.  Today we shared positive top line data from the ATTAIN-1 orforglipron trial in people with obesity.  In ATTAIN-1, patients taking the highest dose of orforglipron lost more than 27 pounds or 12.4% of their body weight.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/earnings/call-transcripts/2026/01/22/eli-lilly-lly-q2-2025-earnings-call-transcript/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ARM] COHR vs. ARM: Which Tech Growth Stock Is the Better Buy Now?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cohr-vs-arm-tech-growth-171800924.html</link><description>Coherent vs. Arm Holdings frames an AI-driven growth contest, comparing margins, balance sheets and valuation to see which tech stock offers the better buy now.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cohr-vs-arm-tech-growth-171800924.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Will Lam Research (LRCX) Beat Estimates Again in Its Next Earnings Report?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-beat-estimates-171001704.html</link><description>Lam Research (LRCX) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lam-research-lrcx-beat-estimates-171001704.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Partner Tests Buy Point On 12% Gain To Begin 2026</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/nvidia-collaborator-vertiv-tests-buy-point-to-begin-2026-stock-market/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia partner Vertiv flirted with a buy point in Thursday's stock market with substantial earnings growth expected.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/nvidia-collaborator-vertiv-tests-buy-point-to-begin-2026-stock-market/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] ABBV vs. MRK: An Oncology-Immunology Showdown for Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/abbv-vs-mrk-oncology-immunology-170300512.html</link><description>ABBV has rebounded after Humira patent cliff, with Skyrizi and Rinvoq driving growth. Rising estimates and a pipeline set to power earnings into 2029 bode well.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/abbv-vs-mrk-oncology-immunology-170300512.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Kevin O'Leary Says Until Bitcoin Hits This Level And Gets 'Fully Regulated,' Owning Electricity Will Be More 'Valuable' Than BTC Itself</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-until-bitcoin-163112579.html</link><description>Renowned investor Kevin O’Leary emphasized the significance of owning energy infrastructure in the cryptocurrency realm on Tuesday, adding that at the right price, electricity can hold greater value than Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) itself. Why Energy Control Is Crucial For Bitcoin...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-until-bitcoin-163112579.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] This Under-the-Radar Stock Could Be the Simplest Way to Build Long-Term Wealth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/this-under-the-radar-stock-could-be-the-simplest-w/</link><description>Rezolve AI looks like a hot pick as annual recurring revenue projections indicate big growth is on the way.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/this-under-the-radar-stock-could-be-the-simplest-w/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Technology Stocks That Could Help Set You Up for Life</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/3-technology-stocks-could-help-set-you-up-for-life/</link><description>These companies are benefiting from massive AI trends that could persist for years.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/3-technology-stocks-could-help-set-you-up-for-life/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba Shares Jump 6.8% as T-Head Chip Unit IPO Option Emerges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-shares-jump-6-8-161944185.html</link><description>Bloomberg reports Alibaba is weighing restructuring its T-Head chip arm ahead of a possible future listing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-shares-jump-6-8-161944185.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Arista Stock Moves Into Positive Territory Ahead Of Q4 Earnings</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/arista-stock-anet-earnings-2026-outlook/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Arista stock popped higher on Thursday, moving into positive territory in 2026. Q4 earnings for Arista are due Feb. 12.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/arista-stock-anet-earnings-2026-outlook/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Assessing Caterpillar (CAT) Valuation After Strong Recent Share Price Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-caterpillar-cat-valuation-strong-160858036.html</link><description>Why Caterpillar (CAT) is on investors’ radar today Caterpillar (CAT) is drawing attention after a strong run in its share price, with the stock up 2.6% over the past day and 10.8% over the past month, prompting fresh interest in its valuation and financial profile. See our latest analysis for Caterpillar. The recent 2.6% 1 day share price return and 10.8% 30 day share price return at a latest share price of US$645.38 sit alongside a 1 year total shareholder return of 64.6% and 5 year total...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/assessing-caterpillar-cat-valuation-strong-160858036.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Has Barclays (LSE:BARC) Run Too Far After A 66% One Year Share Price Gain?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Barclays shares still offer value after a strong run, this article walks through how the current price stacks up against several valuation checks. The stock has been relatively steady in the near term, with a 0.9% decline over the last 7 days and a 1.6% gain over the last 30 days. The 1 year return of 66.2% and 3 year return of 194.8% put recent moves in a much longer context for anyone thinking about risk and reward. That 1 year return of 66.2% and a 5 year...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-lse-barc-run-too-160849132.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Is Rising -- Jensen Hung Says AI Boom Will Create High-Paying Jobs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-rising-jensen-hung-160803061.html</link><description>Nvidia Shares Gain. Why the AI Buildout Could Boost Blue-Collar Pay</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-rising-jensen-hung-160803061.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A) Valuation Check After Recent Share Price Softness</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-valuation-check-160718663.html</link><description>Recent share performance and business scale Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A) has recently seen modest share price pressure, with the stock showing a 0.5% decline over the past day, 2% over the past week, about 4% over the past month, and 2% over the past 3 months. Against that backdrop, the company remains a large, diversified financial and industrial group, reporting annual revenue of US$372.1b and net income of US$67.5b, spanning insurance, rail, utilities, manufacturing, and retail...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/berkshire-hathaway-brk-valuation-check-160718663.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:07:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Why Lam Research (LRCX) Is Up 5.0% After AI Buzz And Tariff Jitters Hit Spotlight</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-5-160707549.html</link><description>In recent days, Lam Research has drawn heightened attention as investors weigh upcoming U.S. tariff developments and their potential impact on chip equipment demand ahead of the company’s January 28 earnings call. At the same time, upbeat analyst commentary on Lam’s exposure to AI-related semiconductor spending and media focus on its leadership have amplified interest in how its tools fit into critical chipmaking supply chains. With the stock moving in the wake of this AI-driven optimism,...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-lam-research-lrcx-5-160707549.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Lets Users Tailor AI Search With Data From Photos, Email</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-lets-users-tailor-ai-160000092.html</link><description>The new feature, part of an offering called Personal Intelligence, will give people a choice to tailor results in the artificial intelligence-powered search mode by using data from their Gmail and Google Photos accounts.  It “transforms Search into an experience that feels uniquely yours by connecting the dots across your Google apps,” said Robby Stein, vice president of product for Google search, in a blog post.  Google, long dominant in online search, has faced new threats from artificial intelligence startups like OpenAI and Perplexity AI Inc., which offer alternative ways to look up information.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-lets-users-tailor-ai-160000092.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Arista Networks Is the S&amp;P 500’s Top Stock Today. Why It’s Soaring Isn’t Clear.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/arista-networks-stock-rally-e5d2a641?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Arista Networks  stock spiked Thursday, though the catalyst for its big move wasn’t immediately clear.  Sell-side analysts told Barron’s Thursday they were still looking for a definitive trigger, but interest in the stock didn’t come out of nowhere, said Ryan Koontz of Needham &amp;amp; Co.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/arista-networks-stock-rally-e5d2a641?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Tata Group Unveils $11 Billion Innovation City Near Mumbai Airport</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tata-group-unveils-11-billion-155202073.html</link><description>Project near Navi Mumbai airport includes a data center and targets AI and semiconductor services, officials say.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tata-group-unveils-11-billion-155202073.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Prediction: 2 Stocks That'll Be Worth More Than Amazon 3 Years From Now</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/predict-stocks-worth-more-than-amazon-tsm-avgo/</link><description>These two fast-growing semiconductor stocks have been closing the gap with Amazon in the past year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/predict-stocks-worth-more-than-amazon-tsm-avgo/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Serve Robotics Takes Physical AI Into Hospitals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/serve-robotics-takes-physical-ai-154925838.html</link><description>Diligent deal expands beyond sidewalk delivery</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/serve-robotics-takes-physical-ai-154925838.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Will Healthy Consulting Revenue Growth Benefit IBM's Q4 Earnings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/healthy-consulting-revenue-growth-benefit-154800822.html</link><description>IBM's Q4 may get a lift from healthy Consulting revenue growth fueled by AI-driven tools and a key Microsoft partnership.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/healthy-consulting-revenue-growth-benefit-154800822.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] HSBC Just Doubled Its Price Target on Intel Stock. Should You Buy INTC Ahead of Earnings?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37176834/hsbc-just-doubled-its-price-target-on-intel-stock-should-you-buy-intc-ahead-of-earnings</link><description>Analysts sharp target hike puts Intel back in focus as AI-driven server demand builds ahead of earnings.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37176834/hsbc-just-doubled-its-price-target-on-intel-stock-should-you-buy-intc-ahead-of-earnings</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Will Relatively Higher Software Revenues Aid IBM's Earnings in Q4?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/relatively-higher-software-revenues-aid-154500451.html</link><description>IBM's Q4 Software revenues are likely to have risen on watsonx.ai momentum, AI partnerships and the Confluent acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/relatively-higher-software-revenues-aid-154500451.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CSCO] Cisco’s AI Pivot: Rebuilding the Tech Stack From the Ground Up</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/cisco-ai-pivot-rebuilding-tech-153800592.html</link><description>Jeetu Patel, president and chief product officer of Cisco, explains how the company is becoming AI-first by rebuilding its technology stack from the ground up—and why AI has turned networking, security, and infrastructure into a single, integrated platform.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/cisco-ai-pivot-rebuilding-tech-153800592.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] ChatGPT Thinks Intel Stock Will Close At This Price In The Next 60 Days</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-intel-stock-close-153120913.html</link><description>Shares of Intel have shown signs of renewed investor interest as the company's push to ramp semiconductor production and expand its AI foundry ambitions intersects with broader demand for compute and deeper strategic positioning versus rivals like Nvidia and TSMC....</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chatgpt-thinks-intel-stock-close-153120913.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] BC-Most Active Stocks</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018945.html</link><description>td class="col-issue"&gt;New Era Energy &amp;amp; Digital Inc.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bc-most-active-stocks-153018945.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Chip Stocks Are Rising. Nvidia's Huang Reignites the AI Trade</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-rising-nvidias-huang-152326038.html</link><description>Global Semiconductor Shares Jump as Davos Fuels AI Optimism.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chip-stocks-rising-nvidias-huang-152326038.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google reportedly snags up team behind AI voice startup Hume AI</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-reportedly-snags-team-behind-151251440.html</link><description>Google has hired the CEO and top top behind voice AI startup Hume AI, signaling that voice is increasingly becoming the preferred interface over screens.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-reportedly-snags-team-behind-151251440.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Should CrowdStrike’s Identity Security and AI Governance Push Require Action From CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD) Investors?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-identity-security-ai-governance-150945571.html</link><description>CrowdStrike recently moved to acquire identity-security specialist SGNL for about US$740 million, advanced its Global Data Sovereignty initiative with new regional clouds in Saudi Arabia, India and the UAE, and secured ISO/IEC 42001:2023 certification for responsible AI across its Falcon platform. Taken together, these steps extend CrowdStrike’s platform beyond endpoint protection into identity, AI governance and regulated-market deployments, potentially reshaping how enterprises consolidate...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-identity-security-ai-governance-150945571.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] AMD Stock Hits Seven-Day Win Streak. AI Partnerships Drive Momentum</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-stock-hits-seven-day-150928719.html</link><description>Advanced Micro Devices Climbs. Venice EPYC and Helios Platform Boost Investor Confidence</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-stock-hits-seven-day-150928719.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[HSBA.L] Intel Stock Falls Back from 4-Year High Ahead of Earnings. What Has the Market Excited.”</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Intel  stock was cooling off Thursday ahead of the chip company’s earnings report but remains at multiyear highs.  Intel was down 1% at $53.77 in early trading.  Intel is expected to report adjusted earnings of eight cents a share on revenue of $13.42 billion for the fourth quarter of 2025, according to a FactSet poll of analysts’ estimates.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/intel-earnings-stock-price-9b0b6002?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Stock Is Lagging Behind Other AI Names. Why the Chips Darling Is Out of Favor.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-today-ai-chips-4f4ddb9d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Nvidia stock is hovering near the same levels it was at last August, while other companies involved in the artificial-intelligence boom have surged.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-stock-price-today-ai-chips-4f4ddb9d?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] From invisibility cloaks to AI chips: Neurophos raises $110M to build tiny optical processors for inferencing</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invisibility-cloaks-ai-chips-neurophos-150052711.html</link><description>Neurophos is taking a crack at solving the AI industry's power efficiency problem with an optical chip that uses a composite material to do the math required in AI inferencing tasks.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/invisibility-cloaks-ai-chips-neurophos-150052711.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA (KLAC) Reports Next Week: Wall Street Expects Earnings Growth</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-reports-next-week-150018308.html</link><description>KLA (KLAC) doesn't possess the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-reports-next-week-150018308.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] Analysts Estimate Caterpillar (CAT) to Report a Decline in Earnings: What to Look Out for</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-estimate-caterpillar-cat-report-150007012.html</link><description>Caterpillar (CAT) doesn't possess the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Get prepared with the key expectations.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analysts-estimate-caterpillar-cat-report-150007012.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia Faces Bipartisan Pushback Over China Chip Sales</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-faces-bipartisan-pushback-over-145440227.html</link><description>Lawmakers question Trump's plan to allow exports of advanced AI chips to Beijing.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-faces-bipartisan-pushback-over-145440227.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] A Value ETF Skips High Dividend Yields, Focuses on ESG, and Underperforms</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/a-value-etf-skips-high-dividend-yields-focuses-on-esg-and-underperforms/</link><description>When large-cap growth stocks dominate headlines and valuations stretch, investors holding pure S&amp;amp;P 500 exposure face a familiar question: how do you stay invested in quality companies without chasing momentum? The Nuveen ESG Large-Cap Value ETF (NULV) offers one answer—a portfolio of established, dividend-paying businesses screened for environmental, social, and governance standards, positioned in sectors ... A Value ETF Skips High Dividend Yields, Focuses on ESG, and Underperforms</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/a-value-etf-skips-high-dividend-yields-focuses-on-esg-and-underperforms/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] CrowdStrike Holdings' Quarterly Earnings Preview: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37175118/crowdstrike-holdings-quarterly-earnings-preview-what-you-need-to-know</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings is set to release its fourth-quarter results soon, and analysts predict a triple-digit surge in the company’s bottom-line figure.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37175118/crowdstrike-holdings-quarterly-earnings-preview-what-you-need-to-know</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet Stock Can Hit $400 a Share, This Firm Says. It’s All About AI.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/alphabet-stock-price-upgrade-1b33e691?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Raymond James upgrades the Google parent to Strong Buy and lifts its price target to $400 in a research note Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/alphabet-stock-price-upgrade-1b33e691?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Are Computer and Technology Stocks Lagging  Applied Materials (AMAT) This Year?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/computer-technology-stocks-lagging-applied-144003179.html</link><description>Here is how Applied Materials (AMAT) and ASML (ASML) have performed compared to their sector so far this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/computer-technology-stocks-lagging-applied-144003179.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Alphabet upgraded, Micron initiated: Wall Street's top analyst calls</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-upgraded-micron-initiated-wall-143731735.html</link><description>Alphabet upgraded, Micron initiated: Wall Street's top analyst calls</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alphabet-upgraded-micron-initiated-wall-143731735.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq rise after Trump backpedals on Greenland tariffs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-greenland-tariffs-143627517.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-greenland-tariffs-143627517.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel stock tumbles as company's Q1 outlook falls short of Wall Street expectations</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-tumbles-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143443764.html</link><description>Intel reported fourth quarter earnings results after the bell.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-stock-tumbles-as-companys-q1-outlook-falls-short-of-wall-street-expectations-143443764.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Does SOUN's New Partnership Signal a Turning Point for Enterprise AI?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-souns-partnership-signal-turning-143400900.html</link><description>SoundHound's partnership with Bridgepointe aims to speed enterprise AI adoption, lift recurring-revenue platforms and strengthen its go-to-market strategy.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-souns-partnership-signal-turning-143400900.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Advanced Micro Devices Extends Seven Day Winning Streak</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/advanced-micro-devices-extends-seven-143340186.html</link><description>AI momentum and analyst optimism keep fueling investor excitement.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/advanced-micro-devices-extends-seven-143340186.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] Is It Worth Investing in ASML (ASML) Based on Wall Street's Bullish Views?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/worth-investing-asml-asml-based-143005569.html</link><description>The average brokerage recommendation (ABR) for ASML (ASML) is equivalent to a Buy. The overly optimistic recommendations of Wall Street analysts make the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric questionable. So, is it worth buying the stock?</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/worth-investing-asml-asml-based-143005569.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Google Stock Upgraded On Rosy Artificial Intelligence, Cloud Computing Outlook</title><link>https://www.investors.com/news/technology/google-stock-upgraded-artificial-intelligence-cloud-computing-growth-outlook/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Raymond James upgraded Google stock amid AI-driven cloud computing growth estimates well above Wall Street consensus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/news/technology/google-stock-upgraded-artificial-intelligence-cloud-computing-growth-outlook/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] Wix Unveils Harmony, Blending Human Creativity With AI Web Design</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wix-unveils-harmony-blending-human-141900218.html</link><description>WIX unveils Harmony, an AI-powered website builder combining natural-language creation with pixel-perfect design, built for speed, scale and reliability.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wix-unveils-harmony-blending-human-141900218.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CDNS] Cadence Unveils HiFi iQ DSP to Power Next-Gen Voice AI and Audio</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-unveils-hifi-iq-dsp-141500916.html</link><description>CDNS unveils sixth-gen Tensilica HiFi iQ DSP, doubling compute, boosting AI up to 8x and cutting energy use to power next-gen voice AI audio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cadence-unveils-hifi-iq-dsp-141500916.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] Jim Cramer Calls KLA Corporation an “Incredibly Well-Run Company”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-kla-corporation-141036133.html</link><description>KLA Corporation (NASDAQ:KLAC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about, along with market froth. Answering a caller’s query about the stock during the lightning round, Cramer commented: Okay, KLA is an incredibly well-run company whose stock is up gigantically. They make the semiconductor capital equipment, you need that, memory. I think that if […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-kla-corporation-141036133.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Remains Bullish on Vertiv Despite Newer Nvidia Chips</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-remains-bullish-vertiv-141031315.html</link><description>Vertiv Holdings Co (NYSE:VRT) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about, along with market froth. A caller inquired if the company would be impacted as a result of NVIDIA’s newer chips, and Cramer replied: No, my understanding is you’re still going to need Vertiv. You’re still going to need Vertiv, which has the […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-remains-bullish-vertiv-141031315.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NBIS] Jim Cramer on Applied Digital: “I Need You to Take Profits”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-applied-digital-profits-141026020.html</link><description>Applied Digital Corporation (NASDAQ:APLD) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about, along with market froth. Cramer mentioned the stock during the episode and said: Next, there’s a whole new class of companies that’s caught fire over the past year, cryptocurrency miners that are converting their racks full of servers into data centers for […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-applied-digital-profits-141026020.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Jim Cramer on Novo Nordisk: “I Think They’re Making a Turn Here”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-novo-nordisk-think-141019696.html</link><description>Novo Nordisk A/S (NYSE:NVO) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer talked about, along with market froth. During the episode, a caller asked if the stock is a buy, hold, or sell, and Cramer replied: No, I would hold it. I met with the CEO last week. I kind of, I liked him a lot. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-novo-nordisk-think-141019696.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 5 reasons why Jefferies thinks Meta’s pullback is a buying opportunity</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-reasons-why-jefferies-thinks-140416001.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Meta’s sharp decline has opened a compelling entry point, according to Jefferies, which called the stock a “Top Pick” and outlined five reasons why the pullback should be bought in a note to clients this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-reasons-why-jefferies-thinks-140416001.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Why Analysts Think Analog Devices Stock Can Hit $375 in 2026</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37173821/why-analysts-think-analog-devices-stock-can-hit-375-in-2026</link><description>Analysts see Analog Devices benefiting from durable industrial demand, edge AI adoption, and margins that support a premium valuation into 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37173821/why-analysts-think-analog-devices-stock-can-hit-375-in-2026</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Banking behemoth JP Morgan Nutmegs rivals with purchase of WealthOS</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/banking-behemoth-jp-morgan-nutmegs-134900772.html</link><description>JP Morgan Chase, the US-based banking giant, has swooped to buy a British pensions technology company as it tries to augment its retirement planning services to personal investing clients.  Sky News has learnt that JP Morgan has agreed to snap up WealthOS, which was founded in 2019.  Chaired by former Google executive John Herlihy, WealthOS is a wealth management software business.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/banking-behemoth-jp-morgan-nutmegs-134900772.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CAT.F] 70 Aristocrat Stocks in One Fund: NOBL Delivers Dividend Growth Retirees Can Trust Right Now</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/70-aristocrat-stocks-in-one-fund-nobl-delivers-dividend-growth-retirees-can-trust-right-now/</link><description>The ProShares S&amp;amp;P 500 Dividend Aristocrats ETF (NOBL) generates income by holding companies with 25+ consecutive years of dividend increases—a proven track record of financial discipline and shareholder commitment. With $11.1 billion in assets and a 0.35% expense ratio, NOBL offers diversified exposure to 70 dividend aristocrats across sectors like Industrials (22.9%), Consumer Staples (20.8%), ... 70 Aristocrat Stocks in One Fund: NOBL Delivers Dividend Growth Retirees Can Trust Right Now</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/70-aristocrat-stocks-in-one-fund-nobl-delivers-dividend-growth-retirees-can-trust-right-now/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Nvidia stock retains the crown as 'retail king' despite lagging in 2026</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-retains-the-crown-as-retail-king-despite-lagging-in-2026-133312545.html</link><description>Retail investors are sticking with Nvidia and CEO Jensen Huang.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-stock-retains-the-crown-as-retail-king-despite-lagging-in-2026-133312545.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] NatWest and Halifax cut mortgage costs</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-halifax-bank-england-131529096.html</link><description>Find out the latest mortgage rates and deals from HSBC, NatWest, Santander, Barclays and more.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/cheapest-mortgage-interest-rates-natwest-halifax-bank-england-131529096.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NWGL.XC] How Recent Price Target Shifts Are Rewriting The Story For NatWest Group (LSE:NWG)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-price-target-shifts-rewriting-130943619.html</link><description>Why the NatWest Group price target has changed NatWest Group has seen its price target updated, reflecting a fresh look at the bank's current position and what that might mean for investors following the story closely. This shift in expectations is rooted in recent commentary around the stock, which has prompted analysts to reassess how they frame its prospects and risks. Stay tuned to see how you can keep on top of these price target moves and the wider narrative as it evolves. Analyst Price...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recent-price-target-shifts-rewriting-130943619.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock Market Today: Dow Rises Ahead Of Key Inflation Data; Nvidia, Tesla Extend Their Gains (Live Coverage)</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-inflation-data-nvidia-stock-tesla-tsla-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>The Dow Jones index rose Thursday ahead of key inflation data. Nvidia and Tesla rallied in premarket trading.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-inflation-data-nvidia-stock-tesla-tsla-stock/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:05:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] Dow Jones Futures Rise After Trump Greenland Shift Fuels Stocks; Google, Eli Lilly Lead 8 New Buys</title><link>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-halts-greenland-tariffs-framework-google-eli-lilly-new-buys/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Stocks rebounded as President Donald Trump said he won't go ahead with Greenland tariffs, citing a "framework" for a future deal. Google and Eli Lilly lead new buys.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-futures-trump-halts-greenland-tariffs-framework-google-eli-lilly-new-buys/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] AI race: How export restrictions may be giving US an advantage</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-race-export-restrictions-may-130051271.html</link><description>Anthropic (ANTH.PVT) CEO Dario Amodei likened permitting the sales of AI chips to China to "selling nuclear weapons to North Korea." Council on Foreign Relations (CFR) senior fellow for China and emerging technologies, Chris McGuire, reacts to these comments and how the US leads China in hardware development amid a tightening AI race. Also catch Chris McGuire's comments on the quality of China's AI progress compared to the US. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more&amp;amp;nbsp;Market Domination.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ai-race-export-restrictions-may-130051271.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Here Are Thursday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Alphabet, Callaway Golf, Datadog, Hyatt Hotels, Palantir, Texas Instruments, Verizon, and More</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/here-are-thursdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-alphabet-callaway-golf-datadog-hyatt-hotels-palantir-texas-instruments-verizon-and-more/</link><description>Pre-Market Stock Futures: The futures are trading higher this morning, following a solid bounce-back rally across the major indices on Wednesday, after the worst day for stocks since October. Stocks were headed lower at the open, but as President Trump addressed the audience at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, the moment he mentioned ... Here Are Thursday’s Top Wall Street Analyst Research Calls: Alphabet, Callaway Golf, Datadog, Hyatt Hotels, Palantir, Texas Instruments, Verizon,</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/here-are-thursdays-top-wall-street-analyst-research-calls-alphabet-callaway-golf-datadog-hyatt-hotels-palantir-texas-instruments-verizon-and-more/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia’s Huang: AI boom will create six-figure trade jobs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-ai-boom-create-125341975.html</link><description>Investing.com -- Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang emphasized that the artificial intelligence boom will create high-paying trade jobs while speaking at the World Economic Forum in Davos on Wednesday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-huang-ai-boom-create-125341975.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cardano Founder Slams Ripple CEO Over Clarity Act: 'You're Handing Keys To The SEC'</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cardano-founder-slams-ripple-ceo-123112176.html</link><description>Cardano (CRYPTO: ADA) founder Charles Hoskinson slammed Ripple (CRYPTO: XRP) CEO Brad Garlinghouse for backing the Senate’s Clarity Act draft, warning the bill hands too much power to the SEC and locks crypto into flawed regulation that favors banks over...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cardano-founder-slams-ripple-ceo-123112176.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba Stock Gains. How It Plans to Rival Nvidia on AI Chips.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/alibaba-stock-price-adr-ai-chips-5fc0deb2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Alibaba is one of multiple Chinese companies hoping to take advantage of the gap left by Nvidia’s current absence from China’s artificial-intelligence chip market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/alibaba-stock-price-adr-ai-chips-5fc0deb2?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Analog Devices price target raised to $350 from $320 at BofA</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-price-target-raised-122609712.html</link><description>BofA raised the firm’s price target on Analog Devices (ADI) to $350 from $320 and keeps a Buy rating on the shares. The firm raised price targets for most of its diversified analog semi stock coverage, noting that it expects modest calendar Q4 beats and Q1 raises across the board led by industrial semis given ongoing rebounds across most subsegments, favorable pricing, and robust growth in strategic AI businesses.Claim 50% Off TipRanks PremiumUnlock hedge fund-level data and powerful investing t</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/analog-devices-price-target-raised-122609712.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] AI Enabler Sparkles And Shines. Now Comes The Main Event.</title><link>https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-analysis/corning-stock-near-breakout-ai-infrastructure-collaboration-with-nvidia-broadcom-microsoft-drives-demand/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Collaboration on AI infrastructure with Nvidia, Broadcom and Microsoft has Corning stock set to light up a breakout.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.investors.com/research/ibd-stock-analysis/corning-stock-near-breakout-ai-infrastructure-collaboration-with-nvidia-broadcom-microsoft-drives-demand/?src=A00220&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Okta’s Profits Are Up, But Its Credibility Still Hasn’t Recovered</title><link>https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/oktas-profits-are-up-but-its-credibility-still-hasnt-recovered/</link><description>You want to talk about irony? Okta Inc (NASDAQ:OKTA) sells identity security to enterprises worldwide, and in 2023, hackers breached its own systems. Twice. That’s like hiring a locksmith who leaves your front door wide open. The question isn’t whether those headlines hurt the stock. They did. The question is whether they’ll haunt it forever. ... Okta’s Profits Are Up, But Its Credibility Still Hasn’t Recovered</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://247wallst.com/investing/2026/01/22/oktas-profits-are-up-but-its-credibility-still-hasnt-recovered/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Nvidia CEO Shrugs Off AI Bubble Talk</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-shrugs-off-ai-121419554.html</link><description>Huang says infrastructure buildout is just starting</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-ceo-shrugs-off-ai-121419554.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI-Powered Box Extract Launch Could Be A Game Changer For Box (BOX)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-powered-box-extract-launch-120808892.html</link><description>Box, Inc. recently announced the general availability of Box Extract, an AI-driven tool that uses models from Google, Anthropic, and OpenAI to convert unstructured enterprise content into secure, actionable metadata within Box. By enabling custom “Extract Agents” that can process complex documents across sectors like finance, insurance, legal, and media, Box is positioning its platform as a central hub for automating workflows and powering metadata-driven decision-making. Next, we’ll examine...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-powered-box-extract-launch-120808892.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Hidden Winner in Nvidia's AI Chip Boom Isn't Who You'd Expect</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</link><description>Nvidia is now outspending Apple at TSMC. Intel may benefit the most from the shift.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-hidden-winner-in-nvidias-ai-chip-boom-isnt-who/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer Discusses Alphabet (GOOGL) &amp; OpenAI’s Rivalry</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Over the past couple of months, Jim Cramer has turned increasingly optimistic on Alphabet Inc. (NASDAQ:GOOGL). Several factors have driven his optimism. Early on, these included enthusiasm for YouTube and the firm’s dominance in […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-discusses-alphabet-googl-114742514.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] “CoreWeave (CRWV)’s Stock is Coming Back,” Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-stock-coming-back-114735873.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. CoreWeave Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWV) is a key player in the AI industry. The firm provides computing infrastructure for AI software companies. It was one of the first stocks that were listed in 2025, and since […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coreweave-crwv-stock-coming-back-114735873.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] People Should Have Listened to NVIDIA (NVDA)’s CEO, Says Jim Cramer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-listened-nvidia-nvda-ceo-114644985.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA)’s shares are down by 1.3% year-to-date. RBC Capital set an Outperform rating for the stock and a $240 share price target for the firm in mid-January. Some of the factors that […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-listened-nvidia-nvda-ceo-114644985.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Recalls Being Bullish on Micron (MU) a Year Ago</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-recalls-being-bullish-114637756.html</link><description>We recently published 15 Stocks on Jim Cramer’s Radar. Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) is one of the stocks on Jim Cramer’s radar. Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) has quietly emerged as one of the top semiconductor stocks in the market. Its shares are up by a whopping 231% over the past year. Micron Technology, Inc. (NASDAQ:MU) […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-recalls-being-bullish-114637756.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Sun Pharma Eyes Organon In What Could Be India Pharma's Biggest Cross-Border Deal: Report</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sun-pharma-eyes-organon-could-114606281.html</link><description>India-based Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd is reportedly evaluating a potential acquisition of Organon &amp;amp; Co (NYSE:OGN), a U.S.-based women's healthcare company. If it goes through, the deal that could become the largest cross-border transaction ever by an Indian drugmaker, according to people familiar with the matter, as cited by The Economic Times. Sun Pharmaceutical has submitted a non-binding all-cash bid and arranged $10–14 billion in acquisition financing. Why It Matters If completed, th</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sun-pharma-eyes-organon-could-114606281.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Intel Jumps 11% as Chip Stocks Rally</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</link><description>AI optimism lifts semiconductors across the board</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-jumps-11-chip-stocks-114238345.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Should You 'Buy' or 'Sell' IBM Stock Ahead of Q4 Earnings?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-sell-ibm-stock-ahead-113935221.html</link><description>IBM Earnings Loom. The Z17 Cycle and 2026 Outlook Are in Focus.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/buy-sell-ibm-stock-ahead-113935221.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LLY0.F] January 2026's Stocks That May Be Trading Below Estimated Value</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/january-2026s-stocks-may-trading-113807425.html</link><description>Amid recent market volatility, the U.S. stock indices have shown resilience with a sharp rebound following geopolitical tensions and tariff threats. As investors navigate these fluctuations, identifying stocks that may be trading below their estimated value can present opportunities for those looking to capitalize on potential market inefficiencies.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/january-2026s-stocks-may-trading-113807425.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] I Called Alphabet's Monster Comeback in 2025. Here's Where I Think It's Heading in 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/called-alphabet-monster-comeback-2025-goog/</link><description>Alphabet's stock crushed the market in 2026.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/called-alphabet-monster-comeback-2025-goog/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Stock Markets Are Relying on the TACO Trade Again. Why That’s Not Good.</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-market-trump-taco-trade-things-to-know-today-6ea34bd7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Trump cancels Greenland tariff threats, Supreme Court justices appear skeptical of Trump’s bid to fire Fed governor Lisa Cook, Amazon hits back at Walmart with planned megastore, and more news to start your day.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/stock-market-trump-taco-trade-things-to-know-today-6ea34bd7?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ASML] TSMC Just Delivered Incredible News for ASML Investors</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/tsmc-delivered-incredible-news-for-asml-invest/</link><description>ASML's stock price got a nice shot in the arm following TSMC's latest quarterly report.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/tsmc-delivered-incredible-news-for-asml-invest/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] My Top 4 Stocks to Buy in Early 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-4-stocks-to-buy-in-early-2026/</link><description>These stocks offer impressive long-term upside with downside protection.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-4-stocks-to-buy-in-early-2026/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Why 'Cheap' Software Stocks Could Be The Next Big AI Value Trap</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cheap-software-stocks-could-110112838.html</link><description>Enterprise software stocks are starting to look tempting again, at least on a chart. Adobe Inc. (NASDAQ:ADBE) is trading at November 2022 lows and has lost 55% of its value since its February 2024 peak. Salesforce Inc. (NYSE:CRM) sits near May 2024 levels, down about 40% from its January 2025 high. ServiceNow Inc. (NYSE:NOW) is at its lowest since November 2023, off roughly 45% from its January 2025 peak. To many investors, that looks like classic mean reversion. AI hardware stocks like Micron T</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-cheap-software-stocks-could-110112838.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[ADI] Do Its Financials Have Any Role To Play In Driving Analog Devices, Inc.'s (NASDAQ:ADI) Stock Up Recently?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financials-role-play-driving-analog-110045816.html</link><description>Analog Devices (NASDAQ:ADI) has had a great run on the share market with its stock up by a significant 25% over the...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financials-role-play-driving-analog-110045816.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Taiwan Semiconductor Just Delivered Great News for Nvidia Shareholders</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductor-just-delivered-increible-news/</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor has raised its growth projections.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/taiwan-semiconductor-just-delivered-increible-news/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sovereign AI partners with Accenture and Palantir on EMEA data centre rollout</title><link>https://www.verdict.co.uk/sovereign-ai-partners-accenture-palantir/</link><description>Accenture leads delivery, and Palantir optimises operations as Dell-Nvidia-powered centres target regulated, high-performance AI workloads across EMEA.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.verdict.co.uk/sovereign-ai-partners-accenture-palantir/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Prediction: This Magnificent Vanguard ETF Will Beat the S&amp;P 500 (Again) in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/prediction-vanguard-etf-will-beat-sp-500-in-2026/</link><description>The Vanguard Growth ETF has a stellar track record against the S&amp;amp;P 500 thanks to its unique portfolio.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/prediction-vanguard-etf-will-beat-sp-500-in-2026/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Trending tickers: AMD, Intel, Moderna, Associated British Foods and Young &amp; Co's Brewery</title><link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</link><description>The latest investor updates on stocks that are trending on Thursday.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amd-intel-moderna-associated-british-foods-youngs-100513122.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] AI power and infrastructure needs boomed in 2025. At Davos, the AI story for 2026 remains the same.</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</link><description>The AI industry's greatest bottleneck, power, drove a boom in infrastructure throughout 2025. At Davos, leaders signal that 2026 is likely to see more of the same.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ai-power-and-infrastructure-needs-boomed-in-2025-at-davos-the-ai-story-for-2026-remains-the-same-100005093.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba shares surge after report co prepares IPO of AI chip unit as demand surges</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-shares-surge-report-co-094300227.html</link><description>Investing.com-- Alibaba Group Holdings (NYSE:BABA) is laying the groundwork for a potential listing of its chipmaking arm, seeking to capitalise on strong investor appetite for companies aiming to challenge Nvidia in the fast-growing AI accelerator market.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-shares-surge-report-co-094300227.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] My Top 5 Predictions for the Magnificent Seven Stocks in 2026</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</link><description>Investors may continue to closely watch the Magnificent Seven this year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/my-top-5-predictions-for-the-magnificent-seven-sto/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Alibaba Is Said to Plan IPO for AI Chipmaking Unit T-Head</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-said-plan-ipo-ai-084012315.html</link><description>As a first step, Alibaba plans to restructure the unit as a business partly owned by employees, people familiar with the matter said.  The company will then explore an initial public offering, though the timing for that remains unclear, the people said, asking to remain anonymous discussing private plans.  Alibaba representatives didn’t respond to an email seeking comment.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-said-plan-ipo-ai-084012315.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] The Motley Fool Interviews Zscaler Founder and CEO Jay Chaudhry</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-motley-fool-interviews-zscaler-founder-and-ceo/</link><description>Cloud security company Zscaler has racked up big returns for investors since going public in 2018.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/the-motley-fool-interviews-zscaler-founder-and-ceo/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Palantir Billionaire Peter Thiel Sells Nvidia Stock -- 100% of His Portfolio Is Now Invested in 3 AI Stocks</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</link><description>Billionaire Peter Thiel has his entire portfolio invested in Tesla, Microsoft, and Apple.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/palantir-peter-thiel-sell-nvidia-owns-3-ai-stocks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Is Bullish on UiPath, Inc. (PATH) Amid Stable IT Spending Outlook</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</link><description>We recently compiled a list of the 15 High Growth Mid-Cap Stocks to Buy. The second stock on our list of high growth stocks is UiPath, Inc. TheFly reported on January 12 that Barclays raised its price target on PATH to $18 from $16 and maintained an Equal Weight rating. As part of its 2026 […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-bullish-uipath-inc-path-081846143.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer Explains Why He Thinks NVIDIA’s Jensen Huang Is the “Greatest Technologist of Our Era”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-explains-why-thinks-081043024.html</link><description>NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Cramer said that only NVIDIA saw the burgeoning demand for chips, as he commented: … NVIDIA… had much more foresight than Micron or anybody else in the industry, so its products are more plentiful… Again, only NVIDIA really saw it coming. They […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-explains-why-thinks-081043024.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on Super Micro: “Sell, I Don’t Need That”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-super-micro-sell-080925610.html</link><description>Super Micro Computer, Inc. (NASDAQ:SMCI) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Answering a caller’s query about the stock, Cramer stated: Sell. I don’t need that. And it just, you know… you gotta move on. You want to own that area, you own NVIDIA. Period. End of story. Super Micro Computer, Inc. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-super-micro-sell-080925610.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on Ares Capital: “I Want to Be Very Careful There”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</link><description>Ares Capital Corporation (NASDAQ:ARCC) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. When a caller mentioned that their top five holdings are AAPL, ARCC, HSY, KMB, and NVDA, Cramer remarked: Wow, okay. Well, you got some yield there. You got some growth. I don’t like the Ares because I can’t really tell what […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-ares-capital-want-080922640.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Jim Cramer on American Electric Power: “One of My Favorite Utilities for Multiple Years”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-american-electric-power-080919183.html</link><description>American Electric Power Company, Inc. (NASDAQ:AEP) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Inquiring if their portfolio is diversified enough, a club member mentioned that their top five holdings are PM, AMZN, NVDA, AEP, and UBER. In response, Cramer said: Okay, Uber, we know is transport. Amazon, we’re going to call it, […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-american-electric-power-080919183.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[TSM] Jim Cramer on Agnico Eagle: “This Is My Favorite Gold Company”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-agnico-eagle-favorite-080918365.html</link><description>Agnico Eagle Mines Limited (NYSE:AEM) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. A caller outlined that their portfolio’s biggest five holdings are BA, AEM, MS, CAT, and TSM, and Cramer remarked: Okay, this is a terrific semiconductor manufacturing company. This is my favorite gold company. This is one of the best machinery […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-agnico-eagle-favorite-080918365.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Jim Cramer on Simon Property’s CEO: “We Think David Simon’s the Best Mall Operator There Is”</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-simon-property-ceo-080916327.html</link><description>Simon Property Group, Inc. (NYSE:SPG) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Starting the round of “Am I Diversified,” a club member mentioned that their top five holdings are SPG, AMZN, AVGO, LNG, and VICI. Cramer replied: Wow, you’re diversified, but we may have to do some work anyway, just in terms […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-simon-property-ceo-080916327.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] Jim Cramer Calls Lam Research the “Best of the Best” But Warns Against Buying Parabolic Moves</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-lam-research-080903287.html</link><description>Lam Research Corporation (NASDAQ:LRCX) is one of the stocks Jim Cramer recently looked at. Noting the stock’s parabolic move since September 2025, a caller asked if there is more room for it to go up or if it has reached the top. Cramer replied: Do you know that that’s got one great CEO in Tim […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jim-cramer-calls-lam-research-080903287.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] The Age of AI Agents Brings a Risk No One Is Prepared For</title><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</link><description>Artificial-intelligence companies have promised that 2026 will be the year of agents: Software that can use AI language models to autonomously execute a complex series of tasks from simple instructions.  The most prevalent use for agents today is for making software.  With enough of a budget, a single developer can orchestrate teams of agents to work on existing codebases or even to start a project from scratch.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barrons.com/articles/agentic-ai-cybersecurity-stocks-crowdstrike-ed44bfbf?siteid=yhoof2&amp;amp;yptr=yahoo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Only 3 of My Top 10 Stocks for 2025 Lost to the Market. Here Are the Ones I Think Are Still Buys for 2026.</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/only-3-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-lost-to-the-ma/</link><description>All three of these stocks have done well; investors' perception is the only thing holding them back.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/22/only-3-of-my-top-10-stocks-for-2025-lost-to-the-ma/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[SNOW] Is Snowflake (SNOW) Pricing Its Long Term Growth Too Richly After Recent Pullback</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-snow-pricing-long-term-043748733.html</link><description>If you are wondering whether Snowflake's current share price lines up with its long term potential, this article will walk through what the numbers are actually saying about value. Snowflake last closed at US$206.50, with returns of 0.2% over 7 days, a 9.0% decline over 30 days, a 4.7% decline year to date, a 16.3% gain over 1 year and 43.0% over 3 years. Recent market conversations around Snowflake have focused on how investors are weighing its long term growth story against the price they...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/snowflake-snow-pricing-long-term-043748733.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[VRT] 2 High-Flying Stocks Worth Your Attention and 1 We Avoid</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-high-flying-stocks-worth-043246981.html</link><description>Expensive stocks typically earn their valuations through superior growth rates that other companies simply can’t match. The flip side though is that these lofty expectations make them particularly susceptible to drawdowns when market sentiment shifts.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-high-flying-stocks-worth-043246981.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Cathie Wood's Ark Unleashes Cryptic ARKmoji Teasers To Showcase Its 'Big Ideas' For 2026: Can You Take A Guess At The Hidden Meaning?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-unleashes-cryptic-033110612.html</link><description>Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest unveiled its “big ideas” for 2025 in a cryptic list, challenging users to interpret a series of custom images called “ARKmoji” to understand their picks for the year. Ark’s ‘Big Ideas’ For 2026 On Monday, in a thread on X, the investment management firm shared six “ARKmojis” along with a poll containing options under each, allowing followers to vote on their interpretation of the idea behind each image. 1. AI Agents The first image pointed towards agentic AI, but users w</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-unleashes-cryptic-033110612.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] 3 Artificial Intelligence Stocks You Can Buy and Hold for the Next Decade</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-stocks-buy-and-hold/</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) stocks still have a lot more room to run over the next decade.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-stocks-buy-and-hold/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stocks track Wall St rally as Trump cools tariff threats in Davos</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</link><description>Asian stocks rose Thursday while safe-haven precious metals extended losses after Donald Trump rowed back on his threat to hit key European countries with tariffs over their opposition to the US takeover of Greenland.Gold and silver, which have hit multiple records this week on a push into safe havens by worried traders, both fell Wednesday, and extended their retreat in Asia.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-track-wall-st-rally-024902242.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Franklin Resources (BEN) Target Raised as Barclays Updates Asset Manager Models</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</link><description>Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 15, Barclays raised its price target on Franklin Resources, Inc. (NYSE:BEN) to $25 from $22, while still keeping an Underweight rating on the stock. The firm said the adjustment was mainly driven by updates to its asset manager […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/franklin-resources-ben-target-raised-023133940.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] Barclays Q4 Preview: Kimberly-Clark (KMB) Target Cut, “enthusiasm” Not Driven by Fundamentals</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</link><description>Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 16, Barclays cut its price target on Kimberly-Clark Corporation (NASDAQ:KMB) to $102 from $132, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The move was part of the firm’s Q4 earnings preview for the consumer staples sector, where […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barclays-q4-preview-kimberly-clark-022848239.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] CubeSmart (CUBE) Target Cut as Barclays Updates 2026 REIT Sector View</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</link><description>CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) is included among the 15 Best High Yield Stocks to Buy. On January 13, Barclays analyst Brendan Lynch trimmed his price target on CubeSmart (NYSE:CUBE) to $43 from $45, while keeping an Equal Weight rating on the stock. The change came as part of Barclays’ broader 2026 outlook update for the REIT sector. […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cubesmart-cube-target-cut-barclays-022045126.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Anthropic CEO goes nuclear on Nvidia</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/anthropic-ceo-goes-nuclear-on-nvidia</link><description>In November 2025, Nvidia (NVDA) said it would invest up to $10 billion in Anthropic. The company also stated it will help optimize Anthropic models for performance, efficiency, and total cost of ownership. Anthropic’s artificial intelligence models have been trained on Nvidia GPUs, Amazon Trainium ...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thestreet.com/investing/stocks/anthropic-ceo-goes-nuclear-on-nvidia</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] 1 Semiconductor Stock Trading at a Discount to Start the New Year</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/semiconductor-stock-trading-discount-2026-nvda/</link><description>Nvidia's stock is cheap to start the new year.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/semiconductor-stock-trading-discount-2026-nvda/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Meta's Recent Stock Decline Is 'Self-Inflicted,' Says Analyst, Predicts Rally If Mark Zuckerberg Does This</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/metas-recent-stock-decline-self-013110659.html</link><description>Suncoast Equity managing director and co-portfolio manager Eric Lynch weighed in on Meta Platform Inc.‘s (NASDAQ:META) recent stock decline amid investor skepticism about the company’s capital expenditure (capex) guidance for the year. Capex Concerns Pressure Meta Stock Lynch, in a recent conversation with Yahoo Finance on Sunday, suggested that investors are wary of a potential increase in capex due to CEO and founder Mark Zuckerberg‘s AI push. This skepticism has led to a 4.6% drop in Meta’s s</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/metas-recent-stock-decline-self-013110659.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] This AI Cloud Specialist Is Poised for a Decade of Explosive Growth</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-ai-cloud-specialist-is-poised-for-growth/</link><description>This company recently reported triple-digit revenue growth.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/this-ai-cloud-specialist-is-poised-for-growth/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Artificial Intelligence (AI) Spending Is Exploding. This Stock Stands to Benefit Most</title><link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-ai-spending-broadcom/</link><description>Broadcom is poised to be one of the biggest beneficiaries of increasing AI infrastructure spending.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fool.com/investing/2026/01/21/artificial-intelligence-ai-spending-broadcom/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] As Taiwan Semi Hikes Its Dividend 20%, Should You Buy TSM Stock?</title><link>https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37163143/as-taiwan-semi-hikes-its-dividend-20-should-you-buy-tsm-stock</link><description>Taiwan Semiconductor continues to increase its payout. Is the growth sustainable? Here's what to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.barchart.com/story/news/37163143/as-taiwan-semi-hikes-its-dividend-20-should-you-buy-tsm-stock</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Sovereign AI Data Center Role Could Be A Game Changer For Accenture (ACN)</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sovereign-ai-data-center-role-002437639.html</link><description>Sovereign AI recently announced it has selected Accenture and Palantir to help build and scale next-generation, sovereign-grade AI data centers across EMEA, aiming to support commercial and government clients with resilient Dell AI Factory- and NVIDIA-powered infrastructure and potential future expansion into APAC. This collaboration highlights Accenture’s growing involvement in critical AI infrastructure and sovereign AI solutions, an area where its own research shows rising investment...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sovereign-ai-data-center-role-002437639.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Surging memory chip prices dim outlook for consumer electronics makers</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-memory-chip-prices-dim-001756209.html</link><description>Global demand for smartphones, personal computers and gaming consoles is expected to shrink this year as companies from Britain's Raspberry Pi to HP Inc raise sticker prices to offset surging memory chip costs.  The rapid build-out of artificial intelligence infrastructure by U.S. tech firms such ​as OpenAI, Alphabet-owned  Google and Microsoft has absorbed much of the world's memory chip supply, pushing up prices as manufacturers prioritize components for higher-margin data ‌centers over consumer devices.  Samsung, SK Hynix and Micron, the world's three largest producers of memory chips, have said in recent months that they were struggling to keep up with demand as they reported rosy quarterly ‌earnings on the back of surging prices for their semiconductors.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-memory-chip-prices-dim-001756209.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] Truist Reiterates Buy on Meta Platforms (META), Says AI Fears Are Priced In</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/truist-reiterates-buy-meta-platforms-235455341.html</link><description>Meta Platforms, Inc. (NASDAQ:META) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 14, Truist Securities reiterated a Buy rating on the stock with an $875.00 price target. While META has underperformed peers since Q3 earnings, the firm believes investor fears are already priced in. In an investor note, the firm noted how Meta […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/truist-reiterates-buy-meta-platforms-235455341.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[NVDA] Stock market today: Dow, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq futures rise after Trump backpedals on tariffs</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-tariffs-234947394.html</link><description>Wall Street was given respite from tariff turmoil as Trump announced he was backing away from the Greenland acquisition.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/live/stock-market-today-dow-sp-500-nasdaq-futures-rise-after-trump-backpedals-on-tariffs-234947394.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BARC.L] 2025 Was a Record Year for Activism: Barclays</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/2025-record-activism-barclays-234806819.html</link><description>Jim Rossman, global head of shareholder advisory at Barclays Capital, says 2025 set a record with 255 activist campaigns. He tells Romaine Bostick and Katie Greifeld on "The Close" that M&amp;amp;A demands were the top focus of these activists.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/2025-record-activism-barclays-234806819.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[LRCX] KeyBanc Raises Applied Materials (AMAT) Target to $380, Keeps Overweight Rating</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-raises-applied-materials-amat-233441836.html</link><description>Applied Materials, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMAT) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 16, KeyBanc raised the price target on the stock to $380.00 (from $285.00) while maintaining an “Overweight” rating. The firm sees AMAT well-positioned for vertical scaling and DRAM-driven capacity growth. KeyBanc noted that AMAT’s valuation is reasonable even though it […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/keybanc-raises-applied-materials-amat-233441836.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[IBM] Evercore ISI Raises IBM Price Target to $330, Adds Stock to Tactical Outperform List</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-raises-ibm-price-232206297.html</link><description>International Business Machines Corporation (NYSE:IBM) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 20, Evercore ISI analyst Amit Daryanani raised the price target on the stock to $330 from $315 and kept an Outperform rating. The firm also added IBM to its “Tactical Outperform list” ahead of IBM’s December-end quarterly results due […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/evercore-isi-raises-ibm-price-232206297.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[CRWD] Citizens Reiterates Bullish View on CrowdStrike (CRWD) With $550 Price Target</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citizens-reiterates-bullish-view-crowdstrike-232102207.html</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ:CRWD) is one of the AI Stocks on Market Radar. On January 20, Citizens analyst reiterated a Market Outperform rating on the stock with a $550.00 price target. According to the firm, CrowdStrike’s recent acquisitions in identity governance and secure browser space help the company close potential functional gaps and limit competitors’ […]</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citizens-reiterates-bullish-view-crowdstrike-232102207.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[KLAC] KLA (KLAC) Outpaces Stock Market Gains: What You Should Know</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-outpaces-stock-market-231503506.html</link><description>KLA (KLAC) concluded the recent trading session at $1, signifying a +2.28% move from its prior day's close.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kla-klac-outpaces-stock-market-231503506.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[GOOG] How Apple’s Gemini-Powered Siri Deal Will Impact Alphabet (GOOGL) Investors</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-powered-siri-deal-231107182.html</link><description>Earlier in January 2026, Apple announced a multi-year partnership with Google to base its next generation of Apple Foundation Models on Google’s Gemini AI and cloud technology, bringing more personalized, AI-powered Siri features while keeping Apple Intelligence workloads on-device and within its Private Cloud Compute framework. The deal effectively places Google’s Gemini at the heart of Apple’s core AI experience, turning a long-time ecosystem rival into a large-scale customer for...</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-gemini-powered-siri-deal-231107182.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[BRH.F] Berkshire to offload Kraft Heinz: What it means in post-Buffett era</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/berkshire-offload-kraft-heinz-means-230357046.html</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway (BRK-B, BRK-A) is reportedly taking steps to offload its Kraft Heinz (KHC) investment. FBB Capital Partners senior portfolio manager Mel Casey joins Market Domination Overtime with Josh Lipton to discuss what it means for Kraft Heinz and signals about CEO Greg Abel's tenure. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://finance.yahoo.com/video/berkshire-offload-kraft-heinz-means-230357046.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>